What does "broccoli" mean?
Depends on the context.
Pubic hair or marijuana. It's a noun.
And "Virginia"?
Vagina. As in, "He penetrated
her Virginia with a hammer."
-Yikes!
-Slang is either sexual or violent.
Or both.
When it's witty,
I think it's really witty.
Yeah.
Hello, how are you?
How are you?
Hi, how are you?
Why didn't you say hi?
I nodded.
Are you happy when you wake up?
No.
Hey, there was a petal storm
out here this morning.
I saw that.
I thought it was a snowstorm.
I thought I was dreaming.
No, there's two stores
we should go to in Soho.
It would not take very much for me
to make you look very good.
You're sabotaging
a fucking incredible figure, baby.
Yo!
Is that your student?
It looks like he wants to eat you.
They all flirt. It's part of the ritual.
-Miss Avery, you're late.
-Am I?
-What, you trying to be ironic?
-Hello.
-What's happening?
-I'm Pauline.
We talked this morning
on the phone.
-Yeah.
-You look different than I thought.
Thank you for sharing your bed.
Bye.
I got a new word for you.
"Meow."
Is this your usual?
Are you gonna write that down?
You should be paying me for this.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
This is valuable shit.
Aren't you afraid your book on slang
is like a dis?
A dis on whom?
People like you think the brothers
are guinea pigs...
...the way we talk and shit.
Cornelius, are you trying to tell me
that you need an extension?
No. Look, I came to tell you
I made a discovery.
See, I discovered I can call
John Wayne Gacy...
...and hear him talk himself,
Miss Avery.
Really? Dead murderers have
their own phone lines?
He wasn't no murderer.
Look, there be a website
for serial killers...
...you know, past and present.
He recorded and explained
himself...
...how he didn't kill no 33 boys.
I got radar for the truth...
...and I'm gonna write
how I know that.
This paper's not supposed
to be about you.
-That's the point of the assignment.
-You said every word a writer writes...
...even the commas and shit,
gotta be a reflection of him or her.
That we be doing this writing shit
to express our vision.
You know I got vision.
You know, I got Africa vision.
You know, I got bitch vision.
I got....
Yeah. Excuse me, I have to go
to the bathroom.
Come on, you guys, you were
supposed to wait for me.
Hey, miss.
Hey, miss. Hey!
You forgot something.
The check.
Stream of consciousness,
I'd like to point out, is not the same...
...as stream of conscience...
...for which some of you
have mistaken it.
A logical error in some ways.
Okay, your assignment for today
is to utilize...
-Nothing happens.
-...style in To the Lighthouse.
Yeah, one old lady dies.
How many ladies have to die
to make it good?
At least three.
-What's this?
-From the bar...
...my half of the check.
Yo, man, where you go?
I waited a long time.
-Couldn't find the bathroom.
-Is that all?
-Is what all?
-All I owe you.
I can't pass you
unless you show up to class.
The still waters of the water
under a frond of stars
The still water of your mouth
under a thicket of kisses
The still waters of the water
under a frond of stars
The still water of your mouth
under a thicket of kisses
Under a thicket of kisses
-How you doing?
-Do I know you?
Detective Malloy.
Are you Francis Avery?
I'm canvassing your apartment
building. I wanna talk to you.
How do I know that's real?
It's still busy.
Why don't you come back.
I'll wait, thanks.
Can I smoke?
Not in my apartment.
You got someplace
I could put it out?
Thanks.
Miss Avery, there was a homicide
in your neighborhood on the 15th.
That'd be Saturday the 15th,
last Saturday...
...between 12 and 2 a.m.
Her body, or part of her body,
to be exact...
...was found in the garden
outside your window.
That's why I wanted to talk to you,
in case you saw or heard anything.
No. No, nothing unusual.
Frannie, it's John Graham.
Are you by yourself?
I don't think you're there
by yourself.
Why did you lie to me?
Doesn't it mean anything to you
that we slept together twice?
Yes, I do count that time
in the shower. Quiet!
Come on, pick up the phone.
Pick up.
Pick up. Pick up.
Pick up. Come on,
pick up the phone.
Are you a writer?
What's all this?
Words, quotes that I like, poetry.
Is it, like, a job or a hobby?
A passion.
"I want to do with you what spring
does with the cherry trees."
Is this you?
It's my sister.
My ex-wife had long hair,
then she cut it.
So you don't remember
seeing anything?
Hearing anything?
Oh, my pen?
It's fake. It's a cop thing.
You don't remember anything? Didn't
see anything? Didn't hear anything?
No cries in the night?
No. I don't remember seeing
or hearing anything unusual.
-And I sleep with the windows open.
-Yeah?
You do that a lot?
Can you tell me how it happened?
Her throat was cut.
And then she was disarticulated.
Here's my card.
My number's there. If you remember
anything, give me a call, all right?
Do I know you from someplace?
I don't know.
Thanks.
Oh, shit.
-Don't bullshit me. Look me in the eye.
-I'm not.
Now, you think about it, all right?
Now, take a walk. Miss?
Oh, miss? Miss?
How you doing? Excuse me.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Am I supposed to get in?
You want to talk on the street?
Never think it's a good idea, putting
your business on the street.
I'll get it.
This is my partner,
Detective Rodriguez.
Hi. How you doing?
-How do you do?
-What the fuck is this?
-It's coffee.
-It's half a cup.
-Take it back.
-He gives me a half a cup.
What, does he expect you to fill--?
How long is this gonna take?
-I'm sorry?
-How long is this gonna take?
-Are you in a hurry?
-Where you going?
-My friend's. Half sister's.
-We'll give you a lift.
-So, what do you do?
-I teach.
-You teach what?
-You get a chance to run those prints?
-Teach what?
-English.
You know what an isthmus is?
Isthmus be my lucky fucking day.
-What the fuck? You ran the prints?
-Yeah.
-And?
-Nada, nothing.
Look, the reason we thought
you might be able to help...
...is the bartender....
Luther Wilker?
-Yeah.
-At the Red....
-Turtle.
-Well, he said...
...you were there
on the night in question.
-He's got a good memory.
-No, we have your credit-card receipt.
Does that look familiar?
That's right.
I was at the Red Turtle
with one of my students.
-One of your students?
-Cornelius Webb.
But it was early. It was 3:30.
I was there for a short time,
then I went home.
Cornelius Webb?
Is that with two B's or not two B's?
W-E-B-B.
You were in the front room
the whole time?
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
Didn't I just say so?
You didn't happen to see
a Caucasian girl, mid-20s?
Not too tall.
Good-looking, wouldn't you say?
-What?
-She was good-looking?
-She wasn't bad-looking.
-Yeah, but she....
Well, did you?
-What is this about, exactly?
-Listen, Miss Avery...
...the deceased was seen in the Red
Turtle the same night you were there.
Seeing how you were there...
...maybe you wouldn't mind
taking a look at a few pictures.
Sometimes you see something
you don't remember.
Take a deep breath.
This one's kind of graphic.
Well, do you recognize her?
No.
Thank you.
Hey. Can't figure you out.
What do you mean?
Am I a murder suspect?
Look, I was wondering if you want
to go for a beer or something.
I got a cousin who works in a bar
in Sheridan Square...
-...and says a lot of writers go in there.
-Now?
No, not now. I'm working now.
-Two hours from now.
-Where?
Here.
What the fuck?
You're a fucking wise guy?
We got nice girls and nicer drinks.
Oh, excuse me, baby.
-Hey, Papi.
-Hey.
-Good to see you. Look at you.
-You are looking good.
Is Pauline home?
-Sorry.
-Oh, baby.
She could be up.
She could be down.
You know, go check the bar, baby,
okay? Hey, hey, hey, look.
That's cute. Is it real?
Of course it be real.
What, you crazy?
I don't let no psycho killer mess
with my girls.
He'd be dead. Bye, baby.
I make sure no one fuck
with my goddamn girls.
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's so humiliating.
Is it the doctor?
Do you want to go up?
Okay.
Thanks, guys.
-Good luck.
-Feel better.
-What happened?
-His receptionist called me...
...with a referral
to another doctor.
He canceled our appointment.
-Was this after you had sex?
-He's right.
He shouldn't have had sex with me.
I mean, of course he's right.
Do you ever think about
just imagining sex?
-What do you mean?
-Just thinking about the doctor...
...not making appointments.
Just....
Just not really trying to have sex
with him in reality.
That's kind of boring.
I mean, I do. I do restrain myself.
You know, I just--
I got so enthusiastic...
...when I thought about him,
and it confused me...
...because I think enthusiasm
is a good thing, you know.
I mean, I think about....
How many appointments
did you make?
Last week?
Eleven.
How about I put on some music?
I waited outside his apartment.
I saw him and his wife...
...and I followed her
to the dry cleaner.
She left a tan suit.
Did you pick it up?
-What are you gonna do with it?
-I don't know.
I feel like such a freak.
This is what I do to get a dick
inside me.
You're not a freak.
I admire you.
You live out of your unconscious.
You're a poet of love.
The lovelorn man who
Sick in soul and of this
Busy human heart aweary
Worships the spirit
Of unconscious life
In tree or wildflower
Gentle lunatic
"Gentle lunatic." That's me.
I have something for you.
It's like a belated birthday thing.
I got it when I was styling that
commercial that got canceled.
Oh, God, that's beautiful.
-What is it?
-It's a courtship fantasy.
See, there's a little wedding bell
and a little house.
Open the baby carriage.
Oh, God.
Oh, no, am I gonna have
to feed this thing?
You should have a baby.
This is the closest I'll get.
And a man. You should have
a man too.
Somebody asked me out.
Good.
Who?
A police detective.
He's investigating a girl's murder.
You know the one who got cut up?
Oh, my God. Yeah.
Part of her body was found
in my garden.
Yuck.
So is this detective good-looking?
He seems young.
He's got a mustache.
They've all got that.
You didn't say no, Frannie?
Frannie?
You gotta go. Just for the exercise,
you should go.
You wanna borrow
some decent clothing?
-Can we look?
-I think you should.
Can you come with me?
Come on.
Get the woman a gin and tonic,
and I'll have a bourbon and Coke.
You got it.
You know, I'm wondering if maybe
you saw something at that bar.
I'm still wondering.
Maybe something
you don't know you saw.
Your colored boyfriend,
did he leave with you?
Cornelius? He's not my boyfriend.
And he left before me.
You saw him leave?
Actually, no.
He's not into popping arms off
of ladies' bodies, is he?
Not that I know about.
What, my hands?
Well, yeah, I know,
I got faggot hands.
They're soft.
Actually, I was wondering
about your tattoo.
Oh, that?
I'm in a secret club.
Are there many members?
Hey, listen...
...I can be whatever
you want me to be.
You want me to romance you, take you
to a classy restaurant, no problem.
You want me to be your best friend
and fuck you...
...treat you good, lick your pussy...
...no problem.
Ain't much I haven't done.
The only thing I won't do
is beat you up.
Why does your partner
carry a water pistol?
-They took his gun away.
-Why did they take his gun away?
Because...
...his wife caught him
fucking a fat chick.
When she found out
she ran upstairs and tosses...
...his Hispanic Society trophy
out the window.
And you know, that's pretty much
when he tried to kill her.
That's a good reason to kill your wife,
of all the reasons that I can think of.
He wasn't gonna kill her, lady.
He was just trying to scare her.
That was his San Juan
Man of the Year Award, you know?
Ritchie takes that stuff seriously.
So those fat-fucking-fucks from IA,
they got ahold of him...
...they take his gun,
take his badge...
...they put him on modified duty
and now he's a house mouse.
What are house mouses?
The guys who don't want
to be on the streets no more...
...or they're on modified duty like him.
You stare back at them.
That's how you flirt with black girls.
Hey, Ritchie, what the fuck?
They let you out?
What am I gonna do?
What can I do?
Nothing. You can't do nothing.
Come here, bro.
If loving you is wrong,
I don't want to be right.
-Don't be. You want a drink?
-Yeah.
Hi.
-How you doing?
-Hey, barkeep...
...two shots of bourbon
and two bourbon and Cokes.
I had to park on Christopher Street.
Must have been 100 faggots
looking to suck my dick.
-I'm jealous.
-Are all cops homophobic?
What are you,
one of them feminists?
I thought you might be
one as well, detective.
-Why?
-Malloy says that you like fat women.
-You told her that?
-Yeah, why not?
Made me think you had
a generous, even a sympathetic, view.
-You like fat girls?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, why?
-I like fat chicks.
-That chick.
-Yeah. What's up?
That chick wants to suck your dick.
All you need are tits,
a hole and a heartbeat.
You don't even need the tits.
You don't even need
the heartbeat, pal.
You going fishing?
-Want me to clock you out?
-No, I'll stay for a while.
Miss?
I didn't hit you.
I'm not-- It's not my fault.
-Are you okay, miss?
-Yeah.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
-I give you a ride.
-Okay.
Are--?
Okay.
-You okay?
-Do you have a phone?
I give you.
Malloy?
It's me.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it looked
a lot worse than it is.
You'll be all right. It's just a scrape.
Did you get a look at him?
No, he was wearing a mask.
Anything stand out? Like...
...a smell, rings on his fingers,
watch, shoes, anything?
How was that girl killed?
-Who?
-The girl killed at the Red Turtle.
Angela Sands?
She wasn't killed at the Red Turtle.
You're getting confused.
What is "disarticulation" exactly?
Listen, it's not likely that
your assailant's the murderer, babe.
It's much more likely
he's after your wallet.
So you won't tell me
how she was killed?
You really want to know?
Her throat was slit
with a straight razor.
He was trying to take her head,
maybe for a souvenir.
We found another dismembered
female body last June along the river.
I think it's the same killer.
Ritchie don't, but I do.
Go over it again.
No. Show me.
Come here. Show me.
-He came from behind you?
-I don't know.
Did you turn?
He just grabbed my head in his arm.
He had his arm around my neck.
So he must have come up
from behind you, then.
Was it his right arm?
Or his left?
It was his right.
All right.
What's that?
Take those off.
No.
What? Yeah.
That's it.
-I've been wondering about you.
-Yeah? Don't.
-I want to know.
-Know what?
How you did that to me.
Somebody taught you.
-Who was that?
-Get the fuck out of here.
You can tell me.
An older woman.
An older woman, huh?
The chicken lady.
-The chicken lady?
-Oh, you know her?
When I was 15, I was delivering
chickens for a butcher...
...to housewives for a buck a chicken.
The first time I show up there,
it was fucking hot, and....
I came to the door,
she offered me a glass of water.
So we're in the kitchen talking
about the weather or some shit...
...and she just reaches out,
she grabs ahold of my joint.
She asks me:
"Does that feel good?"
I said, "Yeah."
And she asks me,
"You ever been with a woman?"
And I said, "Yeah. No."
So she takes me into the bedroom.
She takes her clothes off,
and she's a real woman.
I mean, she's got pubic hair
from here to here.
It's black and curly
like those Spanish girls.
And I want to get the fuck out
of there, so she grabs me...
...and says, "Have you ever
kissed a girl down there?"
I said, "No."
So she wets her fingers.
She touches herself real soft.
She touches her clit
and tells me to lick there.
Tells me to put my tongue there,
take my time, lick in a slow circle.
And after a while she came.
She asked me to give her....
Get on top of her
and look her in the eyes.
-Why did you go back?
-My kids. I missed my kids.
I didn't know you had kids.
How would you?
My oldest boy wants to be a teacher.
I don't know what happened to him.
It's like Martians landed
and took over his brain.
-What does he want to teach?
-Schmoogs. Can you believe it?
Hey, I'm missing one of my....
I'm missing one of the charms
on my bracelet.
Maybe on West Broadway.
Hey...
...there's something
I really do have to tell you.
Oh, yeah?
You've seen me before.
I've seen you at the Red Turtle.
This whole time, I'm thinking,
"I've seen this girl before."
And now you're telling me
I met you at the Red Turtle.
-I don't think so, babe.
-It was dark...
...and I had on my glasses.
And there was a man...
...and a girl, and she was
giving him a blowjob.
A blowjob?
-And I watched.
-Oh, you did, did you?
You like that sort of thing?
You like watching?
You don't remember a girl with blue
fingernails with diamonds in them?
What did you say? Blue fingernails?
-She had brown hair?
-Yes.
Yeah, what about her?
I think that's Angela Sands.
That's the girl that was murdered.
But I wasn't with her.
I think you saw something.
You should come to the station
and look at some pictures...
...as soon as possible.
-Swear you weren't there.
-Swear to God.
I never seen you or her before
in my entire fucking life.
I gotta get out of here.
Hey, I had a nice time.
Thanks.
Oh, God, I could have lost you.
-Then you let the detective fuck you.
-I didn't let him, I wanted to.
-Have you ordered?
-Double latte, no foam.
Yeah.
It's sore, huh?
So the detective guy's sexy?
You like him?
You gonna see him again?
Would you trust a guy
who gets blowjobs in bars?
Yes.
I think he's a liar.
You think he's a liar, or he is a liar?
Because, of course, we never lie, so....
I saw him in a bar with a girl.
Wait.
-A bar?
-Yeah.
I thought you just met him.
I thought that he rescued you.
-lf you don't want him, I'll take him.
-Forget it, Pauline. Forget it.
No, arrange an introduction
with your lying detective.
Who's that?
John Graham.
I thought you said
he looked like a movie star?
He played a doctor on a soap.
Now he's studying to be one.
Hi.
-You look terrible.
-Excuse me, sir. No dogs in here.
I know that.
-Will you be long?
-I just ordered a coffee.
-You're very tan.
-Hi, John Graham.
-Pauline.
-How are you?
Take your time. I'll wait.
Don't look out there,
because he's watching you.
Oh, he's so intense.
I remember every guy
I ever fucked...
...by how he liked to do it,
not how I wanted to do it.
Sometimes I think it's just me.
I mean, are other women able to say:
"Suck my dick, pinch my nipples,
bend over"?
Probably not "suck my dick."
Here's what I think.
I think you can come over to my place
and sleep there for a few nights...
...maybe even a week.
It would make me really happy.
And the mugger has your wallet,
so he's gonna know where you live.
You know, you really have
to see this detective again.
I ordered a coffee.
Miss, we ordered a latte.
-No foam.
-No foam, very, very dry. Thank you.
He's still there.
Whose car did you get into yesterday?
It looked like it'd just come from Beirut.
I don't know how people
can drive around in filthy cars.
-Maybe one of my students.
-Are you dating a student?
Pardon?
You went to the Red Turtle Bar
with a black student.
-Are you dating him?
-No.
I saw you last Saturday.
-What were you doing?
-Is that the point? I don't think so.
The point is that he could
get the wrong idea.
You don't know how guys think.
Are you all right, John?
Not really. I've....
I've been having these
panic attacks lately.
-I don't know. They're pretty bad.
-What happens?
Do you ever get
these funny images...
...from the past, like you saw
something or you knew something?
Weird memories from childhood?
I just wish I didn't keep having
these funny attacks. My brain....
Well, my brain practically explodes.
I'm gonna go on antidepressants.
I need to ask you a favor.
Do you think you could
take care of Patrick?
He's barking all the time. Probably
because my hours are so long.
John, I can't take care of a dog.
Especially not my dog, right?
You'd rather cut his head off.
No, not especially your dog.
Why don't you put up
a notice or something.
Put up a notice? Where am I?
I'm in the hospital 18 hours out of 24.
You don't get it, do you?
Well, okay. Come here.
Say goodbye.
John, are you gonna put him down?
Maybe. I don't know, maybe I will.
I could do it myself.
I could shave his little arm--
I don't think it's a good idea
that we see each other.
Fuck!
Fuck.
Well....
Well, this is out of the blue.
I'm gonna....
I'm gonna have to think about this.
Midway along the journey of our life
I woke to find myself in a dark wood...
...for I had wandered off
from the straight path.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I fell over.
-Truly?
-Yours truly.
You don't never talk.
-It's always just jive.
-Well, I like to be ironic.
I'm looking for Miss Avery,
Francis Avery?
-She's gone. Her class is finished.
-It's over?
-Which one is it? This one down here?
-She might still be in the staff lounge.
I've been thinking on Gacy, you know?
Pogo the Clown?
I've been thinking
that it wasn't his fault, you know?
Like, he were the victim.
What do you know
about Cornelius Webb?
Of what?
Desire.
-Aren't you gonna help carry my bag?
-No.
You're an Amazon, Miss Avery.
That's like an insult.
-So we're here?
-Yeah.
-Hey, Papi.
-Hey, baby.
-I'm gonna help you upstairs.
-No, I got it. Thank you.
-No, let me help you upstairs.
-I really don't-- Okay, bye.
Good night.
-Let me get this for you.
-I got it. Thank you, Cornelius.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
You sure?
Oh, that was very smooth, Daddy.
Oh, that turned me on.
That was nice. Give me a kiss.
-Go away, man!
-Don't do that. Come here.
-Don't do that.
-Sit right here. Oh, you are so sexy.
Help me put my earring back in.
Come here.
In 1978, Mr. John Wayne Gacy
was in trouble...
...when the police dug up
a dead body under his cellar.
When the police were done,
they had 27 dead bodies.
Most of them from under the house.
He said he was innocent
of the crime...
...and sometimes he said
that he loved those boys.
He never said he was sorry.
Not even at the end, when they
gave him his lethal injection.
"He was chatty, " his guard said.
He wanted to discuss the Chicago
Cubs and eat fried chicken.
I'm gonna take a sleeping pill.
Two, in fact.
Do you want one?
No.
It's so fucking noisy I can't sleep.
I have to move.
I mean, clearly, I have got to move.
Why don't you see him again.
You're brave in so many ways.
You're thinking about him, right?
-About sex.
-So?
You wouldn't be thinking
about the sex if you didn't like him.
Well, at least call him.
He doesn't know where you are.
I go to court tomorrow...
...because of the tan suit.
They're trying to get
a restraining order against me.
Probably won't be allowed
within 500 miles of Dr. Cass' office.
Yeah, laugh it up.
-You know what I'm thinking?
-What to wear.
No, I'm imagining
that when he sees me...
...he's gonna realize that
he's in love with me, and, you know...
...one thing will lead to another,
and after a love child or two...
...we'll get married.
Have I ever told you how
our father proposed to my mother?
No. Tell me.
Well, when he was very young,
he was...
...very handsome
and an excellent skater.
And she was the new girl in town,
barely able to skate.