Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Frank just locks himself up
in his room...
... didn't come out
of his villa for a long time.
He had this theory he was gonna
get his hearing back...
... by having complete silence. He
wanted to rest his ears completely.
He hired people to bring in supplies
for him to the villa.
The only accounts we have
of Frank during this period...
...come from various drug dealers.
He was in a very dark place.
I love you too.
- Where is Frankie Wilde today?
- What? I haven't...
I haven't talked to him
in almost a year now.
I've heard some stories. This guy
supposedly saw him in New York...
...wearing a garbage bag for a hat
and shoeboxes on his feet.
And he... And he had a rock...
...and he was trying to eat it
like a sandwich.
I don't...
I don't think Frankie would do that.
He looked like a bum.
He always looked like a bum.
But he had a really special bond
with the homeless.
Hello.
Hello?
Is this where you come if you
want to learn how to read lips?
Of course. You want to learn?
I've got no idea
what you're saying, darling.
I can't hear anything.
This is the place, yeah?
They look like a couple of cunts.
I don't know how to lip read.
Maybe you should
write something down.
I can't hear you, and I can't read lips.
So we need to get started somehow.
So, maybe, write something down.
Temper, temper.
Watch.
Concentrate.
Watch my lips.
Watch...
...lips.
Tongue.
Jaw.
One's facial expression...
...gesture.
Lip reading...
...is about seeing...
...feeling.
Fill in the blanks, Frank.
Stepdad.
Husband.
The quick brown fox.
- The.
- Quick.
- Brown.
- Fox.
- Jumps over the lazy...
- Over the lazy dog.
Faster.
The quick brown fox...
...jumps over the lazy dog.
Good.
Fucking good.
They all speak English here.
Don't worry.
Scotch neat, please, mate.
Double Scotch neat.
- Is that okay?
- It's very good.
See what he comes back with.
To my lips.
Cheers.
You and me got the same hobby.
Another one?
What can I get you?
Scotch neat, please.
Double Scotch again.
In England, it means "fuck off. "
Very similar gesture.
Fuck off. Double.
Double fuck off.
Waiter!
Double Scotch, please, mate.
No, more.
What do you want to drink to?
Do you want to drink to something?
Who's Simon?
Silence.
- Who is he?
- Not Simon, silence.
- Are you finished with him?
- Good.
Great.
I know what I could do.
Fuck the DJ lark.
You know on TV,
you got a little ugly bird...
...bottom right-hand corner,
doing all this business?
I could do that.
I could be a cool one.
A cool little fucker
in the corner of the box. I could.
Think positively.
Yeah. "Are you going down
to Pacha tonight?"
"Oh, no, mate. No, I'm staying in
because Frankie Wilde's...
...at the right-hand bottom corner
of the TV tonight...
...doing the fucking hand jive.
It'll be brilliant. "
You finish?
There's nothing wrong
with being deaf.
I'm deaf.
Trust your other senses.
Your sight,
your smell and your touch.
Just relax.
It will come.
It just takes time.
Well, Frank's system was ingenious,
and with the weight of his sight...
... he proclaims that he began
to see a rhythm in everything...
...a pattern in the visual world
around him.
You know, could see music.
Frankie had worked with this
all his life...
... and then he realized
he was able to piece together...
... those sets
that he used to do. And...
Hey, presto, you know,
four to the floor, returneth.
I once stole 500 quid
from your wallet, in the studio.
Well...
...it's only money, eh? No big deal.
And it was me
who stuck that scaff bar...
...through the windscreen
of your Merc.
- It wasn't that Asian kid.
- Well, he's probably out now anyway...
...so no harm done.
I shagged Twila.
For three years.
Because you're a mate, yeah...
...I only ever made love
to her bum.
She doesn't like it in the bum.
Have a listen to this.
Tell me what you think.
Yeah?
Open the door! Frank!
Frank! Open the fucking door!
Do you want some more coffee?
Frank! Frank! Open the door.
Open the fucking door.
- So?
- Oh, Frank. Oh, God.
- Yeah?
- Oh, God, it's good,
- Fucking good.
- It's good?
Okay, it's fucking hot.
First off, did you...? Who's this?
Max, this is Penelope.
Penelope, this is Max.
Hi, Max.
Hi.
Forget it.
Look, Did you mix this?
- Yeah.
- Did you produce this?
- Oh, fuck.
Fuck it, Frank. It's gold.
Fucking gold.
It's beautiful.
Tell me! I haven't heard it.
It gets in your fucking chest. I've never
heard nothing like it. Fucking:
Like fucking heart. It changed...
What...? What do you mean you
haven't heard it? What do you mean?
Well, I haven't heard it.
Why?
I'm completely deaf, Max.
Completely?
Yeah.
Nothing.
To the handicapped.
Sorry.
The first time I heard
Hear No Evil...
...I was like, you know, "Whatever. "
But then Max told me
Frankie's story...
... and the penny dropped.
People love a good tragedy.
People love handicaps, frankly.
It gets them emotional, you know.
So I'll get on that deaf train
with a wheelchair ramp.
No problem.
First-class ticket, please.
I don't see why we should limit
ourselves to deaf people, really.
I don't want to reveal
too much either...
...about where we're going.
But it's gonna be big.
It's gonna be big,
and it's gonna be handicapped.
Imagine all the deaf people,
all the deaf people in the world.
They need a fucking hero, Frank.
They don't have a fucking hero.
There's no deaf hero, huh?
It's you, Frank.
You're, like, the fucking link.
You're drawing all the deaf kids
that are screaming, with no hearing.
They're yelling out to...
Who's gonna listen?
Not other fucking deaf kids.
They can't hear, huh? You.
You're the fucking voice, eh?
And wait.
Wait. You're gonna love this.
Can you hear me?
"No, I can't hear you, Max.
Are you trying to make me money?"
Yes. I'm making you money. Okay.
Fuck, look...
...that is just the fucking beginning.
I wouldn't put my name to any
old product. If I could describe it...
...as bad speed in a can.
We've all had bad speed,
haven't we?
I'm just gonna have a sip.
I can't resist.
Fuck.
He made disabilities cool.
What's with the fucking ear?
The ear, that represents
your deafness, okay.
Deaf people hate their ears, see.
Don't they? See?
So it's symbolic.
So you're gonna smash it.
The deaf kids are gonna go fucking
nuts. Don't actually hit the ear...
...because I'll put some glass on that
and turn that into a table.
It's wank. I'm sucking
deaf cock for you, mate...
...and I'm fucking choking on it.
- All right, first off, okay...
...you're sucking show-biz cock.
But look, this is gonna be
good money. This is all about cash.
Shitloads of cash, Frank.
And better than that...
...Sonya can't get her grubby fingers
on this fucking money, understand?
- This is Sonya-free cash.
- He's not a whore!
Look, Frank, okay?
You're not giving me any
fucking positive feedback.
I need fucking... You know what really
fucking bothers me about you?
The fact that you think art
just fucking happens.
It's just free.
Like these people just took out...
...time from their fucking day
to come down here...
...and do a bunch of shit for nothing.
What you gotta realize...
...is you're a hero.
That's what the yellow's about.
You make fun of me on that jacket.
I picked that jacket.
Deaf kids all over the world
are gonna see that yellow.
They'll run out, they'll buy that jacket.
Two, maybe $300.
They're gonna run around,
proudly deaf...
...all just yellow,
fluorescently deaf...
Sit down.
Charlize Bondo, Ibiza Beat.
Frankie, can you really DJ
as a deaf man?
How is that possible?
- They murmuring?
- Yeah, quite a bit.
I'm an honest man.
And I can tell you
that this album was made...
...completely without the aid
of my ears.
And at Pacha next week,
I'll be DJ'ing as a deaf man.
And if you don't believe me...
...you know, fuck you...
...because I've got nothing,
nothing to prove...
...to you sluts at all.
- Okay. Okay. Role model.
- Nothing.
- Wait a minute. Okay, role model.
Listen. Listen to me. No. No.
He loves sluts. Frank loves sluts.
Now, I think what
he's trying to say is...
...even though he feels
he has nothing to prove to you...
...he'd be happy to prove
anything you want, to you.
It's important that we all realize that
this is a major comeback from a rock.
You know, what he's accomplished
in the last few months is astonishing.
He'll be at the Pacha nightclub.
You can come down...
...and watch him mix yourself...
...and watch the miracle
happen, okay?
Because, you know, I realize, okay,
that there are doubters in this room...
...which fucks me up.
Because, you know...
...why would someone
pretend to be deaf?
I mean, that's retarded.
That's ridic...
It's not like he's fucking benefiting
from this. It's a fucking obstacle.
He can't hear a fuck...
Your mom's a cunt. Nothing.
Zero. Blank. This man,
what he's done, fucking...
It gets me in my fucking heart,
what he's done. And you...
You come down here, and you
put on this big fucking show...
...like he's gonna
fucking make shit up!
Relax. Relax, man.
All right. Next question.
One more! One more!
I thought it was amazing,
you know, that somebody...
...that's deaf can actually...
Can actually...
...you know, be a DJ.
- Frankie Wilde, good luck.
- Good luck.
I just think that guy is so fantastic.
He has a gift that no one else has.
And somehow, he is gonna do it.
Frankie! Frankie! Frankie! Frankie!
The vibe that night
was incredible.
All the memories had come back,
you know. He'd hit the depths...
... then he was just back.
Pacha, Frankie Wilde, comeback.
"Take this. Check this out. "
I've never seen an atmosphere
like it. It was amazing.
Frankie! Frankie! Frankie!
He probably never thought
he'd ever feel that again.
And to come back
and actually feel that and more...
... it was a great experience.
Everybody in the room...
... shared the same experience.
It was really, really special.
It was kind of what
dance music's about, really.
He just had clubland sparking,
bigtime.
He just took the roof
off the place. It was amazing.
It was like
he was an even better DJ...
... as a deaf man than he'd
been before. It was incredible.
Frankie! Frankie!
We won it! Listen!
Fuck! We're the fucking champions!
We got the fucking award!
This is it.
This is our fucking moment!
There's nothing... I can't... Fuck.
What do you wanna do,
buy the moon?
We'll buy the moon! Doesn't matter.
You don't understand, it's huge.
Hold on.
Okay, they're gonna come in.
Fifteen minutes.
They all wanna talk to you.
Fifteen minutes, Frank.
This is a big moment.
Listen, it's important.
Fifteen minutes. That's all they need.
Tomorrow,
big, fucking press conference.
That's what we're gonna do.
Very important, okay?
- You have to watch.
- Max?
- What? What?
- Can you do me a favor, mate?
Anything. Anything.
Could you leave us alone
for 10 minutes?
No. See, you're not listening.
Okay, listen to me.
Look at my lips, okay? Okay?
They come in for 15 minutes
of your life. Fifteen minutes.
Fifteen fucking minutes. Frank.
No, no, no, no. Frank, no.
No. Frank.
Frank, 10 minutes. Ten minutes.
Ten minutes.
Sure. Okay.
Yeah. Fucking sure.
What the fuck do I know?
Okay, now. All right, now.
Calm down.
Okay, you're getting in, buddy.
Don't worry.
You I used to like. All right.
You could do with some cheering up.
All right. Okay. Hold on. Okay.
Frankie?
Frankie!
Jesus Christ.
Frank! Fuck.
There was like a flat line.
It was...
Still, to this day, I'm...
That was it, gone.
Frankie Wilde, bye-bye. Gone.
And everybody was like that:
Holding the baby.
I've heard a story that he's running
a record shop in Oxford.
There's a story that he went to Fiji
and then died of syphilis.
But nobody knows. You know,
I don't know where he is.
He was another deaf guy
with a deaf guy's needs.
And he went off...
...to a quiet place.
Although, I suppose that
wouldn't make much difference.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org