Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Hey, Tom!
- Nicholas! You should be in class.
I've got company!
- I'm going for lobster.
- Great! Bring me one!
- I want mine with butter.
- Got that, Tom?
So long, turkeys.
Sparky will take you down today.
If you're ready,
let's buddy-up and drop.
Get us in!
For Christ's sake, get us in.
Let's get him in and keep him warm.
Put him in the forward cabin.
He'll be OK. Things'll be OK.
Let's go.
Thank you.
So?
So, I'll go down to the office,
clean out the desk,
turn in the truck,
and maybe get shitfaced
and rap your boss in the mouth.
I better give notice.
Take it easy. We may need the income.
Mike's gone.
He's making out early these days,
must be a morning man.
Like his father.
Good morning. Anything special today?
No. Sean's out somewhere.
Let him have whatever he wants.
- Just keep him away from the candy.
- OK.
- Do I still get my ride?
- Mmm.
Call your brother, the plumber,
that sink upstairs is screwed up.
Frankie? He's my cousin.
Ask if he can use an apprentice.
Have a nice day.
Do you want to just leave
her pointing up?
I'm on it.
There we go. Yeah, this is fine.
What about sailing?
What about it?
Don't you worry. We're gonna make it.
We'll make it to Budapest
if you're not careful!
Hey, what about the others?
What about them?
They'll be there when we get there.
They'll have their bonfire,
clams, liquor...
Yeah?
What are we gonna do in the meantime?
Well, in the meantime,
we'll have to think of something.
Wait a minute.
What?
Get out the blanket.
I got black marks all over my butt
and mom's getting uptight about it.
OK.
Out with the blanket.
You really need a blanket?
I don't need one!
Well... here's your blanket.
Eddie! Help!
Eddie!
- Tina!
- Help me!
Tina!
Oh... Jesus.
Eddie, swim!
Swim fast, it's a shark, Eddie.
Swim!
Oh, God. Eddie, swim!
Swim faster! Hurry!
Come on! Swim!
Hurry, Eddie. It's a shark!
Eddie, hurry! Faster! Come on. Swim!
Hurry! Hurry, Eddie.
Eddie!
Tina...
Oh, Mama...
Please make it go away.
Make it go away.
Honey, it's not your job any more.
I just wanna look.
Come on, get out of there! Come on.
- What happened to him?
- Embolism. Air bubbles in the blood.
He came up too fast, Chief.
Something must have scared him.
He just panicked.
Don't worry,
we're taking good care of him.
How did this happen?
Bite reflex, like a spasm.
It happened after the kids went out.
What kids?
Junior Vaughan,
Brookie Peters, Jackie, Mike...
Our Mike?
They're headed
for the lighthouse. Hey!
Look, Chief, you're not chief now.
I can't let you take her out.
Mrs Brody, look, you can't go.
Neither one of you can go.
- Get that line.
- Mike is out there.
But I signed for the boat.
Mrs Brody, please.
Shit! Chief, go on up to the bow,
you're doing that wrong.
Go ahead, untie the bowline.
They can't fire both of us, right?
Somebody's got to be in charge.
All right,
which direction do you wanna go?
You said something
about a lighthouse.
All right.
Amity Launch to Harbour Patrol.
'This is Harbour Patrol. '
Listen, do you think
you can raise me a chopper?
'Is that you Brody? Not right away.
'It's out checking a buoy. '
Get it out to the lighthouse.
There's some kids sailing out there.
I want them back in port.
'Affirmative.
Turn the kids back to port.
'I heard you. Patrol out. '
Brody out.
Hurry up, suckers, you're dragging!
Hey, let's go past the lighthouse.
I know a better spot. Come about.
You got it!
I got it, Chief.
It's all right. Come on.
It's OK.
It's all right.
No.
Ellen.
No, no.
Tina, Tina...
Tina, it's OK.
- It's still there.
- What is?
What's still there?
Sh-sh-sh-sh...
Shark!
It's still there.
That boat will take you in.
Where the hell are they?
Ten degrees off your starboard.
Take a heading...
Not that shit! Point!
There.
All right, I got it.
Mr Christian! Mr Christian!
Pump up this boat! And shave off
that dreadful moustache.
England expects every man
to do his duty. Fire when ready!
Damn the torpedoes!
Full speed ahead!
This will be our finest hour.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Bligh, someone pop your balloon?
No problem, no problem.
Balance the boat!
Watch out!
Do something!
Timmy! Brooke!
Hey! Look out.
Where is it?
- Get me out of here!
- I'll get you out.
Larry!
Larry! Turn!
Turn!
It's OK.
- Hurry up!
- Mike's out there.
Out of the water.
Somebody look out for Mike!
Hang on to something!
Mike, get out of there!
Hold on!
Oh, my God.
Mike!
Brody!
That's it.
- Get his arm.
- Come on.
Pull his jacket!
Get him clear, it's coming up.
Come on! Come on!
Shit!
He's bleeding pretty bad.
We got to get Mike to a doctor.
Can you sail?
Yeah. We'll take him in.
OK. Get some help here fast.
Let's go.
Let's wrap this mess up.
Throw this to Brooke.
Brooke, get this
and throw it to Mark.
Here, take it.
Tie a bowline around your mast.
Easy.
Come on, pull.
I don't know if it'll hold.
All right. Someone put a fender up.
We could use another hand on this.
Take it easy. Just pull.
Tie it off. All right.
Amity Launch to Air Patrol One.
Do you read me?
'This is Air Patrol.
That you, Brody?'
Yeah. Do you have
a fix on those kids?
'Negative. I'm still down. '
Get the hell up
because I'm out here alone.
'Brody, I got to switch frequencies.
'Call my boss.
I'll meet you by Francis Shoal. Out. '
Francis Shoal?
Where the hell is Francis Shoal?
Shit.
I'm all alone out here.
Anyone want to play charades?
No.
All we have to do is land
at Cable Junction and wait.
How will we do that on this garbage?
What's after Cable Junction?
The Atlantic. Then Ireland.
God, I'm hungry.
Air Patrol to Base.
I have a positive location
on that sailing party.
Disabled and adrift,
about three quarters of a mile west
of Cable Junction,
wind and tide carrying them due east.
Is everyone OK? Is anybody hurt?
No!
I'll tow you to Cable Junction,
then call the Coast Guard.
Throw me a line.
Take it easy. Here we go.
- Oh, what a day
- Here you go!
OK.
- Now, hold on to something.
- OK.
- Hurry up!
- Better hang on.
Sean.
- Sean!
Sean!
Get him in the boat.
- Sean!
- Come on!
Get aboard.
- Hurry!
- Come on.
Come on.
I can't get up.
No!
Take her to the hospital
and meet me at the office.
Try to understand my position...
Tina will be all right. Are you OK?
Ellen, I'm sorry.
Believe me, I'm sorry.
I was only thinking of...
I don't give a damn what you think.
A boy is dead and my son and husband
are still out there.
Amity Launch to Harbour Patrol.
Amity Launch to Harbour...
Damn it!
Sean, catch the rope!
- Come on, the rope!
- Sean!
Sean, catch the rope!
Sean, the rope!
- Come on, Sean!
Come on!
Sean!
Sean, catch the rope!
The rope, Sean!
Come on, Sean!
Come on!
You've gotta help or it won't work.
Will you stop?
Come on, Sean, wake up!
Pick it up!
Sean!
Sean, goddamn it.
Sean, listen to me
or I'll break your ass!
OK, come on.
OK, Sean, now listen.
We'll throw you this rope
and you better catch it.
Sean, you ready?
Here it comes, kid.
Get it, Sean.
Sean, get it.
Come on, get it.
Good. Now tie it around
the centreboard.
Tie it tight.
You ready? Hang on.
Hold on.
Hang on, OK?
Here we go. Hold on tight.
OK, kid.
Take it easy.
Come on.
OK.
- Get him out!
- Come on.
Oh, God. Are you OK, kid?
I thought we lost you.
Cable Junction's ahead.
- Can we make it?
- I don't know.
- Hey, I was just asking!
- I know.
How's she doing?
Just got to keep her warm.
Somebody help me
and we could steer this.
What are you playing
with a tube for?
- If everyone...
- Shut up!
I'm sorry
but I can't stop thinking about this!
Well, you better try!
Oh, God, please help.
Jesus...
Holy Mary,
Mother of Christ,
please help us.
Please help us.
We're begging.
Please save us.
Oh, thank Christ.
Here, take that back to the cleat.
- What happened?
- I'm OK.
- Sure?
- A shark hit us.
Sean's out there.
- What?
- He wanted to come.
Where are they?
They're in the current
heading for Cable Junction.
All right, get to the lighthouse
and stay there, OK?
- Stay there.
- I'm sorry, Dad.
Forget it.
Just get to the lighthouse.
- We're almost there.
- It's not gonna work.
Come on, more to port.
Keep it going. We'll make it.
More to port, goddamn it!
All the way over.
Larry, are we going to make it
to the island?
We're steering for it, kid.
But the wind drift is lateral.
What does that mean?
It means that we're going sideways.
We're going that way.
- We were heading right for it.
- Not now.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
Wait! Stop paddling.
- What about the island?
- The shark!
- What's happening?
- I think we're stuck.
It's just the bottom.
- It's that thing.
- It's just the bottom.
No, it's not the bottom.
It's that thing! It's gonna kill us!
Jackie, shut up!
- No! It's going to kill us!
- Shut up! Shut up!
Leave her alone!
Then you take care of her.
- She's hysterical, beating...
- Sit down.
Be quiet!
Shut up!
Listen!
- She shouldn't freak out.
- Listen!
You hear it?
Over there! It's coming towards us.
It's Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Oh, cool. Cool, come on...
Pull yourselves over
and we'll get out of here.
We can't.
We're stuck on the bottom here.
I'll get you closer.
We'll come aboard.
- Pull us alongside.
- Please hurry!
All right, hold it steady.
Oh, sh...!
Wait!
Dad!
I'm all right. Hold on.
All right,
take this and I'll get you over.
- All right, tie it on.
- OK.
All right,
pull these hooks over with the rope.
Secure them to the raft then I'll
pull you back with the winch, OK?
OK.
All right, pull it over.
It's stuck.
Wait a minute, I'll put...
I'll put it in reverse.
Lucy!
Lucy, look out!
Oh, my God! No! No!
Lucy!
No!
Oh, my God! No!
Dad!
Hold on!
Get away!
No!
Sean!
- Where'd he go?
- Where is he?
- There he is!
- Over there.
What the hell are you doing?
Get out of there!
He's heading right for you!
All right, you big bastard, come on.
I got something for you now.
That's it! That a boy! Come on!
Right over here!
Dad!
That's it. Come on.
No! Get out of the way!
Don't do it!
Get away! Get away!
Dad! Watch out!
Come on!
Look out!
Open wide!
Open wide, say "ah"!
He did it. He got it!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
Did he get it? It's dead?
It's dead!
Oh, thank you.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you...
- And you...
- They made me go with them.
Sure they did!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org