Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Okay.
But first you have to
hold on very tight.
Okay.
Ready?
[ Laughing ]
[Laughing Continues]
Come on, let's go!
Come on! Come on!
Watch out.
[Shouting, Laughing
Continues]
Let's go in the water!
No, don't.
Come on!
No, don't go.
Don't go. Let's go!
Hey! Let go! Don't go in
the water! Don't! No, don't!
Mom! No!
No, you stay! No!
Natalie? Natalie!
[Natalie Screaming]
- Mark! Mark!
- [Prot Shouting]
- [ Shouting Continues ]
- Prot!
Hey, this guy's as strong
as an ox! Betty, quick!
- [Prot Continues Shouting]
- Turn off the goddamn water!
Stay there, Josh. I'll
turn it off! I got it.
[Dr. Powel l]
It's okay.
[Shouting Stops]
Prot?
It's okay. It's okay. No, no, no, it's
okay, Betty. Where are his glasses?
I got it.
Are you all right?
[ Panting ]
Prot?
You're okay.
[ Sniffling ]
Is that apple pie I smell?
Sweetheart, You
all right? Yeah.
He was pushing my daughter on a swing,
like he had done a hundred times before.
Not like he was
some alien from K-PAX.
I saw him. He was
connecting with something.
Some kind of normal
life. That's not enough.
He's a violent patient,
Mark.
He's not violent.
Something violent happened
to him. Something in his past.
When he was going after Natalie, he wasn't
trying to harm her, he was trying to protect her.
From the sprinklers?
I'm not sure from what.
I need more than a hunch to go on,
otherwise I have to send him upstairs.
We need to regress him--
take him back into the past,
find out what happened
and have him confront it.
Regress him? Do you have any idea how risky
it is to regress a patient like this one?
It's his only chance.
Claudia, we have to push
him. There's no time.
He told me that he's going
back to K-PAX on July 27.
That's in three weeks.
I think that he could become violent on
that day. Hurt himself, somebody else.
You know what
the problem is, Mark.
You're too close
to this patient.
Everybody else
can see it but you.
I am transferring him to the
fourth floor, and that's final.
I know I'm too close to him.
All right, fine. I admit it.
Why choose this one
to save, Mark?
I don't know. Maybe--
Maybe because I feel...
he chose me.
Has anyone seen Prot?
He went up north
for a few days.
"North''? [Howie]
Greenland.
Iceland.
You know.
He had a few countries left to visit
before he could finish his report.
Don't worry, Dr. Powell.
He'll be back.
How do you know, Ernie?
Because he took his glasses
with him, darling.
When he returns to K-PAX,
he won't need them.
[ Sighs ]
Patients do not escape from this
institution. They don't escape.
There has been
no evidence of escape,
but obviously, I've notified
the police, social services.
I'm gonna have a great time
explaining this to the state board.
I got psychotics on the fourth
floor packing up their sneakers...
because they all think
they're going off to K-PAX.
Claudia--
Find him.
[Dr. Powell] Well, what
about city shelters?
Have you--
Have you checked?
No.
No, I'm not telling you
how to do your job.
Uh-- Thank--
Thank you.
[ Sighs ]
[ Mutters ]
Dr. Powell,
I presume.
Where the hell
have you been?
Newfoundland, Greenland,
Iceland, uh, Labrador--
All right, cut the crap. We've
been looking for you for three days.
I believe I mentioned my taking a trip
up north, Mark, in this very garden.
"Taking a trip”?
You're a patient here.
You don't leave here without a discharge.
And don't give me this beam-of-light shit,
because I don't buy it.
What would you say
if I were to tell you...
that I don't believe
You took any trip at all...
to Iceland or Greenland
or anywhere?
That I don't believe
You're from K-PAX?
I believe you're
as human as I am.
I would say you're in need
of a Thorazine drip, Doctor.
Well, there--
there is one way...
You could convince me
beyond any doubt.
Of course,
I would need your consent.
It's called hypnosis.
I just don't see the point. Let me
tell you what your alternative is.
A trip to a place where they'll stick
a needle in your ass every morning,
which may or may not leave you
with a stupid grin on your face...
for the rest of your days
here on Earth.
Is that what you'd like?
Prot?
I want to help you.
What we're going to be doing,
Prot, is a bit like daydreaming.
I'm gonna count
from one to five.
On the count of three,
Your eyes will close,
and you will find yourself
in a very nice, deep,
comfortable, relaxed
state of hypnosis.
One. Your eyes are starting
to get very heavy now.
Two. I want you
to use your imagination...
and imagine small lead weights
on your eyelids...
that are just making them
so... heavy.
[Dr. Chakraborty] Pulse
rate is 40 B.P.M. Three.
Keep your eyes closed. I'd
be concerned if he were human.
Let yourself go way,
way down deep.
Four. Let a wave of relaxation
move through your body now...
as you go down
even deeper.
And five,
going way, way down deep.
You are in a relaxed
state of hypnosis now.
How do you feel?
[ Chuckles ]
Like...
nothing.
I want you
to go back in time.
I want you to recall the first
experience that you can remember.
What do you see?
[Dr. Powell On Speaker]
What was that?
What do you see?
Uh--
[ Child-Like Voice ]
I see...
casket.
Silver...
with a blue lining.
Whose casket is it?
It's the father
of a friend of mine.
What's your friend's name?
I'm not telling.
Do you know how
Your friend's father died?
He had an accident at
the place that he worked at.
He was killed
in an accident?
He-- He was hurt
and then died later?
Where did he work? The
place where they kill cows.
Where is this place?
The pulse rate just shot
up ten B.P.M.s. [ Beeping ]
Do you know
-- Do you know where this place is?
I-I want you to relax.
I want to move forward
in time now.
Where are you?
It's nighttime.
We're in his house.
At the other boy's house?
Yeah.
I want him
to come outside.
Why?
To look at the stars.
That's where I come from,
You know.
Is your name Prot?
Wow.
How did you know that?
Where are you from, Prot?
I'm from the planet K-PAX.
It's in
the constellation Lyra.
Do you know
all the constellations?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah. Most of 'em.
And does your friend know
them too? Yes, he does.
When his dad got sick and had to
stay home, they got a telescope,
and his dad taught him about
all the constellations.
But he's not interested
in those right now.
Why not?
Something happened.
That's why he called me.
He calls me when
something bad happens.
Like when his father died?
That's right.
How do you know to come?
How does the boy call you?
I don't know. I just come.
I just-- I just know.
How do you get to Earth?
I wanna go outside.
Can I go outside?
Uh, read-- read
his body language, Mark.
I-I don't think he wants
to talk anymore today.
All right. Prot?
I want you to just relax
now. [ Shuddering ]
Think about the stars.
[ Whimpers ]
That's right. I' m gonna count
backwards now from five to one,
and you'll find yourself
wide-awake and refreshed.
Five. You're starting
to come out of it now.
Four.
You're feeling more alert.
Three.
Even more alert.
Two.
You're becoming awake now.
And one.
So when do we begin?
It's already over.
Oh, the old "fastest gun
in the West'' routine, huh?
[Slaps Knee]
Let's find the locations of all the slaughter
houses operating in the United States.
I mean, how many
can there be?
I don't know.
We eliminate, uh, the ones
in or near big cities...
and we concentrate
on small towns, rural areas,
You know, places where
You can see the stars.
Joyce, we only have
six days.
[Chattering]
Shall I bring the crystal
or leave it here?
I suppose I won't
really need it on K-PAX.
I don't even know what
they drink. [ Laughing ]
Dream on, sister. He can
only take one of us with him.
Why the hell would he take a
stinker like you? He's taking me.
How dare you!
I do not stink.
Nah, forget it, ho.
I'm the one goin'.
Yeah?
Which one of you?
Okay.
Who would like to begin?
Ernie. Uh, I-I was
-- I was wondering if it was possible...
for us to have Cream of Wheat
instead of oatmeal. [ All Groaning ]
Not again.
Howie.
I have a suggestion, because there's
really, really not much time.
I would like to propose
an essay contest...
to decide once and for all
who will go with Prot.
I've spoken with him, and he's
agreed to read them all by July 27.
So if anyone would
like to be considered,
please state your reasons
in a clear, legible hand...
and return them to me.
[ Excited Chattering ]
Russell.
[ Chattering Continues ]
Yes?
Would I get to take
my bible to K-PAX?
Of course you would.
[Betty] We can finish
the essays later.
[Dr. Powell] Now, I want you
to go back in time again,
but not so far back
as last time.
[ Chuckles ]
Is your friend there?
Is he with you now?
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah.
What's his name?
I'm not tellin'.
Prot, I would like to know
Your friend's name.
Well, I ain't
gonna tell ya.
Well, we have to
call him something.
How about Pete?
[ Chuckling ]
Well, that's not his name,
but whatever thrills you.
What year is it?
It's 1 985.
How old are you? One
hundred and seventy-five.
How old is Pete?
Seventeen.
Tell me about Pete.
What happened?
Is there a problem?
Is that why
he called you?
[ Sighs ]
He's got a girlfriend.
And the problem is with the
girlfriend? She's pregnant.
He can see it all coming right
down the road. You get married,
have a bunch of kids, wind up in
the same job that killed your dad.
He blames her for this?
Oh, no, no, no.
He doesn't blame her.
No, he just--
He--
How did he put it?
He hates the chains that people
shackle themselves with.
I mean, we don't have
all that crap on K-PAX.
All right, Prot. I want you
to listen to me carefully.
I want to move forward
in time again.
Oh, say, two weeks.
You--
If you would like to open your
eyes or move around, you may.
Would you like to?
I know that.
Prot?
Prot, when--
It's, uh,
1991,
according to
Your Earth calendar.
And your friend Pete
called you?
Not for anything
in particular.
He just... sometimes
wants to talk things over...
with someone
every now and then.
Tell me about Pete now.
He's a knocker.
A "knocker''?
A knocker is the guy that knocks
the cow inside of the head...
so it won't struggle
while they slit its throat.
I know.
It's barbaric, isn't it?
Does he still live
in the same town?
Oh, just outside of town.
He's got a little place,
but he's fixed it up nice.
It's got some... trees
and a couple of acres...
and a river.
It reminds me of K-PAX,
except for the river.
Tell me, did he ever marry
that pregnant girl?
Wow, what a memory.
Yeah, they got married, but she's no longer
pregnant. Why, that was six years ago.
I've forgotten her name.
S--
I didn't tell you
her name.
Can you tell me now?
Sara.
Did they have
a son or a daughter?
Rebecca.
It's her birthday
next week.
Chak, what's happened?
Howie tried to kill Ernie.
What?
He's fine.
Ernie? I feel
wonderful, Dr. Powell.
For heaven's sake. What
happened? Absolutely wonderful.
My good friend Howie, he just
about strangled me to death.
- What?
- [ Laughing ]
Son of a bitch,
I love him.
Ernie, I don't understand.
[Ernie]
You should've seen it.
I was asleep. You know, the way I like
-- my hands tied and everything.
He wrapped something around my neck
-- a handkerchief or something--
and then tightened it.
There wasn't a damn thing
I could do about it.
Well, when I
stopped breathing,
he lifted me onto the gurney,
rushed me up here,
and they brought me back
as quick as they could.
And when I woke up,
You know what I realized,
Dr. Powell?
Dying.
Dying's something
You have no control over.
Why waste your life
being afraid of it?
I'll sleep on my stomach
from now on.
I'll eat fish
with bones in it.
I'll swallow the biggest pill
you can find. Bring it on.
[ Chuckles ]
I feel good.
[Chuckling]
That's terrific, Ernie.
See you at our
session tomorrow? Yes.
I cured him, didn't I?
Prot says one more task
and I'll be cured too.
And then it's...
bon voyage.
[ Dings ]
[ Sighs ]
Tell me your name, damn it.
I'm gonna give you
a specific date,
and I want you to remember where you
were and what You were doing on that day.
Do you understand?
Perfectly well,
my dear sir.
The date
is July 27, 1 996.
I'm on K-PAX.
- Are you sure?
- Quite sure, governor.
I'm harvesting croppins
for a meal.
Croppins are a fungi,
like, uh, your truffles.
Big truffles. Delicious.
Do you like tru--
Wait a minute.
There it is.
What? Is it Pete?
Yes.
I sense something is wrong.
He needs me.
I'm now on Earth.
I'm with him.
And where are you?
What are you doing?
By a river...
in the back
of his house.
It's dark.
He's taking off
his clothes.
Why is he doing that?
He's--
What?
What is he doing?
He's trying
to kill himself.
Why does he want
to kill himself?
Because something terrible
has happened.
Has he done something? Has he
done something he shouldn't have?
He doesn't want
to talk about it.
Prot, I'm trying to help him. I can't
help him unless he tells me what happened.
He knows that.
Well, then, why won't
he tell me? [Sobs]
Because then
You would know...
what even he
doesn't want to know.
Then you have to
help him, Prot.
You have to help him
tell me what happened.
He doesn't want to talk about
it. Are you fucking deaf?
Time is running out
for him.
for everyone.
He jumps in.
He's floating.
Pulse is up to 1 40.
Respiration's at 30.
For God's sake, man,
bring him back.
[Panting]
All right.
Listen to me.
You can save him.
You're his friend.
I am his friend.
That's why I won't try.
Save him!
No.
[ Shuddering ]
I can't.
The cur--
The current is too strong.
There's no chance.
I... cannot.
Listen to me.
You've helped
a lot of patients here.
You've helped Mrs. Archer.
You've helped Howie and Ernie.
I'm gonna ask you
to help cure Pete now.
Let's call it a task.
- I want you to let me speak to him.
- [ Beeping ]
If he's listening, I want him
to know that he can trust me.
I want him to know that if it was
Sara or Rebecca that he did something--
[ Screaming ]
[ Sobbing ]
[Door Opens]
Get in there. No, no, no,
wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No. No, stay back. Oh,
my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh--
[Sobbing Continues]
It's okay.
It's all right.
Shh.
That's okay.
It's all right now.
I'm gonna count backwards now
from five to one,
and as I count, You'll
become more and more alert.
On the count of one
I'll snap my fingers,
and you'll wake up
feeling refreshed.
Five. You're starting
to come out of it.
Four. You're becoming
more alert.
Three.
Even more alert.
Two. You're starting
to wake up now.
And one.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Feeling fine.
Okay.
[ Muttering ]
[Muttering Continues]
[ Mutters ]
[ Unintelligible ]
Thank you.
Is this
-- Is this area code 5-0-5? Where arey ou?
[ Woman ] New Mexico,
sir. New Mexico?
"Salva.''
Salvation.
Salvation!
[Joyce] There are a dozen Salvation
Army shelters in New Mexico.
Albuquerque,
Las Cruces, Roswell.
Wait a minute. There's one in
Santa Rosa. Santa Rosa. Santa Rosa.
Santa Rosa.
Guelph.
That's pretty damn close
to Santa Rosa.
What's the biggest local
newspaper for that region?
Guadalupe County Observer,
covering Guadalupe County.
All right.
Bring that up.
Go toJuIy27, 1996.
"'Swap meet, livestock sale. '"
Wait.
Go to the 28th.
Okay.
[ Gasps ]
There it is!
"Robert Porter. Drowned!''
His name...
is Robert Porter.
[Bell Dings]
[Footsteps]
Robert Porter.
Ah, here it is.
Yeah, I do remember
this case.
It was about the biggest thing
ever happened around these parts.
He was a quiet type.
As I recall, he was a real
smart fella. Kind of brainy.
Strong as a horse, though,
and worked as a knocker.
Lived about 20 miles outside of
town with his-his wife and child.
Sarah.
His wife's name
was Sarah.
That's right.
Damn shame
what happened.
You got time
to take a ride?
Yeah.
Well,
it's been empty.
Yeah, nobody comes around
here much anymore...
since all that happened.
Ain't no livin' next of kin
to give the place to anyway.
I had detectives come
down from Albuquerque...
to try and piece
this one together.
Well, accordin' to
the official story,
Porter, he was at work
when this, uh, this drifter,
Darryl Walker,
come by the house.
Two-time parolee lookin' for
trouble. You know what I'm sayin'?
Started out
as a robbery.
The wife and the daughter
were out back.
Sarah?
[ Voice Echoes]
From what we can gather
from forensics and all,
this Walker, he, uh
-- he forced the two women into the house.
Raped the wife,
killed 'em both.
Porter, he must've come home
and found Walker still here.
God.
Snapped a grown man's neck
like it was a twig.
[Shouts]
[ Grunts ]
{#####[Woman Vocalizing]
Can't say I wouldn't have
done the same myself.
{#####[ Vocalizing Continues]
Uh, the river's
this way.
They found
the clothes there.
That's probably
where he jumped in.
And this river can be
pretty treacherous.
Even in July
it's got a hell of a current.
Still, I suppose it might have
been a mistake, officially,
to declare it a drowning
when the body was never found.
Doc,
if that boy you got back there in
New York is really Robert Porter,
I'd just as soon
not know about it.
Know what I mean?
Mark.
I'm sorry.
Never do that again.
I won't.
What happened?
I found what
I was looking for.
You sure?
Yeah.
Wish I hadn't.
{##And I think it's gonna be
a long, long time###
{## Till I touch down brings me
round again to find### [ Tooting ]
{##I'm not the man
they think I am at home###
{## Oh, no, no, no###
{##I'm a rocket man###
[Tooting]
If you wouldn't mind
putting mine on top.
{##Burnin' out his fuse
up here alone###
[Tooting]
{##And I think it's gonna be
a long, long time######
Prot.
Have a seat.
You all packed?
Ready to go?
Quite ready.
I travel light.
That's a joke,
Mark. [ Chuckles ]
You humans. There's
just no sense of humor.
I doubt, uh,
Freud ever tried this,
but before
someone goes away,
we usually like to send them off
with a little toast.
Scotch okay, or would you prefer
something more fruity?
I will try
the scotch.
Well,
here's to a...
safe journey.
Tell you the truth,
K-PAX sounds like
a beautiful place.
I'd like to see it sometime.
Think there's a chance of that?
I think you should see
more of your world.
As a matter of fact, I think you
should see more of your own family.
Invite your son
for Christmas.
I may just do that, Prot.
You know what I've learned
about your planet?
There's enough life on Earth
to fill 50 planets--
plants, animals, people,
fungi, viruses--
all jostling
to find their place,
bouncing off each other,
feeding off each other,
connected.
You don't have that kind
of connection on K-PAX?
Nobody wants,
nobody needs.
On K-PAX, when I'm gone,
nobody misses me.
There would be
no reason to.
And yet I sense
that when I leave here,
I will be missed.
Yes.
Strange feeling.
You don't have
to leave, Prot.
I'm sure there must be some way
that I can help you...
to stay as one of us.
I will miss you,
Dr. Powell.
Oh.
And I have to finish
my report, but...
I seem to have misplaced
my pencil.
Take mine.
A much more efficient
writing tool.
Adios, my friend.
Prot?
I wanna show you
something.
That is Robert Porter.
Prot, that's you.
You and Robert Porter
are the same person.
That's patently absurd.
I'm not even human.
Can't you at least
admit the possibility?
I will admit the possibility
that I am Robert Porter...
if you will admit
the possibility...
that I am from K-PAX.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a beam of light
to catch.
Oh, Mark.
Now that you've found Robert,
please take good care of him.
{## That nobody can deny###
# That nobody can deny #
# For he's a-- ##
I can't stand it.
I-- I can't
stand this!
I demand to know...
which one of us
is goin' with you.
Well, I can
tell you this.
There's extra points for
the one who goes to sleep first.
[ Mumbling ]
[Woman]
Out of my way!
Oh, my gosh.
You never gave me
my last task.
What's my last task?
To stay here.
And be prepared...
for anything.
You look tired, Doc. Why don't
you get a few hours of rest?
He's not goin'
anywhere. Uh--
We got seven hours.
I'll see you in four, hmm?
Get some rest.
You're gonna eat.
You need some food
and you need to sleep.
Chow Fun.
Oh, the place on Broadway with
the ugly lanterns in the window?
The mean walter
always shouted at us.
Their fortune cookies never
had any fortunes in 'em.
We never needed any.
I knew my fortune
that night.
He was sitting
right in front of me.
Hope he still is.
Hey.
What's up, man?
Look, 20 says he
goes. You're on.
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Thunder]
Shit!
Oh, damn it!
Two minutes.
You know where Dr. Powell is?
I'll buzz him.
One minute.
Here comes Dr. Powell!
He's moving.
Repeat:
He's moving!
What the hell?
Wait for me, you--
[ Grunts ]
Son of a bitch.
Oh, God.
Oh, man.
Call a code blue.
Help me. Let's get him.
[ Monitor Beeping ]
Who's that? Beats me.
How'd he get in here?
That's not Prot. He's
definitely not Prot.
Certainly not.
Prot's gone.
Where's Bess?
[Man]
Where's Bess? Bess?
He chose Bess.
Bitch!
[Man]
Good-bye, Bess.
Good for you,
homegirl.
Bess went to K-PAX.
[ Mark's Voice ]
Patient 287, Robert Porter.
How I wish I could say that
Robert sat up one fine day...
and said, "'I'm hungry.
Got any fruit?'"
Like most catatonics,
he probably hears
every word we say...
but refuses
or is unable to respond.
Nevertheless,
I keep him up to date.
Let's see.
I told you about Howie.
He got that job
at the public library.
And Ernie, he's determined
to be a crisis counselor.
The only one we're, uh,
really concerned about is Bess.
You know, we've checked
halfway houses, shelters,
churches, bus stops.
Nothing.
Uh, we don't understand.
It's like...
people don't just disappear.
July 27th ?
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
Robert?
No.
Well, maybe
it'll come to you.
Whenever you're ready,
I'll be waiting.
[Prot's Voice] I want to
tell you something, Mark,
something you
do not yet know,
but we K-PAXians have been around
long enough to have discovered.
The universe will expand,
then it will collapse
back on itself,
and then it will
expand again.
It will repeat
this process forever.
What you don't know is that
when the universe expands again,
everything will be
as it is now.
What ever mistakes you make this time around,
you will live through on your next pass.
Every mistake you make...
you will live through...
again and again, forever.
So my advice to you is to
get it right this time around,
because this time...
is all you have.
You're lookin' great,
Michael. Think so?
Thanks.
How you doin'?
Good. How was your--
How was your trip?
Was it--
Was it good?
sync by indraf
{##Maybe this is forever###
{##Forever fades away###
{##Like a rocket ascending###
{##Into space###
{## Could you not be sad###
{## Could you not breakdown###
{##After all###
{##I won't let go###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{## There's beauty in release###
{## There's no one left
to please###
{##But you and me###
{##I don't blame you
for quitting###
{##I know you really tried###
{## Only you could hang on###
{## Through the night###
{## 'Cause I don't
wanna be lonely###
{##I don't wanna be scared###
{##And all our friends###
{##Are waiting there###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{## There's beauty in release###
{## There's no one left
to please###
{##But you and me###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I could
have held on###
have let go###
{##Feel like I could
have helped you###
have changed you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I could
have held you###
have let you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I was a stranger###
{##Feel like I was an angel###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I was a hero###
{##Feel like I was a zero###
{##Safe and sound###
{##Feel like I could
have killed you###
have healed you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I could
have touched you###
have saved you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I should
have known you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I could
have changed you###
have moved you###
{## Until you're safe and sound###
{##Feel like I should
have told you###
{##Feel like I could
have known you###
have loved you###
{##Feel like I couId
attractyou###
{##Feel like I could
have saved you###
{##Feel like I really
loved you###
{##Feel like
I really loved you######
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org