Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Thanks.
- Is it OK if I smoke?
- Sure.
My matches are all wet. You got a lighter?
Yeah. It's here somewhere.
It's my wife's car.
There we are.
I remember going on a school trip
to the top of the Empire State Building.
When I looked down at the people
on the street, they looked like ants.
I pulled out a penny. Some of us started
talking about what would happen
if I dropped it from up there
and it landed on somebody's head.
Of course I never crossed that line
and actually dropped the penny.
I don't think Early Grayce
even knew there was a line to cross.
I mean the mind of a serial killer
as it relates to culpability.
Someone who can't distinguish
between right and wrong is like a child.
In law, he should be treated like a child.
He should not be in prison, or executed.
There you go again.
Next comes the part where
you blame misfiring synapses,
amok biochemicals
and horrendous childhoods.
It's a fact. Most of these people
have severe chemical brain imbalances.
Think I put enough tequila in?
The answer is research and treatment
under hospital conditions.
Not the electric chair.
That's great, Brian. Unless it's your
mother's head they find in the refrigerator.
But executing the killer
would not bring my mother back.
- Thank God.
- Oh, everybody's a joker.
But it'd sure make you feel a lot better.
No, actually it wouldn't
make me feel any better.
Brian, the bottom line is
these people are evil, plain and simple.
How 'bout a bowl of chilli? A hot one.
Be right there!
Antichrist would be a woman
in a man's body,
with seven heads and seven tails.
Make that to go.
Antichrist would be a woman
in a man's body.
Seven heads and seven tails.
Antichrist would be a woman
in a man's body.
Seven heads and seven tails.
Yeah!
I always knew I'd be a writer,
but there's a big difference between
writing a magazine article and a book.
I know. I wrote a magazine article.
Everything I ever wanted to know about
serial killers fit nicely on the four pages.
Brian, what are we doing here?
Research. Come on, look at this place.
You'll get some great photos in here.
This is where her nightmares began.
Her father worked the night shift here.
Most nights, he'd take her with him.
She was 11 years old.
Of course, the bastard knew
that nobody could hear her screams
over the noise of the machines.
The article got me a book deal.
A little cash upfront.
But, between the rent and the convertible,
the advance was gone.
I owed a book and I was stuck.
What little I knew about serial killers
I'd learned in a university library.
The only thing I knew for certain was that
people didn't kill each other in libraries.
She murdered her first victim over here.
They found him stuffed in the corner.
They found her second victim over there.
Can you imagine the rage and pain
she must have felt returning to this place?
The victim returns
to the scene of the crime
and becomes the criminal.
Where did everybody go?
I didn't take that long.
Size seven.
That's right, ain't it? Super size seven.
Oh, Early, you're a specialist.
- Happy birthday, Adele.
- Thank you, honey. These are beautiful.
This reminds me of Cinderella when
the prince gave her his glass slipper.
Except these ones are red
and they ain't see-through.
And there's two of 'em. Is that my chilli?
Oh, honey.
Happy birthday to me. Thank you.
Tonight turned out to be interesting, uh?
Those fascinating friends of yours
and their stimulating conversation?
No, the warehouse. I'm not that stoned.
Oh, the warehouse.
Actually, yeah, it was pretty interesting.
It was definitely the highlight
of the evening.
You know, just bein' there where it
all really happened. I could almost...
Take your shirt off.
Yes, ma'am.
Come here.
Early!
What?
I'll be waitin' for you when you get back.
Put your titty back up, Adele.
Oh, wait, I forgot.
Mr. Diebold stopped by yesterday.
He said if we don't pay him
by the end of the month,
he's gonna kick us
the F-U-C-K outta here.
He said that to you? Cussed at you?
- You gonna talk to him?
- Well...
Shut up!
If he comes back here,
don't you open that door.
Suppose he hears me inside?
I picked up some Chinese.
Did you hear from the gallery?
Have you got your slides back?
What'd they say?
Oh, well, you know.
Same story, different day.
They're idiots.
Too graphic. Too overt.
Not suitable for mass consumption.
I forget what...
You don't wanna be suitable
for mass consumption.
I know.
It's just...
Who cares anyway, right?
Not me.
Christ, I'm dying here, Brian.
Why can't we get out of here?
Why can't we just get the hell out of here?
Why can't we just go to California?
Why not?
- Just like that?
- Yeah. Just like that.
What the hell did I know about California?
For some people, it was still
a place of hopes and dreams.
A chance to start over.
The idea was, if you could just get there,
everything would be OK.
And if it wasn't OK there, well, then it
probably wasn't gonna be OK anywhere.
Adele! Whose car is that out front?
She's not here.
Shit.
Well, look who stopped by.
And I ain't supposed to be at the parole
office till tomorrow. Two o'clock.
You know, Early, you're supposed
to notify me when you lose your job.
Yep.
I stopped by the mirror factory today.
- You left quite a mess behind there.
- That wasn't my fault.
It's dangerous there
and they treat me like shit.
Nobody ever has treated you right,
have they, Early?
Your daddy was pickin' on you
when he threw you outta the house
for stealin' the tyres off his truck.
The police were way outta line when they
kept you from beatin'
that bartender half to death.
You know, Early, I bet the Lord's gonna
be pickin' on you come Judgment Day.
Now, hold on there.
I ain't got nothin' against God, see?
It's just the people he let get in there.
What you lookin' for?
That girlfriend of yours.
Not much for housekeepin', is she?
Well, we's thinkin'
about movin', anyhows.
Maybe down to Texas.
Get me a job in one of them offshore rigs.
What are you talkin' about?
Well...
- You know you can't leave the state.
- Yeah, it's just...
What you can do is get a job.
You be at this address.
Three o'clock sharp.
What is it?
Janitor's job.
Well, don't wanna be no janitor.
I don't give two shits
what you want and what you don't want.
I'm tellin' you to be there. Or you
gonna be havin' dinner with the sheriff.
You understand me, boy?
You oughta try puttin' a bag
over your head for that cough.
Works every time.
Peg-armed piece of shit.
She came back to the warehouse
that her father molested her in.
Why? Because this place is the catalyst.
She needed to relive her own nightmares
before she could kill those men.
How are you, Sleeping Beauty?
- I didn't have the heart to wake you.
- Thanks.
My head.
- What are you doin'?
- I sat down with your photos,
- which are wonderful...
- Thank you.
..and my tapes, and I started writing.
- How's it goin'?
- It's the best stuff I've ever done.
- And I think I know why.
- Why?
Because, for the first time, I understood
that woman as a human being.
I was walking where she walked,
where she killed.
I was in her skin,
looking through her eyes.
I think we got a book here,
with your pictures and my writing.
- It's a book.
- A book on the warehouse murders?
No, on some of the most infamous
murders in American history.
I wanna go to where they lived
and where they killed.
I want you to take the pictures.
I'll write the text.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about this.
We can go through Tennessee.
We could drop through Arkansas...
wherever the hell Arkansas is.
There it is.
Then we can drop down into Texas,
and from there
it's a straight shot right into...
California.
We don't stop till
we hit the fucking ocean.
Thank you.
We don't have enough money,
but we'll figure something out, right?
- Hold on a minute there, boy.
- Shit!
Goddammit, you're gonna
settle that rent here and now.
I'm tired of your bullshit, boy.
I want my money!
Dipshit.
You son of a bitch. Come back here!
That's it. Tell him I want you both the fuck
outta here by Sunday or I'll call the police.
Elvis, get the fuck off of him.
The ride share was my idea.
I thought if we found somebody
who wanted to go to California,
they'd help pay for the gas.
Carrie wasn't crazy about the idea,
but the Lincoln only
got eight miles a gallon.
- They say one day the whole thing...
- Is gonna slide right in the ocean.
''Need somebody to share turns
at the wheel and expenses
on a week-long, cross-country
tour of historic murder sites''?
You've gotta be kidding.
Who in their right mind
is gonna want to do that?
- I would.
- Like I said...
Hey, good luck on that thesis.
Don't know where
the personal office is at, do you?
Personnel office is...
first door on the left.
What, down there?
Stinking bitch.
Shit.
Early!
- How ya doin', momma?
- Fine.
Boy, I'm tired. Dinner ready yet?
Almost.
Well, let me know.
- Early.
- Yeah?
- Will you tell me more about California?
- Yeah, I guess so.
Let's see.
One thing, people think faster out there
on account of all that warm weather.
Cold weather make people stupid,
that's a fact.
That explains why there's
so many stupid people round here.
It sure does. You know what else?
You never have to buy no fruit
on account it's all on the trees.
And they ain't got no speed limits.
I hear your first month's rent
is free - state law.
So till we get settled, we'll just
move around from month to month.
How'd that be with you, momma?
What are we gonna do out there, Early?
The first thing is get us a couple of
six-packs of Lucky Lager
and climb up to that famous Hollywood
sign. We're gonna howl at the moon.
Yeah, just like that.
I heard once that there
ain't nothin' on that ol' moon
except some little golf balls
the astronauts left behind.
Nah, that ain't right. That's bullshit.
The government be sendin' people there
all the time. Just don't want us to know.
Now, git.
Well, let me know when you're finished.
Shit!
So what'd he sound like over the phone?
He was real polite.
He kept calling me ''sir''.
- I like that.
- Yeah, I'll bet you do.
You should try it once in a while.
I don't know. This is really weird.
We should have at least met them first.
Beggars can't be choosers. They were the
only ones to answer the ride-share note.
Oh, God. Please don't let them
be as boring as Brian's friends.
Anything but that.
Early, we shouldn't be doin' this.
You know you ain't even allowed
to be leaving the state.
And these people are strangers.
What kind of people would stop at places
where other people got murdered?
What if these people
are dangerous, Early?
- They ain't dangerous, they're writers.
- Honey... Early Grayce!
- Did you settle things with Mr. Diebold?
- Yeah, I did.
I left him with the car.
We're all straight now.
- What is that?
- That's Lucy.
Adele, what kind of cuckoo-brain
carries a cactus in her purse?
I don't know.
Straighten up.
Oh, Brian. You've got to be kidding me.
They look like Okies.
Oh, Jesus, they look kinda weird.
- They can't have $5 between them.
- Smile. Let me do the talkin'.
- Let's keep goin'.
- Lighten up.
- How many times you gonna say that?
- As many times as it takes.
Lighten up.
- Early?
- Mr. Kessler?
Hi, I'm Brian Kessler. Nice to meet you.
- You must be Adele.
- Yeah.
- That's Adele.
- Nice to meet you.
Hi.
- Can I help you with your luggage?
- Oh, yeah.
- I'll get these.
- OK.
- Hi, I'm Adele.
- Hi, I'm Carrie.
- Oh, I like your hair.
- Oh. Thanks.
Cos it... it's short.
Oh, yeah. Well... Thanks.
Carrie was right. If you looked in
the dictionary under ''poor white trash'',
a picture of Early and Adele
would have been there.
But I knew if I was gonna
be a good writer,
I'd have to ignore the clichés
and look at life through my own eyes.
- So, Early.
- Yep.
- What do you do?
- Well, I do some work at the...
Well, I did some work
at the mirror factory.
Know what, Brian? One night
when we was stayin' up late,
we was talkin' about
how much bad luck
he must have coming
from all those mirrors he broke.
And I swear we came to 449 years that
it would take for him to work it all off.
And he'd have to - after he died,
he's gonna have to keep comin' back
to earth over and over and over again.
Karma.
- What?
- Karma.
You know, when you do
something bad to someone,
and fate pays you back
by something bad happening to you?
Is that French?
We could stop somewhere
if you haven't had breakfast.
It's like this, Brian. I don't eat breakfast.
It's because of what
he read in this book once, Brian.
That folks needin' breakfast
is a myth or somethin',
and it was put out by the cereal people.
- Jesus Christ!
- Who are you?
His parole officer.
Oh, right. Talked to you on the phone.
- What the hell happened?
- They say it's a torch job.
- That sound like your boy?
- Yeah, could be.
- Where would I find him?
- I don't know.
Crazy son of a bitch was talkin' about
movin' down to Texas.
Without his car?
What about the owner of the house,
this... Mr. John Diebold?
- You know where he might be at?
- I don't know.
I tell you what. He's not gonna be
too happy when he sees this.
Jesus Christ!
Early seemed harmless.
Primitive, but harmless.
The fact was that he'd killed his landlord
less than an hour before we met him.
He was even wearing the guy's ring.
Who knows what he did with the finger?
Here you go, momma.
- Oh, thank you, honey.
- Yeah.
Look what I got! I got a camera.
Who gets the water?
Here you go, Bri.
I got chips and some jerky here.
If you want 'em, just holler.
Just in case.
From the moment I began
working on the book,
I found myself asking
one question over and over.
What's the difference
between a killer and any one of us?
What was it they had - or didn't have -
that separated them from us?
The Novaks are long gone.
But the white picket fence
they hired Michael Zeruba to put up
is still here.
- The Novaks...
- Hey, you two.
Come on, show your love.
The Novaks embraced the young drifter
as one of their own.
The neighbours said
he was a quiet young man
who was often seen pushing
the children on the swing set.
Everything was fine until the day
the Novaks ran out of work for Michael
and had to ask him to leave.
How does a man get to the point where
he can kill a human being in cold blood?
Early, could you move
out of the way, please?
The first to die
was the nine-year-old daughter.
Hi, I'm Brian Kessler. What's your name?
Pa!
Pa, where are you?
Pa! There's somebody at the door
who wants to see you.
- What? Who is it?
- I don't know.
Afternoon, sir. I'm sorry to wake you.
My name is Brian Kessler.
I'm a writer.
I'm workin' on a book on some of
the famous murders in American history.
I'm sure you're aware
that this is the Novak farm.
I was wondering if my girlfriend Carrie
could come in and take a few pictures?
I'll walk around, tape some notes and
we'll be out of your hair in five minutes.
I'd like to maybe just walk around
the house and get a feel for it.
Goddamn ghouls.
We drove all day to get here, sir.
I'd be out of your hair in five minutes, sir.
Five minutes.
Brian, come on.
Let's forget about it. Come on.
At the time, I was angry that
Mr. Baxter slammed the door in my face.
But it was just his way of forgetting,
of pretending that nothing terrible
had ever happened there.
I guess it's only natural to try
and forget the bad things that happen.
You never really do, though.
We've come 480 miles so far.
- Not bad for a day's haul, huh?
- Pretty good.
You got any family or friends
in California, Early?
- No. Do you? You do?
- No, I don't.
Do you have any friends or family
in California, Carrie?
What? No.
Well, that's OK.
At least we all got each other, right?
I mean, that's somethin'.
My momma used to say that
when you have people around you,
it's better that you're not by yourself,
because when you're alone
it's hard to develop your personality.
With more people around you, it helps,
cos friends are really important and...
- Thank you.
- Thanks, bro.
We'll get the next one.
We gotta hit the sack.
Let's go, momma.
- Have sweet dreams.
- Night, Adele.
Night, Early.
That's funny.
I didn't know you were so prejudiced.
Because I object to having
somebody take off their shoe
and scratch their foot
while I'm eating... I'm prejudiced?
He can't help the way he was raised.
I kinda feel sorry for him.
You feel sorry for him. That's so sweet.
Obviously you didn't get
a whiff of that sock.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
30 bucks for a motel. For what?
A lumpy mattress, a crummy TV
and a crapper? Don't think so.
- Honey, sing me a song.
- I'm busy, momma. Just stay put.
Please?
OK, if you don't sing it,
I'm gonna sing it myself.
# Do your balls hang low?
Do they wobble to and fro?
# Can you tie 'em in a knot?
Can you tie 'em in a bow?
# And put 'em over your shoulder
Like a continental soldier?
# Do your balls hang low?
Do your balls hang low?
Honey, when we get to California, will
you take me to that Chinese restaurant
where all them footprints are out in front?
Only if they let me put mine down, too.
Pretty smooth how they stiffed us
on dinner, though.
He didn't stiff us.
He paid for the gas, remember?
Brian, I am telling you
they're almost broke
and we are gonna end up
paying for the two of them.
Don't change the subject.
It is my favourite subject, though.
- Morning.
- Morning, Early.
- Breakfast?
- No, I don't eat breakfast. Never do.
Sir? We don't have a liquor licence,
so I'm afraid you're gonna have to...
That's OK. I got plenty more
where this 'un come from.
- Morning.
- Morning, Adele.
You cut your hair.
Early cut it.
He said it makes me look more pretty.
And I think he's right
cos... he's right.
Nice job, Early.
You like to order some breakfast?
No, I won't be having breakfast
this mornin', thank you.
Want some of this?
- Finish.
- Thanks.
What you readin'?
- Sex, Art, and American Culture.
- No, I never read that.
I can't wait to get on the road.
I love that convertible.
- Yeah, it's great.
- Cos...
I like wind, Brian.
So do I.
- You want me to get your stuff?
- No. Thanks, Early, I can manage.
I meant to say luggage. Ma'am.
I got 'em.
- Hi, honey.
- Momma.
When you dream, there are no rules.
People can fly. Anything can happen.
Sometimes there's a moment
as you're waking
and you become aware
of the real world around you,
but you're still dreaming.
You may think you can fly,
but you better not try it.
Serial killers live
their whole lives in that place,
somewhere between dreams and reality.
Guess it's your turn to pay, Early.
Hey, move it.
Stupid son of a bitch.
You know, I used to smoke
before I met Early.
But he broke me of that.
- Broke you?
- Oh. Yeah.
Cos Early, he don't think that women
should smoke or drink or cuss.
So you know what I do?
I spell all my cuss words.
S...
S-H...
S-H-I-T!
But you don't do
any of those other things?
No. I mean, I better not.
- He whips you?
- No, no, no. Only when I deserve it.
- You were in there a long time.
- Yeah, I took a dump.
You don't wanna go in there.
Wall-to-wall stink.
- Just goin' in to wash my hands.
- Ain't got no sink.
- No sink?
- No. Damnedest thing I ever seen.
Let's go.
How 'bout I drive, bud?
- No, momma. Get in the back.
- $28.35, sir.
- How much?
- $28.35.
There. Hope I got that.
Make it an even 30.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
When you first meet people, all you notice
is the differences between you and them.
But, as time passes,
you start noticing the similarities.
I guess that's how all friendships begin.
OK, so you first. You put down
a card, and then I put down a card.
Then when they match up
and it's the same card,
then you go ''snap'' and I take it.
And I take the cards
that's there and... like that.
Snap.
I thought you said
you never played this before.
I haven't. I really haven't.
I'm a fast learner, I guess.
I was reading in your deal there how
they never caught that Black Dolly killer.
- Black Dahlia.
- Yeah.
- They didn't.
- Well, I was wonderin' how come.
See what I'm gettin' at? It's like ''Hmm.”
Well, some people think he just stopped
killing and disappeared back into society.
That's fine and dandy, but I wanna know
what a smart fella like yourself thinks.
I always thought
it was the work of a serial killer.
Anybody who took that much care
bisecting another human being...
- Bisecting?
- He cut 'em in two.
- He hacked 'em up?
- In two pieces, yeah. In half.
Anybody who did that
must have enjoyed it.
He would have done it again and again
and again until somebody stopped him.
That's good. That's a good theory, Bri.
You wanna hear mine?
- Sure.
- OK.
Ain't you gonna record it?
Early Grayce's Black Dahlia theory.
June 23rd.
OK. Now, I'm bettin' he's still alive.
Real old, livin' in a trailer park
or somethin', somewheres.
But he's alive, see.
Now, he's thinkin' about what he done,
goin' over it and over it and over it
in his head, every night,
thinkin' how smart he is
for gettin' away with it.
- That's possible.
- You shoot pool?
Come on, bud.
Designated driver.
Minnesota Fats.
- Don't forget your key.
- Why'd I open my big mouth?
Please come home soon.
Let's go!
Jesus, bud,
you damn near swallowed her!
So why didn't you go with them, Adele?
Cos, you know how Early feels
about women drinkin'.
So how did you and Early
meet, anyways?
I was hitchhikin' this one day.
And Early stopped.
And I walked up to look in the window.
And I looked in, and Early's face,
he was down like that cos he was serious.
And then he said ''You gettin' in?”
And then he looked up
and that's when I saw his eyes.
And I swear, Carrie,
he has the eyes of an angel.
And then, I ended up
movin' in his trailer with him,
cos I thought it'd be kinda neat.
But...
Know what? I was thinkin' that
what if me, you and Brian and Early
all moved into a house
together in California?
Wouldn't that be fun?
Well, I mean...
Well, we'll see what happens.
- You never know.
- OK.
Do you want me to fix your hair for you?
Yes.
Cos... I don't really like it. That much.
Come on, then.
- OK.
- It doesn't look that bad, but...
I think we should fix it.
I'm bettin' we gonna find us
some doors round here.
- Yeah, the door's out front, on the street.
- Not doors.
Not doors, bud.
Openings to other dimensions.
See - I read, bud.
And I'm tellin' you,
if a man knows what he's doin',
he can transport himself to
anywhere in this goddamn universe.
Didn't know that, did you?
No, I didn't. Think I should tell you
I'm not much of a pool player.
Oh, it ain't hard. I can teach you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'll spot you a few balls.
- You're not gonna hustle me, are you?
- How much money you got?
What's that?
That's a portfolio of my work.
That's what that is.
Your pictures? Can I look at 'em?
Yup, go right ahead.
Oh, my Lord!
- Did you take this one?
- I took all of those.
- That one's me.
- No, it isn't.
- Hold still, you.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
My God, Carrie.
If Early ever saw me in a picture like that,
I'd be black-and-blue for a week.
You shouldn't let him do that to you.
You think Early's mean to me?
Well, he's not.
He may punish me once in a while, but...
he's not mean.
When I was 1 3...
there were these three boys.
They raped me in the back of this truck.
They hurt me so bad,
I was in the hospital for,
like, four months.
And I feel safe with Early, cos
most of the time he treats me really nice.
I know that he'd never...
He would never let anything like that
ever happen to me again.
I like my hair.
You did a really good job, Carrie.
It's really professional.
Hey, Marlene! Come here, baby.
Why don't you and me get together
tonight and sweat it up some?
Fuck off, TJ.
There you go. That'll be five bucks.
Wait. Wait a minute.
These aren't Lucky Lager.
- We ordered Lucky Lager.
- Take a look around you.
If you see somethin' lucky around here,
you let me know.
Why don't you tell me
what you think is so funny?
- What?
- Do you think I'm funny?
No.
What would a jizz-garglin',
cum-drunk fairy like you
do with a pretty girl like that, anyway?
- What are you talkin' about, man? Relax.
- Hit him, Bri, cos it's comin'.
- What was that? Is this your boyfriend?
- No, he's not my boyfriend. Just cool it.
- Hey, asshole.
- This ain't Lucky Lager.
Break it up!
It wasn't that guy's fault. TJ started it.
Dipshit.
Rack 'em up.
# Cos your pink replaces your red
- My mom was a beautician.
- Really?
Yeah. She likes pink a lot.
You should have seen her face.
She was mad when she first
found out I was with Early,
on account of him
just gettin' out of jail an' all.
She hasn't talked to me
in over a year now.
I wish she'd call me, Carrie.
Early's been in jail?
What for?
For carryin' a gun.
And resistin' arrest.
It's a really interesting story, actually.
He put up a fight with the policeman
and they struggled because
he didn't wanna be arrested.
I'd have done the same thing.
Why aren't you laughin' now?
I don't know. I just don't think that
carrying guns and resisting
arrest is very funny.
Well... I'm gonna go back
to my hotel room now, Carrie.
I had a really great time with you.
I just think I had too many beers.
And I wasn't even supposed
to be drinkin' in the first place!
Adele, you don't have to go.
I didn't mean...
Great.
Look at this dipshit.
Hey, watch it, asshole!
Get him, Bri. Tear him up.
Oh, I gotta see a man about a mule.
What?
Take a piss.
Hey, see if there's any reebs
in the back seat.
- What?
- Reebs. Beers.
It's what we used to call 'em
when we were kids.
It's beer spelt backwards.
Shit! Think I chipped the concrete, Bri.
The last one. I want you to have it
- for saving my ass.
- Don't want it. Take it.
It ain't nothin'. I picked
that big Yankee mother years ago.
But I'm not a mother and you are.
Come on!
Thank you.
How long you had your woman, bud?
- Three years.
- Yeah? She's a good one.
She's a breeder, you dog.
I'll tell her you said she's a breeder.
She'll like that. I'll tell her you said that.
Can I get that, bud?
Do you remember them doors?
Them doors I was talkin' about, Bri?
I got me a couple.
I found me a couple of 'em in Kentucky.
Hell, I wasn't even lookin'
for the first 'un.
I was on the side of the road
swingin' my sickle.
I turn around and there's this door.
This big ol' door.
And light's comin' out,
blinding me, real gold.
And I'm thinkin', this can't be.
So, I close my eyes.
And I count one,
I count two, I count three,
I count four, five.
And I open my eyes.
It wasn't there.
Come on.
Am I late?
Sorry.
Early and me,
we got into a fight in this bar.
I'm fine, though.
It was me and him against like, 30 guys.
You and I, we gotta talk
about your good buddy Early.
Who said he's my good buddy?
You sure been actin' like you were.
- Out whoopin' it up and drinkin'.
- You been drinkin', too. Come on.
Oh yeah, right.
You should have seen how scared
she was that he was gonna find out.
- He beats her, you know.
- How do you know that?
Because she told me.
That's how I know that.
I gotta see a man about a mule.
But only when she deserves it!
Do you happen to know
that he was in jail?
Yeah. For stealing a car.
Really? Is that what he told you?
He told her it was for carrying a gun.
Brian, it could be for murder
for all we know.
Will you stop being
so fucking melodramatic?
Melodramatic?
If it was murder... he'd still be in jail.
Or he'd be on parole.
In which case, he wouldn't
be allowed to leave the state.
Maybe he wasn't allowed to leave the
state. Ever stop to think about that?
OK, we'll get the keys, we'll get the
car and sneak out. Is that what you want?
- What is the matter with you?
- Can we talk about this in the morning?
So how are you feelin' now, Brian?
Does your stomach feel kinda like
it's in these knots and it's twisty
and you could just explode
at any given moment?
Well...
My daddy, he used to make
this great drink for hangovers.
And he'd make a blend of
sauerkraut juice and Tabasco sauce...
Goddamn! You see that woman?
She's butt ugly.
And he'd put in a little bit of lemon.
For the tartness.
And then the last ingredient -
this is the best one - was an egg,
so that he could have breakfast and get
rid of his hangover all in the same time.
Shave that dog and teach it to hunt!
Early lived in the moment.
He did whatever he wanted,
whenever he wanted.
It was that simple.
I don't know if I was fascinated
or frightened by him.
Probably both.
OK. What shall I call you?
I can't call you Lucy. Lucy's gone.
I'll call you Shelly.
Hi, Shelly. I know you're thirsty.
What? What's goin' on?
- Look.
- What?
Look!
Only thing my ol' man ever gimme
was this goddamn .45.
Japanese, but it's pretty good.
- Go on, shoot it.
- No, I never did this.
- I don't know how to do it.
- Yeah, you can do it.
- I haven't...
- Point and shoot the damn thing.
No, bud, you're jerkin' it.
You're all like this.
You gotta hold it soft -
like your pecker. OK?
Boys'll be boys.
- You know any tricks, Carrie?
- No.
Now hold on. Hold on.
- You wanna learn some?
- No.
OK, loosen up. Loosen your elbow.
Breathe. You gotta breathe, bud.
Hold it.
Shoot.
- Hey, Carrie...
- Good one.
- You look good with a gun, Brian.
- Good one, bud. Super. Good one.
You like that gun? I'm gonna give
it to you. I want you to have it.
- I don't need a gun.
- No, go on. Take it.
I'll get me another one.
You never know out in California - all
them cuckoo-heads. You best hold onto it.
Now, give it another shot,
you mean boy. Go on.
Shoot that damn thing.
That's super.
That's some super shootin'. Look at that.
Lewiston Abattoir Mt. Juliet, Texas
Think we're gonna sit this one out, bud,
if that's to your satisfication.
Fine.
You need some help, bud, just holler.
I'll be there.
Shit.
- What is that?
- A copy of the tape they found.
He recorded everything.
Mister, can you help me?
His mother had him workin' in here
before he was eight years old.
Killing animals with a sledgehammer
that was bigger than he was.
Look. Can you get me
out of here, please?
Look. I don't know who you are.
I don't know what you want with me, but
please, just let me go, OK?
When she was pissed at him...
What are you doing?
..she'd beat the shit out of him,
then lock him in here overnight.
My parents, they have money. I can
give you money if that's what you want.
- Please! Please let me go.
- One morning,
the little boy wakes up,
picks up his sledgehammer...
- What are you gonna do with those?
- ..starts hurting back.
How does he get from...
- What are you doing?
- I'm finished.
- I know you're upset about the gun.
- I am not upset about the gun!
Yeah, I'm upset about the gun,
but that is not it. It's...
God, can we please turn this off!
Goddammit, what is going on here?
A week ago you would never
have picked up that gun. Never!
And this afternoon you're wielding it
like you're Clyde fucking Barrow.
What is going on with you?
Please talk to me.
It was stupid. It was a cheap thrill.
I admit it, it was stupid.
It was just bang bang, like kids.
OK?
But I need you to take these photos.
We need them. I don't wanna blow it.
Oh, the pictures. The book. God, that
really is all that matters to you, isn't it?
That really is all you care about, isn't it?
God, I cannot believe I agreed to do this.
That is such crap.
You know you wanted to take these
photos just as much as I wanted you to.
Wrong.
Wrong. I was willing to do whatever
it took to get you off of your ass
and us on our way to California,
and there's a big difference.
- Early...
- What?
- Jesus Christ.
- Sorry.
I want him out of our car.
- Why? What happened?
- I want him out of our car.
- What happened?
- Next gas station it's either him or me.
..and forced 7 0 people
to evacuate their homes
was originally thought
to have been arson.
Can I get a carton of Victory Kings
and $20 worth of gas in the car. Thanks.
Here's your change.
Looks like a bad one's coming in.
Y'all better be careful.
Where you headed?
California.
California. I hear it never rains out there.
Must be nice.
Hi, Carrie. I have to go to the bathroom.
..fatal stabbing and robbery
of Joseph Davies Robbins
at this east Texas gas station.
He is armed and dangerous.
If you see this man, please notif...
..with a history of arrests, is still at large.
Grayce is 25 years old, 5'1 1'',
with long brown hair.
He has a tattoo on his left arm. He was
last seen in east Texas at a gas station...
I ain't ridin' no bus, bitch.
He is believed to be responsible for
the murder of his landlord, John Diebold.
The murder occurred last Tuesday.
We would like to repeat:
- A nationwide manhunt is on for Grayce.
- Siddown!
I knew that boy would
have a hog leg here somewhere.
Not a word.
Hello. Get over here, skinny.
Sit your ass in that corner.
Come on!
- Honey, what are you doing?
- They gave us the boot, momma.
Keep Brian busy.
I don't want him comin' in.
- You're scaring...
- Not now. Git!
Hi.
I'm just gettin' my things
and then I'm gonna leave, Brian.
- What's your name, boy?
- Walter Livesy.
Well, I think I gotta kill you, Walter.
How you feel about that?
Not so good.
- Are you sure you have to?
- Don't know. Wish I did.
- Early, please be...
- Shut up!
Goddammit! I'm trying to have
a conversation with Walter.
Sorry about that, Walter.
Hey, don't forget your yo-yo.
Adele, you leaving has nothing to do with
you guys. It's between Carrie and me.
Where you from?
- Vernon. Florida.
- Don't know it. Any huntin'?
Turkeys sometimes.
Yeah, turkeys are real smart.
Smarter than most people think.
Tell you what, Walter.
I want you down on your belly.
Get on your belly.
I want you to stay there
for a long time after we leave.
- We got a deal, son?
- Yeah. Yes, sir.
OK.
You mind if I hold onto
that Bible over there?
What do you want with a Bible, Walter?
He thinks I'm gonna kill him.
- Now that'd make me a liar, wouldn't it?
- No, sir.
No?
There you go, Walter.
I wonder if Adele might want it.
- What was that?
- Oh, my God.
Nothin', Brian. Just the thunder.
- Hey, Early! What the fuck are you doing?
- You're gonna like this one, Brian.
Get in there. Get over there.
Adele, you're drivin'.
- What are you doin'?
- Come on. Let's go.
- You all right? What happened?
- Get us out of here, momma.
- What happened?
- He shot him in the head. He shot him.
No, he didn't.
Everybody just shut up.
Goddamn squawkin' hen.
Nothin's changed.
I'm gonna get you there,
safe, to California,
if Adele don't kill us with her drivin' first!
What'd you get us?
I got Chinese food.
What is it?
The guy, he didn't speak too good
English, Early, so I just got what they had.
Smells like butt. Did you get the beer?
What is it, Chink beer?
Goddammit, Adele.
Well... give this one to whatshername.
Come over here, bud. Get you some grub.
What the hell's a Chinaman doin' in the
middle of an American desert anyhow?
Adele, where are the forks and spoons?
Is it just me, or has this trip gone downhill
since we ran out of Lucky Lager?
Wish I had me some chilli beans.
How many people have you killed, Early?
Well, now, how many people
you seen me kill, Bri?
- None.
- That's how many I killed.
- If you say so.
- Damn right I do.
Shut up! Eat your food.
You ain't never killed no one,
have you, Bri?
- No.
- No. Ain't seen nobody killed, have you?
- No, I haven't.
- No.
Tell me somethin'.
How you gonna write a book
about somethin'
you don't know nothin' about?
Momma, sing us a song or... somethin'.
# I
# Wish
# Carrie was happy
# I
# Wish
# She would smile
You guys want your picture taken?
Come on, Carrie, smile.
He was breathin'
when I walked out of there.
See, Carrie, it's OK. He was breathin'.
Ain't we gettin' near
the next murder site, Bri?
- Forget it. It doesn't matter any more.
- Hell if it don't.
Gimme that map.
Someday, me and Adele,
we'll be walkin' along,
see your book in some store window.
We're gonna buy it and put it on our
coffee table, ain't that right, momma?
Davidson Mine Dew Cove, Nevada
OK, let's go have us a look, people.
- Early, I'm just gonna stay here.
- You don't wanna go, momma?
No?
All right, you watch Carrie.
I'll take the pictures, Bri.
You run and Bri gets it. Karma.
Lead the way, bud.
So what happened here?
Two brothers, prospectors,
lived here in the '70s.
Yeah, so?
They picked up hitchhikers,
young men, and brought 'em back here.
Hey, Bri. This ain't gonna
give me nightmares, now, is it?
Wait. Get out of the way.
This one's called ''Walk the Dog''.
My favourite one is ''Rock the Cradle''.
They were asked just before they
were executed why they did it.
And they said ''To be famous.”
Why did you do it, Early?
Do what, Bri?
You didn't have to kill
the gas station attendant.
Move a little to the left.
You wanted to. Why?
Help me out, Early. You're right.
I don't know shit about killing.
You gotta tell me.
Does it make you feel good?
Powerful?
Superior?
What? Who are you angry with?
Your mother? Your father?
You wanna know
about my daddy? Do you?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah. I'll tell ya about my daddy.
Adele, you gotta help us out of here.
You gotta talk to Early because he's sick.
- He needs some sort of help...
- Carrie, you're messin' up my trick.
Adele, listen to me, please.
Adele! The police are after him.
He killed a man back there.
No, Carrie, that ain't true.
I saw him kill a man!
Adele, come on. I'm your friend.
Why would I lie about this?
Why the hell would I lie about this?
I know you know!
- Why are you saying these things?
- Why would I lie?
He said he didn't do it,
and you ain't my friend!
You're on private property, ladies.
I'd like to see some identification.
No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Carrie.
Please don't say anything.
- We got a match. I'll call for backup.
- Please, please don't say anything.
All right, ladies, I'd like both of you
to step slowly away from the car.
Brian!
Early!
Confirm your location, over.
No, Early...
Got 'em both on the dead run.
Come on, momma.
Tell me that don't hurt.
- Here.
- What?
Gotta put that crippled dog
out of his misery.
You wanna know about it,
you gotta do it, son.
Shoot him. Come on, lay it on in there.
Come on, mean boy.
Come on, mean boy. Do it!
Shoot him! Shoot the dog.
Time to live, boy. Shoot him.
Come on. Go! Go, mean boy.
- You faggot.
- Look at his face. It's not your father.
- Look at him!
- I know that, you idiot.
That's police in a world of hurtin'.
This here's a mercy killin'.
Let's hit the road.
You've not even said thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for what, Adele?
I don't know, Early.
Well, Adele, it's for saving
your fuckin' life back there!
Goddamn! You were this close
from spending the night in the county...
- You murdering son of a bitch.
- Stop it, Carrie.
- Are you fucking insane?
- Shut up!
- He's a monster!
- Shut up, Carrie!
Goddamn! Bunch of loons.
Look, momma. There's a pretty house.
Maybe they got some beer.
Look at all the cactuses.
They're beautiful.
You know what makes
cactuses so strong?
You could just leave 'em and forget
about 'em forever and they'd still live.
They keep growin' and...
We gotta do somethin'
before Early kills somebody else.
- And they breathe.
- Adele! Will you listen to me?
You can't do nothin', Brian. Just sit still.
You have beautiful cactuses, ma'am.
I just love them.
My momma had a garden.
And I had this little baby cactus.
- I was gonna take it and plant it...
- You gotta talk to Adele.
She looks up to you. She'll listen to you.
I tried talking to her at the mine.
It didn't work.
- Try again.
- Hey, Bri. Did you ever stop...
Stop and think if you switched
two letters in your name,
it'd spell ''brain''?
Boy, you got a problem.
Goddammit.
What's wrong with Grandma?
Where's your husband?
I'm a widow.
Yeah?
That you, Peaches?
Sweetheart, hey. Come on over here.
It's so clear you can't believe it.
It's just amazing.
Come on over and look.
Take a look, honey.
I want you to see this, Peaches.
Guess what, Early?
Miss Musgrave,
she has this guesthouse in the back
and it's really beautiful.
And it's empty, hon. She said
if me and you wanted to, honey...
Hank!
Well... you're a widow now, Peaches.
Boring.
Dogshit.
That don't leave much
to the imagination, now, does it?
Boring.
I know him. That's my daddy.
Fucker.
Boring.
You're not gonna die.
That's you, ain't it?
Yeah, that's me. Do you like it?
What do you think?
Dogshit.
You can go now.
Call me.
You ought to control your woman, boy.
Stinking. Stinking.
Lucky for you
they take all kinds in California.
That's where we'll be tomorrow.
California.
Don't be stupid.
Goddammit!
Peaches!
Stop! Stop it, Early.
Stop it.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna get the piano up.
Try and slide your hands under.
Momma? What are you...?
What are you cryin' for?
I'm the one who got hit.
Cos I decided, Early,
I'm not gonna climb up
that Hollywood sign with you.
- And why not?
- You're mean, Early.
- No, I'm not.
- You hurt those people, Early.
I don't wanna do it with you.
I loved you, Early.
You just be quiet. You are mean.
Run. Go!
No, I'm not leaving you here. Wait.
Go!
- Adele!
- Shut up!
Looks like I need me a new woman.
- No! Not him.
- Shut up.
Jesus! No!
Oh, God, Early, I'll do anything.
I'll go with you. Please.
Please don't kill him.
Oh, God, I'll do anything.
Please don't kill him!
Oh, momma, we gotta find us a door.
Save us some time.
Goddamn, that's a super dress.
Yeah, that's just super.
Shit.
Oh. I didn't think he left anyone alive.
- Where's Carrie?
- They took off down the road.
Watch your head.
Grab that chair.
I'm gonna lift the piano. Slide it under.
He pulled out all the phone lines.
The nearest one is 21 miles away.
- He took the fire road west.
- Take your car and get to that phone.
Call the police.
Well, how y'all doin'?
I'm Early. This is my woman, Carrie.
Sorry to inconvenience y'all like this,
but looks like we'll be stayin' the night.
Don't you move!
You Pinocchio-lookin' knuckleheads.
No!
Dreamland Nuclear Test Range
California-Nevada Border
Door. Who would it be?
Carrie!
Motherfucker!
Bri came back.
Hey, Bri.
You wanna ask me some questions?
Ask me some questions. Come on.
Do I feel powerful? Do I feel superior? No.
No.
I feel good.
Bri, you're bleedin'.
Bri. You're bleedin'!
# Cos I'm as free as a bird
Skynyrd, man!
Lynyrd Skynyrd. I like that one.
The keys.
They're around his neck.
I'll never know why
Early Grayce became a killer.
I don't know why any of them do.
When I looked into his eyes,
I felt nothing.
Nothing.
That day I learned that any one of us
is capable of taking another human life.
But I also learned that there is
a difference between us and them.
It's in feeling remorse.
Dealing with guilt.
And confronting your conscience.
Early never did.
June 22nd. The Novak farm.
Mr. Baxter slammed the door in my face
today, calling me a goddamn ghoul.
I'm bettin' he's still alive.
Real old, livin' in a trailer park
or somethin', somewheres.
But he's alive, see.
Now, he's thinkin' about what he done,
goin' over it and over it and over it
in his head, every night,
thinkin' how smart he is
for gettin' away with it.
Thinkin'.
Hey, how's it goin'?
Not bad. How was your swim?
- It's freezing.
- It's November.
I know.
There's this gallery in Venice,
and I showed them my work,
the icon series.
- I think they're interested.
- That's great.
Well, it's not definite, but it's encouraging.
Well, let's celebrate. I'll take you to lunch.
OK.
- So what happens next?
- Well, I have a meeting at the gallery,
and they want to see
some more of my work. So...
I'm sure they're gonna love it
as much as I do.
Hi!
Guess who this is?
It's me, it's Adele.
I know I'm probably not supposed
to be talkin' on the tape recorder, but...
I just wanted to say thank you
for takin' me and Early
with you on your trip,
cos me and Early's
havin' a really good time.
I just hope that
when we get to California,
that you guys don't forget all about us.
Cos friends are important and...
Well, you're the only friends we got.
Bye.
# If I believed that destiny
# Changes to fate
# I'd believe for ever
# Was a lonely place to play
# I can see inside your eyes
# A mirror soul cannot tell lies
# I believe that I believe
# Miracles and destiny
# You make your own reality
# I know
# When I
# Look up to the sky
# There's angels in the clouds
# And that you can see their eyes
# See the stars lookin' down
# I feel like the thought of you
# Leaves me with
# Nothin' to hide
# Cos when I'm there next to you
# Naked with my pride
# I can see inside your eyes
# A mirror soul cannot tell lies
# I believe
# That I believe
# Miracles and destiny
# You make your own reality
# And I know
# When I
# Look up to the sky
# There's angels in the clouds
# And that you can see their eyes
# See the stars lookin' down
# Lookin' down
# Lookin' down, down
Visiontext Subtitles: Julie Clayton
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org