Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
They actually
pay you forthis...
...to tag beaver?
Imagine.
Was that,
like, sarcastic?
'Cause I know what you
Fish and Game guys think...
...of county sheriffs.
We know you like to
give these one-word...
...sarcastic answers.
Gee.
You ask me...
...whatan animal
does in the wild...
...is his own business.
So long as he
doesn't do itto man.
I think Mark Twain
said that.
Yeah, I think he didn't.
...butsince you said it,
I guess we're covered.
Everyone's a comedian,
sarcastic.
I'm sleepin'?
And right in the middle
of a good dream?
And all atonce
I wake up?
From something that keeps
knocking atmy brain?
Before I go insane?
I hold my pillow
to my head?...
Aah! Aah!
So whatam I
so afraid of?
I'm afraid
that I'm notsure of...
Help!
I think I love you?
Isn't that what life
is made of?
Though it worries?...
Aah ha!
Ohh! Ohh!
No! Aah!
Aah!
Ohh! Don't let go!
Oh ho ho!
Aah!
Aw,Jesus Christ.
Kelly?
Hey, Kevin.
Hi.
Listen, uh, could I
stealyou for a minute?
What are you doing?
Heavy breathing,
meditating.
Meditating?
Yes. To relieve stress.
Remember, Myra,
you're the one...
...who taughtme
all about breathing.
Yes, butyou're doing Lamaze.
are you giving birth?
If you're upset,
long, deep breaths.
Kevin dumped me.
I know.
He told you?
Well, I sort of had, uh,
inside information.
You?
Itstarted before you,
Kelly.
I neverwould have-
You?
Itwas justa quick thing
thatwe thoughtwas over...
...and... it's notover.
You and Kevin.
I- I wish I could
say something to...
...the heartwants
whatthe heartwants.
Sheriff Keough?
Yeah.
Fish and Game.
Jack Wells.
Any recent
bear attacks?
This was no bear.
Bears don'tattack
people underwater.
Probably a beaver,then.
Ah, a whole sentence
sarcastic.
Thatthe way
he came outofthe water?
Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, Kevin,what's going on?
What's happening?
How's it goin'?
How's yourfamily? Good?
It's great.
So nice to see you.
Fuck off.
This is business.
There was an accident
in Maine.
Some guy got killed
by something in a lake.
Probably a bear,
butthey found a tooth.
Atooth?
Afragmentof a tooth...
...one they say couldn't
have come from any bear.
Evidently it looks prehistoric,
like maybe a dinosaur.
Oh,well,then I'm sure
thatthat's what itwas.
He was killed
by a dinosaur.
Is there anything else?
I, uh,wantyou
to go there.
What?
It's probably nothing,
butyou're a paleontologist.
This is whatwe do.
What do you mean,
this is whatwe do?
I'd like you to
check outthis tooth.
I'm nota field person.
Well, on this one,
I would like you to be.
You wantme to go to Maine
to look ata tooth?
Oh,this was Myra's
idea,wasn't it?
- Uh-
- Oh, of course.
Getme outofthe office
for a few days...
...waittill I cool off...
It has nothing
to do with that.
I don't do field work,
and even if I did, Maine?
I'm allergic to timber.
- Kelly.
- I am not going to Maine.
I'm not going
to Maine.
It's ridiculous.
It's gonna be rough...
...as we go over
these mountains.
Yeah,that's fine.
Thank you.
We're doing
the bestwe can.
Could you not
talk to me?
Thank you.
Keough:
Justcame up screaming.
Kelly:What did he say?
Just kind of gurgled.
He was pretty much dead.
You didn'tsee anything?
The lake was calm
until up he came.
The tooth is in here.
Oh,that's-
that's the morgue.
Yes.
Well, is the dead guy
in there?
That's where they
keep them.
Look...
...you wantme to bring
the tooth out here?
No.
No. Let's...
Afteryou.
This is reptilian.
And this is nota fossil.
You really pulled this
outofthis guy?
Yes, I did.
I'll need to get
a microscopic look at it.
There you go.
Great.
Maybe I should see-
I wouldn't.
I can deal with
dead men-bodies.
Ohh.
Uhh. Ohh,jeez.
How long did this attack
go on for?
Seconds.
8 maybe 10.
Oh, and, uh,this is how
he came up to the boat?
Yes.
Uh-huh.
I'd like
to see this lake.
Keough: Nobody lives
within 25 miles of it...
...exceptsome old couple
who live righton the lake.
Teenagers trek in
every once in a while...
...to skinny-dip.
None have disappeared.
None have spotted
anything unusual.
Did you talk
to the old couple?
Notyet.
What kind of backup
do we have?
We?
What?
I'm a little unclear
as to why the museum...
...would send
somebody here.
You gota thing
againstmuseums?
No, I got nothing
againstmuseums.
Ever been in one?
What is that?
Lightweightforward-area
air-device unit.
Whatever's outthere...
...one shotwith this,
it's dead.
Why exactly
would you have that?
God.
Mosquitoes. I gota thing
aboutmosquitoes.
If you're all set,
let's go.
We're saved.
Amuseum in New York...
...just sent us some
additional backup.
Kelly Scott.
Jack Wells.
Hi.
Uh, some museum
sentyou, huh?
What, are we all
museum bigots in Maine?
She's rude sarcastic.
You two should
get along.
I'm afraid I can't letyou
go with us, ma'am.
Sheriff Keough
said I could.
Unfortunately, Fish and Game
supersedes the sheriff.
Why do you have to supersede?
Maybe I might be of-
Ma'am, look...
...this isn'tsome kind of
fact-finding expedition.
Yes, I knowthat.
It's nota science trip.
Could you be
a little more condescending?
'Cause I'm not real great
with subtlety.
Something in that lake
killed somebody, right?
I appreciate
you're trying to help.
I'm really glad that you
brought the raid.
Now,that's better.
Ma'am,
it's not gonna work-
If you call me "ma'am"
one more time, I'll sue you...
...and with today's laws,
it's possible.
She's good.
Look, I won't interfere.
And if I do,you've got
a sheriff handy to arrestme...
...but I understand if I threaten
your Fish and Game authority-
Excuse me.
Is ittrue
you're going to look...
...for some kind of monster
in Black Lake?
Well,we're just gonna
investigate an accident.
There's no monster.
We heard a man
was bit in half.
Well,
there was an accident.
That's all. It's
nothing to worry about.
Oh, please.
All right. Let's go.
Well, my husband
passed away.
It's been
almost 2 years now.
My department doesn't
have any record ofthat...
Mrs. Bickerman.
Well, I'm sorry.
Incomplete records
hauntme so.
Whatwas the cause
of your husband's death...
...ma'am, do you know?
We don't mean
to invade your privacy...
...but was he ill?
Was he sick?
Was he swallowed?
Sheriff!.
Uh, Mrs. Bickerman,
the reason we're here.
Aman was fatally
attacked yesterday...
...by some animal
in this lake.
Do you know
howyour husband died?
Oh,yes.
I killed him.
You killed him?
Oh,yes.
Wells: Uh...
...and how would you have
accomplished this, ma'am?
Well...
He was very sick...
...and-and he refused
to go to a doctor.
He'd be coherent one day
and incoherent the next.
And,well,
one coherent day...
...he asked me to end
his suffering.
And, um...
...he kept insisting
and insisting...
...and then,well,
finally Ijust gave in...
...and I hit him on the head
with a skillet...
...then buried him
out at the bulkhead.
Well, dig him up
if you don't believe me...
Sherlock.
Keough: Half mile up
there's a clearing.
What's with the water?
It's so black.
There's no waves
or anything.
Well,theywanted to
call it "Lake Placid,"
...butsomebody said
that name was taken.
It's too bad.
Tents were sent
ahead.
They should
already be set up...
...by the time
we getthere.
Tents?
We're staying
in tents?
I told you, 2 days
we'd have to camp.
Yes, camp...
...but I thought that meant
"Ramada Inn. "
I never heard tents.
Will there be toilets?
Maybe we should
justtake you back.
Why, because
I prefer a toilet?
Oh, God.
We forgot to pack
feminine napkins.
Oh, so you're
with him now?
Taking his side.
I didn't
say a word.
Oh, no, maybe I should
just wipe myself...
...with some leafy little piece
of poison oak.
And then I could
spend the whole day...
...scratching my ass,
blending in with the natives.
Then you'd be back
on my side.
You know,you really
don't have to bother...
...telling people
you're from New York.
What the hell
is that?
What?
There. I thought
I saw something.
Kelly:
Looks like a branch.
Oh, my God.
Aah!
Hey.
You threw it at me!
Ijust let go of it.
Did you see that?
Oh!
Ma'am!
Stop hitting me.
Don't throw heads
at me!
Stop calling me
"ma'am!"
Aw,Jesus.
Oh, God.
So, sheriff...
...howm any deputies you got?
What?
Could it be a bear?
I mean,the bears
get big here, right?
Hmm. I don't think a bear
could bite off a moose's head.
Everything you need
should be in there.
Ok. Good. Good.
So will we be
tent-mates then?
Nope.
This is all yours.
Ohh. Great.
Excellent.
If there's anything else
you need...
Uh, one thing
I wanted to ask you.
Uh,what's it like
to be a woman...
...in the woods of Maine?
I mean,the guys don't turn
all horny or anything...
...like they did in
Deliverance, right?
Oh.
I knew you were there.
Hmm.
Never been to Maine
before, huh?
I have good hygiene.
I'm not welcome.
Why are you here,
really?
I told you.
A museum doesn't send an
investigator into the woods-
How would you know...
...what a museum would
or would not do exactly?
Well, even if they did...
I doubtwhether he or she
would have problems with tents.
So I don't like tents.
Why-
Oh,you don't like tents,
and you don't like mosquitoes.
Well, nobody likes
mosquit-
Look at
your finger nails.
What's wrong
with my finger nails?
You have as much business
being in the woods...
...as Emily Post.
No, it doesn't make sense.
They sent you out here
to examine a tooth.
And what are you doing
out here on the lake?
Oh, no.
What?
Ifthis is
who I think it is...
It is.
Who?
Hector Cyr.
He's this rich, kook
mythology professor.
You know him?
He's done some work
with our museum.
He also treks the world to s...
What?
To swim with crocodiles.
Crocodiles?
If he's here...
...he must think
you've gotone.
Oh, look...
I admit I'm no
brain scientist...
...but I do know there's
no way a crocodile...
...can be in Maine, right?
You beat me!
Balls!
Splendid lake, eh?
Became a man
on a lake like this.
Rubber raft.
Sylvia Blake.
She gave a like a cow.
Who do we have
from Fish and Game?
Me.
Who is this man?
I can see the algae blooms
justcoming in.
Look almost stagnant.
Hector Cyr.
Oh,the earth is round
and so should you be.
Who is he?
I need topographic studies.
You got any?
You don't justfly in here
and start barking orders.
I apologize. Ijust don't
wantto lose the light...
...when we gottime
for a quick scout.
Have you had
a little work done?
I have not.
Who are you?
Hector Cyr.
I said itonce.
Letme know
when its inks in, ok?
Have you seen it?
No.
Excuse me.
You came here to...
...help you find it.
A crocodile?
Yeah.
They've been migrating north,
you know?
This lake does connect
to the ocean.
It's not as far fetched
as it may sound.
Crocodiles can't swim
in saltwater.
Yeah,well,that'll be
your little secret.
Come on.
We're losing time.
Why did the big one
heckle me?
Hey, pal...
If he's close,
we'll find him.
Their signatures
are unmistakable.
She tellyou
that we had sex together?
So vigorous!
I never had sex
with you.
Whew. I'm horrible in bed.
They never remember.
God.
Wait.
Stop!
Thought
I heard something.
I don't mean
to be discourteous...
...but, uh, how is it...
...a person could come
to believe...
...a crocodile
is in New England?
How could it
survive winter?
Long as their nostrils
don't freeze...
...they survive.
Am I foolish
to explain things?
He had such trouble
with my name.
- Hector.
- Hey.
Is this
where it happened?
Around here.
Yeah.
We're a mile from the ocean.
Could've easily made it here.
Kelly:Assuming he got
this far up the seaboard.
The big ones
have been on the move.
What have I been telling you?
You call me crazy.
Kelly:
Hector,just paddle.
You know, Sheriff...
...when friends or family
say things...
...they tend not to register...
...so sometimes it helps
to hear it...
...from a total stranger.
You're fat.
Jesus. Hector!
Oh,yeah.
Kelly:What's that?
What is it?
White perch.
Are they feeding?
They aren'tfeeding.
They're scared.
- Aah!
Wells:Jesus!
Cyr: Oh!
Oh!
Get your legs
out of the water.
Don't move
your legs.
Keough:
Are you kidding me?
Cyr:
Keep your legs still.
Get off!.
Hector,
to the left.
Move it left!
Paddle, paddle!
No one actually saw
anything.
Yes, I realize that, sir...
...but something
flipped us over...
...and I doubt very much
if it was a mink.
I am a paleontologist.
I work for
a natural history museum.
I am notsome-
They don't believe her.
Thank you.
It's so rewarding to
imagine my tax dollar...
...finding its way to you,
you fuck-shit!
You're a saucy flirt.
You were right.
U.S.Wildlife
won'tsend anybody...
...without
a confirmation.
We don't need 'em.
Sheriff.
Yeah?
Might wanna come
take a look atthis.
Oh, my God.
Worms.
Oh, I gota thing
about worms.
It's a human toe.
Some decomposition,
a little acidic-
...definitely
been swallowed.
Is this the man
who was killed?
He seemed taller.
Phew.
You gota croc,
all right.
They're
a keystone species.
Did he just
explain something?
Keystone species effects
the whole ecosystem.
That would explain
these worms...
...and those perch.
We gota crocodile.
Here's yourfriend.
TomJones:
It's not unusual?
To be loved by anyone?
To have fun with anyone?
But when I see you
hangin' around?
With anyone?
It's not unusual?...
He paid us.
500.
It's a trap.
You accepted money
from him?
We took a check.
When I see you
outand about?
Law enforcement
is very dangerous work...
...isn't it?
And you have such
big,wonderful boobs.
Ha ha. Thank you.
It's not unusual?
It happens every day?
Hey!
- Hey! -
Hey! - Hey!
You're on
official business.
This is not a party.
Yeah, but now
that you're here...
Whoo!
Yeah!
Quiet!
What's with digging
the holes?
Well, crocodiles are-
...are very brazen.
They like to come on land...
...and of course
they're attracted to noise.
Everybody out!
Back to your tents!
Now!
Oh, could she stay?
We were...
...we were hoping to mate.
No.
Out.
Now,you listen...
If it were up to me,
you'd be on your way home.
But I'm not in charge.
That's a shockerthere.
I'm going to say this...
...because I believe in being
straightwith people.
I think you are a mental.
Sheriff...
I appreciate your candor.
Really, I do.
I think it's always good
to know...
...where somebody's
coming from...
...and,frankly...
...your origins have been
a bitof a mystery to me.
Look howflat
thatwater is.
You could get 10 skips
on a good one, easy.
Sorry?
Skipping stones.
Growing up...
I used to summer
atmy grandparents' place...
...on a lake like this.
I'd skip stones all day.
Beat playing
with the other kids.
I'm sure it did.
Look, I think it's best...
...if you stayed onshore
a while.
I beg your pardon?
I'm not trying
to pick a fight...
...but what ever's out there
did flip a canoe.
I am not
staying onshore.
It's dangerous.
No, I didn't fly up here
just to roast marshmallows.
Why did you fly up here?
Look...
...paleontologists are not
sentto Maine...
...to huntfor crocodiles.
I was sent up here
to look atthe tooth.
You looked atthe tooth.
What are you doing
out here?
I was dating my boss...
...and he turned out to be
involved with a coworker...
...who was also my friend.
And for the sake
of comfort-theirs-
I was shipped off
to Maine.
And I don't feel
like going back yet.
I'm not making it up.
Still,you don't
have to stay out here.
I mean,
you can stay in town.
I've come. I'm here.
I'm staying...
...unless there are ticks.
I know crocodiles.
And I won't
get in yourway.
Ijust really do want
to be a part ofthis.
7:00 A.M.?
Thank you.
Good night.
Jesus fucking Christ!
Ohh. Whatthe hell
are you doing?
Whatthe hell
Oh,Jesus.
You clowning around?
I'm laying
a spring trap!
Aspring trap?
I keep telling you
they can come on land.
I could've shotyou.
This could end up
saving your life...
...which is meaningful
for you...
...because the more
you live...
...the more sex you getto
have with your sister!
What's going on?
He's crawling around
like a cockroach here.
I don'tcare
how much money-
He's waving
his little wang around!
He's scaring the shit
outof me!
How big is this?
All right, all right!
I'll say this once.
Your fancy equipment
aside...
...which we appreciate-
...if you interfere,
you're gone.
Simple as that.
How much of a wacko
is this guy?
Well...
...the thing about Hector...
...is he takes this
crocodile business very...
Oh, man.
He thinks they're godly.
Whatwas that?
In his defense...
...every primitive culture
known to man deified them.
Ancient China, Egypt,
Australia,Asia.
Going back in history...
...crocodiles have been
more worshipped than Jesus.
Is this supposed
to make us...
...take him
more seriously?
No, it's supposed to make you
understand him.
He's a mythology professor.
He believes
thatthey're divine conduits.
And he can find them...
...so we should try
to put up with him.
He's a fruitcake.
We should get
some sleep.
Yeah.
Aah!
Damn it!
And he's a good trapper.
We can expect
a quick response...
...if he hears that.
Adult crocs will move
on distressed hatchlings.
Again, I don'tmean
to be annoying...
...with my questions...
...but if
it is a crocodile...
...which I don'tthink
it is...
...and they do charge these
baby hatchling sounds...
...why would you want to be
underwater at the time?
With you,
it makes sense.
You see, Sheriff,
the thing is...
...they don't really
attack underwater.
ThatWalt guy
got hit underwater.
True. They don'tsee
that well underwater.
They have nictitating
lenses on their eyes...
Burke, stop here.
- Now?
- Yeah.
...You dive underwater...
...and they probably won't
be able to see you.
Wells: I hate to interrupt
but we got work to do.
Hey,we can talk if we want.
Yeah,we can talk
if we want.
Would you mind putting down
the anchor?
Wait till
we're down there...
...before you turn
that thing on.
Got it.
Let's go, Hector.
Good luck.
I brought a pork chop
for luck.
Maybe you can hang it
around you neck.
That's sweet.
Maybe later you can
chew the bark...
...off my big,fat log.
Was that, like,
a homosexual remark?
Don'task me.
Could be a mental.
I heard if a mental person
is rich enough...
...they justcall him
eccentric.
He's notmental.
He's seen every crocodile
in the world.
He even swam in the Grametti
with killer Niles.
He never got nipped.
And that's why he thinks
they're godly-
'Cause they don't
bite him?
I don't know.
He said he knew it when
he looked in their eyes.
"Eyes of a Dragon. "
So much for crocodiles.
It's probably on land.
Yeah, right.
What was that?
I don't know.
Aah!
Shit.
Hey! Something's got
the anchor line!
Untie it!
Untie the line!
I'm trying!
Keough: Hurry!
Cutthe line!
Right!
Keough: Shit!
...come on.
What happened?
I don't know.
Hurry. Hurry up.
Must've just let go.
Come on.
Shit! Hurry!
Hank!
Ok!
Oh!
Hurry!
Hurry.
My God,
it's right underyou!
Aah! Oh, Christ.
Come on,
get in the boat.
You all right?
Yeah.
Where's Hector?
I losttrack.
We went different
directions.
There's some bubbles
overthere.
Pull it up.
All right. Come on.
Bring him aboard.
Hector:What's happened?
Come on.
You see it?
How big is it?
Shut up
and geton board.
We losttrack of it.
Burke, pull up the speaker!
Are you all right?
- Grab him!
- Aah!
Pull him in!
Aah! Aah!
That it?
Yeah.
Nobody actually saw it.
It happened suddenly.
Didn't get caught
in the out board?
It wasn't the outboard.
Tell them
to get here fast, huh?
You ok?
Kelly?
Yeah.
Nobody saw anything.
No.
U.S Wildlife's
on theirway.
The police wantto keep
everything quiet...
...so the press doesn't
getwind of anything.
Everybody just wants us
to...
"Sit tight. "
Are you... Ok?
Well...
...you know...
Yeah.
Well, Sheriff,
I'm, uh...
Very sorry
about your deputy.
He was a good man?
Yep.
Whenever somebody dies,
I...
I always think
that it's such a waste...
...that I didn't know them
any better.
Sorry for your loss,
Hector.
Not really what I meant.
Head was just...
...bitten off.
You know, I used to have
a recurring nightmare...
...that I was headless.
I'd be down
on the ground...
...looking up atmy body,
no head...
...just walking around
bumping into everything.
And my parents...
...wouldn't letme
in the house.
Because they just bought
all these antique lamps...
...and they didn't wantme
to knock them over...
...the fuckers.
Then the neighborhood
bullies...
...they'd see my round
head on the ground...
...looking like a ball...
...and they'd come over...
...and they'd start
a soccer game.
And as I was being
kicked around...
I'd actually
just feel grateful...
...for being allowed
in the game.
What are-
what are your thoughts?
You know, Hector...
I'm sure
you're a fine person...
...in your own mental way...
...but I think it would be best...
...if you and I didn't speak.
Yaaah!
When is U.S.Wildlife
getting here?
I'm still waiting
to confirm if they...
Oh,Jesus.
I- I could probably
cut him down...
...but there's this
odd look of mayhem...
...on his
upside-down face.
Hank.
Yes?
Are you all right?
Could you cut me down?
Do you promise...
...that you won't attempt
to injure me?
I have no interest in ever
looking at you, Hector.
Ok.
Just, uh, pull him down.
It's a counter weight.
Here. I'll get the knife.
If I'd remembered
it was there...
I never would've let
you walk that way.
All right. It's over.
It's over. Remember?
You promised
not to hurt him, so...
I lied.
Wait. Hey! Hey!
Come on! Hold up!
Now here to go,
my friend.
Now,just-come on!
Knock itoff!.
Knock itoff.
Put that down.
Just settle...
Jesus! Look out!
Whoa!
Aw, shit!
Ok.
I admit it.
It's a crocodile.
Kelly: He's an Indo-Pacific.
Scales were oval.
He's an Asian crocodile.
Why would he come here?
It's impossible.
Asia.
How would he get here?
Obviously some
asshole in Hong Kong...
...flushed him
down the toilet.
He was 30 feet, right?
Had to be.
Well, nowmaybe somebody's
happy I broughtmy big gun.
Oh you're gonna
blow him away now?
I should think so.
With your cannon?
Right.
What, I shouldn't?
Well, he's a miracle
of nature...
...but I know
he's very scary.
You're the miracle
of nature.
Guys, guys, easy.
We're not gonna do
anything tonight.
I never heard of a crocodile
crossing an ocean.
Well,they conceal
information...
...like that in books.
All right, pal!
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no.
Let him go.
I'm sick
of him,too.
I do need to warn
you, Sheriff.
The thing
about being rich...
...my parents did have
the added luxury...
...of ditching me off
at karate school...
...on a regular basis,
so I am a brown belt.
Go ahead.
Take your bestshot.
Ohh!
Hank!
He said he knew karate.
You hit him.
I did,yeah.
Here.
Did he say "go"?
Aren't you supposed
to say "go" in karate?
You're supposed
to say "go. "
Hank,just keep your
distance from him.
Go to your tent.
Cool down.
He doesn't answer
my questions?
Why don't you
answer my questions?
I fall into a hole.
I go up in a tree.
I swearto God,
I'll say "go. "
You bow,
and then you say "go. "
As in
"go fuck yourself. "
Jesus. They're just
like children.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I've got something
for that.
I can fix that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Ohh!
Ijust gotta pull it
a little tighter.
There we go.
Who taughtyou
to be a nurse?
Father's a surgeon.
I can even stitch
in a pinch...
...which probablywouldn't
be such a bad idea.
Uh, no,thanks.
Ok.
You should have seen
the look on your face...
...when that croc jumped out.
Uh-huh.
You see the look
on the bear?
That was the look.
I don't know.
The laws of nature
could be changing,Jack.
That thing out there,
that's-
You're having the best time
of your life, aren't you?
What?
What? People
have been killed.
I hardly think I'm
having a good time.
Why would you-
Does it show?
This is the first time
I've ever actually...
...you know, been in
the middle of anything.
Is that why you're here...
...to get in the middle
of something?
Maybe.
I've always read
about what's happened.
I've never...
We should go to bed.
I mean we should
go to, uh...
...rest.
We should go to our
separate tents...
...and-here-
get some-go.
I got it.
Thanks for the bandage.
Night.
Yeah.
Cyr: It doesn't even see him.
There, he got it.
He has one
natural enemy.
Only one.
Man?
Man.
So you're
the big expert.
You think ours is some
kind of mutantor-
Not necessarily.
There's a 30-footer in India.
Biggestone ever killed
on record was 27 feet.
So why is he here?
Honestly...
I don't know.
Keep your eyes peeled.
You know how fast
these things can be.
I've got ticks,
I know it.
They're just
so drawn to me.
I got a thing
about ticks.
Crawling
up your pant leg.
Put their heads
under your skin.
Look.
What?
Jack.
That's a pretty big print.
Gare: Seems like
we're getting lower.
That's what happens
when I land.
Why are we landing?
Because this is the cove
that he obviously lives in.
So why are we landing?
Hector!
We can lift it?
Maybe.
Don't want
to mush it there.
I'm not mushing it.
You might mush it.
It's a little soft.
For Christ's sake,
I'm not mushing it!
Aah!
Oh, God.
Ok.
That is it!
No, no, I keep
getting hit with heads!
Try to calm down.
You calm down!
Calm down, ok?
Just keep breathing.
I'm being very calm!
I am composed!
This is the second time...
I've been hit
with a severed head...
...and it upsets me!
What the hell?
Aah!
I...
I just want to go back
to my tent now.
Can we please go back?
You gotta be kidding.
I'm not kidding!
Look.
The itsy-bitsy spider?
Crawled up the water spout?
Down comes the rain?
To wash the spider out?
Kelly:What is she doing?
Dum de dum de dum?
Kelly: Oh.
Keough:What?
Look 10 feet into the water.
Come and get it!
Wow.
Disgusting.
I haven't broken any laws.
Oh, but you have,
ma'am.
You lied to us.
That can be
obstruction of justice.
A man has been killed...
...in part because
of your silence.
I could make out
a charge...
...of reckless
endangerment.
And I'm sure PETA
would be annoyed...
...at how you treat
your cows.
The reason I lied,
if I told you the truth...
...you'd hunt it down
and kill it...
...which seems to be exactly
what you're trying to do.
How long have you
been feeding this thing?
6 years.
6 years?
Well, Bernie
was outfishing...
...and it followed
him home.
So we threw it
some scraps...
...and,well, he didn't
seem to bother anybody.
He became kind of like a pet
who lives in the wild.
He just appeared?
You have no idea
how he arrived here?
No. Do you?
Your husband Bernie...
...you didn't,
by any chance...
...lead him to the lake
blind folded?
If I had a dick...
...this is where I'd
tell you to suck it.
Did the crocodile
kill your husband?
Yes, but itwas all...
...itwas a mistake.
A mistake?
One of our horses
got loose 2 years ago.
Went to the lake
to drink...
...and the crocodile
started coming in...
...and Bernie went
to intercede, and-
...if I'd reported it...
...they'd have sent people
to kill it.
Ma'am, how could you
not report this?
It puts human life
at risk.
Nobody lives on this lake.
It's really his lake now.
Come on, Hector.
I know you're crazy...
...but you can't do this.
I need to see his habitat
up close, Deputy Gare.
...then watch Nova, ok?
But don't go
in the water.
Please.
I'll have sex
with you.
Let's just
getoutof here.
Darling...
...he's not gonna hurt me.
Don't.
Hector!
Murders and rapes
in the cities.
People bomb planes.
Can the police stop them?
No.
Butfeed one little cow
to a crocodile-
You stay right here
until the police show.
You're under
full house arrest.
Thank you...
Officer Fuckmeat.
Gare on radio: Sheriff,
we gota problem with Hector.
What problem?
He went swimming.
Check.
Oh, my.
Suddenly I feel
a bit foolish here.
You're different
from the others.
Holy Spiritof Sobek.
Holy Ghost.
Holy shit.
Hector!
Just turn the ignition.
It's fuel injected.
Come on!
I know that under
the circumstances...
...biting my head off...
...might seem viable.
Itwould cheapen you.
I may geta shot!
No!
Bullets might not
penetrate its hide.
Oh,Jesus. All right,
justa little further.
Just like that.
Move over!
Go!
- Go!
- I'm trying!
Ahh! Jesus!
That's your last little
stunt, Mr. Crocodile.
You're grounded.
This is some very
delicate equipment...
...thatyou're
throwing around.
I don't care.
You trying to kill yourself?
You want to meet
your maker, is that it?
You might think
they're godly...
...you might get
some spiritual lift...
...outof back stroking
with dragons...
...butyou just put a deputy
at risk out there, sir.
Let's not over look the fact
that he didn't eatme.
'Cause he justate
a cow, stupid.
I'm a civilian.
I'm not a trout.
You have no authority
overme what so ever.
overme whatsoever.
Hey, hey,
I can arrestyou.
Well,then do it.
You hurt his feelings.
I don't care.
Do you care?
No. He's an asshole.
Did you want
to be killed by it?
You think I'm that nuts?
Hector.
What you just did...
...there had to be at leastsome
sort of a death wish going on.
In ancient Melanesia...
...people suspected
of crimes...
...would be thrown
to the crocodiles.
Crocodiles would decide.
They would be the judge.
Oh, and so that was you
wanting to be judged out there?
Maybe I was,
and so what?
Is that too arbitrary?
Better to be measured
by my wealth?
Betterforme
to getmy self-esteem...
...looking in the eyes
of cheap sycophants...
...craving a meal ticket?
There was more honesty
in those dragon's eyes.
There was more dignity
Jesus, Hector,
cutthe shit.
Aw,fuck it.
So, can I tell them you won't
go back in the water?
Oh,yeah, sure.
I'm not going
back in the water.
No way I'm going
Ok.
Kelly.
We can't let'em kill it.
Wells:Yeah,
pull all the trucks in...
...and start packing.
Everything?
Yeah.
All right.
Just heard from Wildlife
and Florida Fish and Game.
They're gonna be here
in 3 hours.
Ok.
So we might as well pack up.
Good idea.
Will they
try to trap him?
Sorry?
Florida Fish and Game.
What'll they do
when they get here?
Cyr:Tell her,Jack.
Won't be able to snag him
in pitments, right?
And you tranq him
in the water...
...and he drowns.
They could try
to tranq him on land.
Oh, sure,they could,
but they won't.
He's taken human life.
The mission will be
to put him down.
Is that true?
They've never been able
to trap anything 30 feet.
But they have
to try, right?
Where are they gonna
take him, Florida?
Back to Asia?
I got enough flaxidyl
with me to put him out-
Forget it.
Jack, hearme out.
I know I'm a fat,
rich, nut fuck,wacko...
...who's about as grounded
as a street pigeon...
Keep going.
Butthis thing...
Here?
Maine?
30 feet?
Don'tyou think
we're dealing...
...with a bit
of a miracle?
Yeah. The miracle would be
to take him alive.
Yeah, but if we could
neutralize him-
How are we gonna
neutralize him?
Lure him on land
and pump him full of drugs.
Oh, right.
I know of an empty
oil tank in Portland.
Ifwe drugged him,we
could contain him there.
He's 150 years old.
He probably swam here
from another continent.
He's migrated to Maine.
How the hell do we say
we just kill it?
Jack,
this thing being here...
...does have some
ecological significance.
And you are
in the business...
...of protecting things
against extinction.
Including deputies.
I understand that...
...but if it's possible
to take him alive-
No, it's not possible.
Look, he follows anything
thatmoves, right?
We set a trap on the beach.
I got enough net-
No. There's no net
that's gonna hold him.
It'll keep him
tangled long enough...
...forthe drugs
to kick in.
For God's sake,Jack...
...they've trapped crocs
bigger than 20 feet.
This is not completely
out of the question.
It's possible,
and you know that.
And those fucks from
Florida won't even try...
...and you know that,too.
I gotthe drugs.
He's gota big cannon...
...if anything goes wrong.
How do you get him
to the net?
Ask Mrs. Bickerman
to call him?
You guys can be
in the trucks...
...with the tranq guns.
If he charges,
you take off.
He's not that fast.
We just have to try.
One try.
Just one try.
Like Hank says...
...how would we lure him in?
I'll sue you!
Go ahead.
You can'ttake a cow
by eminent domain!
We just did!
We won't let her
get hurt, ma'am.
You're all cocksuckers!
I knew atfirst.
I just didn't want to say it.
We know
what we're doing.
We gota cow hanging
from a helicopter.
Not much drag.
As long as I can keep her
from swinging,we're ok.
We're doing
the rightthing.
You might feel different
if you get eaten.
Yeah,thanks.
Tranq gun with every rifle.
That's as far back
as it goes, right?
Hector, keep enough
tension to hold her up.
We don't know
how well she can swim.
Right.
I hate to say it.
The more she thrashes,
the better.
Cyr:You ready
on shore?
Wells:Yeah,
we're all right. We're ready.
Woman: Ok.
If she gets tired,
pull her out.
Jack:
What's she doing now?
She's trying to fly.
This is nota happy cow.
I'm rooting
for the crocodile.
I hope he swallows
your friends whole.
You might want to arrest
me for that,too.
Is that a crime-
To wish the chewing
of law enforcement?
I'm notsure, ma'am.
Man:You got'em?
Second Man:
Yeah, over here.
Little battery!
What's the deal?
Well,we tried.
Justa little
longer, please.
She doesn'tseem
to be swimming.
No, she's floating.
She looks like
a giant tea bag.
Ok, Hector.
Good plan, bad bait.
Game's up.
The cow disappoints me.
Hold on.
I got something
on the screen.
What do you got?
He's coming.
Where?
How far out?
30 meters or so.
He's moving slow,
but he's definitely coming.
Can you confirm visually
or just radar?
Radar.
He's underwater...
...but he is coming!
All right, everybody
back in the trucks!
Move, move, move!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Lead him in.
On ourway.
Remember to aim
for the stomach and the sides!
These darts
won't pierce his back!
He's surfacing.
There's his snout.
Gare:
There he is!
We've spotted him, Hector.
You little snacker.
If he gets near her,
pull up.
She's worried
about the cow now.
Nice and slow, Hector.
This net thing better work.
He got you with it.
We're in about 4 feet
of water now.
She's mooing.
Wells:
You wouldn't?
She's also kicking.
A little closer, Hector.
Oh, shit.
Watch out!
Mother fucker!
Shit!
Where is he?
We gotta getto him.
Back us up.
Lose the tranq guns.
go to the rifles.
Man: Get the rifles!
Where'd he go?
Hold up.
Don't go back
into the water.
If you geta safe shot,
take it.
Do not move, Hector!
Can you see anything
from out there?
Nothing!
Maybe he swam back out!
Jesus!
Hector!
Hey!
Get back
in the truck!
I got him covered.
Where is he?
I don't know.
He's gone under.
Ijust have this feeling
everything's totally safe.
There!
He's swimming out!
I think I see him!
I think I see his tail!
Shit! Kelly!
Aah!
Wells: Kelly!
Kelly, swim, swim to me!
Swim to me, Kelly!
Shoot the fucking thing!
I don't have
a clean shot.
Dive under!
Go under!
Fuck.
"Let's save him. "
What a fucking
great idea.
Come on.
Cyr: Here.
Here we go.
Where is he?
I don't know.
We can't see him.
What-What?
Hector!
All right.
Game over.
Look.
He's suffering.
I getto be humane.
No, no!
No, no, no, look,
he's trapped!
We've done it!
So what? It's not a net,
but he's trapped.
Mission accomplished.
Wells: Shoot him.
I got more drugs.
He's half dead.
He's half alive.
Shoot him!
The drugs are kicking in.
Look at him.
He's done.
Hank.
All right, stand back.
No, no, no, Sheriff!.
Look.
Look, look.
He's got nothing left.
Wells: Go ahead.
Shoot him.
Really?
- Jack,we don't-
- Kelly.
We don't have to destroy him!
God damn it, look at him!
Letme have that.
Kelly:
He's been neutralized.
Cyr: Come on,Jack,
he's trapped!
Look at him!
He can'tmove!
What's the point?
We don't have to do this.
Jack,you don't have to.
Please!
Oh, God!
He's gotme!
Jesus!
Jesus Christ!
Are there 2?
I think there's 2.
I can see that.
He bitme!
There's 2,there's 2!
I can count.
Cyr: No!
Back to one.
Go ahead.
Flax him.
Oh, here they are.
Just in time.
Nice to see you.
We're gonna need
to get this reptile...
...some medical attention.
We, uh...
...trapped him
with our chopper.
Portland?
Yes, Portland.
They'll tank him there
until we figure out...
...something better to do.
So, Sheriff, Sheriff...
...you got to fire
your big gun finally.
Was it fun?
Over rated.
What'd Bickerman say?
Well, she didn't
want to tell us...
...about the second croc...
'cause she was afraid
we'd blow its head off.
Women's intuition.
We got room
for one more.
Someone should
probably go with him.
...uh...
I'm still packing
up some stuff...
...but, uh...
I'll go.
So, I imagine
you're gonna have...
...a few reports to do.
If you need anything,
letme know.
Yeah. It was nice meeting you.
Gee, Hank,
don't get all choked up.
With you,
I'm still mixed.
Oh,well,then,just to
offend you on principle,then.
See you.
Well...
You wanta ride
in my truck?
Oh,we just finished...
...loading up the front
of the truck.
Do you want us to
take some stuff out?
No, no,that's all right.
I'm gonna be
a little while anyway.
I want to go say
good-bye to the lake.
You sure, because
I don'tmind-
No. I actually want
to stay a little longer.
All right.
If I'm ever
in New York, I'll...
Yeah.
So, does nobody ever
make a move in Maine?
That's it?
You slide your duffel bag?
Just...
...get in the truck.
Go for a beer.
There's a good bar
in town.
Bet that's charming.
Are the glasses clean?
Mostly.
You gonna complain
the whole time?
Jack.
Start the truck.
I already miss
the crocodile.
Bob Marley:
I wanna love ya?
And treat you right?
Cute little buttons.
Oh, ho ho.
Oh, mama loves you.
Come on.
Eat your supper.
Nibble mommy's toes.
Yes.
Roof rightover our heads?
We'll share the shelter?
Of my single bed?
We'll share the same room?
Yeah?
Jah provide the bread?
Is this love, is this love?
Is this love
that I'm feeling?
Is this love, is this love?
Is this love,
is this love?
That I'm feeling?
Oh,yes, I know,yes, I know?
Yes, I know now?
I?
Am willing and able?
So I?
Throw my cards on your table?
See, I wanna love ya?
I wanna love and treat ya?
Love and treat ya right?
I wanna love ya?
Every day and every night?
We'll be together?
With a roof
right over our heads?
We'll share the shelter?
Of my single bed?
We'll share the same room?
Yeah?
Jah provides the bread?
We'll share the shelter?
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org