Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
They've found another one.
There's going to be not a treasure left
by the time she gets here.
Mark the location.
That's the French mast.
And over there, crystals.
They're all coming.
All except one.
All right, follow Crystals.
When he dives, we dive.
Maybe we'll get luck and
find what it is down there.
Hey. Look at that, Jimmy, look.
Why isn't she slowing down?
You ask her.
- No way.
Hello, boys. You're wet.
Half the world's trade is already here.
And you make us wait.
But you know I can't resist to be defied.
Lara, tell us, what's all this fuss about it?
What does everyone think is down there?
I don't know what everybody
thinks is down there, but.
I think it's the Luna Temp.
The Luna Temp?
My sons, if it is not on television, forget it.
It's a temple built by Alexander the Great.
who was Greek, in case you don't know.
- Yeah, yeah.
Alexander collected treasures
from all over the world.
He stored them in two places.
The majority went to his library in Egypt.
But his most priced possessions,
went here,
the Luna Temple.
By law, no one was allowed
to record its location.
And in 330 B.C., it was...
...swallowed by the sea...
...destroyed, during a volcanic eruption,
lost forever,
until yesterday.
Even half the temple is intact,
it would still be the greatest find
since the pyramids.
The others heading to this area here
along the shore...
That's based on the currents.
- Yes.
Oh. This is it goes, it's why I was late. -Oh.
It's geological.
Take him two hours after the quake.
The epic enter was here,
five miles northeast of us.
But, look at the current along the shore now.
Wait, they've shifted.
So, while they're all diving there,
the wind will actually be...
Here.
Let's go.
Something wrong?
First Alexander doesn't
report the temple's location.
Then God washed it from the earth
with a volcano.
Now even the currents changed.
Lara, maybe this temple
is not meant to be found.
Everything lost is meant to be found.
Don't worry.
Incredible.
It's unbelievable.
God.
It's huge.
Wonderful.
Jimmy, this is wonderful...
Do you see what I see?
- Oh my god.
Oh my god.
- It's incredible.
Nicky, look at these.
We're going to be rich.
Hey, Lara.
What do you say to two
handsome Greek partners?
When you find two, let me know.
Heard? She's talking about you. -No, you.
Luckily gold coins...give me that...
Lara, what is that?
It's mine.
What is she doing?
Lara. That column is collapsing.
After shows.
I think that's the sign leave.
Two minutes.
Lara, we need to leave now.
We've got to go.
Keep packing. -Do you think
it's going to collapse?
You take those two.
We have to hurry up.
We're going to go,
we're going to go now. Come on.
They're coming up.
Lara.
Lara, it's us, Hillary and Bryce.
She's disorientated, that's
normal after three days.
Nice day for a dip?
Gentlemen, there is an expression,
'It's not nice to fool Mother Nature.'
Yet that is precisely what
I've been doing for some time now.
Whether it will be sorren gas for Mr. Zap...
...improved typhoid for Mr.
Croft to use in the Balkans...
...enhanced cholera for Mr. Devalia.
But, while these weapons
served their purpose,
there have always been limitations.
Stable diseases aren't lethal.
deadly ones burn out too quickly.
Mother Nature can only be fooled so much.
Deploy my weapon, and your
enemies, however great,
will collapse...
...rather Mr. Monza is collapsing right now.
What the hell is going on?
Monza told MI6 about this meeting.
That's why the change of location.
He was going to turn me over to them...
...and then seek asylum in the West.
A smart man would have known
I was onto him.
would never have got on the plane...
...but I knew you would, Mr. Monze...
...because you actually
thought you could fool me.
That, gentlemen,
is the sound of a traitor dying.
That was an accelerated form of Ebola,
the deadliest disease known to man...
...highly contagious.
However, as with all known diseases...
...there exist stockpiles
of anti serums in the West.
There is no anti-serum for
what I'm offering you...
...no treatment...
...no vaccine, no cure.
The modern world has never seen
anything like what I've uncovered.
Uncovered?
Yes, I branched that.
Archaeology.
07744681, that is the account at the
landesbank in Bern.
$100 million dollars each, if you please.
[Hong Kong Chai Wan Private Airport].
Where's Chen Lo?
He's got the orb, but MI6 is onto him.
How?
He doesn't he know,
but rather than risk bringing it to you,
he's waiting.
I have just told a cabin full of men
about Pandora.
the clock cannot be reset.
Tell Chen Lo to bring the orb to me at once.
Find the killers,
don't take it on to me.
Bryce, what have we got?
I haven't even finished loading
the images from your camera yet.
We've got references to an orb.
I took the liberty of checking.
Historic inventories of the Luna Temple
do not list any orb.
I want you both to list...
...every orb ever
mentioned in Greek history.
Ah.
That's... liable...to be...
...thousands.
Then we'll read thousands.
Start with that one.
Perhaps you gentlemen would like
some tea while you're waiting?
No, they wouldn't.
Tea is for guests.
The door is for intruders.
Lara, these men are from MI6.
Yes, I can tell from their
soft hands and pressed suits.
that these are the men
who made decisions...
...and leave the dirty work for others.
I have no interest in...
His name is Chen Lo...
...along with his brother Xien,
he runs a gang of Chinese bandits
known as Shay Ling.
They deal in gun, diamonds
and antiquities, anything that.
Chen Lo can sell them in the black market.
They've followed you the moment
you arrived at Santralina.
where they killed your friend Gus
and sank his boat.
Why?
For this.
After you were picked up in sea...
...our listening post in
Mota intercepted that fax...
...it was sent from Chen Lo to a
man named Jonathan Reiss.
What, a scientist?
won a Nobel Prize.
He is now the foremost designer of
biological weapons in the world.
His creation has been in the heart of...
...every active bio-terror
in the past 15 years.
Reiss's disdain for life is legendary.
He has no political agenda.
He doesn't care who his
weapons kill or why.
A modern-day Dr. Mengelen.
We know Chen Lo followed you
in order to obtain the orb.
we also know he'll deliver it to Reiss.
What we don't know is why.
Candidly, that terrifies us.
Pandora's box.
Reiss is going to use the orb
to find Pandora's Box.
Do you mean the Greek myth?
Pandora was given a box by God,
told not to open it, she does...
...and unleashes pain into the world.
That's the Sunday school version, yes.
How do you think life began?
Shooting stars, primordial ooze.
In 2200 B.C.. an Egyptian Pharaoh...
...found a place he named
the Cradle of Life...
...where, we, life, began...
...and there he found a box...
...the box which brought life to earth.
The Pharaoh opened the box...
...but all that was left inside
was Ramante, or empty life,...
...the plague which came
as the companion to life.
Companion?
Nature is about balance.
All the world comes and passes.
yin and yang, right and
wrong, men and women,
what's a pleasure with pain?
What did this plague do?
It leveled the Pharaoh's army.
The Pharaohs's son dispatched...
...the finest soldiers to take the box,
and transport it to the end of the world.
2000 years later, Alexander
the Great reached India...
...where his army was ravaged by a plague.
After one of his men found a box
among some of the men.
India, that's what the
Pharaoh's men wrote it.
Alexander felt that...
...the box was too powerful to be trusted to
any man...
...so he returned it to its home
the Cradle of Life.
And it has not been seen since.
And this Cradle of Life is where?
No one knows.
Alexander found it using a map
that was with the box.
a map he then hid from the world.
But the name he gave this map...
...was Mati and the literal translation for
the word Mati is 'eye'.
it orbits the map...
...hidden in the Luna Temple by Alexander.
And Reiss will use it to find Pandora's Box.
And when he does he opens it.
The markings definitely
form a pattern, but...
...even if I figure out what they represent...
...we still can't read the whole map...
...because we're going to get past
the view of these, see?
We have to figure out how to read it.
Right, thank you.
On behalf of her Majesty,
we firmly request...
...that you find and recover
this box before Dr. Reiss.
Oh. Now that I have her
Majesty's permission.
Tell me where to find the orb.
The last we heard, it
was somewhere in China...
...with Chen Lo and Sha Ling...
...finding them would be
next to impossible...
...we'll assign two of
our best agents to help.
I don't want them.
With due respect, your expertise
is archaeology, doesn't...
I didn't say that I don't need help.
But your agents would never
get me to Chen Lo in time.
I need an insider
someone who knows the Shei Ling...
...their methods, their hideouts.
I need Terry Sheridan.
Not in a million year...
...not if you're the last man on earth.
Terry Sheridan, former
commander of the Royal Marine...
...turned a mercenary, and a traitor.
You don't honestly expect
me to put that man...
...on a trail to hold weapons...
...you can turn around and
sell to the highest bidder?
[Kazahkstan, Barla Kala Prison].
Open.
I'm your host, Armika.
Welcome to Fantasy Island.
Croft.
Hello, Terry.
So what do you think of my new place?
Not quite Croft manner.
What, a key to your heart?
To a flat in Zurich.
You can pick another city if you want.
Your record will be expound,
your citizenship restored.
Why?
MI6.
Now would that make me Faust,
or the Devil?
Well, you can pick one.
because MI6 would also
arrange a new identity.
Oh yeah, do you think I need their help?
Oh, having two faces doesn't count.
So what do I have to do?
You need to take me to the Shay Ling.
She who?
There's a man named Chen Lo...
...who took something from me and
I want it back.
Yeah. Is that you, or MI6?
Also, I've arranged the government...
...to wire you 5 million in sterling
when we succeed.
you can call it second chance, man.
All right, then insurance for you?
I don't need any.
You and I working alone?
And it's easier to see through you, that way.
So what if afterwards.
MI6 decide that me back in the world
isn't such a great idea?
Then I'll feel sorry for whomever
they get to come after you.
Do you have authorization to kill me, Croft?
Any time, for any reason.
So why don't you just do it now?
What is it they see?
Hell have no fury.
You're not that good.
Shay Ling and the groove's Croft.
They move constantly.
And they're in almost the most
remote mountain region in China.
Region?
You have to do better than that.
Get me into China, and I'll
get you to them in a day.
No guns, no money, no
weapons of any kind.
Talk about taking the fun out of life.
Shay Ling has spies all over China.
We have to get into country undetected...
...so we'll slip into
Beijing, and we go by truck.
Truck?
I wasn't thinking about
something a little faster.
A little faster?
Well, this is a little faster.
But the Chinese will track the pod.
There won't be any pod to find.
Will there be any of us to fight?
Ready? now.
- Ready for what?
The ditching was good, Croft.
I'll give you that.
But we'll never find a vehicle
in a place like this.
...ni hao...
...ni hao.
It's lovely to see you.
So is everything ready?
Yes. Your clothes, guns,
and knives, are over there.
And I took the liberty of tuning your bike.
May I?
- Yes.
Lara.
Ah, what is the happy couple up to?
Accessorizing.
- Where are we on reading the orb?
All maps have a key, Lara,
scale or legend, yes?
The orb's key is not on orbit,
it must have been lost.
or somewhere in the temple.
Go through every image I took...
...start with the ones near the orb.
key must have been linked
to it in some way.
Right, well then...
It's unlike Lara to take a partner.
Where are you two going?
We're taking a nice little trip.
breathe some fresh mountain air...
...stop by my friends the Shay Ling.
Shay Ling watch all the roads.
We have to go around the back.
We'll go straight.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
Shay Ling have men on every road
from here to Luo Yang.
Not every road.
Getting rusty, are we?
Oh, I think it's coming back.
I expected more from a Scot.
I don't expect anything
from an English woman.
Good, cause you're not
going to get anything.
Party's over.
From now on it's by foot.
Best to reconsider that "no gun" rule.
No.
And don't be looking at my ass.
So where do I fit in?
What do you mean?
You'll the guide.
I mean...when you think back...
...on the vast scheme of
hugely adventurous life...
...where do I fit in?
Is that a love of your life?
Or just another bump on the road?
Was that time well spent?
Four months, more good than bad?
Come on I had to be more
than that, am I right?
All right.
It was five months.
You're laughing at me?
No, no. It's the fact that I
used to find you charming.
I am charming.
You're late.
Tilt your head back. Do it!
You might see again in a hour. Maybe.
What's this?
It's not there.
There's no orb.
Is it anything you can tell me about this?
Hello.
I think it you don't like your messenger.
I didn't, but I did like
the men I lost in a temple.
You underestimated Lady Croft.
I underestimated how
much this orb is worth.
So many horrible diseases in the world...
...things we are particularly
susceptible to as children.
You never know when you could be holding
little Shiho or Tai by the hand,
as a mysterious ailment
ravages their bodies.
You kill them,
and I'll give your orb to Lady Croft.
My men tell me, she's a
few miles away from here...
...as we speak.
I wonder how much she would pay.
I'll pay you an additional $12 million dollars.
It will be yours once you've delivered the orb...
...along with Lady Croft's body.
I don't think you know where they are.
You're impossible you know that.
I think you pretended to know
so I would get you out.
This isn't a tomb Croft,
and the Shay Ling aren't mummies.
They're killers.
But if you don't trust me.
I'm sorry I have to do this
but you're wasting time.
You want to shoot me, shoot me.
Personally, I'd rather you do it than them.
bu xu dong (Stay right there. ).
Well, Terry, what part of
'never come back again'
didn't you understand?
You wanted to fight the Shay Ling.
The only way to get into their place
is as their prisoners.
You want to tell me that in jail before.
Would you have believed me?
Make Chen Lo a better
offer than his buyer.
He'll cross them.
Even if his buyer is Jonathan Reiss?
You might've told me that before!
Were you really going to kill me?
Oh, I bet she would have.
I've seen her in action.
Didn't Terry tell you?
The last time any of us saw him,
he was riding away with a truck...
...full of my Ming vases...
...and sitting next to him, was his sister.
Oh, how is she?
You...
...shouldn't come here.
They got me out of prison...
...Besides, the lady has a good offer...
...better than Reiss.
Really?
Should I take it?
Take it.
Or better yet,
you and I run some horrendous thing
back to the British for triple.
Let's talk.
Not you, Terry.
Lady Croft and I.
You wait here.
Catch up.
There will be four minute.
Terrific.
There's something I think
you will have appreciated.
This is the largest group of
terracotta warriors I have found.
The king of Qin made them...
...for use in the afterlife...
...to fend off enemies he made in this one.
Sounds like we could both use a set.
I would be happy to sell some to you.
I hope you're as
entrepreneurial with the Orb.
You lost men, I lost men.
I see no reason we should both lose again.
If I want double, would Reiss offer it to me?
Is it here?
It's worth a lot.
Well then, if you know that,
you'll know Reiss will also kill you
the moment you give it to him.
And your government would
guarantee my safety?
No.
But I will.
That must hurt, saying that to me.
Take the offer.
You presume to give me orders?
Take the offer before it expires.
No.
Then I would have to force you.
Then I would have to kill you.
Has it been four minutes yet?
That was nice.
It's too bad, you're on the wrong side.
Tell me where the orb is,
and it spares your life.
The Flower Pagoda in Shanghai, 9 PM.
This is mine.
Now, we're even.
Freeze. Put your hands up.
Remember that no gun
rule? I reconsidered.
Lara, there was a staircase
we could have used.
Lara, are you all right?
Smashing. I'm on my way to Shanghai.
And I need you to look at something for me.
It's in the Luna Temple near the orb.
And I'm betting it's key to those markings.
She's holding some sort
of musical instrument.
It's sound.
That's brilliant.
Key must have linked into it some way.
I'll start decoding the images we have.
Good.
- You give us the rest, bye, Lara.
Miss you.
- Bye.
[Shanghai].
Flower Pagoda, 8:50 pm.
Trouble is coming, let's go.
well.
Just like old times.
I think that's the first time you've
actually smiled because of me.
Why did you do it?
I started thinking.
I was...tired of doing things
for somebody else's way...
...and it was always going
to be somebody else's way.
So you abandoned your men and
betrayed your country.
Leaving my men and my country...
...that didn't actually
hurt as much as I thought.
But leaving you did.
You're a hard act to follow, Croft.
You know why you and I
get along so well?
No.
We are two of a kind, me and you.
We are nothing alike.
I don't think we're alike.
- Um hm.
But do you think we're a pair?
Opposite sides of the same coin.
My men have the roof covered.
Why don't you set down
at the square instead.
That way, my men would
also have things covered.
Okay, fine.
Okay, so, let's go.
We're arriving at the square.
We're in the wrong position.
Stairs? -No time.
Rooftops?
- No.
I've got a plan.
Stay here, wait for my signal.
Here's your money, come and get it.
Wait for my signal, pal.
Give me that box.
You give me the money first.
Get out of here.
Go, run her over.
Yeah.
- We tried it your way,
now we'll do it mine.
- Bring it to the top of the pagoda now!
Okay.
Come on, come on. Hold it up.
Now we're going to your brother.
We're too late.
Lara, what are you doing?
Take us up.
Move. Go.
Let's go, move.
I'm getting tired of you
pointing that thing at me.
Are you okay?
- Never better.
It looks like we've lost the orb.
Please! You don't think I'd go
vaulting in the thin air for nothing, do you?
I've put a tracer on the crate.
Got it.
Look.
Impressive.
[Hong Kong].
A weapons lab
in the middle of the city? No way.
He must have dumped that in the Cradle.
No, it's here.
One of the buildings?
No.
It's exactly where we're standing.
There's part of me that always
allowed for the possibility...
...that Pandora's Box was just a legend.
But now I know it's there.
She escaped.
She has no idea where we are.
We take no chances.
Have everything we need...
...to manufacture an antidote
transferred to the jet.
I need an orb for two people.
Mid-city, soon.
What? Are you crazy?
Who is that?
Piece of cake.
Wang Jie, come in.
Hello.
So much for easy.
What is that?
He's already decoding the orb.
Bugger!
Headset.
You've gotta get everyone out.
How would you suggest, the fire alarm?
Not bad. But that's just the alarm.
There's no danger.
Do you think anyone here
is paid enough to take that chance?
Don't even think about it.
It's her.
Yes.
I'm glad, Lara.
It would have been too easy.
Give me your best!
How's that?
I'm going offline.
Oh, don't...
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Hello boys, did you
understand the medallion?
Yeah, yeah, the markings are sound waves.
We've translating the
markings from your images...
...roughly half the orb.
Well let's complete the set, then.
I'll record the rest of the images
and send them to you.
Once you have them,
finish the translation...
...and transmit the sounds back to me.
We need more backup.
Smart girl.
Get down.
Move.
Don't shoot her.
Not until I make sure the
computer has done its job.
Do you honestly believe...
...you'll be able to
control what's in that box?
And turn that into one of your weapons?
Really, Lara. You disappoint me.
Have we received payment
from all the buyers?
You're the one who controls the orb.
You're using the buyers.
They'll release it thinking
it's just another weapon.
And the world blames them.
What's left of the world blames them.
Once I get hold of the buyers.
I'll make enough antidote...
...to protect the best and the brightest.
Heads of corporations.
Heads of states...
...life will go on.
Don't tell me you've looked
around never thought...
...wouldn't the world be a better place
without some of these people?
Well, you can say anything to one person
I can deal with that.
You would have been
welcome in my world.
Piss off.
Shoot her between the eyes,
no mistakes.
Asshole.
I'm going to get you.
Follow me.
all right.
Don't worry.
Bingo! Two one-way tickets
out of Hong Kong.
Parachutes.
Something a little faster.
Come on, Grandma.
The rendezvous point is
2, 2.5, maybe 3 miles.
You're aware that no one had
ever gone further than one mile?
I'm not.
This way.
Right, you go first.
No, you go first.
I'll go first!!
Holy cow!
Follow her.
Bye Terry. did you see?
I suppose you want to
pay him then, don't you?
What do you get, two,
three, hundred dollars?
$300...expenses.
So this...
...rock is the map.
Yes, it is.
I've never seen anything like it,
have you?
And it's the only way to find that box.
And just think you could take it now.
and walk right out the door.
No, when it does better
actually off the ship faster,
harder to track.
Oh, Croft, do you really think
I would do that to you?
You can break my wrist,
but I'm still gonna kiss you.
That's not exactly what I had in mind but..
Okay.
Why didn't you shoot Reiss?
What?
He must have walked right
past you in the lab.
Why didn't you shoot him?
I didn't have a close shot.
And I had no idea where you were.
I'll inform MI6 of the completion
secret service.
You'll have your money and your life.
Don't waste it.
Darling Croft, this is no time to split off.
Yes it is, before you
make the wrong decision.
Okay you want to leave, go ahead.
But don't pretend this to try and save me.
You're afraid,
afraid you might not pull the trigger.
Afraid of letting your guard down,
of letting anyone in.
I'm not leaving because I couldn't kill you.
I'm leaving because I could.
May I borrow your TV?
It's important.
Okay.
Thanks.
Lovely.
the music is not the best...
...save the best for the last.
the funniest thing is the
best day of your life...
...becomes the best day of your life.
Hello, Bryce.
Hello.
Are you ready?
Yeap.
Right.
Sending the last images of the orb, now.
Got them.
Translating.
Done.
Send the sounds.
Sending it...now.
No, nothing.
Oh, well, back to the drawing board.
No. Wait. The time's being distorted.
Send me the file.
Look Lara, I really don't think
that's going to work, you know. It's...
Yes, of course, it will.
You ever heard your voice
on the tape recorder?
Same thing.
Why are we having this discussion?
Send me the file.
Lara.
Africa, it's in Africa.
Somewhere in Kilimanjaro.
Right now.
How long would it take Reiss to
put his computer back together?
24 hours at the fastest.
Get in touch with Kosa.
Ask him to get the car,
meet me North of his village.
at 0800 hours. Bye then.
A bit faster than 24 hours.
Out.
Africa it is.
Kosa.
Lara.
How are you?
Lara?.
You had the jeep cleaned.
Of course.
I know how you like your equipment!
Where are you? I can't see you.
Don't worry I can see you.
Okay, where are you coming from now?
Keep going straight,
keep your speed steady.
Lara, welcome back.
Do you ever do anything the easy way?
And risk disappointing you?
I've lost my friend and
I'm not sure where I can find her.
Nice shirt.
Ni hao.
She went to Africa playing
with the elephants.
Kosa, we've never been here, have we?
We didn't come to this area before, why?
Because I've seen that mountain before.
The box is there somewhere.
The locals call it the Mountain of God.
There's a tribe that makes
a home on it...
...that might help us.
Leave the subject and go.
Never speak of it.
To trespass on the Cradle of Life...
...is to risk flooding the entire world with death.
Men are coming for the box.
Now unlike me, they won't look at it
with fear or respect.
They would open, they want to use it.
I'm sorry if I have to disturb your god
to keep this from happening.
I will do whatever I must.
Do you truly understand
what you're doing?
Are you truly prepare
for what you're about to learn?
Some secrets must remain secrets.
These are very heavy burdens,
very lonely burdens.
that if you find the box...
...you would have to carry them.
He warn you that...
...no one who has gone looking
for the box has come back.
Says the land beyond the canyon
belongs to the Shadow Guardians.
Shadow Guardians?!
They do not sleep.
They never rest.
They move like the wind.
And anything that
walks their land will die.
And the Cradle itself?
Only with the orb can it be revealed.
Inside, you will find a place of madness.
Sky and Earth are one.
Direction, meaningless.
He's going to give us 20 men
to take us as far as they can,
to the Cradle of Life,
where the box is hidden.
We're getting closer.
He said you were right.
The Cradle of Life lies near the summit.
He wants to know how you knew.
The orb.
He says, he would not
turn back with the others.
He would go as far as we go.
We will find the Shadow Guardians.
dunka sana.
You're very brave man.
He said your accent is funny.
Get down.
Chinese. (African).
Back.
Thank you Lara, for leading us here,
and for finding the orb, in the first place.
However, you have seen the exact position.
You could save me hours, days even.
Help me, and I'll make
you worth your while.
No.
Think of what I'm offering you, let her go.
The chance to find out,
how it all began,
life line, the origin what we are...
...don't tell me you're not tempted.
That's like a Pandoran trouble.
They told me you wouldn't do it.
And I told them you would
rather than lose two of your closet friends.
There goes the Cradle of Life.
Sorry, Lara.
It's your destiny to see what's inside.
He's right, it's just beyond
the canyon, remember?
Such a short walk
might save your friends.
Well, if it spares my friends...
I'm up for a walk.
I'm sure she'd understand.
Do you have a plan?
You should've just told Lara
we were hostage.
Reiss would never have found out.
I don't suppose either of you
know how to fly a helicopter?
I can.
What?
I've got over 150 hours between flight
simulation...games,... models...
...and then the real thing?
Two.
Two? well, you're only gonna fly it once I'm out,
so remember your two hours well!
I hope you remember your two hours well.
- It's through here?
- Um.
Move, baby.
What's that?
You. Check it out.
Keep moving.
What are you doing?
Back in formation, now.
Holy shit.
Don't. They seem to react to movement.
They're gone.
I know we're close, I've seen it in your eyes.
Take me to Pandora's Box.
I don't know how.
Do it now.
Well you were the one who
wanted to go for a walk.
So start walking.
The next one will be higher.
only with the orb can it be revealed.
All right, I'll need the orb.
Do you want to see
the Cradle of Life or not?
You tell me what to do with it.
Don't think you could outwit me, Croft.
Oh, do shut up.
So this is the Cradle of Life.
Here they are.
It's all yours.  Time to be a hero.
There it is.
Perfect, isn't it?
All that power in such a banal container.
Legend tells it when Pandora
saw inside the box...
...she cried a pool of a black acid for tears...
...and, as it was a woman
who found the box,...
...I see no reason to break with tradition.
A woman should collect the box.
Go on.
It's impossible to reach.
Now, take it.
Take it.
I don't think so, Reiss.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine, fine.
- There you go.
You've come prepared.
Well, I know how clumsy you are.
How are Hillary and Bryce?
They are fighting.
Thank you.
What was that?
Oh.
Thank you.
Let's get out of here.
Terry.
What are you doing?
Well, you're joking, right?
We're taking this with us,
this is ours.
You're not walking out of here
with that box.
So, what are you saying,
we'll just leave it?
Well, it's worth a fortune.
Put it back.
- No, I don't think so.
It could kill millions of innocent people.
Now you're being romantic.
Put it back.
- No.
I've helped you keep this away from Reiss.
This is my reward.
I'm taking it with me.
So it's come to this, has it?
Well you do have authorization to kill me.
You'd better do it, then.
'Cause if you think standing
in front of me is gonna be enough...
You don't have it in you to stop me.
See, all your beliefs...
...all your ideals,...
They're not real.
I am.
And you've loved me.
I don't know how strong you think you are...
...but you're not going
to choose them over me.
No move?
No.
Thanks.
The box is safe now.
Some things are not meant to be found.
Did you ever do anything the easy way?
I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
Larie, are you okay?
Lara, are you all right?
This is...very touching.
You know us, always making
friends, having a laugh.
getting married.
What?
This is a wedding ceremony,
and you are the grooms.
Good luck, boys.
Sanke, Asante.
Asante, asante.
Go.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org