Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Morning, Paddy.
- Morning, Kate.
Looking lovelier than ever.
If I was only a younger man-
Oh, shut up!
Mum, it's me,
your daughter.
- Post.
- Have a cup of tea with me.
Can't. I'm running late.
Sorry.
- He's at it again.
- Who? At what?
The new neighbor,
barbecuing or something.
I've heard he's from Poland.
Oh, well, you know, maybe Polish people
like to barbecue a lot.
I can't find your-
- Oh, here it is.
- Where do you put this?
It's my toothbrush thingy.
Just stop fiddling.
Prescription.
Now listen, you do not
have to keep taking these.
- The doctor said.
- I like to.
Makes me feel better.
All right, well, listen. I'm off.
I'll, um-
See you later, or call you later.
You got that date thing tonight?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Time and tide, Kate,
as your father liked to say.
Was that from his terrace
in the south of France?
Sorry. That was mean.
Hug me.
Hug me!
Bye, Mum.
I am a cow.
Put my score up first.
- They don't want to hear it, Harvey.
- But I want to see it.
- Put it up.
- I'm backed up already.
Johnnie, you were the one that was late.
Just put it up.
Okay.
Listen, Harvey, Marvin wants me
to present my ideas while you're away.
Huh?
Look, I'm not doing myself any favors here,
Harvey, but I'd watch your back.
Harvey:.
Marvin. Hey, Marvin.
Hey, Harvey.
Shouldn't you be in London?
Yeah. I'm heading there now.
What's going on?
Johnnie said something about
you wanting him to present on Monday?
Oh, yeah. No, no.
I was just thinking that, with you being in
London, you should stay a while.
- What?
- There's no need to rush back.
- Enjoy your daughter's wedding.
- What?
Well, Johnnie can do it.
I mean, he can pitch
the Samuelson account.
No. I'm coming back.
Those are my connections.
- They have been for years.
- I know. I'm just-
They've got new people there,
you know?
I think they might want
something different.
I really want to come back.
I should be there in person.
In person?
Yeah. I want to
stand behind my music.
But nobody cares, Harvey.
They're demos.
They're already pressed.
Nobody gives a shit.
They don't need to see you.
They don't need to see me.
I'm back Monday, Marvin.
I'm coming back.
Well, you better land this one,
Harvey.
- What does that mean?
- It means what it means.
Say it.
There are no more chances,
Harvey.
Enjoy London.
- Are you on a holiday?
- No. Business.
You?
Oh, my daughter's
getting married.
Congratulations.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, kind of.
She's American, he's American, and they're
still getting married in London.
I told her we have a perfectly good
wedding system here.
I mean, they both work in London.
That's why they're-
- There you are, Sir.
- Oh, thanks. Thanks very much.
- Can I just give you this?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Does flying make you nervous?
No.
I do it all the time.
Oh. I don't like it.
I have to fortify myself.
You know that old joke,
one guy says to the other-
Tell you what, I have got meetings
in the morning, when we land...
...so I think I'm gonna try
and get some sleep.
- Sure.
- Sorry, I just-
I'll be useless
if I don't get some sleep.
No, no.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
- Morning, Aggie.
- Morning, darling.
- All right?
- Mm-hmm.
"A filmy layer
on the surface of a liquid. "
Scum.
Scum!
"Manicure tool,"
four and four.
Oh, come on, Aggie.
- What? I'm just testing you.
- Nail file!
Sorry, sorry.
Morning. Morning.
Oh, thank God
you're my boss, Kate.
- Morning, Aggie.
- Morning, darling.
So, we still on for tonight?
- Matt's definitely bringing Simon.
- No, no, no. I'm scared.
Oh, now, don't be scared!
He's gorgeous!
He's a big, strong, confident,
gorgeous fella.
You'll love him.
He's beautiful.
Right. Look, I'll come, but only
if you two swear blind.
...you will not leave me
on my own with him.
Oh, no, no.
Promise. Absolutely.
- Kate:. Can I trust her?
- No.
Of course you can trust me.
We'll drive you home.
We'll drive both of you home,
depending on what home you're going to!
- Oh, shut up.
- Yeah. He's got his own business.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What kind of business?
I don't know exactly.
I think it's stationery.
Oh. I've always loved stationery.
So not a business trip, then.
Man: No. Unless you count
three grandchildren as work.
- Some might.
- That's true.
Thank you very much for your time.
You're all done.
- Thank you.
- Safe trip home.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Excuse me. I wonder if I could trouble you
for two minutes of your time.
- Won't take a second.
- No.
I'm tired, you know?
Yes, I do.
Where to, Sir?
Hi, Susie.
It's your dad.
Uh, I made it, uh, and I'm in a taxi
on the way to the hotel.
Uh, I guess all you guys
are already there.
Anyways, I really look forward
to seeing you and everybody else.
I can't wait. Love you.
Bye-bye.
Hi, it's Harvey Shine here.
Just want to confirm that Mike
is going to be in the mix Monday.
And I'm reachable by my cellphone.
You probably have the number on file, but
just in case...
...it's 917-384-5368.
You may need an international code, so,
you know, I think you have to dial 044...
...or maybe, uh, not sure.
It could be 011.
You can try 44 then 1 and then 917.
Whatever it is, whether it's 044
or 44 or 011...
...after that, you may have to
put a 1 be-
Hello?
Hi.
I'm with the wedding party.
There should be a room for me.
Harvey Shine.
Yes. We have
a double room for you.
Good.
Is everyone else checked in?
I'm not sure, Sir.
My daughter - Susan Shine?
She may already be going by
the name Wright - Susan Wright.
W- R-I-G-H-T.
No, sir.
No one of that name.
Sir, Room 522.
Oh, boy.
Hello?
Hi, Susie.
I'm here. Where are you?
Where is everybody?
Oh. I didn't realize.
I thought the plan was
for everybody to stay together.
No. I just wasn't sure.
I-
No. I just- I didn't know
I was gonna be here by myself.
I thought that-
Anyway, so, your mom,
she rented a house for all of you, huh?
Oh, come on.
I'm a big boy.
I'm happy here.
It's very cozy.
Yes, I have the address.
Yeah. I love you, too.
I'll see you there.
Hello, Mum.
What are you wearing?
- Purple dungarees.
- Oh, you're not.
No, not really. I'm wearing a miniskirt
and a boob tube.
- They're totally back in.
- Oh, you're just being silly.
Now, don't be nervous.
Just be yourself.
Yes, thanks for the advice.
Oh, listen.
I've been thinking about Greece.
Yeah. Okay.
Well, can we talk about that later?
All right. Bye!
Bye.
- Kate.
- Ah.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Don't tell me your mother-
- Yeah.
Is that mine?
Cheers.
Thank God. Oh.
She's, um-
She's just on about some Pole living
next to her who's barbecuing a lot.
- Oh, very suspicious.
- Well, that's what she thinks.
Well, they're here.
- Okay.
- He's at the bar.
Very nice fella.
Very chatty.
- Okay.
- I like him. I like him.
- There's Matt.
- Hey.
Hi, Matt.
- How are you?
- I'm well. How are you?
- I'm good, too.
- Kate, this is Simon.
- How do you do?
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
So you're in stationery?
Um, I'm I.T. - Computing.
- You told me it was stationery.
- Oh!
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did, love.
Well, there's a bit of stationery involved.
Mainly computing, though.
- So not stationery.
- Let's sit down.
It doesn't matter.
Sorry, Matt.
It's just that I-
- Cheers.
Cheers, lads.
Hmm.
Shit.
Yeah, I just-
I just got off the plane last night.
- Hey, Harvey!
- Hey. Scott.
- Harvey, you made it.
- Scott, how are you, man?
Hey, whoa.
What's up?
This is Susan's father- Harvey -
Harvey Shine.
This is Josh Hillman
and my best man- Pete Turner.
- How you guys doing?
- Good. How you doing, Harvey?
- Great.
- Yeah, it's great to see you.
Yeah, you too.
How you holding up?
Great, great.
Can't wait to marry Susie, really.
- Is she here?
- Oh, she's in there.
She'll be thrilled you're here.
- I'll just go and find her.
- Yeah.
Ooh. I got to take this.
Grab that phone.
Hello?
Yeah, it's Harvey.
No no no no,
that's not right.
I need this.
I need Mike.
No. I told him two weeks ago.
I booked him.
What?
No, but I-
Look, just tell him
to call me, okay? It's-
I booked him!
Uh, I'll talk to you later.
I'm sorry.
It's always something.
Sure. Yeah.
So, what's your field, Harvey?
Well, I'm in the music business.
Oh, wow.
Doing what?
You know, TV,
background, commercials.
- Cool. What kind of stuff?
- Commercials.
- Sounds profitable.
- Yeah, it can be.
So, you guys-
you work for Scott?
We work with Scott.
- And what is that, oil?
- Yeah, it's-
Well, that can be profitable.
Has its moments.
Yeah, okay. I think I should
just look for my daughter.
Absolutely. Hey, nice to meet you.
We'll see you in there.
- Talk to you later.
- Yeah, sure.
He's got to be younger than me.
Well, look, he's young.
He'll have plenty of energy.
- He's lovely. Big hands on him.
- You'll just say anything.
No, it's not-
don't answer that phone call.
I've got to answer it.
Kate, it's your mom.
You know it's your mom.
I know.
She's on her own. Come on.
Yeah, and so are you.
She is, like, human contraception, honest
to God.
- She's ruining your sex life.
- Shut up.
You go. You go.
Hello, Mum?
Yeah.
Can I ring you back?
Yeah, 'cause I'm out.
Okay, bye.
Hi.
I'll see you guys.
Hi!
Wow. Let me look.
Let me look.
Whoa.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
- You look-
- Like a bad lounge act.
No, you don't.
You look very, very nice.
No. They told me that everyone
was going to wear white here.
But I was misinformed.
It looks good.
I like it.
Thank you.
- How was your flight?
- Fine.
So, uh, that's your guy?
Yeah.
It's a long way to come to see two
American kids get married.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
No. That's just a bad joke
'cause I'm jet-lagged. I'm sorry.
Have you seen Mom?
- No. Is she here with Brian?
- Yep. They're over by our table.
Oh.
So, is the house your mother rented
for almost everyone nice?
- Dad.
- What?
No. I just got to
get it out of my system.
I'm sorry.
It really is good to see you.
Give me a hug.
- Hey, look who I've got.
- Hi.
Oh, my gosh.
Hello.
We'll talk later.
Go ahead.
Hi. Bye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I'm Matt. This is...
- Sorry. We've got to go.
- No.
Babysitter just rang.
Wee bit of trouble at home
but nothing serious.
- Nothing serious.
- Nothing serious at all.
But you stay.
You stay.
All right.
You enjoy yourself, you miserable cow,
and turn that phone off.
- You working tomorrow?
- Yes, half day.
I can't believe
you give yourself Sundays.
- I'll see you Tuesday.
- Okay.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Looks like we've been set up.
Yes.
Sorry.
No, it's not your fault.
I mean, I'm fine with it.
I mean, I'm happy
to meet new people.
Yes. Yes. Yes. So am I.
Why don't you sit down?
So, you're Oonagh's boss.
Yes.
I'm saying "yes" a lot.
Uh, yeah.
Sorry.
Would you like another drink?
Uh, sure.
I'll get them.
No no no, it's fine.
What would you like?
Can I have a, uh-
can I have a glass of white wine?
- Anything dry.
- Dry.
Thanks.
- Hey, Mel.
- You all right?
- Andy.
- Nice to see you.
Gwen.
Mum, can you stop-
stop-
Hang on.
I can't hear you.
Just hang on a sec.
Hang on.
Man: That's true.
That's exactly what happens nowadays,
you know?
Hi.
Hey.
- Harvey.
- Jean.
- Harvey, good to see you.
- You too.
- You're looking good.
- Hi.
So our little girl's
getting married.
Harvey, you remember the Watsons.
Barry and, of course, Jill.
- Jill: Hi.
- Barry.
Harvey.
Boy, I haven't seen you guys
since Jean and I, uh-
You look well.
Thank you.
You look weller.
- Barry, you too.
- Thanks, Harvey.
It's good to see you.
How's your son?
- Jean: Daughter.
- Jill: Betsy's fine.
Right.
Sorry.
I got to take this.
Can you hold on, please?
Sorry.
It's gonna take two hours max,
no longer.
Have you told him
it was for me?
Look, we have to go back.
He'll tell you.
Just have him call me, okay?
All right.
I really got to go.
Okay, bye.
Hi.
Kate, sorry.
I bumped into these guys.
Couldn't shake them.
Everyone, this is Kate.
- That's okay.
- Andrew, Melissa, and Gwyn.
- Gwen.
- Gwen, sorry.
Sorry. I hope we're not barging in
on you.
Kate: No, no.
Not at all. No.
So, how do you two
know each other?
Um, we don't, actually.
We've got some friends in common-
Oonagh and Matt.
And Matt came.
And Kate works with Oonagh.
- They had to rush home.
- Bumped into each other.
Yes.
- Are you on a blind date?
- Yeah.
No. It's not a blind date.
Shall we just leave you to it?
Shall we leave you?
No no no no no.
I mean-
Jeanie, did you move me,
my sweetheart?
- No, darling.
- Dad, I moved you.
I thought it might be easier
if you needed to get up.
Oh, sure.
Okay.
Shall we have a quick toast
just to get things started?
I'm going to save my big speech
for tomorrow.
Dear Susan and dear Scott...
I just want to take us all back.
...to that wonderful holiday
that we had in Rome together.
...and wish you salute, eh?
All: Salute!
Because Jean and I
love you both so much...
...and we're so happy that Scott
is gonna be part of our clan now.
And so, I say, many, many,
many happy, happy years ahead.
- Salute.
- All: Salute!
Uh, my turn.
I thought it was off.
Sorry.
Um...
To a great couple.
- Cheers.
- And cheers again!
- Cheers again.
- Let's eat!
- Scott: Yes! Good idea.
Actually, I'm sorry.
Maybe I should call you dad.
All: Aww!
Harvey.
Hello, Jean.
Could I have a glass of water,
please?
No ice.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm excellent.
Go a little easy,
okay, Harvey?
Why?
Are you afraid I'm going to
embarrass you again?
No, I'm-
I'm afraid you're gonna
embarrass yourself, Harvey.
We're here for Susan.
This is her weekend.
It's Scott and Susan's weekend.
You're good.
You're still good.
I mean, you've always known.
...how to make me feel
like a piece of shit in 30 seconds.
Well, you gave me
a lot of practice.
Why'd you marry me?
I was- I was very young...
...and you were lots of fun.
And how's Brian?
Is he fun?
He thinks I'm fun.
Harvey, go home now.
Get some sleep, hmm?
Come back,
and see your daughter get married.
Our baby girl's
getting married.
- Hey.
- Susie.
- Dad.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm great.
- How you doing, huh?
- I'm good.
- You enjoying yourself?
- Mm-hmm.
That Scott seems like
a very good guy.
He is.
I'm sorry I haven't had a chance
to talk to you.
No no, don't you worry about me.
I'm fine.
This is about you and Scott.
This is your weekend.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
So, how's work?
Oh, it's all right.
It's, uh-
It's just different.
It's sound design now.
It's not music anymore.
It's a business,
so it's computers and digital...
...and you just hit a button,
and it's a triangle chime.
But it's what it is.
Are you still writing
your own stuff?
Well, when I get home,
I play a little.
So, listen, um...
I'm really sorry to tell you this...
...but I have to
get back to New York.
'cause I have
a really important account waiting.
It's very serious.
So I won't be at the reception in the
evening, but I will be at your ceremony.
That's where you're getting married.
I wouldn't miss that.
Okay.
Uh, Dad...
I've been thinking...
...and Brian's
been a really big part of my life.
...for the past few years...
...and...
I'm gonna ask him
to give me away tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I want you to go be with your friends, and I
want you to have a good time...
- And I'm gonna see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
No, but seriously,
I mean, the thing is...
Excuse- Sorry.
Harvey: Right here's good, friend.
Thanks. I want to walk.
Excuse me, could you take me
to Wilton Green?
By the powers vested in me,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
To Heathrow.
Spirits?
Champagne?
Okay. Excellent.
Can we go another way?
You're having a laugh,
ain't you?
It'll be bad everywhere.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I have the 1:30 to JFK.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm dealing with a passenger.
- I want to go straight to the gate.
- I will answer all your questions...
- But you will have to wait.
- Okay. Ma'am, excuse me.
- I'm on the 1:30 flight to JFK.
- Sir- Sir, there is a queue.
I appreciate that,
but I'm on the 1:30 flight to JFK.
That flight's now closed.
No no no, the plane
doesn't take off for 40 minutes.
Sir, the gate
is already closed.
But all I have is hand luggage.
Please, just let me through.
- Sir, that is not hand luggage.
- What, this?
- Now will you let me on, please?
- No, Sir.
When's the next flight?
The earliest I can get you on for sure is
tomorrow morning.
- Tomorrow?
- Sir, you're gonna have to stay calm.
Marvin, it's Harvey.
Listen, the traffic was crazy.
I'm gonna have to reschedule slightly.
Come on, Harvey.
The traffic?
- Jesus. Come on.
- Frank can set up.
I'll e-mail them
the queue numbers...
...and then I'll be there at lunchtime
at the latest.
I'll come straight
from the airport.
Look, just stay in London, will you? Just
enjoy your daughter's wedding.
No no, Marvin, it's fine.
- There's no problem.
- Harvey.
Frank knows exactly what to do, and Mike
is gonna be right there to help.
- Harvey, we've got to talk.
No no no. No, listen.
I'll be there at lunchtime, Marvin.
It's okay. It's all set up.
- Harvey?
- Yeah? What?
- It's over.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- It's out of my hands.
There's people I got to answer to.
I'm letting you go.
We'll talk
when you get back.
Hi.
Can I have a Johnnie Walker...
...and if you have a black label,
neat?
Thanks.
Another, please.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Aw, shit!
Sorry.
Vulgar American.
How you doing?
I'm sorry, by the way.
For what?
Weren't you the gal who tried to
ask me some questions...
...and you were just doing your job,
and I was rude?
I'm sorry.
I don't remember, really,
but you probably were.
Most people are.
Hmm.
Good book?
Would be
if I could finish it.
Ooh!
- That'll help.
- What?
I said, "That'll help. "
- What? This?
- Mm.
Oh, yes it will,
and it is.
Right.
It'll help as much as that trashy novel
and a glass of Chardonnay.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
That was out of line.
Go away!
Stop apologizing.
It's just that I've had
a really shitty day.
Join the club.
Oh no, yours may have been shitty,
but mine was shittier.
Mine was major shitty, you know?
Huh?
How shitty?
I missed the plane, I
lost my job...
...and my daughter,
who's getting married today...
...decided that she wanted her stepfather
rather than me to give her away, okay?
And that took it
to major shitty.
Fair enough.
You win.
What do you say,
let me make it up to both of us...
...and I'll buy you lunch?
Or tea. How about tea,
if it's teatime?
Thanks very much, but I don't know you,
and you don't know me, so-
That's exactly why
we should have tea together.
It's very sweet of you,
but thank you. No.
- Well, you've got your book.
- Mm.
If that's for me,
I'm in the shower.
Aren't you gonna answer it?
No.
Should I take that
as a hopeful sign?
If it is, you can give me
a little wider smile.
Thank you.
See?
We're having lunch together.
No, we're having lunch
next to each other.
Ah.
By the way,
Harvey - Harvey Shine.
Kate Walker.
So, why aren't you
at the wedding?
I knew there was something
that was missing.
I had to get back for work.
What, for the job
you just lost?
Yes, exactly.
Did you enjoy it,
the job?
Yes. No.
Yes, originally.
What was it?
I write jingles.
- Wow.
- That's a normal response.
Did you always want to write
jingles, or was-
was there something more?
What?
No no, I love it.
You cut right through it.
I like that.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
- You should.
I would have given anything...
...to have been a jazz pianist.
Were you good?
No. Not good enough.
Sorry.
I... Can be a bit nosy.
Yeah, and I like it.
- Do you believe me?
- Mm.
I have to tell you that
is a relief to find someone.
who actually says what they're feeling and
what they're thinking.
Especially in a place
that's supposed to be-
...you know -
Britain, English, reserved.
Oh, no no. Haven't you heard?
We're a nation changed.
Ever since Diana died, we're all sort of
flowing out of us like water.
You guys showed us the way,
actually.
No more
stiff upper lip for us.
And what is that, exactly?
- What?
- "Stiff upper lip. "
I'm not sure,
it's kind of...
...that whole clenched thing.
- Clenched?
- I think so, you know.
See, when you cry,
your lips wobble...
...and when you're being strong,
they don't.
Like this.
No, that's sort of
more like a bulldog.
No, don't do that. You look like
you've got no teeth at all.
It's my first attempt
at a stiff upper lip.
- Who does-
- I don't really kn-
I think it's the sort of tension
in your jaw.
Who does that?
- Aristocrats.
- The aristocrats?
Posh people.
- Thank you. I enjoyed that.
- Me too. Where are you going?
- I'm just going to a class, actually.
- What kind of class?
- Writing.
- Ah.
It's just a thing,
twice a week, I do.
I've got to get the Heathrow Express,
actually, so-
- I see.
- What about you?
I don't know. I guess I'll stay
in a hotel near here.
- I have a flight in the morning.
- Oh, so it's- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye, then.
- Bye.
- Good luck.
There's your phone again.
Hello?
Yes.
Harvey: Sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Hi.
The thought of staying at a hotel
near the runway unnerved me.
- Do you mind?
- No no no.
Excuse me.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
You ran.
Well, I wish you'd been on the car
four cars down.
So...
- You okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Where we going?
- Um, Paddington.
Oh.
So, here's the taxi rank.
I suppose it's bye-bye again.
Oh.
They'll take you to wherever
you want to go- Any hotel.
You mean instead of me
walking you to your class?
Carry your books.
I'll throw that in.
Sure.
Is that a "yes"?
Yes.
Why not?
In which case, we um-
we have to go-
we have to go back this way.
You mind
if I just drop these off?
Sure.
It's like "Yours is a glorious country,
Honeychurch!"
Know that? Line from a book.
"Room with a View. "
Ah. E.M. Forster.
- Mm-hmm. Have you read it?
- No.
- Do you think less of me?
- No no, not at all.
It's just- I think
we're just very different.
Probably.
- Is that bad?
- No.
I don't think so either.
Hang on. Sorry.
- Oh, sorry. I should get this.
- Go ahead.
Hello, Mum? Hello.
Sorry. I've been busy.
Yeah.
No. I'm out, actually.
Yes yes, with someone.
No, with someone else.
Yes, a man.
Oh, you did, did you?
What,
an actual body?
Okay, listen.
Listen, I'll come
in early tomorrow morning...
...and we'll check it out together,
all right?
All right. All right.
Bye-bye. Bye.
Yeah, I love you, too.
Bye. Bye.
- Sorry. My mum.
- She worries about you?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Well, about herself, actually.
She's convinced
she's living next to Poland's answer to...
- I don't know, Jack the Ripper.
- Oh.
Do you live with her?
Oh no. No no no.
God, no.
Near, not with.
She's all right.
She means well.
She just had
a really rough ride of it is all.
Why?
Oh, well, my dad ran off to France
with his secretary...
...and then, about four years ago, she got
cancer, but she's completely recovered.
She's fine.
She just doesn't want to admit it.
You know.
So...
...she's bored is what I think it is...
...so she's made my situation...
which is what she calls me
"being single," her major distraction.
It's like a sort of hobby for her,
if you like.
I see.
Sorry.
- What?
- No. I was just-
- I was just talking too much.
- No no, you're not.
- No, I am.
- No, you're not.
Anyway, we're here.
This is my class.
So, how long is your class?
An hour.
I can- I can wait.
Well, it's getting cold.
You don't want to wait, do you?
Not that cold.
Okay.
Careful.
I might get
the wrong impression.
So, uh, how did it go?
Well, the usual.
Lovely, mild-mannered Mike
gave us the latest installment.
...from his psychosexual thriller.
He's 86.
Shall we keep walking?
Okay.
It's nice.
It's nice today.
Do you ever wish you could just live
a different life just for a day.
...just to see
what it would be like?
Do you have an idea
what yours would be?
Mine?
I think it would take place in Spain-
definitely-
...in a little house, inland.
- And what would you do?
- Write a book.
I mean, you know,
not "Middlemarch" or anything.
- George Eliot.
- Yeah. Have you read it?
No.
So, your book-
Would be just a
really good holiday read...
...you know,
for the beach or a plane.
I've got one of those inside me.
And this house that you'd live in-
- Cabana.
- Yeah. Please.
Sorry-
that you'd write in...
would it have a view?
Yes, across the plains...
with a little stream running around it
to bathe in.
- Bathe in?
- Mm-hmm.
- No showers?
- No.
Rustic.
Okay okay okay.
I'll adjust.
I'm there, only if you're
receiving guests, that is.
Sure.
You may visit,
Harvey Shine.
Well, thank you,
Kate Walker.
## I'm a guy
that likes his fun ##
## When I fight,
you'd better run ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun ##
## I'm going down
to the middle of town ##
## I'm gonna shoot
that first man down ##
## I'm a mean, mean son of a gun ##
## My skin's hard as leather,
I'm as tough as any man ##
## When I have to shave myself,
I use an old tin can ##
## I wash my face in boiling wax,
scrub myself with a gunnysack ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun ##
## I'm mean,
I'm mean, I'm mean ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun... ##
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
What happened between you
and your daughter?
Uh, I don't know.
Somewhere along the way,
I just lost her.
I woke up one morning,
and I-
I realized...
...that I didn't belong
in that house.
You know, I always had this feeling
in my stomach...
...that they were
a bit embarrassed by me.
I mean, if you see them now with Brian, my
daughter's stepfather...
...you know, they just-
it just makes more sense.
I mean, they really look right
together.
And I was not
a great father.
Is the wedding reception
still going on?
I don't know.
Am I still on New York time?
What time is it?
About 7::00.
Where is it on?
Grosvenor House.
Well, you have to go.
- No no no no no.
- Yes, you do.
No.
No, Harvey.
It's ridiculous you're not there.
- You have to go.
- They really don't want me.
Harvey, she's your daughter,
and you're her father. You have to go.
Harvey, I really mean it.
It's absolutely unforgivable.
You have to go.
- Come on.
- I'm thinking.
You come with me.
No. I-
I can't go
to a wedding reception in...
...bloody green polyester.
Are you trying to get me
to buy you a new dress?
- Is that what this is all about?
- No.
- It is! Yes, it is!
- No, it's not.
- I'm not coming.
- Come as my bodyguard.
- No. No.
- Come as my friend?
Okay.
I am not spending
more than 200 on that frock.
- Is it a deal?
- Yes. Yes.
## I'm a guy
that likes his fun ##
## And when I fight,
you'd better run ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun ##
## I'm going down
in the middle of town ##
## I'm going to shoot
the first man down ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun ##
## My skin is hard as leather,
I'm as tough as any man ##
## When I have to shave myself,
I use an old tin can ##
## I wash my face in boiling wax,
and scrub myself with a gunnysack ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun ##
## I'm mean,
I'm mean, I'm mean ##
## I'm a mean, mean,
mean son of a gun ##
## I'm a mean, mean, mean
son of a gun. ##
Oh.
Where was it?
Hello.
- My ex-wife just clocked you.
- Did she?
Huh? Oh.
- You should go say hi.
- Okay.
Here comes my daughter.
- Hi.
- I didn't go.
- I'm glad.
Uh, this is, uh, Kate.
- Oh, hello.
- A friend.
How do you do?
Congratulations.
You look fantastic.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry
I've gate-crashed, actually.
- No, she-
- But it was your father.
He insisted.
No no. It's fine.
I'm sure there's room.
No no no no.
We'll just fit in wherever.
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hmm?
- Could you find them a seat?
- Sure.
Ladies and gentlemen, could I have
your attention, please?
It's time now
for the best-man speech.
Oh. Except we seem to be
missing the bride.
You may have seen her -
dark hair, white dress.
Oh, there she is.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
Without further ado,
our best man, Pete Turner.
- Pete: Thank you, Josh.
- Hi.
And thank you, Jean and Brian,
for such a beautiful occasion and for-
You do know
this is the children's table.
Yes.
I'm gonna need to take you
back to the early '90s...
when a tall,
far-too-cheerful Chicago man...
- Kate: Hello.
- ... walked into my room at Duke...
- Bit of a chatterbox.
- Mm.
And finally, I'd like to
propose a toast to Susan.
...for making
my friend Scott complete.
All: To Susan!
Cheers.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's now time
for the father of the bride.
...to say a few words.
Tonight, that enviable task.
will fall to the ever-charming,
ever-distinguished Brian...
...ladies and gentlemen.
Well, that was
quite some speech, Peter-
quite something to follow.
But I will try.
- Brian.
- Yes, Harvey?
Excuse me for interrupting.
I think he said
"father of the bride. "
Ah, yes.
May I?
Go- Go ahead, Harvey.
Hi, everybody.
Um...
I think there's something.
...that Jean and I learned
from our failed marriage...
...and that is that it's the children
of divorce that suffer the most...
...and the child of Jean and Harvey Shine
has had her share.
...of pain and disappointment, but-
- ... and this is a tribute to you, Susan
- it has served her well.
...because she's somehow
separated herself.
...from the fracture
of her birth family.
...to become a strong and determined
and independent woman.
And yet...
...you've kept your sensitivity
and your vulnerability.
...and your loveliness...
...and you look
quite beautiful tonight.
Um...
- Scott?
- Hey.
You're a lucky guy,
and I'm a lucky guy.
...because I'm looking forward
to you being my son.
You are my son-in-law.
I've never had a son.
Okay.
Well, no pressure,
but, Jean...
I look forward to grandparenting
with you...
...but that's no pressure, Scott.
I toast you, Scott.
I toast your wife...
...my daughter.
I toast our family.
And if I can just linger
a moment longer...
I'd like to hand this back to you, Brian,
with a note of gratitude.
Thanks for being there.
I would like to ask you all to please stand
up and join Harvey and I
- ... in a toast to the bride and the groom
- To Susan and to Scott.
Susan and Scott!
## Baby, I'm yours ##
## And I'll be yours ##
## Until the stars
fall from the sky ##
## Yours until the rivers
all run dry ##
## In other words, until I die ##
## Baby, I'm yours ##
Harvey. Harvey.
## And I'll be yours
until the sun no longer shines ##
- Hi.
- Don't cry.
- I won't.
Oh, Susan.
Oh, thanks for coming back,
Dad.
Thanks for having me back.
## Do my best to keep you satisfied ##
## Nothing in the world
can drive me away ##
Huh? Ready?
Whoo!
## Hold it ##
## Don't let go ##
## Baby ##
## Not too slow ##
## Higher ##
## Make me know ##
## Move it faster ##
## Don't let go ##
## Don't let go, don't let go,
don't let go ##
Is that one of yours?
Yes.
It's lovely.
Don't go.
Okay.
- We have to hurry.
- Why?
Because I'm gonna dance
your socks off.
Bye! Bye! Bye!
Okay!
Oh, the bouquet!
Three, two, one!
Yay!
Have a great time.
- Hey!
- Oh, sorry! Bye-bye!
Bye!
- Good luck.
- Thank you, and thank you.
Crowd: Bye!
Bye.
- You all right?
- Yes. Yes, I am.
- Do you want to get out of here?
- Sure.
Excuse me.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- Why?
- "Why"?
Well, you did
about five different dances.
No, no. I mean, why is it called "cutting a
rug"?
I love these fountains.
Children play in them
in the summer.
They sort of sit on them.
They sit their little bottoms down,
and then they get tickled by the water.
They love it.
I don't think
I've stayed up all night...
...since I was a student.
You got sad.
Why?
I was pregnant once.
Didn't have it.
I mean...
I didn't think twice about it.
That's what smart girls did.
Yeah.
I do...
I do sometimes wonder,
you know, wh-
whether they would be funny
or clever or...
Oh, I don't know...
...neurotic.
Stupid, really.
I don't know why
I told you that.
Meet me here tomorrow, okay?
What?
Right here,
right in this spot, noon.
Okay?
What about your flight?
I don't have to go.
Why?
Oh, shut up, Harvey.
Stop it.
You think that now,
you wait till tomorrow.
Today is tomorrow.
Harvey.
We don't know anything
about each other.
You're, you know-
- Old.
- No, I wasn't gonna say that.
Well, okay, you're a bit older.
I'm...
I can be mean.
So can I.
No. Truly cantankerous.
Cantankerous, I've never been.
I should be going.
I'm very serious.
I'll be here waiting at noon,
okay?
Okay?
Harvey Shine.
Tell me what time!
Noon!
I can't hear you!
Top o' the morning
to you, Sir.
I'm afraid they're both out of order, Mr.
Shine.
If you wouldn't mind
using the stairs.
I wouldn't mind at all.
Whew!
- Are you okay, Sir?
- Huh?
What's the problem?
Are you okay?
- Uh.
- Can you-
I'm gonna bring you a doctor.
Just wait here, please.
Shit.
Hey.
Hey!
- Morning, James.
- Morning, Kate.
- You all right?
- Ooh!
Actually, can I have, um,
can I have some grapes?
I've got some lovely
seedless grapes today.
All right, then. Give us a little
bunch- Three quids worth.
- Okeydoke.
- That'll do me.
Thank you.
Man: Clutching his chest?
Yeah?
All right.
Sir, you said that you've been
drinking more coffee than usual.
- Yes, but I have to be somewhere.
- And you're under stress.
- You haven't been sleeping well.
- Yes, but I already told the nurse.
Please, I've been up all night, I'm under
stress, but I have an appointment.
Okay, sir, try and calm down.
I just need you to stay tonight.
I have to be somewhere.
It looks to me like arrhythmia,
which is an irregular heartbeat.
Yes. I told the nurse
it's called SVT's.
I've had it since I was a kid, and I left my
medication in New York...
...so if you can just make me out
a prescription for Digoxin.
Digoxin, yeah. That's right.
We can do that, no problem.
First, I just need to rule out
all other possibilities.
No, no. It's arrhythmia.
Please, Doctor.
- I have an appointment.
- I'm 99% sure it is arrhythmia.
Nurse, can you do a 12-lead ECG
and send for tests troponin?
You can't keep me here.
No. You cannot keep me here.
Also a thyroid function, please.
Thank you.
And can you arrange a monitor bed
for him for tonight?
Okay, Mama. It's me. Done.
I've got to get to work.
Why don't you stay
and have some lunch?
I can't.
I've got to go.
Not to pry or anything...
...but why is there a large smoked ham under
the stairs?
Oh, that. Yes.
It's, um...
The neighbor gave it to me.
The Polish neighbor?
So, probably not
a mass murderer.
Probably not.
Are you sure
you're gonna be all right?
Yeah. Of course I will.
I'll be fine.
Men. Who needs them?
Remember, we've got Greece
to look forward to.
Yeah.
Got lipstick on your face.
See you.
- Morning, Kate.
- Morning, Paddy.
- Lovely as ever.
- Thank you.
Right.
Okay, thanks a lot.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Hello. PSA.
Heathrow branch.
Hello.
Is there a Kate Walker there?
- It's Harvey.
- Hold on.
Kate, it's for you.
Some guy called Harvey.
I'm sorry,
she's, uh, not here.
Please, this is important.
Kate!
I'm sorry.
She's busy.
She won't come.
Okay, thanks.
Sir, if I can get you
to sign here.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey, Harvey. It's Marvin.
Where are you?
I'm still in London, Marvin.
Well, you get yourself back here,
my friend.
I got some great news.
You were right.
The Samuelson account,
none of the kids could handle it.
They couldn't nail it.
They ended up picking
one of your old tunes.
They want you to come back
and update it.
We need you back, Harvey.
Your old room's here waiting for you.
Harvey?
- Oh, well, that's great, Marvin.
- Yeah. Yeah. It's great.
Look, I know
when to eat humble pie.
So, hey, when can you
get back here?
Harvey?
I'm not coming back.
What?
I quit.
What do you mean you quit,
Harvey?
Look, man, you need us.
No. You know, I don't.
As you said, it's my last chance.
Look, I got to go.
Taxi!
Taxi, Heathrow.
I'm in a hurry.
- Hi.
I'm looking for Kate Walker.
Kate.
Who wants to know?
A friend.
Oonagh, there's a man out here
asking for Kate.
- He says "a friend. "
- Yes.
- Friend?
- Well, more than a friend.
- More than a friend?
- Yes.
- Are you the American?
- Yes, that's right.
She likes you.
I can tell.
Don't you go messing her around, now.
Don't you hurt her.
Oh, I won't.
I wouldn't.
She's not here.
She's left for the day.
You might still find her
at her class.
In fact, it starts about now.
It's down at the South Bank.
Called the National.
- Yes, I know.
- Oh, you know, do you?
- Yes.
- Go on. Go and get her.
See you, Harvey.
"The blood oozes from his wound like dark
chocolate on a warm summer's day.
He could still smell her on his glove-
...that deep, penetrating smell of sex.
It was silent, but with the faint sound of
dripping sweat.
Salt was the taste
that he remembered most-
...so salubrious, so sensual...
...so sexy. "
Oh, thank you.
Here you go.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You still here,
still in London?
Sure.
- Can I explain?
- No no.
- You don't need to explain, Harvey.
- I want to.
- No, honestly. I don't need to-
- Kate, please.
- I was in a hospital.
- Oh, God. Why?
No. It's nothing.
I left my pills in New York.
I have this irregular heartbeat.
- I had it since I was a kid.
- Arrhythmia.
- How do you know what it is?
- 'Cause my father has it.
Well, young men get it, too.
Aw, Kate, I'm so sorry
I wasn't there.
- Oh, it's fine, Harvey.
- No.
I had a lovely time, Harvey,
and I like you- I really do.
Thank you.
But, you know, I don't really do fountains
at noon either.
I mean, I live in-
Well, I live in Wilton Green,
and you live in wherever you-
- I live in White Plains.
- Exactly.
And Monday morning, life kicks in,
and we're not teenagers.
Got a life and our jobs and our family
and everything, and I had a lovely time.
- I won't forget it. Thank you. But-
- What?
- Well, it's not, you know, real life.
- It is.
- No, it isn't, Harvey.
- No, it's not, Harvey.
- No. It is real life.
- It's real life for me.
- No, no. I know. I know.
But it's not just about you, is it?
It's about me, as well.
You don't know anything about me.
Look at me. I mean, it's pathetic.
I actually expected you
not to show.
In fact, I think I actually almost
wanted you not to show...
...because it's just sort of easier
that way.
You know,
you just dive in there.
You just whoosh anywhere.
It's the deep end...
...and I'm not a bloody swimming pool,
Harvey, and I'm not-
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna do it
because it'll hurt.
Sometime or other, there will be-
...you know, it's not working,
or I need my space, or whatever it is...
...and it will end, and it will hurt,
and I won't do it.
I won't do it,
and I won't...
You see,
what I think it is, is-
...is I think I'm more comfortable
with being disappointed.
I think I'm angry with you
for trying to take that away.
Mum, I love you,
but not now.
Should I take that
as a hopeful sign?
If you give me
just a little wider smile.
Oh, shut up, Harvey.
So how's this going to work,
Mr. Shine?
I have absolutely no idea.
But it will.
I promise you that.
Shall we walk?
Yes.
- You okay?
- Uh, yeah.
Hang on a sec.
Oh.
That's better.
I think
you're my kind of girl.
Why don't you ask me
those questions?
Which ones?
You know, at the airport,
when I avoided you.
- Oh, the questionnaire.
- Yes.
Oh, okay. Name?
Harvey Shine.
Place of residence?
I'm in transition.
## Where do we go from here? ##
## Where can we hide? ##
## 'Cause I made a U-turn,
and I'm still alive ##
## Where do we go from here? ##
## And where did they put
the signs? ##
## 'Cause I need an exit ##
## After this life ##
## And where is
this better place? ##
## And where are
these better times? ##
## And we cannot find ##
- Hi.
- Hello.
I wanted to say thank you
for the ham...
...and sorry for taking so long
to say thank you.
You're welcome.
- It's smoked.
- Yes.
- Please, come in.
- Oh, no. I can't. I shouldn't.
- I have to...
- Please.
Perhaps, um...
Perhaps you could just show me
how to cut it.
Absolutely.
Please, come in.
## I've got my foot down,
it's too slow ##
## Ooh, hoo-hoo-hoo ##
## Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo ##
## Yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah ##
## Can you hear me
calling out? ##
## Look how much fun
we had ##
## And now
it's all turning bad ##
## I've got my foot down,
it's too slow ##
## Look how much fun
we had ##
## Now it's all turning bad ##
## I've got my foot down,
it's too slow ##
## Look how much fun
we had ##
## Now it's all turning bad ##
## I've got my foot down,
it's too slow ##
## You should know. ##
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org