Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Tell me when you're gonna come.
- Are you coming? You're coming?
- Yeah.
Hello.
Hey, bro, what's up?
I'm crashed out.
What are you doing?
What party?
What are you talking about?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Where?
Fuck!
The number you have reached has
been disconnected. If you feel you...
No fucking way!
Where's the phone? Payphone.
Straight to the back,
past the bathrooms, on the left.
Hey, Mallory.
Oh, hey, Syd, what's up?
You gonna go
to Becca's thing tonight?
Yeah, you know, I was gonna go
and say goodbye.
Why, you going?
Yeah, I think so.
Thinking about it. Yeah.
So you still talk to London?
Yeah, you know,
here and there. Why?
Oh, you know, I was just a little
surprised to hear she was moving.
Did she get a place out there?
Is she staying with somebody?
She didn't tell you where
she was staying? Come on, Mal.
I mean, she said something
about moving in with her boyfriend...
...or something, but, I mean,
that's pretty much all I know.
- Can I get you a drink?
- Yeah.
Can I have a vodka? A large one.
Naked, please.
Excuse me. One second here.
Here you go.
Thanks. Hey, look, I didn't...
I didn't mean to be rude.
It's okay.
- Hey, Syd, I gotta go cash out, so...
- Yeah.
- See you tonight.
Listen, I'm gonna get a bit of sniff,
so if you want some, just let me know.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
How much is it?
Oh, no, don't worry. Just find me.
Don't tell London.
You know she hates that shit.
Yeah, like I'm gonna say something.
- All right, well, see you later.
- Yeah, I'll see you.
Your name wouldn't happen
to be Bateman, would it?
- Unfortunately, yes.
- Hey. Syd.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming down.
I know you don't deliver this far down.
I just had a shitty day.
I have to clear my head out.
No worries, mate.
So where do you wanna do this?
We don't want to go in the bathroom.
It's horrendous in there.
I drove. You wanna use my car?
Your car? Why not?
So how is this shit? It's pretty good?
Can't say I've sampled
any of this batch...
...but considering the source,
I imagine it to be pretty clean, yeah.
So is this like a full-time gig for you?
A full-time job?
No, mate, I'm a banker.
Foreign exchange dealer.
Currency trader.
- Currency trader?
- Euros, pounds, arbitrage, yeah.
Okay, so you're not a dealer.
Mate, I ain't a fucking dealer.
Strictly a buyer.
I was uptown, you were on my way.
It's just a favor.
Gotcha. Well, whatever it is,
I really appreciate it, man.
Here we go.
So a currency trader, huh?
How's the money in that, good?
Not if you get stuck on this shit, no.
Yeah, I know.
God, what a stupid fucking drug.
I don't know what you're doing after
this, if you got plans or anything...
...but a friend is having a party two
blocks from here, if you're interested.
No, thanks, mate,
but I've had a shit day, believe me.
I just figured, you know,
you came down this whole way.
It'll probably be pretty good.
What kind of party is it, exactly?
Actually, it's a...
It's a going-away party for this girl,
for my ex-chick.
But it'll be good, you know,
free booze, free food, hot chicks.
I really shouldn't. Thanks anyway.
I appreciate the offer.
Fuck it, Syd. I'm gonna go.
Take it easy.
Why are you gonna go?
Don't go. You just got here.
You walked all the way down here.
Why leave?
Because I've had a horrendous day.
I've decided not to go because I don't
want to meet a loft full of strangers.
- You enjoy yourself.
- Come in for five minutes.
- Get a drink.
- No, man. You go, fuck it.
What do you got
that's better than this?
Girls, free booze, do a line.
I've just come out of the most
psychotic therapy session...
...l've had in fucking years.
Almost smacked some cunt for a taxi.
I really don't know
if I'm ready for this shit.
Just come in for five minutes.
You don't like it, you can leave.
One fucking drink, bro.
Mallory will be here.
One drink?
One fucking drink.
- How you doing, man?
- Evening.
- What is it, 5011?
- Yes.
Thanks, man.
- Hey, Maya.
- Hi, Syd.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- It's been a while.
- Yeah. How you doing?
I'm good.
Bateman, this is Maya. Sorry.
- Maya, Bateman.
- Nice to meet you.
How you been?
What you been up to?
In hell, man. I fucked up on the SATs,
I gotta retake them.
- That's it, you know?
- Right.
Just wanna kill myself. Yeah.
Well, you know, if you want to get out
of SAT mode, I picked up a lot of:
- You know, so...
- Are you dealing now?
Yes, I'm dealing. No, I'm not dealing.
I got more than I need, so if you're...
- All right, man, thanks.
- Just come find me.
- I might take you up on that.
- Did anybody...?
Coming.
- Hello.
- Hey, baby.
- How are you?
- I'm good. Hey, Syd, how are you?
- This, my darling, is for you.
Oh, you guys, shut up. Thank you.
- You know you are the best.
- Nobody's here yet.
Grab a drink.
Make yourself at home.
Hello? Syd and London.
- Don't disrespect them in public.
- In public.
Let's go upstairs.
Why? Who's upstairs?
Very bad. Catch me.
You're crazy.
What is this?
It's for you.
- For me? For me?
- For you.
Oh, my God, Syd, I love it.
Thank you.
I love you.
Come on, "I love you too, London,"
you fucker.
You can say it.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
- London, don't.
- What? What am I doing?
- This.
- What am I doing wrong?
Whatever this is, this obsession
to put a verbal label on everything.
- It's not about words.
- No, it is about words.
Because if we didn't have words,
we'd be living in caves...
...and still talking with our hands.
- Stop.
We haven't even
come close to a fight.
If we can avoid that first fight,
by theory we'll never fight.
Okay? Please.
It's been so perfect till now.
Don't do this.
It's been perfect for you. For you.
London.
Coming.
Wait a minute,
someone's at the door.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Wow, you look beautiful.
You look hot.
Nice hat, nice boots.
Thanks.
- Hey.
- Hey, Becca.
- Rebecca.
- Bateman. Friend of Syd's.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nobody's here yet, guys.
So just come on in
and make yourself at home.
Okay, so you're not gonna believe
who's just fucking shown up.
Great party, mate.
Oh, it'll be better. It'll be better.
Trust me. I promise you.
Okay, I've gotta go.
Please tell me
you did not bring Syd here.
Oh, my God, I just rode up
in the elevator with him.
- Why? He's not invited?
- He's so not invited.
He's fucking touching
my Buddha's head.
Hey, London, it's me.
Give me a call as soon
as you get this, okay? Okay, bye.
Fuck it.
Hey, Syd. Do us a favor, yeah?
Don't touch the Buddha.
Okay?
He's a fucking cocksucker.
Where did you get your hat?
It's so cute on you.
He's fucked.
To show up at someone's party.
He isn't even fucking invited.
Did they just go upstairs?
Right. Nice. Nice of them to ask.
Wait, I'm confused, did you say
you do believe in God or you don't?
"God" might not be
the appropriate word for it, actually.
It's more of an epiphany.
Epiphany?
What was your epiphany?
Well, for me, an epiphany
is when you really see the universe...
...in all it's splendor and beauty...
...and you suddenly
understand everything.
- What does that mean?
- Fucking everything.
Everything you can imagine. You don't
know what "everything" means?
I know what it means. I don't know
what you mean by "everything."
It means everything, doesn't it?
You know, everything.
- So, what's your problem?
- For someone who's seen the infinite...
...you're vague. You'd think
with someone who's had a revelation...
...you'd be more specific.
- It's not about specifics.
It's an energy that hits you between
the eyes and you're enlightened.
- You see everything?
- You don't see everything.
You see nothing.
But you understand everything.
And you know what
got me the most?
- Is that I understood time horizons.
- What's a time horizon?
It's like this. I understood
where I stood in relation...
...to where the Romans and the Jews
were 2000 years ago...
...and why I was here now.
Then I felt this enormous
compassion...
...for the struggle of the human race
and what it had to go through for us.
You know, for life as we know it
to come to this point.
It's truly remarkable, but at the same
time, it's utterly fucking disturbing.
I mean, we're the same people
that were living in Roman times...
...throwing boiling oil on each other
and crucifying Christians.
Not that that's entirely a bad thing.
Hey, Syd, are you in there?
It's Maya.
Oh, fuck! Fuck me.
- Fuck, fuck. Give me one second.
- What the fuck have you done?
- Sorry. Fuck.
- You clumsy bastard.
- What have you fucking done?
- Shit.
Look at that.
It's covered in fucking beer.
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God.
What are you gonna do?
- Goddamn it, Syd.
- Instant karma.
- I got it.
- That's enough to give up blasphemy.
- Get up here.
- No, we can totally save this.
What are you gonna do,
eat food off the floor?
- Fucking gross.
- Do me a favor.
- God fucking damn it.
- God, is this it?
- Yes.
- Are you kidding?
- No, it's my fucking fault too.
- Just snort it off the floor.
You don't wanna do that. I shouldn't
have put it by the fucking sink.
What are you doing?
- What's that?
- As I said, all is not lost.
- Bateman, Jesus Christ.
- Oh, my God, you fucking rock.
- Do you know this painting?
- No.
It's Van Gogh's
Wheatfield with Crows.
The most significant painting
the man's ever painted.
- Oh, well, then.
- Fuck, it's true.
That'll do for starters, won't it?
Look, this is the last painting
the man did before he killed himself.
It's his suicide note. He even put
his left ear in the fucking clouds.
There is his mutilated left ear.
Can you see it? Not everyone sees it,
of course, but there it is.
He mutilated his left ear
and put it in the fucking painting.
What does that mean?
Maya, I'm curious.
Do you believe in God?
You guys have been doing
too many drugs.
Answer the question. Yes or no?
God, that's a really long
conversation...
...but I will tell you something I read
the other day that freaked me out.
I don't remember where it was.
It was like Russia or Germany
or one of these places...
...but these scientists,
they took this pregnant rabbit...
...and they hooked up to,
like, a heart monitor and an EE G...
...which sensors your brain waves.
And, like, the second after she gives
birth, they take these babies...
...and they jump in a van
and they start shooting them...
...one by one in the back of the head
with, like, a.22 rifle.
From, like one mile away:
Five miles away:
Twenty miles away...
Don't tell me people are
killing little bunny rabbits.
What's so interesting
is that every time they'd shoot...
...one of these poor babies
in the back of the head...
...the mother's heartbeat
and brain waves would go crazy.
So I'm just saying there's,
you know, shit like that, and then...
The mother knew the babies
were getting shot...
Yes. Every fucking time. Exactly.
I mean, there's all that stuff, you know,
like those weird identical twins, right?
One of the brothers is
walking down the street...
...gets stabbed
by some serial killer.
Wait. So he gets stabbed, right?
And then 900 miles away,
at the exact same time...
...his twin brother falls down.
Weird, it's very weird, yes.
Do you want to let me finish
what I'm saying?
- Please, please, finish.
- Okay, he falls down.
Gets hospitalized
due to heart palpitations...
...at the same time
his brother was stabbed.
- Why are you shaking your head?
- You sound like London.
- It's coincidence.
- How is it a coincidence?
I've had this conversation before.
I'm not having it here.
Well, then, let's not. Then don't
ask me about God, okay, Syd?
Hey, is London here yet?
No, I don't think so.
Did you meet her boyfriend?
Yeah, a couple of times. He's nice.
Is he, like, an attractive guy?
Is he good-looking?
Are you asking me
if he's an attractive guy?
I guess.
You guess?
What do you mean, you guess?
I mean, I guess.
All right, so I'm curious. Do you think
he's more or less attractive than me?
Syd, I don't know.
Well, you do know.
You just aren't telling me.
I don't know, Syd. You guys just...
You have totally different looks.
All right, yes.
We have very different looks.
But whose do you like more?
His or mine?
This is stupid, Syd.
Okay, fine.
I guess, on some level,
I find him attractive.
That doesn't mean that I find him...
...any more or less attractive
than I find you.
Okay?
I won't lie to you.
Just because we're going out...
...doesn't mean I'm gonna,
you know...
...suddenly not be attracted
to the opposite sex.
He's a friend
who happens to be attractive.
It was one lunch.
Why are you freaking out?
You don't see me going to lunch
with a bunch of attractive people.
Okay. First of all,
it was one guy, not a bunch.
And it's really not my problem that
you don't have female friends, is it?
Because no one's stopping you
from having female friends.
I love this, by the way.
- So for the sake of conversation...
- Syd.
- Let's just pretend you and I...
- Please, can we just drop it?
...don't know each other.
Just listen to me.
Let's pretend for five minutes
you don't know me, I don't know you.
Me and what's-his-name
are in the room.
- Who do you pick?
- I do know you, Syd.
Remove that from the equation.
- You can't.
- Gun to your head. Who do you pick?
I would pick you.
I would pick you in any equation.
Are you all right in there?
Everything is fine. Thank you.
Syd, literally, this has got to be one
of the most insane conversations...
...l've ever had with you.
I don't want to fuck him. I don't.
- Fuck him?
- It was one lunch.
Who said anything
about fucking him?
- I didn't say fucking, I said attracted.
- That's what you meant.
- It's not.
- Please keep your voice down.
I meant attracted, you said fuck.
Can you just fucking
shut the fuck up?
What do you want?
I want you to answer
the fucking question.
Syd, you're a cute guy. You are.
You really, really are, but I don't know.
He has this angular, sexy,
Diesel-ad thing going on.
But I don't even know him.
- So maybe he's an asshole.
- You know what?
Fuck you, Maya. If you were my friend,
you would've lied.
Syd. Syd, you are at
her going-away party.
If you don't calm down,
you'll drive me...
...and you, and everyone else,
and her at this fucking party crazy.
Just say goodbye and let her go,
because she's gone.
She's gone, man.
Line, anyone?
No. No, thank you.
But do you have a cigarette?
I'm sorry.
Light. I'm sorry.
All right, all right, you know what?
I'm gonna go.
- Are you leaving?
- Thank you. Thank you for everything.
- Really.
- Listen, do me a favor.
Don't tell London I'm doing blow
in here. That'll really screw me.
You know, Syd, yeah,
you know, I'll try to remember that.
Maya, I'm serious. Please?
Hey, please tell me you're not doing
coke in my parents' bathroom.
- What?
- I saw you go upstairs.
- Where did you go?
- To the bathroom.
Swear to God, you're not doing coke
in my parents' house.
Oh, my God, I swear to God...
...l'm not doing coke
in your parents' house.
Okay, I'm sorry, darling.
All right.
Have a good time. I'm sorry.
How long were you two together?
Who? Me and London?
Two and a half years.
- You split when?
- Six months and a few days ago.
You're counting, Syd.
Not a good sign, mate.
Why? Why do you say that?
Joking.
I mean, what's the girl's name?
- Maya. Can I have one of those?
- Maya.
Maya.
I'd do some terrible things to her.
She's like an X-rated Barbie doll.
- How old is she?
- I don't know, like 16, 17.
Seventeen?
- Now I really wanna fuck her.
- You'd fuck a 17-year-old?
What, you wouldn't?
If it's not against the law,
what's the problem?
You can fuck a 15-year-old
in France.
Does that make them
all pedophiles?
Right situation, right country,
you'd fuck one too, believe you me.
Right, right. International waters,
deserted island, shit can happen.
But if any of my female friends
knew I fucked a 17-year-old...
...they'd lose it.
- What's the matter with you?
If we told women a tenth of
the things we think and do...
...do you think we'd ever get laid?
- Like when I asked a girl to piss on me.
- To piss on you?
Yes, mate, but I was on
a horrible amount of X at the time.
Did she piss on you?
Actually, no...
...she pissed in my mouth.
She pissed in your mouth?
It was not a pleasant experience,
believe me.
How the fuck does that happen?
What is the conversation that leads to
a girl having to piss in your mouth?
It was a fucking mistress.
- You paid an S & M chick?
- Many times.
"Many times."
Listen, it's an expensive hobby,
both mentally and financially.
So, what's the deal?
How does it work?
I don't know if I want
to go there, you know?
Come on, explain it. No one cares.
Did you get your shit wet? Me too.
It's my fucking Savile Row suit.
It's fucking 5 G's.
I've kept it out of the rain all day.
Look at the state of it.
Look, I don't wanna go there.
All right, Syd?
Come on. I'm not gonna tell.
- Why the fuck do you wanna know?
- How does it work?
- You just go over there?
- Look at you, you fucking dirtbag.
- You brought it up.
- You wanna go there...
...you fucking go there. Leave my
fucking demons to myself, mate.
- Where is it?
- Tribeca, you cunt.
Explain it. How does it work?
You just walk over?
Look, you phone from downstairs...
...and magically they let you in
through these enormous iron gates.
You get all excited.
You get all wrapped up.
You can't wait to get in there.
The whole thought of it just
gets amongst your fucking veins.
You're into it, you know?
All of a sudden,
they give you a form.
It's a five-page disclaimer
in fucking triplicate.
And you're like, "Hold on.
What is this? Paperwork?
I've come here
to get my dick sucked.
I didn't come here to sign forms."
It's hilarious.
You don't pay them,
you give them a fucking donation.
I mean, that is so American, isn't it?
Come on.
And then they give you a list and
a little pencil, like in the sushi bar.
You start checking off the
requirements. Whipping, spanking...
Come on, you fucking dirty
shit-cunt whore. Fucking whip me!
- Nipple clamps, coprophilia.
- What's coprophilia?
- When they shit on you.
Shit in your mouth.
You can have it in the mouth
or you can have it over a glass table.
Can you imagine? They fucking
wheel out a glass table and they just...
...shit all over it,
and you're just like:
"You dirty bitch!"
Who the fuck
asks for that fucking misery?
I hope not you.
Yeah, what about me?
Anyway, you know, there's a lot...
I mean, the list is long, mate.
- Infantilism, you've got...
- What's infantilism?
They make you a baby,
give you a bottle.
Put you in diapers, nurse you,
turn you into an infant.
I mean, it's the sickest,
most twisted place you'll ever go.
I mean, they claw your balls.
They'll tie your cock up
with a shoelace...
...stick truncheons up your ass.
It's twisted. It's fucking twisted.
But I'm telling you,
the moment you come...
The moment you come,
you are so sober.
I mean, so fucking sober.
You're like, "What have I just done?
What the fuck have I just done?
I've just paid $275
for some stranger...
...some chick I don't even know,
to, like, whip me...
...and piss on my head."
So where's the upside?
Why do you do it? I don't get it.
Well, on a physical level,
it can be rather pleasurable.
Psychologically... This is without
getting too deep here.
- I think it has a lot to do
with pain and self-flagellation...
...both literally and metaphorically.
I mean, I don't know whether
it's the culture or what...
...but the English, in general,
are very into pain and spanking.
The English? Really?
Yeah, you're always reading
some story in the papers...
...about some judge or vicar
bent over a hooker's knee.
I didn't know the English
were so fucked up.
Mate, the English are very...
...I mean, very fucked up.
Yeah, one sec.
Sweating like a fucking rapist.
Syd.
Come and have a look at the view.
Yeah. It's Mallory,
the girl from the bar. I'll hook you up.
- Come back in.
- Who?
Mallory. The girl from the bar.
- She's hot. I'll hook you up.
- No, no, mate, no.
I'm too... I'm wanked, mate.
I can't be fucking with girls.
So what? So am I.
I've been drinking this piss.
No, I can't, fuck it.
- I can't operate like this.
- Who cares?
- I'm fucking dizzy.
- She'll be in and out.
You help yourself to that,
I'm gonna leave.
- It's been a fucking pleasure.
- Don't leave.
Please don't fucking leave.
Go get a drink, come back.
- No, mate, no.
- Bateman, one fucking drink.
Come right back.
Work Mallory, she's hot.
Fuck you. A drink of what?
What do you want?
Anything. A bottle.
Jack, tequila, whiskey.
You're staying, though, right?
- One fucking drink.
Fine, fine, just don't go anywhere.
You'll fucking thank me.
I haven't had a bump
in like three hours.
Bateman, this is my friend Mallory.
Mallory, this is Bateman.
Hey.
You're the guy from the bar, right?
Mallory, yeah?
Bateman.
Nice to meet you.
- Sorry.
- Excuse me.
- What a clumsy idiot.
- Sorry.
Well, how do you guys
know each other?
A friend of a friend.
What friend?
I don't know, Mallory.
What's with the 20 Questions? Fuck.
Just asking. So, what,
are you leaving or something?
I'm just gonna grab us a drink
and then...
...l'm coming back.
Do you want one?
Sure, I'll have another one.
- I'll see you in a minute.
- Good.
I'll see you in a minute, Syd.
Damn, kid.
So how do you know that guy?
He got this blow. He's not
a dealer, he just knew the guy.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah. Good guy, right?
- Yeah.
- Hey, you don't know if London's here.
Yeah, she got here like a minute ago.
What'd she say?
Does she know I'm here?
No. She didn't say anything.
I can't believe she's leaving tomorrow.
That's just so fucked up to me.
Well, instead of staying here all night,
why don't you go out and talk to her.
- I'm sure she'd love to talk to you.
- I doubt that.
Why wouldn't she wanna talk to you?
You guys in a fight?
A fight? Mallory, she hasn't
called me in two months.
I wasn't invited tonight.
Don't you think it's odd...
...she wouldn't tell me she's moving
across the fucking country?
- She didn't call you?
- No.
- That's fucked up.
- Didn't even leave a message.
- I know that girl better than anybody.
- When's the last time you talked?
- I don't know, two months.
- Really?
- I'm sure she was gonna call you.
- When? I just checked my messages.
- Is she gonna call me from LAX?
- Dude, I don't fucking know. Man.
Fucked up!
Hey, Syd, can I ask you
something personal?
What?
Well...
It's probably... I don't know if it's true,
that's obviously why I'm asking...
...and since we're cool and all,
I just figured... I'm kind of concerned.
But l... Anyway, I kind of heard that...
- What? Something about London?
- I heard... It's probably bullshit.
- But I heard you...
- What, Mallory? Spit it out. Fuck.
Dude, I kind of heard that
you tried to kill yourself.
- What? Who told you that? London?
- No, it wasn't London.
- Who told you that? Who?
- Dude, I don't know.
I don't even remember.
London's the only person
that knew about that.
So any way you heard it,
it's pretty fucked up.
- So, what? It's not true?
- No, it's not fucking true.
Dude, I don't get it.
What the fuck happened then?
You tell me what you heard happened,
then I'll tell you what really happened.
Just after this bump. Hold up.
All right. Okay.
I heard that, like, you guys had a fight
or something, and you broke out...
...she drove to your place,
found you unconscious...
...next to some sleeping pills, and you
had to get your stomach pumped.
Okay, now do you wanna know
what really happened?
Yeah. I mean, that's why I asked.
- You know my dog, Toker?
- Yeah.
- Yes, well, he's epileptic.
- Okay.
- So the vet prescribed phenobarbital.
- Pheno...? What the fuck is that?
They're barbiturates.
They're downers, for his fits.
Wait a minute. Your dog has epilepsy
and got prescribed...?
Let me finish. Anyway...
...it was our two-year anniversary
and she thought I'd forget.
- So...
- Syd, you always forget. Always.
Oh, fuck.
- I feel like such a bitch.
- Well, you are a bitch.
Open it.
- Open it.
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
This is so gorgeous. How did
you know I wanted this dress?
I saw you drooling all over it
last time we were at Valentino.
I love it!
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Thank you so much, baby.
There's more.
- What is that?
- It's a basketball.
What...? Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hi, little guy. Hi, little guy.
Oh, baby.
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
Look at him.
I can't believe you did this. L...
Thank you. Okay. Okay.
Hello?
Hey. Can I just call you back?
No, I'm just
in the middle of something.
All right, bye.
- Who was that?
- It was Mallory.
Look at his paws.
- What? What is it? What's wrong?
- I heard a guy's voice on the phone.
What? Are you fucking crazy?
That was Mallory.
You swear to God?
Yes, I swear to God.
If you don't fucking believe me,
go ahead and call her.
Syd. Are you really gonna
fucking call her?
Yeah, is Mallory there?
This is London's boyfriend.
Who the fuck is this?
London, what the fuck is this?
Who was that? Why did you lie?
- Let me just explain.
- You better fucking explain.
What? Why did you lie?
Are you cheating on me?
No, no. Listen.
I was really fucked up.
I was out with the girls.
- Fucking perfect.
- Are you gonna let me explain?
Yes, yes, you better
fucking explain, London.
Okay, the clubs were closing, we went
back to Becca's boyfriend's loft.
I fucking passed out.
I wake up the next morning...
...and the guy... There was someone
lying in bed next to me.
Then he didn't try anything?
You're fucked up in his bed,
he didn't try anything.
I find that hard to believe.
And don't fucking lie to me.
If you fucking lie to me,
I'm walking out the fucking door.
He tried to kiss me. But there was
nothing because I pushed him away.
- It was not a big deal...
- Define "tried."
I wanna know
every single fucking detail.
Were you on or under the covers?
Was his hand on your tit?
No, Syd. He tries to kiss me
and I pushed him away.
- You pushed him away?
- Yes. I walked outside.
Mallory called me a cab,
and I went home.
If you went home,
why is he calling you?
- How does he have your number?
- I don't know.
Maybe Becca's boyfriend
gave him the number.
But I definitely didn't give it to him.
Nothing happened. I swear to God.
Don't you fucking believe me? Please.
I don't know what to believe.
You swore that was
Mallory on the phone...
...and it wasn't.
So, what the fuck?
We've dated for two years. I believed
everything you said until now.
Now I don't know
what the fuck to believe.
It's like your words are meaningless.
I just don't trust you anymore,
London.
I made a mistake.
I made a fucking huge mistake.
- I'm sorry.
- Lf it was one fucking mistake...
...why did you say
you were gonna call back?
Why would you tell a guy
who you don't know...
...whose number you don't have,
you're gonna call him back?
What the fuck is that?
So I took a couple
of Toker's phenobarbital.
Wait, you took
your dog's medication?
Phenobarbital is phenobarbital.
It doesn't matter if it was for my dog.
People have been taking it
recreationally for years.
Smoke that.
So wait a minute,
what does it do to you?
They make you feel good.
They're like downers.
- Okay.
- Anyway...
...I was pretty drunk
and I took like five or six of them.
- Five or six doggy downers?
- Toker's 50 pounds, he takes two.
- I'm 170, five or six seems pretty good.
- Shit.
The problem is that if you're drunk,
you can fall into a coma...
...if you're not careful.
- You went into a coma?
- What's wrong with you?
- No, I didn't go into a fucking coma.
London came back
to apologize or whatever.
Syd? Syd!
Syd! Somebody, please, help!
It's so fucked up. The fact she's telling
people that makes me so furious.
I would never do that to anyone.
It's just fucking rude.
- They never pumped your stomach?
- No, I went to the hospital.
I took a few coherency tests.
That's it. That's all.
Do you see how reality gets twisted
when little fucking girls gossip?
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, I guess.
- What? Do you not believe me?
- No, of course I believe you, Syd.
That's why I asked. I was concerned.
Makes me so livid
that she's out there...
...telling people this warped version
of what happened.
You know what? Just please don't
go out there telling her I told you this.
That's the last thing you need.
The last thing I'm gonna do
is mention your name.
Well, honestly, if I were you, I wouldn't
even bring the shit up, okay?
It's her last night here.
Focus on something positive.
She don't wanna hear that shit.
Fuck.
What? What's wrong?
I don't know, I don't know.
Because I start sweating
and my heart starts pounding...
...and I feel like my head's spinning
and the world's crashing.
And I get pulled down,
further into, like, the darkest...
...meanest places of my brain,
and I start suffocating.
And you feel like you're dying.
What? What? Say something.
- What would you like me to say?
- Anything. Something. I don't care.
I can't be your crutch, Syd.
Oh, you are such a miserable
fucking human being.
Miserable in what way?
The way that you're sitting there,
taking my fucking money...
...and I'm dying. Nothing you do
helps me. The Prozac doesn't help.
The lithium doesn't help. The Zoloft
doesn't help. Nothing you do helps.
You're kind of a fucking asshole.
I just wanna fucking
turn the pain off, you know?
Just give me something that
the pain can go away with, you know?
Can you do that? Don?
I think you're doing great.
When that anxiety hits,
it's terrifying...
...because you're like,
"Maybe I'm really going crazy.
Maybe I've finally
fucked with my head enough...
...that I just detached from reality."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org