Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
On the other side of the cosmos
in deep space
a parallel universe was born
Vic 's W orl
It wasjoyful It was full ofjoy
Vic 's W orl was
goddamn fucking full ofjoy
Things changed
Vic 's W orl now
No cops no laws no morallty
No order no meaning
-How are you, Red?
-I,m OK , Ben .
-Vic is getting out.
-OIh, yeaIh.
He wanted me
to personaIIy tIhank you
for. IheIping to keep
tIhe RougIh-House running smootIhIy
wIhiIe Ihe was gone.
W eII, it,s my pIeasure .
And Vic aIso wants you to know,
tIhat as far. as Ihe,s concerned,
tIhe entire JuIes FIamingo tIhing
is over
CIean sIate.
So consider. yourseIf
back on tIhe payroII.
Y ou know, I judge a man ,s Iife
by tIhe way Ihe dies.
Y our. Iife is a mess, Red.
How are you, Mickey?
Vic is getting out.
And Ihe wanted me
to personaIIy tIhank you
for. keeping Ihis girl company
wIhiIe Ihe was gone.
My pIeasure .
He tIhougIht it was reaIIy
considerate of you. He did.
OnIy troubIe is,
nobody knows wIhere Grace Everly is.
So tIhey can give Iher. tIhe good news
about Vic getting out.
Mickey, wIhere ,s Grace?
Mickey, wIhere is Grace?
I tucked Iher. away in a nice, safe spot.
Y ou know, it,s a pity
you didn ,t stick to just tucking.
OtIherwise you wouIdn ,t be in tIhis jam .
Consider. tIhis tIhe coup de grace.
Ben , you,re not gonna kiII me.
You don ,t Ihave tIhe baIIs.
I don ,t Ihave tIhe baIIs?
Did you Ihear. tIhat, SIeepy Joe?
I don ,t Ihave tIhe baIIs.
I,m ,,Brass BaIIs,, Ben London .
I,ve got baIIs of brass.
Brass baIIs Ihas Ben .
I,II kiII anybody I want to kiII.
Just ask Red.
OIh no, Vic wanted Red dead.
Vic doesn ,t want me dead,
tiII Grace is found.
And your. baIIs beIong to Vic.
I,m IhoIding aII tIhe cards, Ben .
I,m IhoIding Grace.
He,s got a Grace in tIhe IhoIe.
Rita.
HeIIo, Mickey.
Long time, no see, sweetie.
TIhis is strictIy business, HoIIiday.
Y ou,re working tonigIht,
if you,re in tIhe mood.
My boss is waiting.
-FIamingo,s outside?
-SIhooting matcIh is on .
OK , bye.
-Hi, HoIIiday. Good to see you again .
-Doctor
Y ou want some cIhampagne?
A sip.
Y ou know Red, don ,t you?
W e discovered Ihim sitting tIhere
wIhen we got in .
To Iife.
Vic is getting out.
And Vic is gonna want you dead.
No, Vic,s gonna want you dead.
Ask Red.
Let,s face it. It,s mad dog time.
Y ou know Ihow Ihis brain works.
He,s trigger. Ihappy.
He,II want me dead, you dead,
Grace dead, everybody dead.
He,II want you dead first. I just tried
to get my mitts into Ihis business.
But wIhere you put your. mitts
couId get a feIIa kiIIed quicker
Not as Iong as I know wIhere Grace is
and Ihe doesn ,t.
So tIhe gent from back east Ihas arrived?
Lee Turner
He,s at tIhe ,D,
witIh tIhat conniving manager. of Ihis.
Odds are stiII running 8 to 5.
Good evening, JuIes.
Mickey, weIcome.
GabrieIIa.
-Good Iuck.
-Sweetie.
-K nock ,em dead.
-W atcIh tIhis.
-Jake.
-FIamingo.
Hi, Lee.
Fuck you.
-I,ve Iheard nice tIhings about you.
-I don ,t give a fIying fuck.
If tIhere ,s anytIhing I can do to make
your. stay in town more comfortabIe,
pIease don ,t Ihesitate to ask.
I,m gonna bIow your. fucking brains out,
HoIIiday.
SIhow me.
Y ou gotta Iook at tIhis tIhing
pIhiIosopIhicaIIy.
Y ou saved on buIIets again .
Y eaIh, you are tIhe cIhamp.
It,s over. between Grace and me.
Rita.
Nice work , HoIIiday.
I Iost a bundIe tonigIht.
TIhere ,s onIy one in your. Ieague now.
Anew feIIow. FaIco.
Heard of Ihim ? NicIhoIas FaIco?
TaIk to me again next year
But cIear. it witIh JuIes first.
I Ihear. you may not be aIive next week.
I Ihear. Vic,s getting out.
FIamingo just toId me.
-Rita, you Iook IoveIy tonigIht.
-Jake, you can stick it up your. ass.
I missed you.
SIhow me.
TIhis is tIhe best way
for. Grace and me to pIay it.
I wanna see Iher.
coming out of tIhis aIive.
I owe Iher, in fact.
Fine. And do you Ihave a pIan
on Ihow to pIay it witIh Vic?
W eII, I won ,t know Ihow to pIay it
witIh Ihim untiI I see Ihim .
OK .
I,II be at La Difference untiI 2:30.
JuIes Iikes me to cIose up.
If you want me to feed you,
get tIhere before midnigIht.
-TIhat,s wIhen I sIhut down tIhe kitcIhen .
-OK .
Lee Turner
WIhat a fraud our. paI turned out to be.
But gentIemen , I Ihave great news.
Vic,s getting out.
Now everyone is gonna
get in everybody,s way.
How do you see tIhis going down ?
Vic naiIs Ben . Vic naiIs HoIIiday.
We naiI Vic.
-Vic naiIs Ben ?
-Ben ,s baIIs are getting too big.
Vic wiII straigIhten tIhat out
fast enougIh.
I Iook forward to seeing Ben dead.
I Iook forward to seeing Vic dead.
And I especiaIIy Iook forward
to seeing Mickey HoIIiday dead.
It won ,t be Iong before tIhis pIace
is wide open for. us.
Vic,s getting out of
tIhe funny farm tomorrow.
Vic, Vic...
...is dead.
Y ou wisIh Ihe was dead.
W Ihen I teII you wIhat Ihe toId me,
you,II wisIh tIhat you were dead.
Anyway...
W Ihen Vic cIhecked into tIhat cIinic
a wIhiIe ago, I tIhougIht:
He,s gonna Ihave a nervous breakdown ,
no big deaI.
But Vic is sick, Mick.
Vic is a sick prick, Mick.
Vic is a paranoid scIhizopIhrenic.
W Iho wouId Ihave tIhougIht it?
Our. Vic, a paranoid scIhizopIhrenic.
And I tIhougIht Ihe was just a putz.
Vic toId me,
tIhat God speaks to Ihim
aII day and aII nigIht.
He can ,t get a good nigIht,s sIeep
because God won ,t stop yakking.
And Ihere ,s tIhe bombsIheII, Mick.
Vic does not want you dead anymore .
But God does.
At Ieast, tIhat,s wIhat Vic cIaims.
So, you,re off tIhe Ihook witIh Vic.
But you,re in deep sIhit witIh God.
TIhere are Iong periods of time
wIhen Vic Ioses contact witIh reaIity.
TIhat means Ihe couId kiII you
and not even reaIize it.
I tIhink you sIhouId teII Ihim
tIhat Ihe Ihas kiIIed you aIready.
And Ihope tIhat Ihe beIieves you.
Hey, Ben . Do you want a drink?
TIhe onIy otIher. tIhing is
Ihis personaIity. No Ionger. integrated.
In fact, Ihis personaIity Ihas spIit
into severaI distinct personaIities.
W IhicIh is wIhy I tracked you down .
To Iet you know tIhat Ihis personaIities
are getting out tomorrow.
TIhe cIinic can ,t Iet tIhem aII out
togetIher. T Ihat,s too dangerous.
But aII of Vic sIhouId be regrouped
by tomorrow evening.
So, wIhy don ,t you
drop by tIhe RougIh-House
and weIcome tIhem aII back Ihome?
Hey, I migIht.
I Ihear. tIhat you,re banging Rita again .
Rita Everly.
Grace Everly.
TIhey,re some women , Mick.
TIhose Everly sisters .
How is Grace IhandIing aII tIhis stuff
witIh you and Rita?
How is Rita IhandIing you and Grace?
TaIk about sibIing rivaIry .
Y ou,II Ihave to stop banging around.
TIhe tIhing is, if one of Vic,s
personaIities don ,t get you,
one of tIhose Everly sisters wiII.
TIhat is my Big Bang TIheory .
NicIhoIas FaIco.
Have you Iheard anytIhing about Ihim ?
NotIhing I beIieve.
Here ,s tIhe kicker
He Ihas tIhis crazy Iung tIhing.
It,s incurabIe. He wants to make
tIhe most of tIhe time Ihe Ihas Ieft.
Let,s get HoIIiday and FaIco togetIher
QuickIy.
How quickIy?
In Ihonor. of Vic getting out today,
Ihow about five minutes?
Less tIhan a year
TIhe guy is so young.
TIhat,s a tougIh break FaIco got.
He,s onIy in Ihis forties.
I,II teII you fIat out:
Life is Iike tIhat. It,s trigger. Ihappy.
And tIhere but for. tIhe grace of God,
go tIhe four. of us.
Some nitrogIycerin .
For. tIhe angina.
How are you gonna pIay Vic?
You need my IheIp?
Don ,t worry about me.
I aIways Iand on my feet.
Today you,II Iand on tIhe coffee tabIe.
Meet NicIhoIas FaIco.
Take your. time.
Now everytIhing is in order
It,s aII going according to pIan .
Time to send for. Jacky Jackson
and tIhe rest of tIhe boys.
I aIways knew it.
As cIose as tIhey were , I knew
Vic and Mick wouId Iock Ihorns.
It,s tIhe nature of tIhings.
I knew tIhat if I waited,
everytIhing couId be mine.
I waited so Iong knowing wIhat I knew.
K nowing no one eIse knew wIhat I knew.
And I knew tIhat I knew tIhat.
I,m one aII-knowing fucker
TonigIht is tIhe first nigIht
of tIhe rest of my Iife.
Vic 's getting out
of the loony bin tonight
Vic,s car. just puIIed up.
Vic.
W eIIs, Davis, Jake.
-How,s tIhe vagina?
-Angina.
Rita. Vic wiII be in Ihere any second.
W ouId you be my date
at Mickey,s memoriaI service?
I wouIdn ,t be caugIht dead witIh you
at Ihis memoriaI service.
I,m not Iike otIher. guys.
I,m not tricky.
I don ,t Ihave a Grace up my sIeeve.
I understand tIhe tangIed web
of a woman ,s emotions.
OK , boss, I,II see you inside.
W e,II be waiting for. you.
W eIcome back.
TIhank you.
W eIcome Ihome, Vic.
W e Iike to tIhink of it now
as our. Ihome, too.
From me and tIhe boys.
TIhank you.
Can you join us
for. a round of TIhorazine?
TIhorazine. TIhat,s funny.
Y ou,re a funny guy.
-Good to Ihave you Ihome, boss.
-SIeepy Joe.
Y ou gotta stay interested.
TIhat,s my pIhiIosopIhy. I,II IheIp you.
-How are you, Vic?
-Good. Y ou?
-I,m good, too.
-Good.
-Send a tIhank you note to Jake Parker
-OK , Vic.
Mickey HoIIiday.
HeIIo, Mickey.
GabrieIIa, pIease stay.
-Care for. a drink?
-No, tIhanks.
-SometIhing to eat?
-No tIhanks, Vic.
Are you back witIh Rita? Or. are you
just waiting to see Ihow I pIay it?
-Y eaIh, I,m back witIh Rita.
-And?
It,s over, Grace caIIed it quits.
-Any interest in seeing me?
-W eII, sIhe,s scared.
W Ihat Ihave you Iheard
about my situation ?
I don ,t pay mucIh attention
to wIhat I Ihear. secondIhand.
TIhere ,s no reason to get Iong-winded
or. fancy about tIhis.
I,m a Ioony.
CIinicaIIy.
But we tIhink we found some ways
to keep it under. controI.
TeII Iher. it was tIhe cIhemistry
tIhat made it impossibIe to be witIh me.
TeII Iher.
tIhat I,m sorry about certain tIhings.
I,II teII Iher
So...
-How do you read Jake Parker
-He smeIIs weakness.
He,s gonna move in on tIhat
unIess you do sometIhing.
-W Ihy don ,t you do sometIhing about it?
-OK .
And soon . Before tIhey reaIIy dig in .
W Ihen did Ihe sIhow up
witIh Davis and W eIIs?
TonigIht was tIhe first time
I,ve seen tIhem togetIher
-He must be crazy to come after. me.
-Jacky Jackson is tIhe craziest.
Don ,t Iet Jake get Ihis crew in town .
Don ,t wait untiI it gets too crazy
for. you to IhandIe.
HoIIiday caIIs aII tIhe sIhots
on Jake Parker
-No probIem .
-God...
Ben ?
-Understand?
-Fuck tIhat, Vic.
-TIhat,s Ihow it,s gotta be. My way.
-OIh, no.
-Y eaIh, my way.
Y eaIh.
OK .
Be nice to Ben ,
but if Ihe gives you any troubIe...
...sIhoot Ihim .
AII rigIht.
TIhere but for. tIhe grace
of Vic and Mick, go you.
CIean up tIhe craziness for. me, Mickey.
Get tIhe baIance back.
And I want Grace coming tIhrougIh tIhis
in one piece.
K eep Iher. out of sigIht
untiI tIhings are back to normaI.
More buIIsIhit.
-Consider. yourseIf on tIhe payroII.
-Consider. tIhis a freebie.
But nobody Iays a finger.
on JuIes FIamingo.
Y ou,II Ihave to excuse me.
Lot of running around to do tonigIht.
I,ve been away from tIhe sIhooting matcIh
for. too Iong.
Is sIhe stiII pregnant?
Y eaIh.
I,m giving a Ihomecoming party
for. myseIf tomorrow.
Y ou,re aII invited.
Hi, HoIIiday.
Can ,t say I,m tickIed to see you aIive,
but I Ihad a contingency pIan .
How about FaIco and you at tIhe ,D,
in IhaIf an Ihour? Just for. fun .
-I toId you, taIk to me in a year
-Y ou,II be tIhere .
FaIco kiIIed JuIes FIamingo.
I,ve Iheard a Iot about NicIhoIas FaIco
over. tIhe Iast few days.
He,s quick on tIhe trigger
Very quick.
Quicker. tIhan Mick.
Nick,s quicker. tIhan Mick
and Mick isn ,t as quick as Nick.
I pick Nick over. Mick,
wIhicIh is not so good for. Vic.
Is Grace pregnant by Mick or. Vic?
Mick, if you are tIhe daddy,
can we seII tickets
for. wIhen you teII Rita?
Be at tIhe ,D, in 20 minutes.
-Pregnant? W Iho is tIhe...?
-Vic,s tIhe fatIher
I can ,t expIain tIhis
witIhout expIaining aII of it.
And you,re kind of toucIhy wIhen
it comes to stuff about your. sister
-I figured tIhis was tIhe best way.
-For. you, maybe. Not for. me.
I tIhougIht tIhis time around
maybe we wouIdn ,t buIIsIhit eacIh otIher
W Ihat eIse are you IhoIding back?
Jake said
that Falco killed Jules Flamingo
HoIIiday?
TIhis is NicIhoIas FaIco.
TIhanks to Ihim ,
I,m now using JuIes as a giant coaster
PIease, sit down .
-So, wIho you got coming?
-Ben London .
Y ou and Ben sIhouId reaIIy Ihit it off.
-Just a feeIing.
-FaIco and I worked up a pIan .
Y ou wanna Ihear. Ihow you,re gonna die?
First I,m gonna sIhoot you
in tIhe stomacIh.
TIhen I,m gonna sIhatter. your. sIhin bones.
TIhat,s so you don ,t go nowIhere .
TIhat,s tIhe first part .
Second part , Jake and me are gonna
sit back and Ihave a drink,
and watcIh you die reaI sIow.
And wIhen you,re aImost dead...
...I,m gonna bIow
your. fucking brains out.
I see.
NicIhoIas...
Geez, wIhat,s tIhat second part
of tIhe first part ?
I don ,t get it. Y ou,re pIugging me
in tIhe beIIy,
but tIhen you,re gonna waste
two more sIhots
witIh tIhis
sIhattering of tIhe sIhin sIhit?
W ouIdn ,t it be better. to bury
a buncIh of buIIets in my beIIy,
skip tIhe second part of tIhe first part ,
go into tIhe first of tIhe second part ,
you know, tIhe bit witIh tIhe booze,
and tIhen tIhe bIowing out
of tIhe brains buIIsIhit.
To be Ihonest witIh you,
it just seems so IhigIhfaIutin for. me.
My way is simpIer. I sIhoot you
in tIhe foreIhead and go Ihome.
Sorry I,m Iate.
Hey, Nick. I,m Ben .
I Ihear. you don ,t Ihave to do
any CIhristmas sIhopping next year
I Ihear. you got a date
witIh Jimmy tIhe Grave Digger
TIhe world is an ungracious pIace.
Y ou gotta Iook at it in a positive way.
We,re aII gonna die.
Y ou gotta Iook at it Iike
you,re beating us to tIhe finisIh Iine.
Y ou are coming first in deatIh.
Y ou know wIhat my pIhiIosopIhy of Iife is?
Nobody knows beans, but Ben .
It,s kinda Zen .
Zen by way of Ben . Ben Zen .
I,m a practicing Ben BuddIhist.
In certain circIes I,m known
as ,,Bubba,, Ben London .
Y ou,re not so Ihot
on tIhe cIhit-cIhat, Nick.
Is Ihe aIready dead?
I tIhink Ihe,s dead,
but witIh Ihim it,s kinda Ihard to teII.
AII tIhose stories.
TIhis guy was a big, fat notIhing.
W Ihat do you figure is better.
over. tIhe Iong IhauI?
Cunning or. baIIs?
A IheaItIhy mix.
Jake was cunning,
but outfoxed IhimseIf.
In my opinion ,
Ihe Ihad a reaIIy crappy Grand Design .
Angina. TIhere ,s notIhing wrong
witIh tIhis guy,s Iheart .
NitrogIycerin , my ass.
TIhese are Tic Tacs.
W Ihat are we gonna teII W eIIs and Davis?
TIhat Ihe died of bad breatIh?
OIh yeaIh, tIhat,s ,,W acky,, Jacky Jackson .
It,s about time tIhe rest of Jake,s crew
came out of tIhe woodwork .
Let me fuck witIh tIhem for. a wIhiIe.
HeIIo, boys.
Tic Tac, anybody?
Jake,s dead.
Died of cirrhosis IhaIitosis.
Sit down .
Not now. TIhose two guys
got too many paIs Ihere .
W e,II do it...
...tomorrow.
Tomorrow at Vic,s party.
GottIieb and Ihis gravedigger. want you.
Everybody wilNbe at Vic 's party
It's gonna be mad dog time
Do you tIhink
Vic wants Grace dead, Mickey?
TIhat,s a tougIh one to caII.
But I gotta stick around to find out.
I...
Y ou know, I went dead inside
a wIhiIe back
and sIhe IheIped puII me out of it.
So, I owe Iher
Before Grace disappeared,
sIhe said sIhe was stiII nuts for. Vic.
SIhe wants to get back togetIher. witIh Ihim
if everytIhing is rigIht witIh Ihis Ihead.
I promised I wouIdn ,t kiII Ihim
unIess Ihe backed me into a corner
Are you torcIhing for. Iher, Mickey?
No.
If you,re buIIsIhitting me
about any of it,
I,II sIit your. tIhroat
from ear. to ear
Come Ihere .
TIhat,s Jake,s RSVP to Vic,s party.
I,m gonna go get you sometIhing to eat.
Don ,t dawdIe, Mickey.
Mickey.
I...
I tIhougIht you sIhouId know:
SIeepy Joe got Ihis Ihead
fuII of IhoIes Iast nigIht.
He got Ihis brains bIown out.
In fact, Ihe,s dead.
Y ou don ,t know tIhe size
of someone,s brain ,
untiI you,ve swept it up
off tIhe carpet.
Let me teII you,
SIeepy Joe Ihad quite a brain .
Let,s face it, Mick.
Vic didn ,t beIieve you Iast nigIht.
Tic Tac?
TIhank you, Ben London .
Rita, Ihow are you?
Are you coming to Vic,s party?
It,s gonna be some wing-ding.
Be sure to bring Mick,s
dentaI cIharts for. identification .
TonigIht we,II get to see
eacIh otIher' s cards.
And tIhe way I figure it is tIhis:
Mick is bIuffing.
Vic isn ,t pIaying witIh a fuII deck.
And I get to take Ihome
tIhe wIhoIe kitty, Rita.
See you at Vic,s party tonigIht.
Rita.
-GIad you made it. Y ou Iook beautifuI.
-TIhanks, Vic.
Ladies and gentIemen . FoIks.
And Vic.
I cooked up a IittIe sometIhing.
It,s kind of my way of saying:
,,W eIcome Ihome, Vic.,,
Ladies and gentIemen ,
Mr. Danny Marks!
Take it away.
Vic, tIhis is for. you.
And now, tIhe end is near.
And so I face tIhe finaI curtain
My friends
I,II say it cIear.
I,II state my case
Of wIhicIh I,m certain
He Iived a Iife tIhat,s fuII
He traveIed eacIh
And every IhigIhway
But more , mucIh more tIhan tIhis
Vic did it Vic,s way
He did it Ihis way
Regrets, Ihe Ihad a few
-Introducing Grace to Mickey. K idding.
-But tIhen again
Too few to mention
He did wIhat Ihe Ihad to do
And Ihe saw it tIhrougIh
W itIhout exemption
-Y ou,re a paranoid scIhizopIhrenic, Vic.
-He pIanned
EacIh cIhartered course
EacIh carefuI step aIong tIhe byway
But more , mucIh more tIhan tIhis
Vic,s gonna do it Ben ,s way
He did it Ihis way
-He Ioved
-Not IateIy.
He IaugIhed, Ihe cried
He,s Ihad Ihis fiII, Ihis sIhare of Iosing
A Iot of tIhat IateIy.
But now, as tears subside
He finds it aII so amusing
Danny, is Ihe finding it amusing?
To tIhink Ihe did aII tIhat
And may I say
Not in a sIhy way
OIh, no
OIh no, not me
Ben did it Ben ,s way
For. wIhat is a man ?
WIhat Ihas Ihe got?
If not IhimseIf
TIhen Ihe Ihas not
To say tIhe tIhings
He truIy feeIs
And not tIhe words of one wIho kneeIs
TIhe record sIhows
I took tIhe bIows
And did it my way
Y eaIh!
OIh, yeaIh.
Danny, you,re tIhrougIh in sIhow business.
TIhis is tIhe Iast time
I ever. sIhare a stage witIh anyone.
From now on , I,m doing a singIe.
I tIhougIht it was impossibIe,
but you reaIIy brougIht
sometIhing fresIh to tIhat song.
For. my money,
tIhis is tIhe definitive version .
Is tIhat you taIking, Vic?
Or. is it tIhe medication ?
TIhank you aII for. coming.
Rita, nice of you to drop by.
HoIIiday...
Y ou stay.
Vic, I Iike Ihow you IhandIed tIhat.
Very nice.
Y ou certainIy Ihad grace under. pressure .
PersonaIIy I prefer. Grace under. me.
Vic, wIhat wouId you say is best
over. tIhe Iong IhauI?
BaIIs or. grace?
A IheaItIhy mix.
I tIhink too mucIh grace makes you Ioony.
It triggers craziness.
TIhink of tIhe craziness
your. craziness Ihas triggered.
Y our. girlfriend Ieft you.
Mick Ihooked up witIh Iher
Y ou got more crazy.
TIhat made me concIude
tIhat you don ,t know sIhit.
Ben , go Ihome.
Pack your. bags and Ieave town .
First of aII,
nobody teIIs me wIhat to do.
Ben , Ihop Ihome, pack your. bags
and Ieave town .
I,II Ihop Ihome
wIhen I,m fucking good and ready.
I judge a man by tIhe way Ihe dies.
Y our. Iife was one note.
Ben , you can ,t sIhoot any better.
tIhan you can sing.
Now put tIhe gun away, roII Ihome,
pack your. bags and Ieave town .
I am ,,Bubba,, Ben London .
Mickey, don ,t you get it yet?
Vic is using you to cIean up
tIhe craziness and tIhen
Ihe,s gonna cIean you up.
EverytIhing under. controI?
W Iho tIhe IheII are you?
NicIhoIas FaIco.
Mickey, didn ,t we kiII Ihim aIready?
TIhe reaI NicIhoIas FaIco.
TIhere ,s never. been anybody Iike Ihim .
Best trigger. man I,ve ever. seen .
Bar. none.
Y ou mean ...
...we kiIIed...
...a pIhony FaIco?
W e kiIIed a pseudo Nick?
Y ou mean Jake puIIed a Nick trick?
It,s aII reIated.
AII oneness.
Mick...
...Vic...
...Nick.
Life is beautifuI.
BrutaI.
MysticaI.
Cockamamie.
I am ,,Brass BaIIs,, Ben London .
OIh, wIhat a pair. of baIIs Ihad I.
Y ou got a coupIe of minutes?
I wanna sIhow you sometIhing.
-GabrieIIa.
-Mickey. Meet Nicky.
Mick, take a Iook at my new cIhairs .
-OIh, nice.
-I picked tIhem up today.
ReaIIy?
Very , very reIaxing.
-RigIht, Nick?
-HeII, yeaIh.
Y ou gotta sit down in one of tIhese
to appreciate it.
Come on , take a Ioad off.
W Ihat,s aII tIhis?
OIh yeaIh, it,s comfy.
Comfy?
TIhat,s wIhat W eIIs and Davis said.
-TIhey were Ihere ?
-Y eaIh, tonigIht.
-TonigIht?
-Y eaIh.
I asked NicIhoIas
to sIhow tIhem my new furniture .
TIhey fIipped.
W eII, sure .
It,s good quaIity mercIhandise.
-I suppose you Iheard tIhat NicIhoIas...
-OIh, Vic.
I never. pay attention
to wIhat I just Ihear
W eII, anyway.
NicIhoIas is fit as a fiddIe.
He,II be working witIh me
for. a Iong time.
Maybe so.
One.
Two.
TIhree.
Are we gonna tIhrow tIhe guns
at eacIh otIher
SIhow me.
Vic. Grace wants to see you, Vic.
TIhis buIIet dropping sIhit.
TIhat,s fun stuff.
Hey, Mickey.
I couId be way off on tIhis,
but I tIhink I spotted your. weakness.
Y es, yes.
I couId be wrong, but...
Jackson . ,,W acky,, Jacky.
SIhouId I run down
and pick up tIhose buIIets?
-Hi, Mickey.
-I couId kick myseIf.
Hi, Mickey.
W Ihat Ihappened to Ben ?
He was reIhearsing a one-man sIhow.
It cIosed.
TIhat,s too bad. I Iiked Ben .
He Ihad a fresIh breatIh.
Vic, I Ihear. you,re Ihaving
a IoIIapaIooza of a depression .
I Ihear. you,re feeIing bIue.
I Ihear. tIhat you,re Ihaving a,
Ihow do you caII it...a bad day.
TIhat couId Iast tIhe rest of your. Iife.
-W anna Ihear. my pIhiIosopIhy of Iife?
-I reaIIy wouId.
I,d Iike notIhing better
but Mickey and I are very busy.
-W ouId you Iike to recommend tIhe book?
-It,s too sIhort to be in a book.
I tIhink pIhiIosopIhies sIhouId be sIhort .
My pIhiIosopIhy is:
I don ,t give a fuck.
-TIhat,s a IittIe over. my Ihead.
-Doesn ,t botIher. me.
Because I don ,t give a fuck.
W Ihen it comes to not giving a fuck,
you guys are just dabbIers .
Have you ever. Iheard of a guy
named NicIhoIas FaIco?
Can we taIk a minute?
Maybe Ihe sIhouId Ihave given a fuck.
A sIhort pIhiIosopIhy
isn ,t necessariIy tIhe best.
Sometimes it pays
to sIhop around for. one.
I tIhink tIhey Iocked
into tIheir. pIhiIosopIhy too quick.
An Eastern pIhiIosopIhy
wouId Ihave been good for. tIhem .
I don ,t know. Jackson is not tIhe type
to searcIh for. IhimseIf.
So...
W Ihat do you tIhink of tIhe new gent?
FaIco? He,s a Ihumdinger
He,s so quirky and interesting.
I Iove tIhose sungIasses.
I Iove tIhe way Ihe Ieft tIhe gun beIhind.
TIhat was good.
And tIhat voice. Spooky.
Spooky voice.
I,d say very good.
Maybe I finaIIy found
someone better. tIhan you.
W eII, Vic...
...you found somebody quicker, but...
...pretty soon you won ,t Ihave
anyone to taIk to but Ihim .
Everyone eIse wiII be in GottIieb,s
Mortuary witIh Jimmy tIhe Grave Digger
TIhen you,II be
taIking to yourseIf again .
-Did you teII Grace everytIhing I said?
-Y eaIh.
-About tIhe imbaIance triggering tIhe...
-And tIhat I was sorry about...
-Y eaIh.
Y ou didn ,t teII Iher. anytIhing, did you?
No, I didn ,t.
Because I don ,t know wIhere sIhe is.
SIhe disappeared.
OK ...
OIh, so I got a message.
MidnigIht tomorrow at Grace,s office.
But I,m not sure it was from Iher
RougIh nigIht, IhuIh?
It,s about to get rougIher
-I may need you tomorrow nigIht.
-OK .
Vic may Ihave Iocated Grace.
It,s aII coming to a Ihead.
Mickey?
Let,s try and make it work
between us tIhis time, pIease.
Come Ihere .
W Ihat,s your. pIhiIosopIhy of Iife?
LaugIhs.
LaugIhs are deep in your. bIood too, Vic.
TIhere ,s a Iot to IaugIhter. as an eIixir
It,s a IheaIer, Y ou feeI bIue, rigIht?
I,m feeIing down , but...
I,m better
I Ihope we don ,t crasIh.
Don ,t you, Vic?
W anna Ihear. my fucking pIhiIosopIhy?
To IheII witIh goddamn everytIhing.
Y ou gotta teII me
if Grace sIhows tomorrow nigIht.
Do you wanna kiII Iher
or. do you want me to kiII Iher
It,s time to make arrangements witIh
GottIieb and Jimmy tIhe Grave Digger
It 's goddamn time
I,m gonna need you Iater. tonigIht.
Sweetie.
Vic,s getting out today?
Grace, Vic got out two days ago.
He wasn ,t ready for. you. I,m stiII
not sure if Ihe,s ready, but...
...if you wanna take a cIhance...
He says Ihe Ihas sometIhing
for. tIhe baIance.
And to keep tIhings under. controI.
Now, tIhat may be true,
but it may not be true.
In wIhicIh case,
Ihe,II be dancing on our. graves.
I,ve been seeing Rita
over. tIhe Iast few nigIhts.
Y ou,ve been seeing Rita at nigIht,
and me in tIhe day?
Y es.
Rita is gonna kiII you. OIh, yeaIh.
Do you Ihave a deatIh wisIh?
I know.
How Iong did you tIhink
you,d get away witIh tIhis?
I was Ihoping forever
A IittIe Iheaven on eartIh.
Y es.
-I,m gonna miss you, Mickey.
-SweetIheart .
-Do you Ihave a pIan for. tonigIht?
-Y eaIh.
Do you tIhink Vic,s got a pIan ?
Y eaIh.
GottIieb.
HeIIo.
Hey, Vic.
Jimmy tIhe Grave Digger.
is rigIht on time.
Come on .
SeII me your. motIherfucking Iheart .
It,s dead.
How are you, Vic?
Better
Nick FaIco. Grace Everly.
-I,ve Iheard a Iot about you.
-TIhank you.
Vic gave me tIhe wIhoIe works.
He,s crazy about me.
-I toId Mick to teII you some tIhings.
-He toId me.
HeIIo, Rita.
HeIIo, Grace.
-Rita Everly, Nick FaIco.
-I,ve Iheard a Iot about you.
Let,s get everytIhing out in tIhe open .
It,s IheaItIhier
Vic, you want to kiII Mickey.
And you wanna kiII me too.
Rita, it,s been so Iong, you probabIy
forgot wIhy you wanna kiII me.
So I,m gonna give you
some fresIh reasons.
I owe Mickey a Iot.
I kinda went dead inside a wIhiIe ago,
and Ihe IheIped puII me out of it.
-BuIIsIhitter
-He was witIh you tIhe past four. nigIhts.
But you don ,t know tIhat
Ihe,s been witIh me tIhese Iast four. days.
One more tIhing, Rita.
Mickey,s crazy about you.
Do you know wIhat I wisIh?
I wisIh tIhe two of you wouId go dead.
On tIhe outside, goddamn it.
TIhis trutIh sIhit is fun .
Anyone eIse Ihave sometIhing to sIhare ?
How am I doing, Mickey?
Vic, I,m nuts for. you.
And I,m gonna Ihave your. cIhiId.
I want us back togetIher
W e,re kind of a IheaItIhy mix.
Y ou tIhink about tIhat.
I know it,s your. favorite game.
Mickey, I,m quicker. tIhan you.
Y eaIh, I know, but...
...you onIy Ihave one buIIet.
Y ou onIy Ihave one buIIet.
No, I got anotIher. buIIet tucked away.
I tIhink I,ve got
a buIIet tucked away, too.
Y ou see, I,d bet my Iife
tIhat you don ,t Ihave one tucked away.
Bad bet for. you, HoIIiday.
You missed tIhe trutIh.
Vic ain ,t interested.
He doesn ,t want to Iive anymore .
It was triggered
by a goddamn profound ennui.
Not tIhat again .
Since I,ve known Ihim , Ihe,s gone
tIhrougIh tIhat Iike IhaIf a dozen times.
TIhis is tIhe Iast time.
After. I finisIh kiIIing off
you and Grace...
...Vic Ihired me to kiII...
...Vic.
Let me make tIhis reaI simpIe for. you.
First of aII, I,m making a bet.
TIhat Vic is not
going to tIhrow it aII away.
Grace triggered Ihappiness in Ihim once.
I,m betting Ihe,s coming back
for. more , because sIhe is...
...just wIhat tIhe doctor. ordered.
But no matter. Ihow it aII goes down ...
...I tIhink I,m covered.
Mickey, I spotted your. weakness again .
Y ou care .
Mickey, I tIhink
I,m mucIh better. covered tIhan you.
SIhow me.
Y ou son of a bitcIh!
Nobody two-times me two times.
You buIIsIhitting bastard .
I,m gonna sIhoot tIhe sIhit out of you.
You are sucIh a dick, Mick!
I am so sick
of tIhis Vic, Nick, Mick sIhit.
Y ick, yick, yick.
I,m running out of peopIe to kiII me.
Don ,t Iook at me.
I just ran out of buIIets.
Ben wouId Ihave wanted it tIhis way.
But tIhen again , fuck Ben .
Looks Iike it,s gonna be tIhe Iong IhauI.
No miracIe cures.
Do you wanna...
...IheIp me stay interested?
W eIcome Ihome, Vic.
TIhat was some smack you gave me.
Y ou toId me to smack you,
Ieave tIhe purse and storm out.
Y eaIh, weII.
I don ,t recaII teIIing you to storm
back in pointing anotIher. gun
rigIht at my face
and Ihaving a conniption fit.
,,Y ou two-timed me two times.
Vic, Nick, Mick. Y ick, yick.,,
-W Ihat was aII tIhat?
-I made up tIhat part aII by myseIf.
Nice toucIh.
Now, just wIho went dead on tIhe inside
and wIho puIIed wIho out?
SIhe went, I puIIed.
Did you say anytIhing in tIhe Iast
five days tIhat wasn ,t buIIsIhit?
-No, it was aII buIIsIhit.
-OIh, buIIsIhit.
Except for. tIhe part about me
being gIad tIhat we,re back togetIher
BuIIsIhit tIhat wasn ,t buIIsIhit.
OIh baby, come Ihere .
Let,s go Ihome, crack open a IittIe
cIhampagne, Ihave some IaugIhs.
Sounds to me
Iike tIhe perfect way to pIay it.
SubtitIes: Broadcast Text InternationaI
www.broadcasttext .com
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org