Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Bull's-eye!
-You bet, Dad!
You go straight home.
Bombs away!
Sayonara, sucker!
No preservatives, just pure water!
Cool, clear water.
Step up, schmuck, get some dealing done.
H20, that's my go.
Don't you understand? This is water.
You can't live without it.
What's a little fallout, huh?
You get a sack of grain
...or a woman for 2 hours.
What are you trading?
-I'm looking for someone.
Are you trading or not?
He had a team of camels.
People come here to trade, make a little
profit, do a little business.
If you've nothing to trade,
you've no business here.
An hour inside.
Next!
I got skills I can trade.
Sorry. The brothel's full.
One hour.
And if you find him?
-I'll ask him to return what's mine.
And he'll be desperate
to clear his conscience.
He will be.
You that good?
Perhaps
you have something to trade after all.
Keep talking.
24 hours of your life.
In return,
you'll get back what was stolen.
Sounds like a bargain.
It's not. Let's talk. Come inside.
Leave your weapons here. It's the law.
Remember, this is the vehicle
that sent Detroit broke.
Where did you get these animals?
The glorious dromedary.
The ship of the desert.
They got independent suspension power
steering and no emission control.
Ride them away now.
A warrior, Aunty.
Lost everything. Looking for a deal.
But he's just a raggedy man.
He's quick.
Ironbar...
...can he do it?
Maybe.
What did you do before this?
I was a cop, a driver.
But how the world turns.
One day cock of the walk,
next, a feather duster.
Play something tragic, Ton Ton.
Do you know who I was?
Nobody.
Except on the day after,
I was still alive.
This nobody had a chance
to be somebody.
So much for history. Anyway...
Water? Fruit?
Congratulations. You're the first
to survive the audition.
Drink.
It's okay.
Come with me.
Look around. All this I built.
Up to my armpits in blood and shit.
Where there was desert,
now there's a town.
Where there was robbery, there's trade.
Where there was despair,
now there's hope.
It's civilization.
I'll do anything to protect it.
Today it's necessary to kill a man.
What do you say?
What do you pay?
I'll re-equip you... vehicles, animals.
Fuel, if you want.
It's a generous offer.
Why me? You've got warriors, weapons.
Give the order.
We are dealing with subtleties here.
This is no enemy. It's almost family.
I see, real civilized.
The reasons don't concern you,
just the conditions. Deal?
First, no one knows you're working
for Aunty.
You hit him, you go.
Second, it's a fair fight.
And third, it's to the death.
Who's the bunny?
We call it Underworld.
It's where Bartertown gets its energy.
Oil, natural gas?
Pigs.
Pigs like those?
Bullshit.
-Pigshit.
Pigshit.
The lights, the motors, the vehicles...
...all run by a high-powered gas
called methane.
Methane comes from pigshit.
Have a look. Tell me what you see.
I see a big guy
giving a little guy a piggy back.
MasterBlaster. They're a unit.
They even share the same name.
The little one is called Master.
He's the brains.
He runs Underworld.
The other one is Blaster.
He's the muscle.
Together they can be very powerful.
They are also arrogant.
We want to keep the brain,
dump the body.
He's big. Is he good?
He can beat most men with his breath.
I want a closer look at him.
How do I get in there?
It's a factory. Ask for work.
-I know nothing about methane.
You can shovel shit, can't you?
Hey, you!
Let's talk!
Here, free man, come help a convict.
You don't want to end up like me.
How long are you in for?
The big one. Life.
For killing a pig?
I had to feed the kids.
Doesn't worry me. Down here
life's two, three years.
Where is that bum mechanic Blackfinger?
We got a real problem.
Twelve pounds of dynamite set to blow.
You expert! Disarm!
It's a class Job. One mistake,
it'll blow the crap out of this place.
Literally.
Think what to do!
Now... the dynamite is connected
to the timing device...
...which is connected to the switch,
which I can't find...
...which is connected to the...
...battery.
I'll disconnect the battery!
I wouldn't do that.
Who you?
Me Max.
You smart.
That's my vehicle.
Disarm!
How much?
No trade. Do!
Fetch!
Me order. Me Master!
Me run Bartertown!
That's why you live in shit.
Not shit! Energy!
Call it what you like,
it still smells like shit.
Not shit! Energy!
No energy, no town!
Me King Arab!
Sure. Me, fairy princess.
Embargo, on!
Embargo on! Main valve off!
4, 3, 2...
For God's sake, what now?
Who run Bartertown?
Damn it!
I told you, no more embargos.
More, Blaster.
Who run Bartertown?
You know who.
Say.
MasterBlaster.
Say loud.
MasterBlaster what?
MasterBlaster runs Bartertown.
Louder!
Lift embargo.
You want foot in face?
Disarm.
Good boy.
Over here, Blaster.
What are you laying for?
-Nothing.
Who are you?
-Nobody.
No, mister, I can feel it.
The dice are rolling!
I want my camels, my vehicle,
food, water, methane.
Deal.
You said a fair fight.
What does that mean?
As provided by law.
Thunderdome.
Two men, hand to hand.
No jury, no appeal, no parole.
Two men enter, one man leaves.
Weapons?
Anything's possible. Chance decides.
Thunderdome. How do I get in there?
That's easy. Pick a fight.
Everybody have a good time!
That's my vehicle and I want it back!
Hearing wonky.
Sounds like an order.
That's right.
Yumping Yesus! Him sad.
Brain broken.
Me explain.
This my vehicle. You...
...pedestrian!
Three seconds...
...break neck. One...
MasterBlaster!
Listen to the law!
Aunty, two men in dispute.
These our witness, Aunty.
Us suffer bad. Us want justice.
We want Thunderdome!
You know the law.
Two men enter one man leaves.
This Blaster.
Twenty men enter, only him leave.
Then it's your choice. Thunderdome.
Aunty! Aunty!
Welcome to another edition
of Thunderdome!
Listen on! Listen on!
This is the truth of it.
Fighting leads to killing,
and killing gets to warring.
And that was damn near
the death of us all.
Look at us now, busted up
and everyone talking about hard rain.
But we've learned by the dust
of them all. Bartertown's learned.
Now when men get to fighting,
it happens here.
And it finishes here.
Two men enter, one man leaves.
And right now, I've got two men.
Two men with a gut full of fear.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls...
...dying time's here!
He's the ball cracker. Death on foot.
You know him. You love him!
He's Blaster!
The challenger,
direct from out of the Wasteland.
He's bad. He's beautiful.
He's crazy!
It's the man with no name!
Thunderdome's simple. Get to the
weapons, use them anyway you can.
I know you won't break the rules.
There aren't any.
Remember where you are.
This is Thunderdome.
Death is listening and will take
the first man that screams.
Prepare!
Two men enter, one man leave!
You know the law!
-This is Thunderdome!
Kill him!
No, no! Look at his face!
He's got the mind of a child.
It's not his fault.
Blaster, I'm sorry.
This wasn't part of the deal.
Deal?!
What do you mean, "deal"?
You must have tasted it.
It was in your hands.
You had it all!
What do you mean, "deal"?
No more methane!
This place... finished!
No, little man.
We've only just begun.
Open it.
Two men enter. One man leave!
What's this?!
Do you think I don't know the law?
Wasn't it me who wrote it?
And this man has broken the law.
Right or wrong, we had a deal.
And the law says,
"Bust a deal, face the wheel."
Bust a deal and face the wheel.
All our lives hang by a thread.
Now we've got a man
waiting for sentence.
But ain't it the truth?
You take your chances with the law.
Justice is only a roll of the dice...
...a flip of the coin,
a turn of the wheel.
Fix It.
You run Bartertown.
You fix.
Not pigs! No!
That's enough!
Do you want to use him or kill him?
Bring him up.
Master, do what Ironbar says.
I will. Yeah, I will.
Savannah!
Finn, look.
It's him. I finded him.
It's Captain Walker.
What's his talk?
-He ain't made wordstuff.
It's a long track.
Maybe he's burned out.
Maybe.
Maybe he's just listening.
Walker? Hello?
Maybe he's talking,
but we ain't hearing.
You see his lips ain't moving.
Not with wordstuff, with sonic.
That ain't never gonna work,
sonic-bonny bullshit!
This is Delta-Fox-X-Ray.
Can you hear me?
Delta-Fox-X-Ray.
Come In.
Is anybody out there?
Can you read me, Walker?
What's up, Doc?
Hey, take me with you!
Can you hear me, Walker?
Fly, Walker!
Who are you?
Quiet!
Shut up!
Enough!
Who are you?
The waiting ones.
Waiting for what?
Waiting for you.
And who am I?
I think he be testing us.
This a testing, Walker?
You reckon we been slack?
I don't know. Maybe you've been slack.
We ain't. We kept it straight.
It's all there.
Everything marked, everything
'membered. You wait, you'll see.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org