Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I'm putting this with your things.
Why?
Because they're yours.
You're my nephew and I love you.
No matter what you've decided.
Good night.
Don't waste time making friends
with him.
We're only here a few days.
We're starting a procedure to
look for a match.
Please, Bob. I'll take this.
We're starting a procedure to
look for a match.
Questions?
How big is the needle?
It's not important that you
understand.
Bob.
Follow me, please.
Are you fixing the door for Ruth?
It's so boring.
There's nothing else to do.
Want to keep me company?
Sure.
It's a Ford, huh?
Would you like to drive?
Are you sure?
Yes
You want me to drive?
It's okay, you can drive.
I'm fast, I'm warning you.
Be careful. Don't go too fast.
You're a natural born driver.
I have an idea where we can go!
Turn here.
Do you know my dad?
I met him once.
Doesn't your mom talk about him?
No.
I know your mom war nuts
about him.
Did you go to the wedding?
No.
I knew I war going to be down
here with Dad and Ruth
so I went back home to sell
the rest of my stuff.
Did they have you over for dinner
No, it wasn't much of a visit.
I just stopped by.
Your dad was asleep,
and Lee didn't want to wake him
so we stood in the hallway
and talked a while.
Your dad was still asleep
when I left.
How'd he seem?
He seemed nice enough.
What?
We ware just down by the water.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Wally called.
He'd like to test the boys next.
Dad, what's Wrong?
No, Dad, it's just us.
You awake?
You might be afraid about this
procedure
but I hear it's like having
a tooth pulled.
I'm not afraid,
I just haven't decided yet.
You'll have the test!
My sister is not going to die
so you can have one of your moods
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but leukemia that's a disease
they've worked out, right?
That is wrong.
What'll happen to my sister?
On the chance you can't
find a donor?
Why don't you sit down?
Without a bone marrow transplant,
we rely on chemical therapies,
chemotherapy,
as a way of sustaining the
patient over a number of years.
What kind of a number... 10?
A lower number.
Nice?
A much lower number.
As the immune system suffers
under chemotherapy
she'll grow weaker and could
have respiratory problems.
She may be bedridden, totally
dependent hopelessly depressed.
You'll need a nurse to help you.
Help me, what?
Your sister your father
and your aunt.
I'm not doing any.
Why'd you think that?
I assumed.
No. I live in Ohio.
I just got a degree
in cosmetology.
She's going to be fine.
Yes.
How can one sister be so good
and the other so bad?
So, you're saying Coral is good
and Amber's bad?
Coral Used to be bad.
But she's been a saint ever since
her car accident.
That Volvo was a blessing.
I bet they have good care here.
Dad never put Mom in a home.
Remember how he cared for her?
I was little.
I wasn't allowed in the room.
I get my degree next quarter.
You should be proud of that.
I already did a freelance job.
I did hair for a local
TV commercial.
Guess what it paid?
I don't feel like guessing.
Guess.
300 dollars?
Right. Why'd you guess that?
It popped in my head.
Most people would guess lower.
$300 is a lot of money.
I fell like my life is finally
starting.
Ladies.
What a beautiful room.
Wouldn't Ruth love this?
This place gives me the creeps.
Marry me, Coral.
I want to be your wife.
Do you mean it?
I'll drop the charges.
What's Coral up to today?
I'm going to show you something
that we're proud of.
Out state-of-the-art physical
therapy room.
Right over here.
I wouldn't mind living here.
Great!
Isn't it? Hello, Doctor.
We have a full range of
activities computer games,
video library, sing-alongs Nerf
basketball, date nights.
Who's Dad going to date?
You'd be surprised.
Women outnumber men here 5 to 1.
I don't think we can afford
such a nice place.
If you drop to a lower income
bracket you get financial aid.
Lower?
70% of our residents qualified
for assistance by spending
their savings on something
hat has no resale value.
Lower?
What do they buy?
Most buy elaborate tombstones.
I'm going to wait in the car.
Do you have something
I can take with me?
Of course.
Can't you take Dad and Ruth?
I don't think so.
You could move here.
I got Hank to think about.
He's unhappy there!
If he were happy
he wouldn't be there.
Transfer him!
You find a place for him here!
You could have the house!
You could find work down here!
No.
Why not?
Just... no.
Give me one good reason!
I don't want to!
I decided this before.
When Dad had his stoke,
I chose not to waste my life.
You think I've wasted my life?
Of course not.
I can't imagine a better way
to have spent it.
Then we made the right decision.
What decision?
Dad got sick, I came to help.
You didn't.
I had plans, a husband.
I couldn't!
You didn't!
You think I didn't have plans?!
You're the most.
Say it!
You've said it a million ways
since I came.
Leave her alone! Why are you
yelling at her?
She wants to tell you
I'm terrible.
I've tried to be nice
since you came.
You're think she's being nice
suddenly
because she felt an urge?
Shut up!
Did you ever get a gift from her?
I thought about you all the time.
How about a card?!
Ever get a card form Bessie?!
We were not close!
You didn't speak to me
for 20 years!
You've got to care of your family
I took care of my family!
I raised two kids,
never heard from you!
I am finally getting my life
together,
nobody's going to take it away!
I can't wait to get out of here.
Thanks for helping me.
It's a lot to ask of you
to donate bone marrow.
I think it sound neat.
Your medical history care,
please?
Your medical history card,
please.
Now, Hank.
I'm Charlie.
I'm Doctor Wally.
You have to fill out one too.
He's not here to get the test.
Okay.
Am I reading your card correctly
Are you currently on lithium?
Yeah.
Isn't it a great drug?
Can I ask you something did you
gain weight since?
No.
Nervous?
Thank you.
These offices used to be
infested with bugs.
Bugs don't bother me.
No?
They crawl out the boys' shower
drain hide
in the auto shop junk pile
and float in the basins.
You get used to it.
I wouldn't.
This one dude he catches bugs
and puts them on a leash.
A leash?
A hair leash.
He ties a hair to the bug and
tacks it down under his bunk.
He had a zoo of bugs walking in
circles all over the place.
My friend grabbed his cafeteria
tray and smashed them all!
That was funny.
Why make up these stories?
What do you mean?
Razors under the tongue,
hair leashes.
It's not made up.
Pretending you weren't
getting tested?
Think I'm lying about that?
Fine, you win! I'm lying!
I haven't told you shit!
You don't know about it!
Tell me!
You don't know!
I was in the hospital.
I hated it! I was scared!
There's this dude.
If this is another tale
I'm not interested.
I'm going inside to see
if Charlie's done.
I played in a pool tournament
in my ward.
Mom tell you that?
No.
I came in fourth.
It's true.
She doesn't think it's a big deal
That's great.
Got my toe broken in there.
How?
This guy threw a garbage
can on my foot.
Why'd he do that?
No reason I know of.
There's a lot of drugs that float
around there.
Do you take them?
Most of the time
I just keep to myself.
I think of what it would be like
to be someone else.
Like I could have a house with
land around it
and have dogs around and build
a go cart track.
Those places make so much money.
Be raking that stuff in.
And nobody would know where I was
Just be gone.
Mostly I just think about
being someplace else.
Then why aren't you?
Why don't you go?
What?
You said people do what they want
Yeah.
So.
You must want to be there.
No!
Then show them you don't.
It's not easy.
I don't want you wasting
your life.
Neither do I.
Why are you there?
Because they put me there!
Why?
I burned down the house!
Why did you burn down the house?
Come inside while we get
Charlie some juice.
Would you come?
Sure I would.
I forgot my coffee.
Why coffee so late?
I don't know. I like it.
You have a way with Hank.
I don't
Yeah, you do.
He's a good boy.
Is he?
Sure he is.
I wish I knew your secret.
I don't know. I just talk to him.
You saying I don't?
I'm tired and we've got Disney
World tomorrow.
I can fix that wig for you.
Does it look bad?
No.
But if you have a wig you should
try to have fun with it,
try different looks.
Something sporty,
out on the town kind of thing.
I just brush it.
I also have my whole makeup kit.
Want to see?
This is a really great
night cream.
I never bothered much with makeup
You should.
Because it's fun and you might
meet somebody.
Goodness, I haven't thought
about a man in years.
You're lying.
I'm sorry we haven't seen eye
to eye.
I don't want to fight.
We haven't been.
I want to get along.
We do.
I don't want us to just get along
be polite.
I don't have any problem
with that.
Nothing much seems important
to me now.
We're sisters.
Shouldn't we?
No, he just startles himself
sometimes,
then goes back to sleep.
Are you seeing anybody now?
Usually.
I hope you have someone real
in your life.
I don't have any trouble
with that.
I'm not talking about that.
You should. There's no reason
you haven't had love.
I had a true love.
You did?
Yes.
Did he know?
Yeah.
Why didn't I know?
He wasn't someone you'd know.
Come on, I won't tell anyone.
Clarence James.
Who?
He was only here during summers.
My God! You went
with a carny worker!
A very nice person!
I didn't say anything.
That's why I kept it secret.
Which one was he?
He mostly ran the ferris wheel.
Yeah, I remember him.
He was cute.
He had the funniest laugh.
He'd open his mouth wide and
no sound would come out.
No sound would come out!
What happened?
You know, they'd have that
last picnic?
Down by the river?
Clarence goes swimming,
everyone's watching him
and everybody's there.
His family, his friends, and me.
He's laughing.
He's making that monkey face.
It gets us laughing.
Then he dunks under the water.
He pops up again,
and he's laughing even harder
and dives again
and he doesn't come up
and he doesn't come up.
What?
Laughing and choking looked
the same on Clarence.
He drowned.
Oh, God, we were just standing
there watching.
Oh, my God!
And you never told me.
If I couldn't say I had a carny
boyfriend,
I couldn't say my carny
boyfriend drowned.
You should have told me.
We weren't that close.
We weren't?
No.
Shall I fix that wig?
What?
I don't know.
Let me see it.
Here.
No, you got to take it off.
I won't hurt it.
Here.
It's a good wig.
Nicely ventilated.
We can do something with this.
You want me to?
Yeah, sure.
It's a good weave.
I'm glad we made this trip.
I wish we could stay longer.
I'll get my brush.
I found it.
Is that too much wind for you,
Hank?
What?
Is that too much wind?
NO, it's okay.
Stick your hand out the window,
Charlie.
It's like an airplane.
Here we go!
Faster!
Charlie, faster, faster!
Charlie, slow down!
We'll meet by Pirates of
the Caribbean in an hour.
Where the line starts.
Bye.
Oh, God.
This Swiss Family tree house
is huge.
I'm really proud of you,
Hank for getting tested
for Bessie.
You're disgusting.
You want me to push Aunt Ruth
a while?
I like pushing her.
He's a good driver.
I'll catch up.
I'm going to sit in the sun.
All right. Bye-bye.
Hold on, let' go.
Pick out something nice
for Bessie.
How about my bone marrow?
Think she'd like that?
Look!
"Love Bug."Remember?
We saw it on TV together.
No.
I remember Dad took me to see
"Indiana Jones," though.
You're doing well on this trip.
Sort of. Stop it.
Tomorrow when we go back,
everyone'll hear about how well
you did.
Stop it!
I'm not going back.
I'm staying with Bessie.
"Peter Pan."
That was a cute movie.
I saw it with Dad.
No, you didn't.
Dad never hit me.
He did.
I would remember that!
You were 4 years old.
You're the one who fought
with him!
Yeah. But he hit you.
My feelings for you are like
big bowl of fish hooks.
I can't just pick one up
at a time,
I pick one up and they all come
so I just tend to leave them
alone.
You're a liar.
What happened?
I fainted.
There was blood in my mouth.
Is your mouth still bleeding?
No.
Did a doctor look at me?
No,
he thought you fainted so he
carried you here to lie down.
Who's he?
Goofy.
Goofy?
Yeah.
Goofy carried me to Mickey's
house?
Yeah.
He didn't know you were bleeding.
Maybe you felt faint because you
haven't been eating.
Maybe that's all.
I fainted because I was scared.
I can't sleep anymore.
I never sleep.
I'm afraid to close my eyes
because if I close my eyes
I'm not going to wake up.
So I jerk myself awake.
I yank myself awake
all night long
and then I pour myself a cup
of coffee,
but I'm trying to be brave.
Oh, darling, I know.
I'm scared.
It's all right,
you're going to be okay.
What've you got to be scared of?
There's still Hank and Charlie.
You're forgetting about them.
You're going to be okay.
Where are they?
They're sitting outside.
You're so lucky to have
those boys.
I know I am.
They're good boys both of them.
We re fooling ourselves.
Hank and Charlie won't match.
I won't pretend any more.
We have decisions to make.
We don't have to make them now.
We'll hear about the boys'
tests tomorrow.
I haven't had reason to pretty
myself up
since I can't think when.
Today is the day.
They almost got married
once before.
But amber set the church on fire.
Is Coral the same character who
shot Lance's dad in the head?
They're getting married?
Well, he lived.
And she felt awful about it.
What a good job!
You look beautiful!
Don't make fun of me.
I'm not.
I'm just a silly old woman
dressing up for a TV show.
No, you're not.
Where 's your brother?
I don't know.
Aunt Bessie
Gone someplace else like you said
Wish I could stay. Love, Hank
What re you doing up?
I'm getting Dad's 1 o'clock.
I was going to do that.
I can do it.
You're suppose to be resting.
I am.
Want some snacks?
I'm making nachos.
Better just cut me some fruit.
Hello?
Yeah, she's here.
Who is it?
Dr. Wally.
You did?
Good!
What is...
I see.
Then I should keep taking what
I'm taking now...
No, no!
I understand. I'm not.
Thank you. Goodbye, Doctor.
They got the boys' tests back,
and it looks like it didn't
work out.
It's pretty much what we expected
We knew that the...
May be they made a mistake.
Maybe.
I'll continue my therapies...
That's good, because...
...those are good things to do.
We should tell the boys.
What was l...?
Oh, Dad!
You want to go lie down?
No, no.
I'm fine. I just...
I can do this.
I've been so lucky.
I've been so lucky to have Dad
and Ruth.
I've had such love in my life.
...and I've had such...
...such love.
They love you very much.
That's not what I mean. No.
I mean that I love them.
I have been so lucky to be able
to love someone so much.
Yeah. You are.
We should tell Hank.
About the tests.
We will.
I better...
Where are you going?
I'm going...
Going into the kitchen.
Nobody's had any lunch yet,
have they?
What?
Nothing.
But if you take a drive
or something,
you ought to let me know.
I worry about you.
Hi.
Dad's Medication.
Around and around.
See?
It's just us.
Look, Lee's here, too.
You know Lee, don't you?
Bessie, you missed it!
Coral finally married Lance.
Wasn't Lance married to
Coral's mother?
No, Coral was married to
Lance's father.
He's really a nice boy.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org