Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
An eight-year-old boy
from Manhattan
was delivered
dead on arrival today...
- The Centers for Disease Control...
- Are we dealing with an epidemic?
Whatever the carrier,
we that know it's not the water.
We don't believe that it's airborne.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
Strickler's disease
was first diagnosed two years ago.
We're no better off now.
I needed you to see this
for yourself, Dr Tyler.
It's the same
at every hospital in the city.
For the lucky ones,
it's a lifetime in leg braces.
Most of these kids won't make it.
We need your help.
Strickler's disease came to New York
like a thief in the night,
threatening to steal
an entire generation of our children
- from before our eyes.
...Centers for Disease Control...
The killer was cunning.
It was deadly.
Neither a cure
nor a vaccine could be found.
We at the CDC had to contain it
before it could spread
beyond Manhattan Island.
So we went after its carrier,
the common cockroach.
Or rather she did.
Dr Susan Tyler is the reason
that there hasn't been
a new case of Strickler's
in this city for six months.
Dr Susan Tyler,
Professor of Entomology at the
New York State University...
Thank you, Peter.
I don't need to tell you New Yorkers
just how resilient cockroaches are.
Since it has proven to be
virtually immune to chemical control,
we had to find
a new avenue of attack.
So, with the aid of genetics labs
across the country,
we recombined termite and mantid DNA
to create a biological counteragent,
a new species
to be our six-legged ally
in wiping out the roach population.
We call it the Judas breed.
Once in contact with
the Judas's secretions,
an enzyme caused the common roach's
metabolism to go into overdrive.
- Susan! You're missing it.
- No matter what the roaches ate,
every last member of the nest
starved to death within hours.
I hope someone's taping this.
This announcement's
been a long time coming.
The Strickler's outbreak
has officially been contained.
- The epidemic is over.
- Hey, Susan. Honey.
Dr Mann, what did this victory
mean to you personally?
I can move on to other projects...
Our 15 minutes are gone.
...and personally,
it's where I met my wife.
What is this? Is this
some kind of Catholic guilt thing?
We don't even know
what the impact is of what we did.
The impact is that a lot of kids
will be running around next year
because of you.
A lot of kids.
Maybe we get lucky.
Maybe a couple
of them'll be ours someday.
Oh, a couple, huh?
Oh, OK. We're not rushing things.
I didn't want to overtax you.
It's been a hard year.
It's been a great year.
Oxfords. Seven and a half.
Black. Leather soles.
Funny, funny shoes.
Funny...
- CDC.
- CDC?
Hey, Boss, welcome to disease land.
- Tuck it in.
- All right. All right.
Are you sure this is yellow fever?
Are you ignoring your pages now?
These cops saw the broken scaffold
and then the paint here,
then they looked into the cellar.
Go ahead. Take a look.
Pleasant, isn't it?
Couldn't let 'em out
until you gave me the OK, so...
There were three dozen people
in here.
Bacterial readings are off
the scale, though nothing's airborne.
We got a Reverend Harry Ping -
preacher, if you can imagine that.
He ran this place.
There's no sign of him.
Oh, have you had lunch?
Try to keep it down
when you see this, OK?
Piece of shit on the ceiling.
- Figure that one out.
- Here, Josh.
- The subway?
- This is what I love about my job.
I get to travel, see the world
and meet new exotic cultures.
It's all bacterial but hey,
what the fuck, right?
- Thanks a lot.
- Board up every exit.
If this leads to the subways,
I don't want anything to spread.
Quarantine everything.
What's going on, Remy?
I'm just commemorating
my sad moments.
We're at this great restaurant.
I'm thinking, finally, a gentleman.
I go to the ladies', I come back,
I catch the schmuck
slipping sedatives into my drink.
- What a pervert!
- This city is full of perverts.
You don't know
who anybody is any more.
Jesus, I look like shit.
- Hey, guys.
- You the bug lady, right?
We're here to deal.
You should pick 'em up by
this front vein on the wing
cos it's the strongest part -
that way you don't break it.
Now, let's see what else you have.
Ah, look.
- What do we have here?
- Swallowtail?
Excellent.
How come you like bugs so much?
Lmagine that you're one of them.
Eating furniture and stuff?
That's gotta suck.
Don't judge them too quickly.
These guys were building castles
while dinosaurs were still
wimpy little lizards.
Now, say you're him.
He's what we call a soldier.
There is no way
you would ever quit fighting,
no matter how badly injured
you were.
It would be a battle to the death.
But most insects don't kill
unless their territory is invaded.
You'd just stun your prey up here
and then you'd drag it all
the way down through here to there,
into what is kind of like a pantry.
- They eat it alive?
- Yeah.
They're not really squeamish
about those kind of things.
This is the nest. It's the heart of
the colony, the big enchilada.
Why?
If anything happened to the nest,
the entire colony would die out.
- I'd just bail and start my own.
- Well, you couldn't do that.
See that big guy there?
Next to the queen?
Wait. Look over there.
He's the king. And out of all
the nest, he's the only fertile male.
He got a good deal.
It's a simple structure
designed for survival -
perfectly balanced
and very beautiful.
Whatever peels your banana, lady.
You wanna buy the butterflies,
or what?
You guys have done a really good job,
so how about five bucks?
- That's your best?
- Show her the weird bug.
- Costs a dollar just to look.
- Got it on the subway.
- We kind of broke it a little.
- OK. My best offer.
Ten bucks for everything, plus
a specimen jar, tweezers and mounts.
Deal.
Are you crazy? This is the best.
This is our meal ticket.
Come on. Bug's almost dead anyway.
It's yours.
- You gave 'em ten bucks.
- They're from Alphabet City.
There's worse things
they could be selling.
Oh, no. Your papers.
Help me get the window.
Susan. Push.
- Oh, come on.
- Oh, I hate this window.
OK, on three. One, two, three.
Who are you
to put my officers on quarantine?
Listen, Captain.
Those two, they go home,
kiss their wives and kids
and I've got a full-blown epidemic...
- Chuy, we have to make dinner.
- Dinner.
- I don't care.
- I do! Jesus, I hate cops.
They make the worst coffee.
- Shiny wire.
- Giving you a hard time?
Don't stare.
People look back if you stare.
It's not polite.
- I can't believe this.
- What?
I spend an hour in the field.
I get a weekend's worth of crap.
Oh, speaking of that.
That turd that I took to the lab?
I found these in it.
- What are they?
- Buttons.
Maybe they needed fibre.
Sorry.
Oh, my God. You're just a baby.
Oh, my God.
The transfer of recombinant genetic
material from termites and mantids
into Judas breed
will allow rapid enzymatic change...
...ensuring 100% sterility
in all Judas females...
...utilization of suicide gene...
...leading to a life expectancy
of 120 to 180 days.
Not too little...
and not too much.
You rub it in.
Around and around.
Like this.
Let the leather take it.
Funny shoes.
Mr Funny Shoes.
No one is there. Is empty.
Chuy, listen to me.
They have Jesus on the cross
but that is not a holy place.
Can you call me back tonight?
Thanks, Officer.
- Cops are on it.
- Good.
Well, they said...
Can you do me a favour and hold off
working at night for a while?
I can't do that.
I have to get back...
Someone broke into your office, OK?
- I'm sorry you lost a specimen...
- This is not just a specimen.
I did a pH test and there are only
two species that match what I found.
One of them is a leafcutter ant
in the Amazon.
The other one
we released here three years ago.
You said...
You said the ones we released
only had a lifespan of six months.
We engineered sterile adults. They
were supposed to last one generation.
- So what happened?
- The one I saw today was a baby.
They were designed to die.
They are breeding.
I shine them good.
Chuy, Black Lincoln.
Black Lincoln. This one.
Pay attention, please.
- Is this where you found the bug?
- Yeah. But they changed the lock.
- You haven't seen one of those?
- No. What is it?
It's an ootheca. It's kind of
a fancy name for an egg case.
There's probably more,
like, weird bugs inside.
No way! I see one of those, I puke.
Here you go.
Hold on. Is there money to be made
on this egg thing?
- Sorry.
- Dealing days are over. Vamonos.
These egg things look nasty.
Thought you liked
finding nasty things.
If we find these,
she'll pay us, right?
Is that all you think about?
Come on.
This bug. What does it look like?
Did you hear that?
- How deep does this go?
- Let's see.
Let's take a look.
- You see anything?
- Not yet.
Shit! I dropped it.
I can't reach it.
Let me try. My hands are smaller.
- Just leave it.
- No, wait. I'm almost there.
How much do you think we'll get
for this egg?
At least a twenty-spot.
Jesus!
Fucking moles!
- Got any change?
- Get a job, scag.
Kid! Get the hell off the tracks!
- How about a quarter?
- Get off my tracks!
- That's where he is. Long John.
- Slow down, hot shot!
Don't be talking to the moles.
They messed up.
Hey, moles! Eat my long john!
Look, I already told you
this is CDC business.
And I'm telling you
those lockers are MTA business.
We'll pay for the lock we broke,
Officer. I mean...
- Who am I talking to? You or him?
- You're talking to me, OK?
- All we wanna see is...
- See what?
- That's the old maintenance bridge.
- This insect we're looking for...
Your lady want a bug or its eggs,
or whatever she wants,
that's fine by me.
But it's like Swiss cheese
down there.
Tunnels in, tunnels out, old tracks.
You go messin' around, break your
neck and it's my ass on the line.
Lace-up shoes. Black. Nine West.
Chuy, finish your sandwich.
It's good. It's chicken.
Penny loafers. Eleven. Double E.
- He's really good at that.
- Oh, yes.
He imitates anything.
Doesn't he go to school?
He doesn't need school. He's special.
What you making there?
Is that a superhero?
Mr Funny Shoes.
He knows everything about shoes.
- I'm talking to you.
- No, you talking at me!
Come back with the permits,
we'll have a conversation.
- Great. We'll do lunch.
- Yeah, I look forward to it.
- Uptown.
- What happened?
Napoleon is alive and well
and working for the MTA.
We have to get down there.
He wants a permit?
I'll give him a special one.
What's that?
Is that the egg thing?
Give me a hand.
Man, that smells.
I can hear the bugs.
Come on. Cut it. She's gotta give us
at least 40 bucks.
- What's up?
- I think there's a guy down there.
Oh, shit! It's got me!
Help! Oh, God, please!
Please, help me!
Alex!
A philosopher named Hobbes
once wrote that
"Life, by its very nature,
is nasty, brutish and short."
An ant would put it more succinctly:
"Can I eat it or will it eat me?"
It's this kind of simplicity
that governs the phylum Insecta.
- Hello?
- I got the permits.
- You did?
- We're going down tomorrow.
OK, that's great. Listen,
I gotta go, I'll call you later.
...or of cellular phones, as my
distinguished colleague can tell you.
So, you think your Frankenstein
has got the better of you?
I was hoping you could tell me.
I really need to find
some answers, Walter.
Dear Susan...
is it answers you want from me,
or is it absolution?
You still think
making the Judases was wrong?
Three years ago,
I would've called it unforgivable.
But I have two grandchildren who are
alive today probably because of you.
It would be a tad hypocritical
for me to pass judgement.
That's not an answer, Walter.
It's not an easy question.
But as to the Judases,
I think it's likely some survived.
Evolution has a way
of keeping things alive.
But they all died in the lab.
Yes, Susan.
But you let them out into the world.
The world's a much bigger lab.
Funny shoes.
- Yeah.
- Hi, Peter. It's Remy.
Yeah, hi.
Is Susan there?
I need to talk to her.
- How you doin'?
- Fine.
- It's really important.
- Yeah, sure.
What are you doing?
What have you got there?
- Where?
- Right there. In your hand.
- Nothing.
- Are we testing it?
Maybe.
- Maybe. I don't know. Could be.
- It's Remy.
- Good. So give me the phone.
Give me the phone.
- Are we testing it?
- Yes.
Can you hold on, Remy?
Hey. What's up?
- They found what?
- At the water filtration plant.
- What's going on?
- I'll be there in about 20 minutes.
OK. Bye.
How long you got?
Patience.
We'll just try again.
Try again.
You know, sometimes these things
can be wrong.
That's OK.
I gotta go, OK? Bye, babe.
Susan, we got
the subway thing today.
I know. I'm gonna have
to meet you there when I'm done.
Wait.
Done from what?
Boots, toys, beer bottles,
body parts, cocaine-filled condoms,
little baby alligators...
Shit, you wouldn't believe
the stuff I've seen.
Yep. They flush 'em down.
We fish 'em out.
But this thing.
We didn't know what this was.
We nearly threw it away
but then I remembered Remy.
Jeremy plays bass in my band.
Anyway. So...
Yep. I remember Remy says to me,
"If it's got more than four legs,
it's not a mammal."
It's a lobster, right?
My father saw me stay in bed,
he go get the pitcher
of cold water and whoosh!
I tell you, that's some alarm clock.
- How big did you say these bugs are?
- Hurry up.
My shift's almost over.
I need my beauty sleep.
If I'm blowing off my Saturday,
then so are you.
Yeah. It looks like somebody
requested you for overtime.
Come on. Hurry up.
Let's find these things.
We've got a long way to go.
All right. Watch your step there.
We've got burrows going
down seven storeys here.
- No shit?
- Oh, yeah.
It's five storeys down, partner.
You fall, I don't wanna pick you up.
OK, it's all yours. Go ahead.
- It's 48 hours.
- I can't wait that long.
You got a pen?
- I write it.
- You gotta write this down.
The case number is two, seven...
What you say? Two, seven.
Yes, two, seven...
...eight, three.
- All right. You got that?
- What does this mean, case number?
It means I deal with you
in 48 hours, OK?
Hijos de puta!
Mr Funny Shoes.
Hi, Doc.
Susan sent you some homework.
- People actually do live down here?
- Yeah, man. The mole people.
This section was pretty popular
all the way to Fulton Street.
Tweaked-out crackheads,
dopeheads, shitheads, mental cases.
Then suddenly, poof! All gone.
Rumours got started.
Someone found a couple of stiffs.
Yeah, they make up
some crap about a killer.
Overcoat Slim, Long John.
Down here is the land of talk.
The wildest version
goes the farthest.
Hold it right here.
You got it? I see...
But this... Look!
The organs are perfectly formed.
They were functional.
I'm guessing here, and, of course,
they don't have
a complete specimen, but...
What do you think it is?
This thing is not just
some random mutation.
It's a highly evolved soldier caste -
a formidable killer.
It couldn't have developed
in a vacuum.
It's part of a colony.
All right! Hold it!
Check the other end, will ya?
This way, this way.
Should have stayed at the office.
- How much longer?
- Keep looking.
It's the size of your palm.
Aw, man. Take a whiff.
- God, it smells like acid.
- No. It's ammonia.
Hey, guys.
- There's some weird shit here.
- What kind of weird shit?
Lots of it.
God!
Man!
Go ahead and ask him. Ask.
You seen anything like this before?
Why you askin' me if I've ever seen
some shit like this before?
Do I look like I have?
Hell, no, I ain't never seen
no shit like this before!
Who the fuck would wanna climb up
these walls and hang one of these?
Must've been a big elephant-ass
motherfucker. I don't know.
The Delancey Street station
will close in five minutes.
Please find alternate routes
to your destination.
- Carlito?
- Yeah?
Aqui mismo estoy!
Come on, Peter. Hurry up.
Do you have the time?
Sir, the time?
You know, my father always
wanted me to become a dentist.
I said, "No way.
"I'm not gonna spend my life
looking into people's open mouths."
What could be worse
than that, right?
Oh, man, I've never been this deep.
This is the old Armory Station.
They built it turn of the century.
It's been closed for decades.
Yeah, I guess we covered everything.
Look. You got your shit.
I'm happy for you.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Josh, I want a full team
here by six tonight.
Right.
- Oh, shit! What the fuck?
- No, don't!
- Look what the fuck you did, man!
- You see the size of that thing?
Peter, are you all right?
It's OK, Josh.
It's OK. I think I'm OK.
- Get the hell off me.
- Yeah, I think he's OK too.
How am I gonna get you back up?
I don't know.
- See a way up?
- No.
- Shit.
- There is no way up.
- Oh, man, that's gonna work!
- Do you know a better way up?
Show that to the station manager.
Tell him Leonard said
he's gonna have his butt
if he don't have someone down here...
Wait, I can't find
my way back alone.
Look, look, look.
Just go back the same way we came.
Wait, wait.
Take the first tunnel to the left,
then go to the fork, right?
- Then right, right, left.
- Left... Can I stay here
- and help you guys back up?
- Toss the glow-sticks down and go.
Keep headin' up. You'll get there.
- Hurry!
- All right! I got it.
Help me!
Help! Please, help!
Help! Please!
Please! Somebody, please help me!
Piece of shit.
This is really weird. We should've
seen some track bunnies by now.
- What are they?
- Track bunnies. Rats.
They're usually around.
- They big?
- You damn right.
Could you just knock it off, please?
Knock it off.
Hey, I sing when I'm nervous.
- Turn these lights back on.
- What?
You said the cables
are still live.
- Oh, man.
- Maybe we can rewire them.
- There you go again.
- What?
How are you gonna rewire all of this?
You need a whole crew.
What is your problem, man?
Do you need a memo
every time you take a shit?
Don't go there.
You better be careful
how you speak to people.
- Josh?
- He wouldn't be comin' from there.
Manny, what the hell
are you doin' here?
Hurry. The lady needs help.
Honey, we're coming!
Oh, Jesus, please hurry.
Please. Come on!
- No! It's coming!
- What the fuck is that?
Come on. Get her, man! Get her!
What the fuck is that?
- What the fuck...
- Go!
Look there! There! There!
The car! The car!
Close the door!
Close the fuckin' door!
What the fuck was that?
- Come on. Here, here!
- Just wait a minute!
- You wait! I wanna make sure!
- It's not dead.
Well, it's gonna be very soon, lady!
- There it is.
- Drag it out.
You better tell me what the hell's
goin' on around here.
Oh, man.
OK, Leonard. OK. It's gonna be fine.
You'll be fine.
OK. You just stay calm.
OK, there we go.
- Everything's gonna be OK.
- Ah, Christ.
- Josh will be here soon with help.
- You're dreamin', man.
If your boy was comin',
he'd be here now.
- They ate his ass.
- We don't know that.
If there's more of them out there...
What's been puttin'
that shit all over the walls?
If you keep on
screaming like that,
we're gonna meet
the rest of its family.
Manny? Manny, be careful.
- It's dead.
- No, no, no.
I emptied two clips
and it kept comin'.
Wait a second. Help me turn it over.
- Peter, these are lungs.
- What the hell is she talkin' about?
Biology 101.
You know, insects don't have lungs.
- That's what limits their size.
- The secretions are the same.
When I increased its metabolism,
I sped up its breeding cycle.
We're talking hundreds
of thousands of generations,
- who knows how many mutations!
- Listen, I...
I just don't fuckin' get this.
How could the...
How could the Judas evolve into this?
Think generations, not years.
It took only 40,000 generations
for apes to turn into humans.
So?
We changed its DNA, Peter.
We don't know what we did!
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute! Hold on!
If that thing has been around,
how come nobody's ever seen it?
I think we have.
Sometimes an insect will evolve
to mimic its predator.
A fly can look like a spider.
A caterpillar can look like a snake.
The Judas evolved
to mimic its predator.
Us.
- Nobody knows about this?
- Nobody would until it's too late.
These things can imitate us,
they can infiltrate us and breed
before anyone would even notice.
How could you do this?
How could you do this?!
You take something
and you make it like a man.
A man who's not a man, he's a...
He's a thing!
That steals my child!
Manny, you tell her,
cos she don't give a goddamn.
- Your kid's gone.
- Shut up.
My leg's chewed up! And they're
talkin' about insects with lungs!
Oh, shit! They're everywhere!
Manny, get over here!
It's the blood! The smell of
the blood is driving them crazy!
Shit!
We have to cover the scent!
Manny, give me your razor!
Here. Take it. Rub it on the windows.
Anywhere there's cracks.
- Just do it!
- Come on.
- What is it?
- Scent glands.
Insects use them to identify
themselves. Rub it all over yourself.
They won't attack you
if they think you're one of them.
Manny!
It worked.
- Do you mind if...?
- Go ahead.
Manny, give me your lighter.
Look. This is where we are. These
tunnels may lead to the surface.
If we can get this car moving,
we might be able to make it.
What...
What do you mean, might?
I mean, probably.
But even if they do,
this thing's been down here
rotting for half a century.
- How do you know it'll move?
- Listen to me.
This car is a CR-17
from Coney Island.
Believe me, it was made to last.
Now, Manny, there's a track relay
switch in this room here.
Switch the tracks.
That'll get us going.
Yes, I'll try. I'll try.
Do. There's a fuse box
down the tracks.
If I can rewire it,
I can juice up the whole system.
Leonard, man. Look at yourself.
I'll do it. If you talk me
through it, I'll go out there.
- All you've gotta do is...
- No, no, no, no. I'll go. I'll go.
Why? I know much more about
what's out there than you do.
You're right.
You understand the creature,
and, uh...
Leonard knows the subway, so...
This is the way it's gotta be.
Whatever happens, it's Manny and me.
Why?
You two have gotta stay on this car.
You gotta get back up.
You gotta undo this.
So, I'll go.
We'll go.
I have to put this on you now.
They mimic us. We mimic them.
Peter, Peter. Peter, look.
You'll find two wires...
one green, the other blue.
OK.
Man, this shit can't be sanitary.
Take it off.
No, man. Leave it on. Leave it on.
Don't touch it.
Try not to sweat.
They sense chemical changes.
OK, I'll try not to sweat.
Chuy!
Susan, he's in.
He just needs to find the switch.
Green. Blue.
Green, blue. Green, blue.
Shit.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Chuy!
Chuy, it's me.
Come on, Manny.
What's takin' you so long?
Do these subway tracks
lead to the train tunnels
at Grand Central and Penn Station?
Yeah.
Well, they'll use them
to migrate out of the city.
After that, they'll set up
colonies anywhere they can.
Every specimen
we've seen has been female.
A male would be a lighter colour
and would have no wings.
If they follow
the Judas's spawning pattern,
the nest will have
only one fertile male.
Now if we could catch
that male and kill him,
then the females
won't be able to breed
and the whole generation
could die out.
Where the hell is the male?
Come here. Come here. Come here.
- Friends.
- Come here, please.
Oh, goddammit! He must be in trouble!
- He must be in trouble!
- Wait. Listen.
- Oh, Jesus!
- I'm goin' out there.
You stay here.
Listen. If the car starts...
I'll meet you
at the end of the platform.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Manny.
Yes! Yes! CR-17
from Coney Island, goddammit!
Shit!
Goddammit!
Goddamn! Shit!
Leonard!
Get away! Go away! I'm bleeding!
- I found a way out on a dumbwaiter.
- Go away!
Peter, I'm bleeding.
Go away! I can't stop it.
I can't stop it.
They'll be here soon.
Where's my wife? Where's Susan?
- Where's Susan?
- She went to get Manny.
They haven't seen us yet. Don't move.
Peter, go!
My God.
Leonard?
Come on, Chuy. Come on.
That's all right. That's a good boy.
Stop it. It's OK. It's OK.
All right, Peter.
Come on. Get in. Get in, Peter.
Come on. Chuy, shh! Stop it!
Stop it!
Get in, get in, get in.
- Peter, what are you doing?
- I gotta stop them here.
Oh, no. Peter, don't do this!
Chuy! Stop it. Stop it.
Train!
We're here! Help!
Watch it. Got it. Go on.
Get out! Hurry! Go!
Fuck you!
Chuy?
My God.
It's the male.
You will not hurt him!
No! Turn around!
Turn around!
Come on.
Police and emergency crews
continue to work
in the aftermath of tonight's
explosion on the Lower East Side.
Hustle up! Team leader!
We swept the area twice. It's burnt.
Nothing could have survived
down there.
What about one of us?
I'm sorry, Susan.
I really am.
Shiny wire.
Mountain boots. Ten. Brown.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org