Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What is it?
- What do they want?
- I do not know.
Pass... Pass.
Is it a cop?
I cannot see.
- What are they playing at?
- They are not playing...
- What are we going to do?
- I do not know.
Okay, hold on, guys.
There is a truck, too.
It is a cop.
You had better stop.
Sit tight and do not say anything,
let me talk.
We will be all right. Just relax.
- You ride at the speed you want here?
- You scared us to death, man.
- Do not call me "man", jew boy.
- Sir, what should I call you?
Do not call me anything,
nigger-Ioving jew boy, just listen.
Yes, sir.
You even smell like a nigger, jew boy.
- Take it easy, we will be all right.
- Sure you will.
He is seeing your face, that is no good.
It does not make a difference anymore.
They only left me a nigger,
but at least I shot me a nigger.
Yes, indeed.
Listen communists, niggers and jews.
Tell your buddies to spread the news.
The day of judgement will soon be nigh.
As the Lord in his wisdom
looks down from on high.
Will his battle be lost
by mixing the races?
We want beautiful babies,
not ones with brown faces.
Never, never, never, I say!
For the Ku Klux Klan is here to stay.
The Ku Klux Klan are better with lynches
than with lyrics.
Just read the file, Mr Anderson.
I can do without the cabaret.
You do not like me, boss?
Sure I do,
but I do not share your sense of humour.
Sometimes that is all you have left.
- How long have you been in the bureau?
- Three years.
- Right out of college?
- No, from the Justice Department.
Kennedy boy, now I see.
No, I do not think that you do.
Let us get this straight:
I have not had a pimple in years,
I shave every morning, -
- I even go to the bathroom by myself,
so you can quit this boss stuff.
I am in charge
because I have tried this before.
- Birmingham, Montgomery?
- Oxford.
I was with Meredith.
You were hit on the head
and got an promotion?
No. Shot in the shoulder.
- At least you lived.
- No, Meredith lived. That is important.
- What has four eyes and cannot see?
- What?
Mississippi.
Never, never, never, I say!
For the Ku Klux Klan is here to...
A big building for a small town.
Good Morning. My name is Alan Ward,
I am with the F.B.I.
Federal Bureau of Integration?
You are not exactly undercover, are you?
- We are here to see Sheriff Stuckey.
- The sheriff is busy now.
You will have to wait
or come back some other time.
We will wait.
Listen, you ass, you have
two seconds to get him out here, -
- or I will kick the door in, okay?
Looks like we have some company.
The Hoover boys have come down.
- How are you?
- Good.
- I am Sheriff Stuckey.
- Rupert Anderson.
Rupert, we have been expecting you.
- I assume you have met Deputy Pell?
- I sure have.
- Are you here about our nigger problem?
- No, it is a missing person case.
Come on.
Do you want the boy with us?
Sir, I am Special Agent Ward
and I am in charge of this case.
We think it might be more serious
than missing persons.
I do not think so, boy.
I think it is a publicity stunt
cooked up by that Martin Luther King.
Around 3 p.m. Deputy Pell
arrested 3 boys for speeding.
He held them in jail until 10 p.m.
And then released them.
They drove off. He says
he followed them to the county line -
- and never saw them again.
- Why did they not make a phone call?
- Why should they?
These boys were trained activists.
They are to check in every hour and the
moment they are released from custody.
The hotel is two minutes from the jail,
they could phone from the lobby.
- Maybe they went for a beer?
- Not these boys.
The Civil Rights Office made calls
when they did not check in.
The Sheriff's Office here said
they had no idea where the boys were.
First lie.
By who? The sheriff's office or
the Civil Rights Office?
Who would you believe?
Maybe you do not know it,
but I was a sheriff in a town like this.
- I know that.
- Lying does not come into it.
We were right on the border -
- and so far away from everything.
If a sheriff in a little town says "that
is what happened," then that is so.
Let us go and eat.
- We are full up, do you want to wait?
- Is it worth it?
We are not full for nothing. Will you
look at the menu while you wait?
- So will you wait or leave?
- We will wait, just to be near you.
- There are some empty seats down there.
- Mr Ward...
That is coloured.
Do not even think about it.
Some people here are ready to leave.
Are you not hungry, Mr Anderson?
Good afternoon. Looks good.
Do you mind if I ask a few questions?
I am looking for some information.
- I have nothing to say to you, sir.
- Just a few questions.
I have nothing to say to you, sir.
The three civil rights boys came here
to set up a voter registration clinic.
Before the locals could say yes,
the Klan burned them down.
Give the man a vote,
but do not let him use it.
What does the office in Rossville say?
They confirm that the boys came
to apologise to the congregation.
Sorry the folks did not get to vote.
Most probably did not know they had one.
Now you have no place to go on Sunday.
After they came here, they talked
to some locals down the road.
That is where we should start.
You can talk to them,
but they will not talk to you.
They have to live here
long after we have gone.
They would rather bite off their tongue.
Bureau procedure, Mr Anderson.
The church caught fire
and you ran home?
Yes, sir.
And then the four white men stopped you?
- And they attacked your husband?
- Yes, sir.
But you cannot identify them?
No, sir.
- Did you report this to the police?
- No, sir.
- You told the civil rights boys about it?
- Yes, sir.
Did they tell you
where they were going after that?
No, sir.
- Nothing?
- No, sir.
- All right, thank you.
- You are welcome.
Open up.
- Is your brother Halifair Finn?
- Yes, sir.
- Wake him up, we want to see him.
- Why?
- Just wake him up.
- What is the matter?
Get back here, you nigger!
We had better not catch you
talking to the F.B.I.
- You admire these kids, do you not?
- Do you not?
I think they are being used.
They are being sent down here
just to get their heads cracked open.
Maybe they believed in
what they were doing.
- Did they know they could end up dead?
- Maybe.
- In Washington they knew, did they not?
- Some things are worth dying for.
Down here they see things
a little differently.
People down here feel
some things are worth killing for.
Where does it come from,
all this hatred?
When I was a little boy...
...there was an old negro farmer
down the road, named Monroe.
He was... I guess he was
a little luckier than my dad.
He bought himself a mule.
That was a big deal around that town.
My daddy hated that mule -
- because his friends were always
kidding him about Monroe and his mule.
And Monroe was to rent another field
now he had a mule and...
One morning that mule was dead.
Poison in the water.
After that there was never any mention
of that mule around my daddy.
One time we drove down the road,
Monroe's place was empty.
He just packed up and left,
gone up north or something.
I looked over at my daddy's face...
...and I knew that he had done it.
He saw that I knew.
I guess he was ashamed.
He looked at me and said:
"If you are not better than a nigger,
who are you better than?"
- Do you think that is an excuse?
- No, it is just a story about my daddy.
Where does that leave you?
The old man was so full of hate -
- that he did not know that
being poor was what killed him.
Get the light! Get the light!
Are you all right?
I guess they know we are here.
Now you know what you are getting into.
I will call Washington for more agents.
Will it make a difference if I say
that is the wrong thing to do?
No.
The whole place for $75 a month.
It is private, central and perfect.
There is room for 100 more agents.
200 maybe.
More on the balcony.
We are trying to find the three boys.
I take all the help I can get.
When does the show start?
- Who is the big shot?
- It is the Klan.
No pointy hats,
but plenty of pointy heads.
Let me run a check on the plates.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
- Say hello to Mayor Tilman here.
- How do you do, Anderson?
Mr Mayor, Mr Barber.
This looks like the place to be.
Even for me.
There is no place like a barbershop
to get the latest gossip.
- Where are you from?
- Thornton, Mississippi, sir.
- Just a spit from Tennessee.
- Then you know how we feel down here.
We do not like outsiders telling us
how to live our lives.
Our negroes were happy until those
college kids came and stirred things up.
- Before that nobody was complaining.
- Nobody dared.
We have a peaceful community down here.
They are like any other folks -
- if you push them too far.
It is like three sticks of old dynamite.
Shake it up... and we will be scraping
bodies off the street.
I am here to investigate the missing
three kids, ask some questions.
It all boils down to gravy. It would not
be enough to cover a chicken steak.
The kids you are looking for,
I bet you a shiny new dime -
- they are sitting up in Chicago now -
- drinking a cold beer,
laughing about all the commotion.
I sure hope so.
Tell your bosses that people have
the wrong idea about the South.
You know what I am talking about.
Everybody running around ragged,
backwards, illiterate, -
- eating sour belly and corn pone
three times a day.
The fact is
we have two cultures down here:
White culture...
and the coloured culture.
That is the way it always has been
and the way it always will be.
The rest of America do not think so.
The rest of America do not mean a shit.
You are in Mississippi now.
That is for sure.
- What is the score, Mr Barber?
- St. Louis on top, five to nothing.
- Do you like baseball?
- Yes, I do.
It is the only time a black man
can wave a stick at a white man -
- and not start a riot.
We checked the plates: Clayton Townley.
Townley, grand wizard of
the white knights of the Ku Klux Klan.
I think we have a lead on the car, sir.
We are waiting for a call.
Good.
You have an appointment for
next Tuesday. See you then, bye.
Good afternoon, ladies.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
I just hate the way I look.
What do you think,
a permanent wave maybe, or a bleach job?
That looks good, did you get that here?
No, in Jackson.
I think a wig is your only help,
you cannot do much with that cue ball.
You can ask us some questions,
this is where you will hear it all.
Actually, I will. I wondered who that
was who drove in over there?
- I know it is not President Johnson...
- His name is Clayton Townley.
- Are you one of those F.B.I. Gentlemen?
- Yes, ma'am.
I think it is a shame if those
two boys are dead. I hope you find them.
Thank you. Actually it is three kids.
There was also a coloured kid.
You think you would have come
if it was not for those two white boys?
- Maybe not, Miss.
- Mrs.
Pell. Her old man is Stuckey's deputy.
But I am single.
Keep out of the way.
We will take care of this.
We will handle this.
We do not need your help!
Blood on the main street.
How will that look on the TV news?
It is the kid from the diner. Do not
talk to coloured kids with an audience!
They sent a message from the big boss.
I know, Clayton Townley,
chief pointyhead.
- Yes, how did you know?
- Bureau procedure, you should try it!
We did!
We found the car the kids were driving.
Good morning.
Two beer cans, a coca cola bottle,
a green plastic bottle, -
- a wristwatch that stopped at 12:45,
a set of keys. No bodies.
- I want the entire area searched.
- Yes, sir. It is a big swamp.
Every inch, Mr. Bird.
I guess they never left Mississippi.
They are dead.
- Mr Bird?
- Yes, sir.
There is a telephone at the truck stop.
Get on it and get me 100 more men.
100? ...Bureau people, sir?
I do not care if it is an army.
I want this entire swamp searched.
- Do not do it. You will start a war.
- It was a war long before we got here.
Get the fuck out of here!
The sheriff's alibi is solid. He was
playing poker with his wife's brother.
- The whole time?
- For three hours. He lost $11.38.
There is something else, sir.
We have trouble with the motel manager.
- What kind of trouble?
- He wants us out. Bad for business.
- Buy it.
- Sorry, sir?
Buy it! The motel.
- How high can I go?
- Whatever it takes.
Today in Jessup county, Mississippi,
amidst the violence that erupted, -
- the eyes of the nation
have been fixed -
- on the search for
the three missing civil rights workers.
I think it is a big hoax. If they are
in that swamp, then they asked for it.
Naval reserves have been brought in
to join F.B.I. Agents -
- in their search for the missing men.
I think they planned the whole thing.
They sit in New York and laugh at us...
- You think it is a hoax?
- Yes. They will not find anything.
Civil rights leaders are still
optimistic as to their whereabouts.
But privately there is concern
that they will never be found alive.
They came looking for trouble
and they found it!
This is Merrick Bobby, Network News,
Jessup county, Mississippi.
You ought to look up in Canada
for the boys.
They are not in our swamps here.
It is a publicity stunt dreamed up
by these N.A.A.C.P. People.
It stands for niggers, alligators, apes,
coons and possums.
You got your N.A.A.C.P.,
your S.N.C.C., your C.O.F.O.
You know what it all is?
B.U.L.L.S.H.I.T.
You got it?
One day we will not have to say:
"Good morning, sir, Mr Sheriff."
Maybe we will not have to say:
"Mr. Stuckey".
One day we will just say:
"Stuckey, our sheriff."
And one day the sheriff will not even
be a white man.
Hello.
Can I ask a few questions?
Can you tell me
what kind of flower these are?
I see them all over the place here.
I never saw such a pretty plant.
They are trumpet pitchers.
They are beautiful. They do not smell
so good, but they are really pretty.
It was nice talking to you.
Sorry about interrupting your meeting -
- but we cannot get anybody
to talk to us.
They "zip up",
like my mum used to say.
They will not talk to you because they
are afraid it will get back to the law.
- We are the law.
- Not around here.
We were sent here to find out
what happened to those three boys.
- They were here to help you.
- You should not talk to the coloured.
Who should we be talking to?
You should start with the sheriff's office.
- Why are you not afraid?
Aaron, come on, son.
Good evening, Mrs Pell. I am
Agent Ward, this is Agent Anderson.
We are with the F.B.I. Is your husband
home? We want to have a word with him.
Come in.
The F.B.I. Gentlemen
want to ask you some more questions.
I will put your dinner in the oven.
Leave us alone.
Do you mind if I take a seat?
What is so important
you have to bother me at home?
I just wanted to run through your
movements on June 21st once again.
- June which?
- June 21st.
Deputy, we both know what day we are
talking about. Let us do this civilised -
- so you can get back to your ball game
and we can get back to Washington.
Please, do not let me interrupt you.
But when you have heard a question
asked a dozen times, it gets boring.
I guess so.
- You do not eat together?
- He works funny hours.
- Do you think it is odd?
- No, I work funny hours myself.
I eat when I am hungry, he eats
when he can. Can I get you something?
No, thank you.
It is a nice house.
How long have you lived here?
I was born here. But my father lost the
house in a poker game a long time ago.
We have been paying rent ever since.
It is a wicked game.
Poker.
Mr Anderson?
It was nice talking to you.
I have to go.
Do the pork chops still look good?
Bring me a beer, honey.
Let us get back to baseball. It is the
only game where a black man can...
...I know, I have heard that one.
50 minutes of his alibi
hinges on his wife. What is she like?
She is a nice lady.
How does a woman like that
end up with...
...the shithead in there?
You know these small towns.
The girl spends her time in high school
looking for a guy to marry -
- and the rest of her life
wondering why.
There is something wrong.
He is too confident.
- Did you see the wedding photograph?
- No.
The three ushers have this way of
hooking their thumbs in their belts -
- with three fingers pointing down.
What is that?
Some sort of masonic thing?
No! KKK.
Hi. There was a couple of things
I needed to check with you.
- My husband is not here.
- It was you I wanted to talk to.
Me?...
Okay, you had better come in then.
It will just take a minute.
My boss is a pain, a real college kid.
He has to dot all the i's...
What is it?
It is a tiny thing
we are not clear about.
- Shall I put your flowers in water?
- Actually, they are for you.
- They are beautiful.
- They are pretty, are they not?
But they do not smell nice...
- Can I get you anything? Some tea?
- Yes, thank you.
Do not look at that!
It is a terrible photo.
I do not know about that.
- Is this recent?
- No. I wish.
- This sure looks recent to me.
- We were married 14 years ago.
You are kidding me!
- Do you take sugar.
- I sure do.
- I grew up in a town like this.
- You were smart enough to leave.
- Why did you not leave?
- "For better or for worse."
How about you? Are you married?
I was... as I remember. She did not
last very long, I was never home.
She got fed up with phone calls from
Miami and postcards from Des Moines.
There was always a guy around.
Any guy that could spare the time for
a movie or a beer -
- or a quarter for the jukebox.
She left.
- How about you?
- You know the South, Mr Anderson.
Leave high school, marry the first boy
who makes you laugh.
Your husband is quite a guy.
My boss has this thing about an hour.
50 minutes that your husband says
he is with you.
- And I guess he was?
- Guess he was.
That is a pity. Then I do not have
an excuse for hanging around here.
- Thank you for the ice-tea.
- Thank you for the flowers.
- Do you know what kind they are?
- I was told they are trumpet pitchers.
Right, my daddy used to call them
ladies from hell because they are...
...Carnivorous.
- Yes, that is the word.
The pretty colour is the bait. The
insects tune in on them and they die...
Maybe I should have picked
something more appropriate.
"May the peace, the joy and the holy
ghost abide to you forever. Amen."
You have already been told once, nigger.
We do not have to tell you again.
If you make any more trouble flapping
your lips at those federal men, -
- we will have to put you in the ground.
Without a pine box.
Do you understand me?
How have the negroes been treated?
They are treated about fair.
As good as they ought to be.
The niggers around here
have been treated bad for a long time.
I think Martin Luther King
is one of the leaders.
J. Edgar Hoover said that he was
a communist, they had proof of that.
I do not know that for sure,
but that is what they say.
You really want to find that nigger?
They say we have to eat together and
use the same bathrooms as the niggers.
That is hard for some Mississippi folk.
They are not like us.
They do not take baths, they stink...
They are nasty...
They are just not like white folks.
- What happened to the three boys?
- Dead.
They are as dead as they can be.
Is she asleep? Is she?
I am sorry I woke you up.
Honey, I will be away a couple of hours.
- Mary, is that your Bessie's kid?
- Yes, she is growing up real quick.
Tuesday will be fine on those, Mary.
Funny...
Their kids are so cute.
Is that thing on again? If all of secret
service could not protect the President -
- how are we suppossed to protect
a few negroes?
It is nothing but a bunch of lowlife
white trash drinking too much alcohol.
More like paint thinner and snake juice.
This state is as dry as a Martini.
We have the alcoholics to prove it.
- Your name, please?
- Clayton Townley, local businessman.
Are you spokesman for the Ku Klux Klan?
I told you: I am a businessman. I am
also a Mississippian and an American.
I am tired of the way the Mississippians'
views are being distorted -
- by the newspapers and on TV.
So let us get this straight:
We do not accept Jews
because they reject Christ.
Their control of the international bank
cartels are today's communism.
We do not accept papists
because they bowed to a Roman dictator.
We do not accept Turks, Mongrels,
Orientals or Negroes -
- because we want to protect Anglo-Saxon
Democracy and the American Way.
Thank you, sir.
This coloured boy wants to
play football for Barry Bryan in Alabama.
So Barry says: "I will give you a try."
What will he run with? A watermelon?
He is going to keep on running, too.
He says:
"You get down there on the goal line."
He puts a whole other team there.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org