Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Well, when a fellow
needs a diamond,
what better place to get one
than the Tower of London?
The rest is all
a bit hazy, but
there appears to have been an
altercation with the yeoman of the guard.
You didn't.
Thirty days
bread and water.
But you know what?
Prison certainly
clears the head.
Pure and simple,
I want you to marry me.
And it's a one-word
conversation, Delysia.
Don't you think that on
such a momentous occasion
a little time
should be allowed?
Oh, stalling tactic.
Is it because I'm not
rich enough for her?
Certainly not.
Well, it's true. I'm wearing
most of my worldly possessions.
I could never offer
this kind of blackmail.
Oh.
And who pays you
for playing the piano, huh?
You telling me you give Nick
his money back after every show?
No! And every damned shilling
I take hurts me to the bone.
Which is why it's got
to change, Delysia.
Money or love? That's the
question I'm asking, D.
With you singing and me playing,
we could knock the world flat.
Yes or no, Delysia?
You are a most uncommonly
persuasive man, Mr. Pardew.
But surely a lady
should have a moment or two
to consider the most
important decision of her life?
A moment?
She's had a whole year.
You did say you
were in my debt.
Damn it, I did, too.
Fair enough.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'll play for you today,
Delysia,
and for the rest of your
life, if you'll marry me.
Never again
if you don't.
See you later, Miss Pettigrew.
-Later?
In my professional
capacity.
As for you,
it's now or never.
The ship sails
tomorrow morning.
He is...
Impossible.
-Magnificent.
So you marry him.
Guinevere?
-Mmm-hmm?
Tell me the honest truth.
It's a darned fix, isn't it?
Nothing that can't be unfixed
with some good common sense.
But take a look
at the headlines.
With Nick, I get this magnificent
flat and my job at the Peacock.
And with Phil,
I get the best part on the West End
stage and my chance to be a star.
And with Michael?
With Michael...
I get the best friend
I ever had.
Is that all Michael is?
Well,
he's rather passionate, too.
I know what
you're thinking.
Michael's the one.
But what about
everything else?
And who says I'm looking
for a darned husband
this very minute, anyway?
Not everything comes along
just when we want it.
There are times when
choices just have to be made,
or you certainly
will miss out.
No.
No, I won't accept that.
I won't.
This " all of you or none of
you" stuff that Michael's pulling.
It's too much.
But he is in love
with you, Delysia.
Can you say that
about anyone else?
Guinevere,
haven't you ever been torn between
more than one person at the same time?
No, I can't say I've had
that particular problem.
You are beautiful, Delysia.
Well, it's not a bad figure,
if I do say so myself.
Have you ever been
in love at all, Guinevere?
Once.
-And was it this
" all of you
or none of you" stuff?
Oh, yes.
From him or from you?
Both.
Really? Do tell.
No.
All a long time ago.
You'll catch your death.
Put this on.
Allow me.
Excuse me, madam.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Take that through
to the kitchen, please.
And you do the same as well.
And tell John to pull the rug up.
Party about to start
soon, so chop-chop.
Party? There's a party?
Miss Lafosse?
-Hmm?
There's a troop of people downstairs who
appear to be under the misapprehension
there is to be
a party here.
Yes.
Today?
Yes. Didn't I say?
-No.
Oh.
Silly me.
Will there be many people?
I should say so,
Guinevere.
It's the big one.
The big one?
-Pile on the Pepper.
Phil's going to make
the announcement.
What do you think?
Do I get the part? Hmm?
Oh, yes.
My dear, you look as if you've never
been to a cocktail party in your life.
Why, thank you,
but I don't drink.
Oh, it's not a drink,
really. It's a cocktail.
Good luck, darlings.
Joe's the old one
over there.
Work your magic.
Of all the nerve.
Well. Time to make
the Rabbit run.
Are you sure
that's wise?
Mmm.
Phil, darling.
Delysia, sweetheart.
Lovely to see you.
This is Charlotte Warren.
Do you know
each other?
A pleasure.
How nice
to see you again.
Phil and I had such a lovely lunch
together today, didn't we, darling?
Well, I thought he'd have a
big appetite, after last night.
May I suggest retiring
to a safe distance?
I think you're
absolutely right.
Tin hat on.
I'm sorry,
it's Phil Goldman.
How do you do?
-We've met before, actually.
You were entirely
naked at the time.
Guinevere?
Is that you?
My goodness!
You look marvelous.
Charlotte, I just wanted to let
you know there are no hard feelings.
That is so
gracious of you.
To the victor the spoils, to the
vanquished two comps for Press Night.
And so wise.
I hope I can be
like that one day.
Wisdom requires more than
the passing of years, I fear.
Though a little bird tells me that the
part of the crippled mother is still open.
You'd look ravishing
with a stick.
And I won't forget about those
tickets. Is it two, three, four...
Silly me, I've forgotten how
many boyfriends you've got.
Now, Philip,
how are your deliberations over
Pile on the Pepper proceeding?
Well, between
you and me,
Charlotte has the most
alluring singing voice.
And I have to say, Daddy's quite
keen. In fact, more than keen.
So you're going to give
Miss Warren the part?
Delysia's going to be a bit
off-color about it all, I'm afraid.
Hey ho.
-Just one question.
Does Charlotte have quite the
same attachment to you as Delysia?
No. No, no,
she certainly doesn't.
Do you think that was more
than a passing attraction?
I mean, we both
know actresses, Guinevere.
It did occur to me
that it might be, you know,
purely to secure the part?
I have no doubt that Miss Lafosse
believes that you are one of the most...
Unquestionably, the most
important man in that room.
My dear woman,
do you really think so?
I do.
The scales have fallen
from my doubting eyes.
So pleased to have helped.
-Helped?
You've just made me
the happiest man in the world.
You seem to have made
quite an impression on him.
Oh. Yes.
I do, don't I?
Joe Blomfield.
A great pleasure.
Have we met before? I feel sure
I recognize you from somewhere.
I don't think so,
but I'm delighted
to make your acquaintance.
I have met your fiancée,
I believe.
Edythe? Um...
No longer my fiancée,
I'm afraid.
Really? I'm so sorry.
Not a permanent rift, I hope?
It would be ungentlemanly
of me to go into the details.
Of course.
You know, these things
are amazing, aren't they?
May I?
Why not?
-Excuse me.
Progress?
I'm afraid not.
Nor is there likely to be.
Transformations work
both ways, Guinevere.
It would take me 30 seconds to put
you back in the soup kitchen queue.
I told you,
I never forget a face.
Victoria Station.
Nor have I forgotten with whom
you shared a taxi last night.
Oh, you have.
If you want to continue
working for Delysia, you have.
Now we all of us need things in
our life. I need Joe for his...
Well, he's a man of
connections. And you need...
You need to stay off of
the streets, I imagine.
I see Edythe
has told you all.
If it weren't to commit another
indiscretion, I might disclose Edythe is...
As Miss Lafosse would say,
crazy about you.
To be indiscreet back,
she's rather more crazy about my position
in the fashion world than she is about me.
A woman scorned
is a dangerous thing.
And a bruised heart will often
speak harshly, Mr. Blomfield.
Oh, I sometimes wonder where
Edythe's heart has got to.
A woman with an absent heart
would not shed such tears, I think.
Edythe?
Shed tears?
You people!
With your green drinks and your
parties and your subterfuges.
You're all playing at love.
One minute her, the next minute
someone else. Flit, flit, flit.
Well, I'm not playing.
Love is not a game.
You've worked
your magic again.
I can't do it.
-You've already done it.
Joe just came up
and asked me
if he was being a cad
breaking off the engagement.
I've no idea what you said,
but I believe we've got him.
It must be extraordinary
being you.
Extraordinary? No.
Very, very ordinary.
Delysia, darling, is it
true what Guinevere said?
Well, if Miss P said it,
you can bet your shirt on it.
So I can tell the whole
world about you and me?
Officially an item, what?
Till death us do part?
What?
At the very same time that you
announce your casting decision, sweets.
Oh!
And what better time
than right now?
You're absolutely right,
damn it. This very minute.
Come on, gorgeous, no
time to waste. To horse.
Well, I suppose
that was necessary.
You wanted the part. He'd
already chosen the Rabbit.
No, Delysia,
you mustn't do this.
But I must.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you might know,
I'm putting on Pile on the Pepper
at the Ambassador, don't you know?
Have I mentioned this?
Anyway, it is my pleasure to
announce that I have, today,
cast the lead
actress, what?
She is not only Hortensia
in Pile on the Pepper,
she is also my Hortensia,
if you know what I mean.
Ladies and gentlemen,
your Hortensia
and my Hortensia,
Delysia Lafosse!
So
let's dance!
Michael?
May I?
-Please.
They don't remember
the last one.
No. They don't.
Delysia's name in lights at the
Ambassador. What do you think of that?
Well, it's certainly what
Delysia's always wanted.
Joe, my dear,
I don't think I could ever forgive
myself if last night's misunderstanding
got in the way of something
so, so important to us both.
I was wondering, could you
walk me home and let me explain?
Of course, my dear.
Of course.
Nice to have met you.
Did you see the planes?
Weren't they magnificent?
Madam?
Not now, thank you.
Well, what do you know?
It's my last night
singing at the club.
I'm going to be a star.
Well, aren't you going
to congratulate me?
I have done you
a disservice.
You have done what I asked.
That's your job.
It may well be my job, but what I have
done is untrue to you and untrue to me.
You have lost a man who
loves you for who you are,
not for who
you pretend to be.
And you, who are you to tell
me what's best for my life?
I'm nobody. But apparently
an expert on love.
No.
I have no one.
I am not
an expert on love.
I am an expert on the
lack of love, Delysia.
And that is a fate from which I
wish most fervently to save you.
Guinevere.
No pity, please. I endure
quite well, thank you.
Where to, ma'am?
Scarlet Peacock, please.
Do you know what
my name is, Guinevere?
I was under the impression
it was Delysia Lafosse.
Sarah Grubb.
One of the Pittsburgh Grubbs.
My father
is a steelworker.
No one else in the world
knows that, apart from Michael.
He doesn't judge me.
No. He wouldn't.
But you do.
-Me?
I certainly do not.
Oh, you think you don't,
but you do.
This is all I own,
Guinevere.
And two dozen pair
of shoes.
For all the fancy apartments
and fashion shows,
do you know how close I am
to having nothing?
Every day I wake up
and I think,
if I make the wrong move,
I could be out on that street,
with no clothes,
no food, no job
and no friends.
Just plain old
Sarah Grubb again.
Do you know what that's like?
Yes, I do.
You do?
In that at least,
we are alike.
And now my mascara's gonna run.
That will never do.
Here we are, ma'am.
How are you?
Hey.
Having fun?
Sweetheart.
-Nick. Hi.
Now, I've heard the news, darling.
Congratulations. It's the big time, huh?
Oh.
I thought you'd
be furious.
Furious, me? Why?
No. You and me,
we're the same.
We both get what we want
by bending a bit, don't we?
I get it, D.
It's business.
No, Nick, I...
I'll see you back
at mine later.
How can he just... He treats
me like I'm a common...
You don't think of
me like that, do you?
Of course not.
Delysia!
Darling!
Darling, you look perfect, what?
Doesn't she?
Guinevere, how lovely.
To you, I owe a special
debt of gratitude.
Champagne! The only thing as
delightful as my dear Delysia.
Darling, come on, finish
your glass. There's plenty.
It's all back on.
Darling,
that's marvelous.
Did you hear
the news?
These two lovebirds are
finally tying the knot.
Congrats, dear fellow.
When's the happy day, what?
We were going to keep it to ourselves
for the present, but you know the ladies.
Oh, do I ever.
Sorry, darling.
Couldn't keep it in.
It's nice to see
you again, madam.
May I add my
congratulations?
Let's dance!
If you don't mind,
Edythe, I have a...
Oh, you drone on, Joey.
Leonard will take me for
a spin, won't you, Lenny?
Be delighted, Edy.
Delysia, Phil, come on.
Of course!
Well, as we have
no conversation,
I have no option but to
ask you for the next dance.
Alas, I can dance
nothing but the waltz.
Are you all right?
-Yes.
Well, to take
another woman's escort...
You didn't take me,
I took you.
I'm sure Edythe can cope.
What happened to that
particularly beautiful scarf
you were wearing
at the fashion show?
What are you
talking about?
Despite your most elegant transformation,
the body is still the same.
Mr. Blomfield.
As are the eyes. Most
fetching, if I may say.
I'm not really sure
you should say.
I'm sorry. Professional
habit. A bad one.
I have to remember you're
not like these people.
Am I terribly
old-fashioned?
Indeed you are.
And all the better for it.
Am I making you
feel uncomfortable?
This is the most comfortable
I've felt all day.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Nick Calderelli's
Scarlet Peacock.
I'm delighted to introduce you tonight
to a very talented lady friend of mine.
And she can sing, too.
It's my pleasure
to bring you
Delysia Lafosse!
You're too kind, really.
Hello, Michael.
How was prison?
And to get us
in the mood,
we'll start with
Hot Shoe Shimmy.
Change of program.
If I Didn't Care.
If I didn't care
More than words can say
Would I feel this way?
If this isn't love
Then why do I thrill?
And what makes my head go
'round and 'round
While my heart stands still?
If I didn't care
Would it be the same?
Would my every prayer
begin and end
With just your name?
And would I be sure
that this is love
Beyond compare?
Would all this be true
If I didn't care
For
you?
If I didn't care
Would it be the same?
Would my every prayer
begin and end
With just your name?
And would I be sure
that this is love
Beyond compare?
Would all this be true
If I didn't care
For
you?
Thank you, thank you.
Really.
Well, let's try something a
little more upbeat, shall we?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is an air raid shelter!
Sir, stay...
-I'm going home.
You don't want to put
your wife in danger.
My wife?
She doesn't know I'm here.
I'm here, Delysia.
-Guinevere, I'm scared.
It's just a drill.
I'm sure it's just a drill.
But it won't always be,
will it?
We're going to war,
aren't we?
Yes, we are.
And that is why you must not waste
a second of this precious life.
Listen to me.
Once, I too
had ambitions.
Not your grand ones.
Simple ambitions.
Marriage, children
and a house of our own.
He died.
In the mud in France.
A good, solid man.
You would call him
dull, no doubt,
but he smiled whenever he saw me,
and we could've built a life on that.
Your heart knows
the truth, Delysia.
Trust it,
for life is short.
Michael?
Oh!
Delysia!
My God. I...
Nothing for 19 years and
then two in one day, what.
I'm so sorry.
The part's still yours,
darling.
Well, that's all right, Phil.
You enjoy your Hortensia.
In every way.
It's just a drill, ladies and
gentlemen, it's just a drill.
This is the safest
place in London.
Come on, let's have
some drinks on the house.
And some music, please!
Michael?
Michael, please wait!
Delysia, you've made your
decision. I hope you'll be happy.
Michael. Please. You have...
Where do you think you're sneaking
off to? The night is young.
You have the rest
of a set to sing.
No, Nick,
I don't think so.
Nobody walks
off my stage.
She said no.
What, and she does
what you say?
Never once, as a matter of
fact, but that's not the point.
The point is she doesn't
want to sing. End of story.
Let's go, Delysia.
No.
I'm warning you,
Calderelli.
You, warning me?
After you, Delysia.
Sock him in the jaw!
What?
I'm a pianist, damn it.
It could ruin me.
Why, you pathetic...
Darling.
This is your fault.
Is the offer still open?
Get up!
Well? Is it a yes
or is it a no?
What?
Will you doggone marry me
or will you doggone not?
Yes. God help me. Yes.
I don't think
I can bear it again.
Did you lose many?
Just one. You?
Almost every
school friend I had.
One tries to forget.
If only one could.
You know, I distracted
myself with ridiculous things,
youth, parties,
lingerie.
I mean, I trained in
socks, for goodness sake.
Socks?
There's a great deal of engineering in
a gentleman's sock, I'll have you know.
Stitching of the heel...
By comparison, designing a
brassiere is a piece of cake.
Not that there
aren't compensations.
None of them
over 20, I imagine.
And all very easy
on the eye.
But you know what?
I'm done with it.
I'm going back
to gentlemen's hosiery.
You know who you are
with an honest pair of socks.
You certainly do.
Told you about Gerry,
has she?
Didn't take you long
to move on, hmm?
Joe?
Hello, Edythe.
Did she also tell you that she hangs
around the soup kitchen at the station?
A tramp masquerading as some
sort of social secretary, my God.
Goodbye,
Mr. Blomfield.
No, actually,
she didn't.
Neither about that,
nor about you and Gerry.
But I'm grateful for
the truth, for a change.
Hello?
Delysia?
Miss Lafosse?
Come on, come on,
the taxi's waiting.
Michael,
don't rush me!
Guinevere! Are you all
right? We've been so worried.
Perfectly well,
thank you.
We've been scouring London for you.
Miss Lafosse...
You have not been at the roulette
wheel all night, have you?
Please, Delysia,
I'm trying to apologize.
I expect you've heard that I am
not a social secretary at all.
I'm afraid I found
myself pretending.
Miss Pettigrew, if that's you
pretending, then you're jolly good at it.
Guinevere,
Sarah Grubb is not going to
judge anybody for pretending.
Come on, Grubb! This is
us, I'm afraid, Miss Pettigrew.
Boat won't wait.
Are you really going?
-Mmm-hmm!
To New York?
-Yep.
How wonderful.
But, Guinevere,
what will you do?
Don't you worry
about me, petal.
Why, Miss Holt is holding a job
for me this very morning, I expect.
I will never forget the day
we spent together.
Not ever.
Nor I.
Oh, goodbye, Guinevere.
I love you.
Off with you. Away.
Oh, come and visit!
New York's bopping!
Forgive the intrusion.
I'm glad to see
you're safe.
Oh, yes. Quite safe.
Am I right in thinking you're no
longer employed, Miss Pettigrew?
Quite correct.
So you're free?
-Quite free.
Might you be looking
for a social secretary?
No. Absolutely not.
Oh.
I'm looking for you.
Me?
I've been looking for you
all night, and, I believe
all of my life.
If you'll have me.
A nod of the head
will do me fine.
And I am, at a stroke,
the happiest man in London.
What a night.
-What a morning.
Have you eaten,
my dear Guinevere?
Oh, Joe,
I have not eaten for
a very, very long time.
Some music, please!
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org