Here we go.
Come on.
Come on, seven!
What are you doing
at the house of God?
This is where I grew up.
Mott Street.
I'm Charlie Luciano. In my
neighborhood there were two dons.
Two bosses, each fightin'
for control of New York.
And sometimes innocent people
got caught in the middle.
I got a right to
drink a glass of wine!
I got a right to find work
that uses my brain!
You clean the fish and the
calamari, just like me!
What are you sayin'? 'Cause I'm a greasy
immigrant, all I can do is clean fish?
That ain't enough, Pop!
Buon giorno.
Che cazzo "buon giorno."
You come in my house, hmm?
You tell the
son of a bitch Faranzano,
the miserabile bestia.
I give him...
Oh.
Don Faranzano.
Faranzano.
Faranzano, I no
mean what I say.
You have been very loyal.
Done favors for me.
Always made your
payments on time.
Now, you've stopped paying.
I have to ask myself, "Why?"
No, no. Faranzano,
Mia piccola bambina she's sick.
I no have the money.
I no got the money.
Fat pig.
When I came from Sicily,
you went with me.
Now, you're drifting back
to that fat pig, Masseria.
- No! Faranzano...
- You are, I see.
No, no, no.
Tu sei mi padrone... Aaah!
I can't take chances.
If one man can desert me,
everybody can. Understand?
Yes.
If you have to sell your
daughter, you will pay!
You have a pretty wife.
Usually, after children,
they get fat.
Nice sweet taste.
Disgraziato!
Get out of my house!
I felt your balls, so I
know why she needs her own.
Figlio mio,
put down the knife.
You'll have your
chance one day.
That was one boss.
Don Faranzano.
Some things change
your life forever.
Yeah, I know.
I know. Loyalty.
My father sweated
blood for him.
The guy with me here is Frankie
Costello. Loyalty, Frankie, yeah?
He and Joey DeCarlo were my
two best friends. ThatJoey?
But on these streets
friends were hard to keep.
Don Masseria!
Lo bisogno, per favore.
Chi e chieste?
Look at this.
Lo bisogno aiuto,
per favore.
Chi e chieste?
No, don't!
Sono sangue.
Terrible what these
niggers are doin'.
They come down from Harlem,
kill my own nephew.
Right in front
of my face.
My son!
Oh!
Oh, no, my God!
Oh, my son!
Joey!
Oh, Joey!
Oh, my God! Oh, Joey!
That was the other boss.
Don Masseria.
Some way, some time,
no matter how
long it took,
I knew what
I had to do...
to both bosses.
He kills his own blood,
you know?
I mean his own nephew.
What kind of man is that, huh?
And on top of that,
he pays some in'ish to do it.
Uh! Ah!
The law of the street was:
Take or be taken.
Everybody fought everybody.
in'ish, Italians, Germans, Jews.
But this was different. This was
that in'ishman who killed Joey.
Beatin'up on some skinny
Jewish kid, Meyer Lansky.
And theJewish kid
wouldn't stay down.
Meyer wouldn't give
no matter how bad he got it.
You had to respect that.
Meyer's big pal was Benny
Siegel. Leave him alone!
Benny loved a good fight.
Even a bad fight, but they
wouldn't let him in on this one.
What is it? You in love
with the littleJew boy? No.
Joey was
a friend of mine!
Meyer!
What the hell's
everybody looking at?
He just
saved your life.
Come on.
Let's get the
fuck out of here.
So that's how we started.
Two Italians and twoJews.
Funny combination, huh?
Frankie... he liked to worry,
so he paid off the cops.
Benny liked to brawl,
so he was our muscle.
And me and Meyer...
we were both the leader.
At least it
started out that way.
Just four mugs
off the street.
At fin'st we were penny-ante,
but together we grew.
Thing that worries me is
things is goin' too good.
Relax.
How can I relax?
When everything's goin' right,
you know it's gonna go wrong.
We can't keep operating like four
kids running around the neighborhood.
That's what I mean. If we're
going to expand, we need a leader.
And who's that
gonna be, huh?
Tommy's meetin'
us over here.
After you. Please, be my guest.
Thank you.
I got 'em comin'up
right now, sin'.
Do like I said with the kid. Okay.
What is this, huh?
You'll see.
Charlie, come sta?
How's everything?
Meyer. Good to see you.
I got everything ready
for you in the back.
What do you got
to show me, huh?
It's a little
experiment.
You asked me a question.
I'm gonna answer it.
Come here.
Yeah.
He's telling this kid
there's a guy here,
very powerful, successful,
who's got a job for him.
Easy money.
You got that?
Good, get out of here.
Let's go.
Now he realizes.
Bugsy didn't tell him,
right? Me or you.
Got a job for me?
You just did it, kid.
Get lost.
Now do
you see?
Between you and me,
we're equals.
But other people,
they look to you.
What're you sayin', huh?
I'm your front man?
No.
This ain't a con, Charlie.
You're it.
You're the one.
Tommy Reina,
Charlie, Meyer.
Good pal, gonna even
be a better partner.
From your mouth
to God's ear, hmm?
He's got a line on the
good stuff. How good?
Bottle in Bond
Scotch Whiskey.
I got a friend got a boxcar
sittin' on a spur in Philly.
He wants 35 G's.
I only got 10.
Ahhh.
Who's this friend?
Arnold Rothstein.
No disrespect, Tommy. Why would Rothstein
wanna do business with bums like us?
'Cause some of us are
Jewish bums. Right?
You'll find out Monday night
when you go to his hotel.
No one ever
called you all bums.
Come on.
It's very
good stuff.
Come on in, fellas.
I want you to meet the genius
who fixed the World Series.
Mr. Arnold Rothstein.
This here's
Charlie Luciano...
and Meyer Lansky.
Tommy, thanks.
Yeah.
Well, sit down.
Sit down.
Mr. Luciano,
you're walking
down the street.
Suddenly you realize
you're being followed. It's a hit.
Walking toward you
is a second gunman.
You have time to fin'e at only
one of them. Which one do...
I don't accept the question.
To live, I gotta kill 'em both.
Next,
your wife... I don't have a wife.
- Why not?
- Emotion is dangerous.
- Arert you human?
- Would it help?
Next. I have ships
and distilleries in Scotland.
I need distribution
in New York.
Masseria? Faranzano? They'd kill me.
- I won't?
- You haveJewish partners.
Maybe I kill them too.
You can't afford to.
You're in the squeeze. Masseria
has 700 soldiers. Faranzano, 600.
Either one realizes you exist,
they squash you like an ant.
Unless I get a
powerful friend, huh?
Exactly.
Next.
What's the
secret of America?
What's the matter with
this guy? I'm 24 years old...
Money!
Everything is
money, Charlie.
Don't ever forget it.
But you, you'll
never make any money.
- Why's that?
- You dress like a schmuck.
Ah-ha.
Let's do
some business.
Check it.
It's raining money.
We got money
to burn, Charlie.
Wanna burn some?
Want to? Want to?
Be my guest.
All right!
Everybody ready?
The party.
Our fin'st million.
Paisan, you ready to make
some money? I'm ready.
- I'm always ready.
- Just don't hog all the broads.
I can't help it.
They're all over me.
Tell us something we
don't know, huh? Gentlemen,
before we go,
let's have a toast.
Our fin'st
million dollars.
Say this bottle is bootleg
business, greater New York.
This is our business
when we started.
Nobody noticed us,
nobody gave a shit.
Now this is our
business right now.
It's big enough for
us to have a party.
Big enough for
other people to notice.
This is where we want
our business to be.
But the bigger we get,
the more we're taking
from other people.
Thanks. Masseria's already calling us.
Faranzano, calling.
You see what I'm saying?
Yeah. I didn't get no whiskey.
I'm saying this.
If we're
not careful...
Charlie!
Hey.
I got the room
in the back for ya's.
Father,
how are you?
Tommy, you bum,
you look beautiful.
How you doin'?
Good to see you.
The table looks beautiful.
Hey!
Giovanni!
People will love
to play numbers.
It's smart business. Somebody
hits big, you gotta publicize.
All right. I'll get
somebody downtown.
Excuse me,
gentlemen.
Anna Citron,
these are my partners.
Frank Costello.
Hello.
Benny Siegel.
Hi.
And um, these are
thein' girlfriends.
He has two girlfriends? At least.
Salute.
Charlie, this is my girl.
I want you to meet
Anna Citron.
My goodness,
I'm honored.
Sit down.
You met my priest? Anna Citron,
this is Meyer Lansky. Hello.
This here is Father Bonotto.
Buona sera, signorina.
Buona sera.
Father! Ah, Tommy, you stupid
bootlegger from the Bronx.
Charlie,
I want to talk to you.
You see, this is why
alcohol is outlawed.
You son of a bitches, uh?
They're threatening us.
Then talk to the bosses.
You mean buy ourselves
some time. Exactly.
I agree.
Hey, Frankie.
We made it.
Let me tell you this.
Watch your back, all right?
Good.
Yeah.
So,
you talked to Rothstein?
Yeah. He worries too much.
So do I.
Faranzano wants to
meet in the morning.
I think we should go.
Not yet. Let him beg.
He is begging.
Aaah!
Meyer!
Move! Move!
You okay, Meyer?
Anna?
Yeah.
- That's twice I saved your life.
- You're telling me.
I hate owing somebody.
Listen, we're meeting
Faranzano in the morning.
Whatever you say, Meyer. Good.
You all right,
Anna?
Don Faranzano.
Have we met?
Maybe around
the neighborhood.
When I
was a kid.
This is my associate,
Meyer Lansky.
I don't talk
business with Jews.
You talk business with me. If Meyer
works with me, that ain't your concern.
Let's be blunt.
If you go with Masseria,
maybe he wins.
If you go with me,
maybe I win.
This seems to give you
a lot of power.
So what're you
offering me?
Masseria's the boss of
all bosses. I respect him.
He's a fat pig.
I offer you this.
Join my family.
We combine all operations.
You'll get
15 percent.
Yes?
Well, it's a very
handsome offer.
We have to think it over. That means no.
Means what it means. We have
to talk with our partners.
Show them out.
Fifteen percent, huh?
You know how much
money that is?
Well, I don't,
and neither do you.
But it's a hell of a lot.
Fifteen percent?
As soon as we sold to Faranzano,
he'd knock you off.
Why would he do that? You're Sicilian.
One day you
might wanna be boss.
If he iced you now,
there would be a stink,
but if you're workin' for him,
who's gonna come after him?
Who is gonna give
a fucking shit, except us.
And we'd be history.
He's right, Charlie.
That's why we're in partnership
with theseJews, Frankie.
Excuse me.
How're you, Charlie?
Right this way.
Show Mr. Luciano his table.
Hey, Charlie!
Nice to see ya.
Good to see you.
I heard you told
Faranzano to go fly.
I told him I'd think it
over. Always so polite?
Now you come to
seeJoe, the boss?
It's a very smart move, Charlie.
Everybody needs protection.
Even me.
Where is he? He's up in his balcony.
You oughta come
aboard, Charlie.
We're just one big pasta-eatin'
family over here. All right.
I'll see you later. All right.
Hi.
Geez.
I don't believe my eyes.
It's me. Hey, Charlie!
Come on, sit down.
I send messages, send flowers
and you don't come to see me.
I had some things I had to
straighten out with Faranzano.
I heard. You won't marry him...
that's beautiful.
Still, you won't go to bed with me,
and I'm so gorgeous.
I know. I've always held
a warm spot for you, Joe.
Your nephewJoey
was a friend of mine.
It's too bad,
Charlie.
Charlie,
you belong in this family.
Someday I will
join you, Joe.
- You don't like today?
- No. No, I don't like it.
It's too bad, Charlie.
I've seen a lot come and go.
Guys just like you.
The ones who come, they come
to me. The ones who go...
I'm the guy
who sends them off.
Hey, you want
a little broccoli?
- No. No, thank you.
- Come on, it's full of garlic.
It looks wonderful, but I
gotta get back downstain's.
Enjoy the show.
What do you think?
I don't trust him.
You don't trust anybody.
I doubt that you trust me.
He's stringing us along. Yeah.
Hi.
You boys enjoy the
show? Park it here, baby.
How're you doin'?
Great. Couldrt be better.
Got a light?
A light? For you,
I'd burn down this whole joint.
Excuse me, Joe. I hate to interrupt,
but can I talk to my sister?
This is
your sister?
Yeah. Go ahead. Be my guest.
It's nothin'.
Just relax. Whoa!
Thanks.
No problem.
It's not really my favorite
part the job. I could see that.
It's a nice... nice outfit.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Mara Motes. Somebody said
you're Charlie Luciano.
Let's just say I'm somebody
who believes in his friends.
Good.
Maybe you and I can
be friends sometime.
Yeah. Yeah. I could pick you
up after the show if you like.
You sure you
wanna do that?
If you want to be somebody's
friend, it takes time, doesn't it?
I guess it does.
I should
really get back.
Okay.
Bye.
Friends, huh?
Yeah? Charlie, it's Meyer. We got hit.
We got no shipment
New Year's Eve.
We gotta see Rothstein.
Right.
Now!
We're supposed to meet
Mr. Rothstein.
Yes.
Of course.
Hey, you know
where to find me.
I'm Benny Siegel. You
heard of me? No, not really.
What do you do?
I kill people.
Who hit us? Masseria or
Faranzano? Probably Masseria.
But who knows?
Could be either one.
I'm the fin'st guy
to worry,
but doesn't
everybody get hijacked.
You think this was
business as usual?
I shouldn't have to
explain this to you!
Next week, our customers will
be buying our scotch from them.
In a month, I'll lose my distillers
toJoseph fucking Kennedy.
And we'll all be
out of business!
We gotta get tough.
Yeah!
Only, we can't
afford a war.
They got armies;
we don't.
Happy New Year,
honey.
Balls and brains. You got 'em,
you don't need an army.
A hundred years ago,
Austria was run by
a prince named Metternich.
Austria was weak,
its neighbors strong,
but Metternich was
a cold, calculating fox.
If one country
got too strong,
he organized
an alliance against it.
He would bring Europe
to the brink of war,
then everybody thanked him
when he kept war from happening.
He barely
had an army?
But he had Europe
by the kishkes.
We gotta send a signal.
Nobody messes with our stuff.
We have a shipment landing.
Cape May, tomorrow night.
This is a perfect
opportunity to set a trap.
Aaah! Aaah!
Cowards!
Try this again,
I will kill your mothers,
fuck your sisters and turn
your brothers into eunuchs.
I think you've made your
point, Benny. Let's go.
Tony No Nose. Well, well,
this is a surprise.
Give our regards
to Don Faranzano.
Who's next?
You wanna start a war? I don't mind.
Well, I do. Sometimes you're
so stupid I can't stand it.
Let's go.
Move it. Move it.
I knew it. You had to
kill him, didn't you?
In 24 hours, Faranzano
comes after us. So?
So? We can't fight him.
We ain't got the guns.
Masseria does.
Masseria?
We're goin'
with Masseria?
He ain't so bad.
He's a fat, stupid fuck!
Other than that,
I guess he's swell.
Frankie, right now, this fat stupid fuck can
save our lives. Remember, it's only temporary.
A few more stupid moves like that,
they'll knock us over like bowling pins.
It's time to play
with the big boys.
Yeah, I used to be
skinny like you.
Hey, pay attention!
I'm talkin'
for a reason here.
I used to move fast,
jump fast, dodge bullets.
Fourteen! Fourteen
with my name on it.
Yet, never a scratch
on this beautiful body.
So I realized,
hey, I can't be hit.
So, why be skinny? Eat!
That's what we are here for.
- What are you here for?
- I wanna talk details.
Yeah, I hear
you got some trouble, huh?
You hear wrong.
I hear you gotta join my family
to stay alive another 24 hours.
I don't deal from weakness. Hey!
You sit down.
I like you...
up to a point.
What are the details?
I'm number two, above everybody.
Including Catania here.
We get a fain' piece
of all the action,
and everything from me and my
associates goes into the pot.
Everything.
Except whiskey. The booze
stays with us and Rothstein.
So, my family
shares in everything,
except...
The whiskey, huh?
Right.
You suckin' bastard!
You son of a
flea-bitten bitch!
Thank God
I can't kill him now.
He made such a tough deal.
He's no phony.
You and me together,
Faranzano is a dead man.
In six months,
you pass
the whiskey to me,
or I kill you.
You're part
of the family.
Ah, that's my boy.
It's not a question of numbers.
Anyone can rack up numbers.
It's how you do it.
It's a question of style.
I don't kill with style? You
don't know how to kill at all.
Gentlemen, sit down.
Very interesting to
see you again, Mr. Coll.
Again?
About three years ago, you
ambushed me and Meyer here.
Oh, yeah.
By the old way of doing things, I should
let Benny shoot you in the head now.
But I'm not
gonna do that.
So, you're not
gonna kill me.
So?
- So, we have a problem.
- Name him. He's dead!
Our problem is you.
See, you freelance.
When you hit people on
our turf, it upsets the cops.
No!
Plus, you're very,
very good at what you do.
I figure, I upset somebody else,
you don't miss a second time.
That's my motto.
Nothing so pretty as the
back of a mars head, huh?
What, you want Mad Dog
to go back to sellin' argyles?
No, we want Mad Dog...
to move
his operations out west.
Los Angeles,
San Francisco.
We promise to keep
you very, very busy.
Out west?
I'll think about it.
I'll let you know.
Gentlemen.
Maybe we should just kill
him. No. He could be useful.
Let's just see if he
leaves town. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Gloria!
Hi!
Hey, Mara.
Yeah? Could you come
out here for a minute?
Sure.
Hi.
Let's go upstain's.
Gambling doesn't start
till midnight. Okay? Okay.
Come on.
Ah, I'm sorry I haven't been
in to see you. I had business.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't?
No. I knew you'd be back.
You believe in fate?
I don't know.
I do.
Some people are born to be
chorus girls and dog catchers,
and other people,
people like you,
have something they
don't even realize.
What don't
I realize?
I can't tell.
Wouldrt be fain'.
There's another kind of fate.
Between two people.
I mean,
why did I meet you?
You're very gentle, you know that? I am?
Very.
Most guys, tell 'em you want
to be friends and they skip town.
But you really can,
can't you?
Can what?
Be my friend.
I'd like to be.
I gotta ask you a question.
Not that I'm complaining,
but if we're gonna be friends,
why did you kiss me?
If somebody's your friend,
you can trust them, right?
With anything?
Yeah.
Do me a favor? I would
do anything for you.
Don't forget
we're friends.
Once you throw sex into the
kitty, guys forget thein' manners.
I won't
forget mine.
Or they start getting all
goo-goo and talking about love.
Love is a very confusing thing
which I personally do not understand.
Well,
neither do I.
Can we do this again?
I gotta go to work.
I don't mean right now,
I mean, um...
Sure. I can do it as often
as you can. Probably more.
I'm sure.
I'll see you later. Okay.
Don't fall asleep.
I won't.
Hey,
how's it going?
Lansky's inside.
He is?
Hey.
What're you doin'?
Drinkin'.
Straight?
Yeah.
Beauty.
I got a serious
question for you.
Ask away.
You wanna
sleep with Anna?
What?
My girl, Anna.
I'm offering
her to you.
She's...
very beautiful, Meyer.
I happen
to think this.
But she's
not my type.
She's not your type?
Why isn't she your type?
Because she's
your type.
You're turning
down this offer?
That's right.
I'm marrying her next week.
Or month.
We're not gonna rush it.
But I'm gonna marry her.
Congratulations.
Maybe you'll stop with all
these ridiculous questions.
Friendships, Charlie,
they never get tested.
You and me, if we're gonna
stay in this business,