Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My last ones
Yeti!
Where are you?
I need you!
Yeti! Come now, quick!
Appearable snowman?
The Tibetan called them Yeti.
She speaks Yeti?
Why do I always have to save the day?
Get the other guy!
You can die slow or you can die fast?
Ya! I did it!
Oh, man.
I did it.
Time to retreat I think.
I'm in your team.
I'm a team player!
One for all, all for me, kind of thing?
The dynamite, always dynamite!
We should
get out of here..
Wow, back off!
Back of!
I hate mummies!
They never play fair.
Dad!
What are you doing?
Over here!
Over here, come on!
Shangri-La!!!
That's a diamond.
I can use a diamond like that.
Dad!
Avalanche!
Help!
Help me!
Please, help me!
I'm fine, and I'm still alive.
Help me please, somebody help me?
We're here!
Mom, we're down here!
Oh my god.
We've got to take them to Shangri-La.
Now it's an only chance.
We've made it!
The pool!
Thank you.
You must rest.
We'll take you into my chamber.
Well it's not everyone that gets the brother all from the death.
Is this Shangri-La?
I can live here.
Lots of opportunity
A casino.
Now rest them all. Thank you.
How can you get involved in all of this?
The emperor murdered the only man I've ever loved.
Lin's father.
I would have died too by his hand...
...if the Yeti had not found me and brought me to this pool.
How old is this happened?
Is is before the Christ?
How long you've got in this tomb?
Over two thousand years.
The emperor must never be allowed to reach the pool.
Or he will have the power to raise his army.
Once he becomes immortal, he can transform himself
into the most hedious creature ever seen.
I will check the first watch at the entrance.
I have no problem dating an older woman.
I'm afraid we can't be together.
Why?
Because I'm gonna live forever.
I don't want to watch you die.
So what? That's it?
You just gonna see the sideline for eternity.
My mother has mourned of my father for the centuries.
I don't know if my heart can bear it.
People can live in entire lifetime if one want.
I want my parents to live everyday.
Alex, your father is awake.
In up here.
If this is heaven, it is pretty good so far.
Nice to see something has never changed.
Go easy on him, he feels terrible.
I saw you laying there, Dad.
I've never been so scared in my life.
Well, I'm get used two of us.
You supposed to die.
You know you're Ricochet O'Connell, right?
You beat up us around but you still stand in the end.
I really never thought a world without you.
The truth is
I am just trying ...
I am just ...
I am trying to be a good husband and I am trying to be a good parent
and the truth is I've been dropped the both.
I've been a world greatest's son.
I know it's good cause I  rise a family.
Come here.
My boys.
Oh, no.
His power has been fully restored.
Time to go.
He is immortal.
Hey you three any shape something son of a bitch.
He is taking her back to his tomb ro raise his army.
- Is there any faster way down from here?
- The Yeti. No help.
But he's already on the air.
It will be too late.
Mad Dog have quite three headed lizards anyday in the week.
Let's go
Foreside, at nine o'clock.
Should I quit drinking?
Jonathan to Rick.
You've better get move on if you gonna be to the tomb.
Just back here as fast you can reinforcement, not sight seeing.
Here, Dad.
Lent me?
Nice.
The terracotta army is not indestructible until  they cross the great wall.
How it exactly we supposed send them of?
When the emperor build the wall he buried his enemies
underneath then curses souls to hold it up eternity.
Most of them the conquered soldiers.
I will call them to battle once again.
My mark on altar, rise an army,  that sounds like a plan.
Let's go.
- Alex. Where he go?
- Where do you think?
Open the gate of the past and free the souls of the wrong who he's damned.
In the name of the ancesters and rightious,
I sacrifice my immortality and that's of my daughter
so that you may rise this day.
Bring down the rough of the oppressed on his emperor and all who follow him.
I call of the hundreds, and the thousands,
that you may rise up and seize this moment
to take your victory
to take your justice.
And to take your revenge!
These  are
your good dead guys, right?
Zi Yuan sent us.
Do we speak English?
We're with Zi Yuan.
It's coming.
Welcome in twentieth century.
I really hate mummies.
Run!
Die you mummy bastard!
Die!
There's no call for the bad language.
Have you regret, darling?
None, not ever.
- You OK?
- Yeah, sure.
No problem
We had completely under control.
This guy ever won a trick?
Mother!
No!
Mother.
Hit this through his heart
You must still live.
My daughter.
She said, through the heart
Through the heart.
Enough tricks!
Where is your honor?
Fight like a man.
Devide...
and conquere.
Now you can rule...
...in hell!
Evening girls.
Looking well.
Good evening Mr. Maguire.
You dance great for an old lady.
Someone told me to stop living on the sideline.
Well you sounds like the smart guy.
He is.
Ciao-Ciao Shanghai,
Peru, here I come.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org