Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
They're coming!
-Let's go to the water!
- They're heading for the beach!
Down by the beach!
-Run!
-Look out!
Run, Doc! No! Doc, no!
Don't stop moving!
They're down there!
There they go! Okay.
Lay down! Lay down!
Lay down or I'll shoot you, goddamn it!
-Hurry up!
-Lay down!
That's right, shoot them!
I give up, Mr. Glenn. Please!
-Shut up, Henri!
-Please, don't hit me! Please!
Clean him up! Take him to the hole!
And call the press!
Dateline: San Francisco.
Alcatraz was the scene last night
of a dramatic escape attempt.
Four desperate prisoners
were apprehended...
...on the rocky beach below the prison.
The recently completed
Golden Gate Bridge serves as a backdrop.
So near, yet so far from freedom...
...the surviving escapees, Henri Young
and Rufus McCain are escorted back...
...while their less fortunate cohorts
are destined for the morgue.
The body of Doc Barker,
son of the infamous Ma Barker...
...lies bullet-riddled,
cooling on a steel gurney...
...attended by a triumphant guard.
The jubilant correctional officers
who foiled the escape...
...congratulate each other
and reluctantly show their battle scars.
A proud Warden Humson,
supervisor of three penitentiaries...
...Folsom, San Quentin and Alcatraz,
and confidant of J. Edgar Hoover...
...congratulates his troops.
Humson returns to his duties...
...as the inmates are sent
through metal detectors...
...cells are searched,
extra guards are called up...
...and Alcatraz goes on full alert
to forestall any additional trouble.
As public interest reached a frenzy...
...Warden Humson
and Associate Warden Glenn...
...left the island in the bay
for a press conference...
...headed for the San Francisco City Hall...
...which was inundated with a plethora
of reporters from around the globe...
...all gathered to hear the official reaction.
Associate Warden Milton Glenn...
...introduces Warden John Humson.
Warden Humson will now make
a brief statement and...
...if you please, no questions at the end.
Thank you.
l just want to reassure
the American people that...
...Alcatraz is an escape-proof prison.
They have nothing to fear.
The inmates, McCain and Young...
...will be brought up on escape charges.
There will be time in solitary confinement.
Privileges will be taken away from them.
And the whole rehabilitation process
will begin.
Definition of rehabilitate:
''To restore to a state of physical...
''...mental and moral health
through treatment and training.''
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Eleven times 1 1 ...
...121 .
Twelve times 12...
...144.
Thirteen times 13...
...169.
Fourteen times 14....
When Henri Young began
his rehabilitation...
...I was in my first year of law school
at Harvard.
How long?
Alcatraz was opened as
a federal penitentiary in the spring of 1934.
In the era of the gangster...
...it was opened more for
the publicity value than the incarceration.
Alcatraz was the most feared prison
in the world...
...and the most expensive.
There were only so many Al Capones
and Machine Gun Kellys...
...so the prison had empty cells.
To justify the costs, the government took
incorrigibles from other prisons...
...men that had committed smaller,
more petty crimes...
...men like Henri Young.
''Our Father who art in heaven.
''Hallowing be Thy name.''
Prior to 1938, there had been
five escape attempts.
No one had made it.
The reputation of Alcatraz as being
unescapable was secure.
Six inmates had died.
The ones who didn't die
sometimes wished they had.
The federal guideline regarding
solitary confinement states...
...that the maximum stay for an inmate
shall not exceed 19 days.
''Our Father who art in heaven.
''Hallowed be Thy name.
''Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done...
''...on earth, as it is in heaven.
''Give us this day our daily bread.
''And forgive us for our trespasses...
''...as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
''And lead us not into temptation...
''...but deliver us from evil.
''Amen.''
Thank you, gentlemen.
Alcatraz is a half-mile
off the coast of San Francisco.
There were 276 inmates,
1 10 guards with their wives...
...and children stationed on the island.
And the Associate Warden, Mr. Glenn.
This is the story of Henri Young
as I know it.
1936:
American League Yankees visiting
National League Giants.
The Yankees score 18 runs...
...a series record and every single man
in that lineup hits at least once.
Every single man in that lineup scores
at least one run.
Daddy!
Hello.
Have you been a good boy?
Take Daddy's lunchbox.
We'll go see Mommy.
Good news, Henri.
lt's over. You're out of the hole.
You stink, boy.
l did it. l made it.
Come on.
-Did good.
-l made it.
l did it. l did it. l did it.
They were fucking killing you.
You did good.
The only other survivor
of the escape attempt was Rufus McCain.
He had betrayed his fellow inmates
by tipping off the associate warden.
McCain was rewarded
and left in the general population.
Henri Young was sent to solitary.
Come on.
Henri.
Some men are broken...
...by the laws that they break...
...unable to resist...
...the forces that are pulling them down.
Other men...
...live by the rules...
...that society has set down.
You're not one of them.
Henri, l have a job to do here at Alcatraz.
Do you know what that is?
To protect you...
...from yourself.
You were among the selected sinners...
...the state set apart
so that you could simmer in scum.
The good people of the United States
have decided...
...that you are better off here.
l had nothing to do with that decision.
But where l play a part in your life is
to make sure that you stay here.
That you rehabilitate yourself...
...become a model prisoner...
...a better human being.
That's my job, Henri.
You too have a job.
And trying to escape...
...is not one of the duties
of your job description. Understand?
ln life...
...for every action...
...there is a definite and distinct reaction.
Action...
...reaction.
-Yes, Mr. Glenn.
-Now, if you escape, action:
l lose my job.
Reaction: l have a family...
...that l will not be able to provide for!
l'm not done yet.
Now, knowing this information...
...can you tell me...
...why you would possibly
want to escape...
...and jeopardize my family?
l've done nothing to you but my job.
And instead of letting you learn...
...by breaking the rules,
l feel l need to show you how to...
...obey them.
Tolerance.
Tolerance for pain.
My tolerance of you.
But tolerance can be mistaken
for kindness.
And kindness can be mistaken
for weakness.
And we can't have weakness,
can we, Henri?
l understand. l will be good.
l'm not gonna try and run again.
No, you won't.
Action, reaction, Mr. Glenn.
Action, reaction.
Good.
Clean him up, take him to the hole.
Christmas, 1939,
I celebrated visiting with my brother.
Henri Young celebrated in Alcatraz.
''Let nothing you dismay
''Remember Christ our Savior
Was born on Christmas day
''To save us all from Satan's power
When we were gone astray
''Oh, tidings of comfort and joy''
Stop it!
Get in there!
Please, no, no! Please, don't put me back!
Please, don't put me back!
l don't want to! l don't want to! No!
They sound great.
Merry Christmas.
''Standing 'round a flagpole
And he caught himself a head cold''
He sings it over and over.
l can't get him to shut up.
lt gets on your nerves.
In January of 1941,
I had passed the bar exam.
Henri Young was in his third year
of rehabilitation.
Welcome to Alcatraz, gentlemen.
Step off the boat and onto the dock.
Eyes straight ahead at all times.
There was a boat
named after Warden Humson...
...which handled the traffic
to and from Alcatraz.
In the morning and afternoon, it shuttled
the children to San Francisco for classes.
It was also used to transport prisoners
to the island.
When possible, having children
and prisoners on the boat...
...at the same time was avoided.
Don't look at the children.
l'll take the kids to the city.
We'll go shopping.
Honey, can l call you back?
The warden's here.
Good morning, Warden.
Good morning.
-When did you arrive on the island?
-About 20 minutes ago.
Good.
-Sit down.
-Thank you.
Mr. Glenn...
...l've been going over
the rotation figures...
...in the solitary-confinement cells.
ls there something wrong?
Well, l don't know.
l don't think this can be right.
What's that?
Here, 244.
According to this, he's been in there
since March of '38.
l don't believe there's been
an attitude change with regard to 244.
He's not like the other inmates.
That's over three years!
He masterminded
the escape attempt in '38.
There hasn't been one since.
If you let those animals believe
that escape is possible...
...you might as well stick in
a revolving door.
I think he has learned his lesson.
Come on, Henri. Let's go.
Henri Young had been rehabilitated.
I was now a public defender
in San Francisco. We'd meet in three days.
Eat, Young!
You know the rules!
You don't eat, you go to solitary!
Now, get with it!
Two times two is four.
Two times three is six.
Two times four is eight.
Eight.
Two times five...
...ten.
Twelve times...
...eight...
...ninety-six.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe more--
Henri, McCain, he put you in the hole.
Put you in the hole.
McCain's still here. Look!
McCain put you in the hole!
Put you in the hole!
McCain, he put you in the hole.
Get them back!
Get them back against the wall now!
Do it now!
What happened?
l don't know.
The United States of America
vs. Henri Young.
Charged with murder in the first degree.
Approach the bench.
''Henri Young, Rufus McCain...
and there, striking and wounding...
''...sharp steel instrument...
to wit, a spoon.''
No, this can't be right.
lt's right.
lf you say so.
''To wit, a spoon
about four inches in length...
''...which, striking and wounding,
described as foresaid...
''...caused the said Rufus McCain
thereafter, to wit...
''...on June 1 1, 1941 to die.''
Trial set one week from Thursday, June 22.
This court stands adjourned.
l know you can do it!
Come on, boy!
You can do it! You've got four furlongs!
Don't be cursing this street!
Pick them up and lay them down!
Let those legs pump like pistons!
Yes! Come on! The spirit is willing!
l can see it in your eyes.
Come on!
Pump it! Go!
Remember Jesse Owens
at the '36 Olympics?
Maybe tomorrow, sonny boy!
Watch it, buster!
Sorry, Counselor!
You're all right?
Mary, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry. Mary, you okay?
-Stop that!
-Okay, l'm sorry!
lf Henkin saw us, he wouldn't think twice
about suspending us.
-All right.
-Fix your tie.
Why?
You need to look good
when you thank Henkin.
What do l want to thank Henkin for?
The man's a cretin.
-He's given you a case.
-Case of what? Scotch?
Yes, James, a case of Scotch.
An actual case where l stand
in front of a jury?
-Federal murder one, no less.
-Henri Young.
He's a convict who killed another convict
in front of 200 witnesses.
Was it self-defense?
With a spoon.
What with a spoon?
That was the murder weapon.
He used a spoon to kill the man.
Weren't any forks or knives available?
My first case l can't possibly win.
Do this one for the experience, for the next
time, when maybe your guy didn't do it.
You could learn a lot.
Go see your client
and make nice to Henkin.
-l'll see you tonight?
-Maybe.
Thank you for your confidence in me
in getting this case.
l don't have any confidence in you.
The guy is guilty.
A monkey could try this case
and not make it any worse.
-l see.
-Remember that.
-Thank you, sir.
-A monkey.
l guess l'm a monkey.
-James Stamphill to see Henri Young.
-l need you to sign the release.
-lt's a nice day.
-Yeah, great.
Where are you going?
To the cell, talk to my client.
What, are you nuts?
l want to speak to him face to face.
Well....
You've already signed the release.
lt's your life.
Hi.
So, then, Mr. Young, is it?
You're Mr. Young, is that correct?
Mr. Young, that is your name, isn't it?
Henri Young?
l'll just assume that's your name
until you tell me differently.
Mr. Young, l will be acting
as your defense attorney.
l'm James Stamphill
and anything you tell me...
...will be protected under the rules
of confidentiality...
...of the attorney-client relationship.
So feel completely free...
...to answer my questions
in an honest and forthright fashion.
Just for the record,
your name is Henri Young, right?
This isn't an admission of guilt.
lt's just your name.
You speak English?
Yeah, you do speak English.
lt says so right here in the file.
Mr. Young...
...l am your attorney but l can't provide you
with much of a defense if one of us is...
...catatonic.
You see...
...we both have to be able and willing
to answer when our name is called.
Can you hear?
Mr. Young?
You okay, Mr. Young?
Henri Young was born in Kansas in 1913.
His parents died ten years later...
...leaving Henri to raise his younger sister.
At the age of 17, Henri went into
a local store to try to get a job.
He was refused work.
Out of desperation he reached
into the cash register and took $5.
The store also doubled
as the town's post office.
Henri was tried and convicted
of the federal crime of mail robbery.
Henri's sister was taken
to live in an orphanage.
He would never see her again.
Eleven years later,
Henri would kill Rufus McCain.
Mr. Young...
...you killed a guy, so...
...you're not catatonic.
l know that you can talk.
l don't know...
...maybe you could write something.
You want to write something? Write here.
Something. Just....
Look, you want to give it a try?
You want to write?
Something...
...please.
Mr. Young, you're looking at me.
You hear me, don't you?
lf you won't answer my questions,
maybe we can start with something else.
What do you want?
There has to be something.
Can't be to sit there, because if you do,
they'll just stick you in the gas chamber.
Do you understand that?
Look...
...Mr. Young, l've read your file.
l am trying to help you.
That's all l'm trying to do.
l just want to help you.
Maybe there are...
...extenuating circumstances in your case.
Getting sentenced to Leavenworth
for stealing...
...$500, that's extenuating.
You have to understand, l'm on your side.
$5.
What, Mr. Young?
lt was $5, not $500.
l knew you had it in you. Now, come on.
Why did you kill Rufus McCain?
You just talked. Don't do this again.
Come on, don't quit now.
Come on, you just talked!
Why did you kill McCain?
What?
-What are you saying?
-How....
How? How? How?
Are you saying ''how''?
How.
How?
How. What are you, a fucking lndian?
Don't quit now. How what?
How is....
You want to know how somebody is?
l'll find out immediately.
How is....
Who?
DiMaggio.
How is DiMaggio?
ls he a prisoner over at Alcatraz?
How is...
...DiMaggio...
...doing this year?
DiMaggio, the baseball player?
Yeah.
How is Joe DiMaggio, the baseball player,
doing? That's what you're asking?
Mr. Young...
...l don't really follow baseball.
You know.
Excuse me, Mr. McNeil,
I'm James Stamphill.
-Counsel for Henri Young.
-Yes.
l was wondering if l could talk to you
about continuance?
No.
You don't understand.
He just sits there and won't speak.
Maybe he's practicing for the gas chamber.
Tell him to take deep breaths.
You won't even consider a joint motion
in the interest of justice?
-Are you old enough to be a lawyer?
-Yes, sir, l am.
No joint motion for a continuance.
No psychiatrist.
And trust me, pal, no plea bargain.
Your boy's gonna suck the pipe.
l don't know who you pissed off
to get this shit case and l don't care.
No breaks.
Mr. Young, DiMaggio is having
a great year.
Last year he was the American League
batting champ with a .352 average...
...which was just a bit off the year before
when he had a .381 average.
The Yankees, they too had a good year.
New York defeated Chicago 4-0...
...led by jolting Joe DiMaggio hitting 400.
400, that's pretty good, isn't it?
June 1 7, 1941 ...
...our friend DiMaggio hits safely
in 32 straight games.
Twelve more and he will tie
Wee Willie Keeler's all-time record...
...who set the mark in 1897
for the Baltimore Orioles.
Joe Louis was the victor in what some
consider the toughest win of his career.
Here we go.
Here's some entertainment news.
Betty Grable.
See?
Says here she's just--
How old are you?
What, Mr. Young?
l'm 24.
l think...
...l am too.
No, you're...
...you're 28.
Would you like me to keep reading to you?
This ought to make you
a little bit more comfortable.
The defense requests a new jury.
Having been eliminated from this process--
Three new members.
And that's it.
Next.
The defense requests a continuance
of 60 days...
...so l may confer with my client--
He doesn't need 60 days.
The facts in this case are so clear,
six minutes should do it.
My client has been almost catatonic.
-Yesterday was the first day--
-He wasn't so catatonic...
...that he couldn't walk over and slit
a guy's throat in front of 200 witnesses.
ls it your contention
that the defendant is insane?
ls that what you mean by ''catatonic''?
Approach the bench, Counselor.
ls this laying the groundwork...
...for a not-guilty by reason
of insanity plea?
l don't know yet. l haven't even spoken
to him about the case--
One week, Counselor.
Then you will either tell me
you are ready for the trial...
...or you will come in here with a request
for a competency hearing.
One week.
This court is in recess.
Mr. Young, you and me,
we've got to talk now.
Would you like a cigarette?
No, thanks.
That shit will kill you.
That's...
...kind of funny.
''That shit'll kill you.''
l'll die in that gas chamber anyway,
so that's kind of a joke.
What's this about Nazis? We at war?
No, not yet, Mr. Young.
-lt's brand new.
-What?
-Mr. Glenn told me.
-The associate warden?
He says it's brand new.
He said they're gonna try it out on me.
No.
You only have a week.
You've got to talk to me. Okay?
Why did you kill Rufus McCain?
How could you not know about baseball?
You said, ''l don't follow baseball.''
-How could you not?
-Why'd you kill him?
Over and over, it must have been
maybe a year, l don't know.
All l did was hear them in my head.
What are you talking about?
Are you talking about McCain?
l'm talking about baseball.
The great American pastime.
l went over every game
l ever heard on the radio.
l went over every game l ever heard.
Just playing them over in my head.
You had all those games to go to...
...and you didn't even care.
l'm talking about Rufus McCain.
l'm talking about three fucking years
they had me in that bucket!
Three fucking years!
Without any fucking light!
You had all those games to listen to!
You didn't even know
what DiMaggio hit this year.
What kind of asshole are you?
Calm down, boy!
You know the average length of time
an inmate would be in solitary?
Nineteen days.
l understand, but he killed a man.
Henry did three years in total darkness.
ln a black hole.
That's tragic, but he took a life.
Your brother will tell you what l did.
-You won't get him off.
-He's the best lawyer l know.
He can tell me if we've got a chance
for some kind of insanity plea.
Your brother won't give a damn.
Your client is a two-time loser.
This case is much more
about you than him.
He has no future.
This is your first time in the spotlight.
lt's what you worked for.
This case is a lost cause...
...so you must handle it like a lost cause.
Maybe you're right,
but the guy's not exactly Al Capone.
No, he isn't.
All they had him on was
income tax evasion. Your boy...
...they got on murder one.
Hi.
How are you?
Hi, Henri.
Listen.
You're not mad at me
for blowing up at you yesterday?
Nobody talks back.
No, l'm not mad at you.
l'll get the hang of it.
l got a sense of humor.
We gonna have some good times
before this is through.
You know how to play cards?
Could you get some?
l set this up for you. Sit down.
How much light got into the cell
you spent three years in?
-Like when you offered me a cigarette.
-l want to get that straight.
That was pretty good, huh?
You gotta help me if l'm going
to defend you now.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Have a look here.
Did you kill this man here? Rufus McCain?
l must have. l'm here.
l don't remember it,
but everybody saw me, so, yeah.
-But you don't remember it?
-No. So what?
Did you want to?
Once there was this spider
that crawled over me.
lt was like having company.
l looked for him again, couldn't find him.
He had a way out.
McCain landed you in the bucket, right?
142 times 93. Ask me that one.
-How long after you came out--
-13,206.
13,000? You mean, days?
What are you talking about?
No, that's the answer. 142 times 93.
-Concentrate on what l'm saying!
-l know what you're saying.
-How long was it?
-l don't know! l don't remember!
Who's the new girl l've seen in the papers?
lngrid Berger?
She's a looker. You seen her movies?
l want you to think!
l don't want to think!
l spent three goddamn years in the dark...
...smelling my own shit and piss...
...doing nothing but thinking!
l hate thinking!
l'm sorry, Henri.
l'm sorry.
l'm just trying to help you.
You got a girl, right?
Take your jacket off.
-What?
-Let me smell it.
You were easier to understand catatonic.
What's she like?
-Who?
-Your girl. That's perfume.
Let me smell your jacket.
l'll make you a deal.
l'll give my jacket, my pants,
whatever you want. Sports, girls....
But you gotta tell me just one memory
about something l ask.
Deal?
Sure.
l've never been with a girl.
Let me try it on.
How long was it you went
without any daylight?
Did they ever let you out for any exercise?
-Merry Christmas.
-Please, don't hit me.
-Get the tear gas.
-How long l been in here?
-You're out of the hole.
-l made it! l did it!
lt's Christmas, 1940.
You've been down there two years.
Two years!
l did it.
Two fucking years.
l made it. l made it.
l'm not too crazy, am l?
l did it! lt's over!
Nothing's over, Henri.
Thirty minutes exercise, that's all you get.
No!
You don't want it, we take you back.
l want it!
l want it.
l'll be good. l'll be good.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury:
The defendant, Henri Young...
...is accused of murder in the first degree.
It is your responsibility,
as a juror, to deal with truth.
Rufus McCain was murdered...
...by Henri Young.
Mr. Stamphill...
...public defender...
...will play upon your sympathies.
He'll use every trick in the book.
Why?
To avoid the gas chamber.
The United States of America
will demand...
...that you return a verdict of guilty...
...so that this...
...this animal...
...will receive the punishment
commanded by the Bible.
''An eye for an eye.''
A life for a life.
For if ever there was a man
guilty of murder...
...it is Henri Young.
And if ever a man deserved
to die for that crime...
...it is the accused.
Thank you very much, Mr. McNeil.
Mr. Stamphill, are you prepared
to make your opening statement?
Your Honor...
...ladies and gentlemen of the jury:
When l was a kid, my heroes
weren't Babe Ruth or Lou Gehrig...
...they were Clarence Darrow
and Émile Zola.
ln other words, l have waited
for this moment all my life.
To stand, like l am, in front of a jury
of 12 good people...
...to plead the case of an innocent man
who's been unjustly accused.
The only problem is he did it.
l know it, the prosecutor, Mr. McNeil,
knows it.
Henri doesn't know it 'cause he can't
remember it, but he won't deny he did it.
All those witnesses the prosecutor
will bring forth will tell you...
...Henri Young killed Rufus McCain.
Now that we all know that,
why don't we find the man guilty...
...and gas him because that's
what we all know is going to happen?
Right, Henri?
What?
There's only one problem that'll keep us
from wrapping this up in record time.
Henri Young did not act alone.
They haven't caught all the killers.
There was a co-conspirator. Because of
this co-conspirator, whom we shall name...
...Henri Young is innocent
of the crime of murder.
What?
Objection, Your Honor! l must protest!
l figured you would.
This is absurd.
Before the counselor is allowed to waste
this court's time and this jury's time...
...l'd request that he supply some proof
or evidence of this co-conspirator.
Can you bring forward evidence
of the existence of a co-conspirator?
Not at this time, but it is my intention
to do so during the course of the trial.
He's not going to provide such proof
because no proof exists.
This man spent three years
in solitary confinement...
...during which time no one had
any influence over him...
...because no one had
any contact with him.
He came out of solitary.
He went directly to a shower.
Then he went directly to a haircut.
Then he went directly to the dining hall...
...where one convict had said
one sentence to him.
This does not a co-conspirator make.
l'm inclined to agree with the prosecution.
Unless you can justify
that line of defense...
...l will sustain the prosecution's objection.
The district attorney, with his own words,
has just made my case for me.
That'll be the day.
Your Honor...
...for three years,
three long, tortuous years...
...no one and nothing had any influence
whatsoever over Henri Young.
No one and nothing.
This was a man whose only crime was
to steal $5 from a local post office...
...to feed his starving sister.
He came to Alcatraz a petty criminal
who had never harmed...
...or attempted to harm
another human being in his life.
He came out of the dungeon a vicious,
barbaric, maniacal murderer.
A man who had been put
into a psychological coma.
Within an hour of coming out
of that hell hole...
...he did what would've been unthinkable
to him three years before.
Unthinkable!
His only thought was murder!
His only instinct was murder.
His first act was murder!
He himself was a murder weapon,
but the hand that held that weapon...
...and plunged it into the throat of McCain
belonged to someone else.
l point to Associate Warden, Mr. Glenn...
...Warden Humson and the institution
known as Alcatraz and say, ''l accuse! ''
-Objection!
-l accuse them individually and collectively.
l accuse Alcatraz of the torture
of Henri Young!
-l accuse Alcatraz of McCain's murder!
-Come to order!
Silence! This court will come to order!
Henri Young is not going to be
the only defendant here!
Alcatraz is on trial!
I will address your objection
tomorrow morning!
Henri Young, on trial for his life, is seen
leaving the San Francisco courthouse...
...followed by his young and now very
popular public defender, James Stamphill.
Stamphill has accused the infamous Rock
of torture, using the tag line...
...''crimes against humanity.''
He has turned the once quiet trial
of a convict killing...
...into a media circus.
ln most cases, they do get better.
ln the case of Henri Young...
...this happens not to be true.
Young is a...
...noisemaker.
Some prisoners have a problem
when they're in...
...solitary.
All we do is try to discourage misconduct.
This is the first verbal attack
on the jewel of the prison system.
This bastion that houses evil
opened in 1934.
It brought gangsters like Capone...
...Machine Gun Kelly and Henri Young
close to the magical city by the bay...
...less than one half-mile
from the world-famous Fisherman's Wharf.
We went to the streets
to find out public opinion.
You can't put a place on trial.
lt's a prison for prisoners.
Now the murderers are accusing
the wardens of this and that.
Doesn't make a lot of sense.
Humson seems like a good guy.
lf Alcatraz wasn't here l wouldn't live here.
-You think it's too close?
-l think it's perfect.
He's innocent until proven guilty.
He'll get a fair trial, but, nonetheless,
he's a murderer.
This grizzly evidence bears mute witness...
...to the brutal crime
perpetrated by Henri Young.
Note the spoon.
Can a prison be put on trial?
Judge Clawson's ruling tomorrow
may clear the way...
...to put Alcatraz on trial.
''The warden can be relied upon
to carry out the instructions...
''...of the Bureau, that no brutality...
''...or inhumanity shall be practiced.
''Sustained food and medical attention
shall be given.''
We have wholeheartedly followed
those instructions.
Thank you.
So many opinions being expressed.
We attempted to get a statement
from the recent Harvard graduate...
...assigned to defend Henri Young.
Why don't we keep the trial
in the courtroom? Thank you.
l would like to address a few words
to the counsel for the defense.
Mr. Stamphill, you are hereby
put on notice...
...that this court has no interest
in newspaper headlines...
...and will not be swayed by them.
l further admonish that counsel's attempts
to try this case in the press...
...and not before this court,
will put him in the utmost peril.
ls that clear, Mr. Stamphill?
Yes, Your Honor.
Good.
Bailiff, approach the bench.
Before l hand down my ruling
on Mr. McNeil's objection...
...l'd like to address a few words
to the counsel for the defense.
While l cannot give legal advice
and sit on the bench at the same time...
...l will express grave concern
with the defense's strategy.
Counselor, l strongly recommend
you walk a straight line...
...in terms of your defense.
Anything you state in this courtroom
will be evaluated not only by the jury...
...but very closely scrutinized by myself.
ls that understood, Mr. Stamphill?
Yes, Your Honor.
Very well.
Prosecution's objection is overruled.
You may pursue your line of defense...
...concerning the penitentiary at Alcatraz...
...and l will rule on any objections
on a point-by-point basis.
Exception.
Noted.
Mr. McNeil, you may call
your first witness.
Prosecution calls Terrence Swenson.
Terrence Swenson.
Witness shall remain standing
until sworn in.
Put your hand on the Bible.
Cut it out.
Do you swear to tell the truth
and nothing but the truth...
...so help you God?
So help me God.
You may be seated.
Mr. Swenson, as a guard at Alcatraz,
did you know Henri Young?
Yes, sir.
Could you point him out for us?
That's him right over there, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Whitney.
Thank you.
Now, on the morning of June 1 1, 1941,
where were you?
l was on duty in the dining hall.
Everything was normal.
And l saw the defendant--
Henri Young.
That's correct.
l saw him standing over Rufus McCain.
He lifted up his chin and....
-Excuse me, l'm nervous.
-lt's all right.
And he plunged a metal object...
...which l later learned was a spoon...
...into McCain's throat.
He then ripped it open.
Did the defendant ever appear
to be ranting...
...or raving?
No, sir.
Mr. McKeon, was he frothing
at the mouth?
No, sir.
Did he in any way give the impression
of one who was insane?
Objection. This man is not
a qualified psychiatrist.
Sustained.
So, it appeared to you that it was a cool,
calculated and deliberate act?
-Objection!
-Overruled.
The witness may answer the question.
Yes, sir. Young did it,
just as cool as a cucumber.
Thank you.
No further questions.
This court will reconvene
after the holiday...
...9:00 a.m., July 5.
All rise.
You should have played cards with me.
Alcatraz.
lt was built by the military
during the Civil War.
ln May of '33, the War Department
abandoned the island.
lt was leveled, all except for the lower
floor which is now used for storage.
Note to myself:
Get access to the lower level...
...because that's where the dungeons have
gotta be located.
The only guard on record to be fired...
...or dismissed during Henri's solitary time
was Derek Simpson.
Locate Simpson.
The prison opened in June of '34
under Warden Humson.
He insisted on a high level
of guards to prisoners.
Glenn was the first appointee.
Mr. Henkin.
Two things: First of all, you work for me.
Let me finish!
You work for me, which means
when l call you, you drop everything.
Return my call or you will cease
to work for me.
l don't care if you're with Rita Hayworth!
Understand?
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
What the hell are you doing with this trial?
Defending my client.
Then why don't you defend him
for Christ's sake?
Try to knock down the charges
as a crime of passion or figure out...
...how you'll cross-examine
the witnesses...
...instead of this ''psychological coma'' crap
that doesn't mean anything in court!
l think it does. As long as it's my case--
Fair enough. l tried to talk reasonably
to you, but you're not going for it, so...
...you're not handling this case anymore.
lt's done.
Mr. Henkin...
...they're printing my opening statement
in 250 newspapers across the country.
lf you want me off the case because
you're afraid of taking on Alcatraz...
...that's your choice.
But l'll just go to Jerry Hoolihan
and tell my side of the story.
lf you want to play hardball, sir,
l'll play hardball too.
l'm trying to be your friend.
You know who the warden of Alcatraz is?
He's the most highly respected warden
in the US dealing with hardened criminals.
lf you try to make Humson
look like a Nazi...
...they will eat you for breakfast.
You'll die if l can't get corroboration
about what goes on over there.
l need names! Names of men
who'll come and testify.
What made you think
these men will come and testify?
Maybe you got some friends
you don't know about.
-You want to play cards?
-l'll make them testify with a court order!
What about when they're back
on the Rock with Mr. Glenn?
They'll kill them, that's what.
This is our only chance.
We're talking about your life.
For a smart guy, you're awfully slow.
l'm already dead. l told you that.
You can't change Alcatraz.
lt just is.
So why fight it?
You stand in court preaching. l don't
even know what you're talking about.
Justice. l'm talking about justice.
l killed him, they saw it,
they're going to kill me.
Nothing you say will change that.
So l don't see what you're
so excited about.
This trial doesn't interest you at all?
You don't care about it a bit?
You look like you're having
a good time, so....
No, l don't care.
Main thing is, l got a friend my age
to talk to until they gas me.
l'm not your friend, l'm your attorney.
l'm trying to save your life. Guard!
You know, l have a sister, but...
...l ain't seen her since they put me in jail.
l got nothing. l got nobody.
l don't need a lawyer. l need a friend.
You're doing all this to prove something
to a guy named Darryl, not for me.
You want to do something for me?
Let's play cards.
Go ahead and play cards.
l got a case to try.
Hold it, Jim. Where are you going?
Where are you going?
I'm Henri Young's attorney.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
I'm going to call prisoners to the stand
to testify about life on Alcatraz.
Where are the dungeons?
What is solitary time
in those dungeons like?
I want the jury to know and understand.
You tell them to get caught
robbing a bank. They'll find out.
l'm done talking.
Mr. Murphy...
...if we can get decent treatment for you,
it makes it possible for everyone.
lf we ignore cruelty in one place,
it makes it more acceptable everywhere.
l ain't gonna do shit for you.
You can't get me no good time
knocked off.
You can't get me no privileges.
You can't even get me seconds at dessert.
lf l testify for anybody...
...l testify for the DA.
He's got some juice here.
Mr. Baker, could you tell me anything
about Henri Young?
Don't know Henri Young.
Could you tell us anything
about Mr. Glenn?
Warden Glenn has always been
good to me.
Have you ever been in the dungeons?
l don't know nothing about no dungeons.
That's all, ma'am.
l gotta go now.
Fuck you.
Did Mr. Glenn tell you
not to cooperate with me?
Fuck you.
Where are the dungeons located?
Don't take my fucking picture!
You know l can get
a writ of habeas corpus testificandum...
...and force you to come
and testify in court?
Fuck you!
Thank you very much for your time.
Don't mention it.
And you, sweetheart....
l'd like to fuck you.
I hope your day has been fruitful.
l don't see your photographer.
ls he still taking pictures?
He's trying to.
We're not receiving a great deal
of cooperation.
lt almost seems as though someone told
the prisoners not to talk to us.
There's no conspiracy.
No one talked to them.
Maybe it's because they are
dangerous people who belong here...
...with no interest in you or your case.
-l'd like to see the dungeons.
-l'm sorry? Dungeons?
The old citadel, the sub-level of the prison.
That's mostly storage...
...a few solitary cells.
No dungeons.
l would like to see
the solitary-confinement cells.
l would love to show those cells to you,
but l can't.
lt's an insurance risk to visitors during a
riot. lf you're there, we can't protect you.
Thank you for your concern.
l could show you the exercise yard.
You have papers.
l have papers, so you can cut
the good-guy act.
l do consider myself
as one of the good guys...
...and perhaps more than you...
...l know what the bad guys are like.
l'd like to read them. Please.
Thank you.
That's a court order...
...instructing you to permit us access
to the solitary-confinement cells.
And to allow the photographer
to take pictures of the same...
...to be used as exhibits in the trial
of The People vs. Young.
You are also instructed
to hand over to us...
...the complete medical
and disciplinary files as to therein.
If you refuse to do so...
...you'll have to appear in court
and show just cause.
Why don't you take Miss McCasslin
out for some air?
l was told not to leave you alone.
l don't care. You may be used to
these conditions but obviously she's not.
We've been searched. Take her outside,
or we'll discuss this with Mr. Glenn.
All right.
No more photos.
You all right?
Thanks.
l just need some air.
My God!
My name's James Stamphill.
l'm Henri Young's attorney.
l can force them to let you out
so you can testify...
...in San Francisco in a court of law.
You just have to give me your name.
I promise I will do what I said for you.
James, she's okay. Just needed some air.
Can we go now?
Feeling any better?
l guess l'll make it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org