Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- It must come to an end
- Taxi for the rehabilitation centre?
- Hang on. I have to get my smokes.
- Look at me now
- Okay.
Will I ever learn
I don't know how
But I suddenly lose control
There's a fire within my soul
Just one look
and I can hear a bell ring
One more look
and I forget everything
Oh-oh-oh, Mamma mia
Here I go again
My, my, how can I resist you
Mamma mia, does it show again
My, my, just how much
I've missed you
Yes, I've been broken-hearted
Blue since the day we parted
Why, why did I ever let you go
Mamma Mia, now I really know
My, my, I could never let you go
I've been angry and sad
about things that you do
I can't count all the times
that I've told you we're through
- And when you go
When you slam the door
- Keep going.
I think you know
that you won't be away too long
You know that I'm not that strong
- Just one look and I can hear--
- Stop the car!
Beautiful.
I hope the photos help your sister
out of that coma.
- Mariel! What are you doing?
- No-Nothing.
Why didn't you tell me
you were gonna marry Tim?
- Who?
- Tim Simms, your fiance--
the one who wants to shoot you.
Now, now, now, now just a minute. You
can't come in here and threaten brides.
- I don't care how unfortunate you are.
- Fuck off.
What is going on, Mariel?
I've seen your wedding album.
You've tried on every dress in Sydney.
- That doesn't mean I'm getting married.
- What else does it mean?
I wanna get married.
I've always wanted to get married.
If I can get married, it means
I've changed-- I'm a new person.
- How?
- Because who would want to marry me?
- Tim Simms.
- There is no Tim Simms. I made him up.
In Porpoise Spit,
no one would even look at me.
But when I came to Sydney
and became Mariel, Brice asked me out.
And that proves
I'm already different than I was...
and if someone wants to marry me,
I'm not her any more.
- I'm me.
- Her?
Muriel! Muriel Heslop!
Stupid, fat and useless!
I hate her!
I'm not going back
to being her again!
Why can't it be me?
Why can't I be the one?
Have you been in a coma?
Rhonda?
Dad.
If they have a copy of this document,
then the option is...
giving you a doctor's certificate
saying you are unfit to testify.
Can I have that title deed, Paul?
That's the one.
We can only assume that Victor Keinosuke
has given them a copy of this deed.
Muriel, why'd you do it to me?
I gave you money. I got you jobs.
I put her through
this secretarial course.
$2,000 for two years, it cost me.
Comes out, she can't even type.
I get her into selling cosmetics.
We all think she's making a go of it.
Turns out she's robbin' us blind.
You're a disgrace, an absolute disgrace!
A-Are you Bill the Battler?
I saw you on TV.
Can I please have your autograph?
Me and my dad think
that you're not guilty, Bill.
I've changed my name to Mariel.
Good on you, son.
You spread it around.
You can't stop progress!
You're comin' back to Porpoise Spit
with me.
We'll leave in three weeks,
once this inquiry crap's over.
- I can't go back. I'm a new person.
- You're a thief.
The only reason
I never got the coppers onto you
is your mother begged me not to.
I want that money back.
I'll get you a job at the Leagues Club.
I'll arrange a bank loan for you.
You're going to make up
for what you've done, Muriel.
It's Deidre Chambers.
Deidre! Deidre!
Hey, Deidre!
Bill!
What a coincidence!
What are you doing in Sydney?
Well, my sister lives in Sydney.
I'm down for the long weekend.
- Pull up a chair.
- What a coincidence!
- My barrister, Graham Newman.
- His two solicitors,
and Muriel you know about.
- Hello.
It's Mariel!
We should get back, Bill. Victor
Keinosuke's testimony starts at 3:00.
That Jap bastard! He's gonna testify
that I took bribes from him.
- Commissions.
- Commissions. I took commissions.
Cut through all that red tape for him.
I deserve some sort of acknowledgement.
They'd never have got to build
that resort on Crown Land without me.
- It was the Crown Land that did it.
- Total overreaction.
- There were aboriginals living on it.
- The federal police raided the house.
Your mother just let them walk in.
She and Perry made statements--
told them I had money problems.
- Don't think about it.
- Of course I had money problems.
- She stole most of it.
- You need your family around you.
If the Feds come near you,
don't you say a word.
- Are you and Deidre together?
- What?
Have you left Mum for Deidre?
Yes. We're in love.
What about Mum?
What happiness has your father had
in his life if he doesn't have me?
- What about Mum?
- She'll have you.
You got three weeks.
It's come back-- the tumour.
I have to have another operation.
I'm not gonna walk.
But what about
your rehabilitation?
They're gonna cut
my spinal cord, Mariel.
Mum called.
She wants to take me back
to Porpoise Spit.
I told her I was gonna
stay here with you.
Head down! Head down!
Come on! Come on! Swing it!
Blokes with no legs and no arms
cut through the water faster than that!
Look at that! You're going through there
like a constipated duck!
Look at 'em flopping around
all over the place!
Burchett, what do you think this is,
synchronized swimming?
Water aerobics for geriatrics?
You're supposed to be a sprinter!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Mariel?
Ken Blundell. How are ya?
Van Arkle!
I think we found you a girl.
David Van Arkle, Mariel Heslop.
Mariel, you've probably seen the news
about the civil war in South Africa.
Well, just as the South Africans
seem to be doing the right thing
by the blacks...
the police open fire on a black soccer
club, and that is bad news for David.
- Are you black?
- What?
I don't know why I said that.
Well, well, it is funny, in a way.
But let's be honest. The South Africans
were never much chop in the pool anyway.
David here
is a bit of a freak, really.
And I think that he is gonna get
the gold medal...
for the 1,500 metres
in the next Olympic Games.
Mariel, how did you feel
when Kieren Perkins...
took gold for Australia
at Barcelona?
- Who?
- Kieren Perkins.
- He's an Australian champion.
- Now, David's family...
are willing to do anything to see him
fulfil his potential as a champion...
even if it means swimming
for another country.
And they're willing to pay
$10,000...
to the girl that'll help Dave out.
Are you from Sydney originally?
What? No, Porpoise Spit.
A-And why did you leave there?
Well, because of all the mental things
that happened to me.
I got shallow, and my physical being
could have been improved...
and as well as my mentality.
- What about the black-haired one?
- No, she was Turkish.
She's only been in the country
five minutes.
Now, whoever marries David
will have to...
tell the immigration authorities
that they're in love with him.
Now there'll be media attention...
so they'll have to live with David
in his flat...
for at least four months
after the marriage.
I've worked out all the details
of the romance...
which you and David
will have to stick to.
But the most important thing
is to convince people...
that you two are really in love.
- What about the blonde?
- You didn't like her.
- I'm not so sure now.
- Now, I think Mariel might be...
just what we're looking for.
Well, it's up to you now, love.
Would you find it difficult to lie?
I could try.
Well, don't rush your decision...
but if you could let us know
by tomorrow morning.
You can dance, you can jive
Having the time of your life
Ooh, see that girl
Watch that scene
Diggin' the dancing queen
I know you couldn't have got up onto
the altar, but at least she could have
asked you to be bridesmaid.
- She did.
- Why didn't you say yes?
You could have been on television.
I don't want to sit up here, Mum.
- I wanna sit in the corner.
- No one'll see you over there.
Well, if this is your attitude,
I don't know why you bothered coming.
At least you won't
be in anyone's way.
Rhonda?
Is that you?
- You're the bridesmaids?
- Isn't it fantastic?
- We always knew MarieI'd come good.
- She's in all the papers.
- What happened to you?
- I had cancer.
It's all right. They cut it out.
I won't walk again though.
- You were so full of life.
- I'm not dead, Cheryl.
Come on. We better get ready.
Mariel's coming.
You must be so happy for her.
God, she has cancer!
I'm divorcing Chook.
I suppose I have you
to thank for that.
I hope I can do the same
for you one day.
You told me it would be
a quick civil ceremony.
Ah, it's good she wanted
a church wedding. It's romantic.
It looks like you mean it.
All the guests are on her side.
I should have hired you some friends.
The charges don't surprise me.
The bastards have been out to get me
from the beginnin'.
I just wanted you to know--
Mariel, are you marrying David
for money?
Is this a marriage
of convenience, Mariel?
Mariel, how long have you and David--
Your Mum's arriving in Sydney by bus
because I can't afford a plane ticket.
- You see what you've done to me?
- Where is she now?
I don't know.
Trying to get a taxi, I suppose.
Mariel.
You're beautiful.
Love me or leave me
Make your choice, but believe me
I love you
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do
I can't conceal it
Don't you see
Can't you feel it
Don't you too
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do
Oh, I've been dreaming
Through my lonely past
Now I just made it
I've found you at last
So come on now
Let's try it
I love you, you can't deny it
- 'Cause it's true
- Oh, God.
- Don't panic. Think of the games.
- I do, I do, I do, I do, I do
She's all yours, mate.
Father, when You created mankind, You
willed that man and wife should be one.
- Join David and Muriel--
- Mariel.
Mariel in the loving union
of marriage...
so that they may be living witness
to Your divine love in the world.
David, do you take Mariel
to be your wife?
Do you promise to be true to her
in good times and in bad...
in sickness and in health-- to love and
honour her all the days of your life?
Uh, yeah. Okay.
All right. Why not? I do.
Mariel, do you take David
to be your husband?
Do you promise to be true to him
in good times and in bad...
in sickness and in health-- to love and
honour him all the days of your life?
I do.
You have declared your consent
before the Church.
May the Lord strengthen that consent
and fill you with His blessings.
What God has joined,
men must not divide.
Mariel, take this ring
as a sign of my, uh--
- Love and fidelity.
- In the name of the Father--
- In the name of the Father,
Son and the Holy Spirit.
David, I take this ring
as a sign of your love and fidelity...
in the name of the Father and of the Son
and of the Holy Spirit.
I now pronounce you man and wife.
Congratulations.
You may kiss your bride.
Congratulations! Oh, David!
Good on you.
- Mr Heslop.
- It's Bill.
Mrs Heslop.
- Thanks.
- Mariel, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- You look lovely. Have every success.
Well done, love.
Good on you.
- How do you feel?
- He's fighting fit.
The next gold you'll see
on this hand will be the gold medal
for the 1,500 metres!
- You reckon?
- Oh, yes.
Mariel and us
have been friends for years.
We went to Hibiscus Island together.
- We're like sisters.
- She's my best friend.
- I-I tell her everything.
- Mariel! Oh, you look beautiful!
Oh, isn't she beautiful?
She is wearing the make-up,
isn't she?
Smile.
- I was tryin' to hide from you.
- I saw your wheels.
- I didn't think you'd come.
- I had to see it for myself.
Just the bridesmaids were worth it.
I didn't call them.
They came crawling back to me.
The way they picked on me
in Porpoise Spit...
saying I wouldn't amount to anything--
And here I am, famous,
and they're at my wedding.
- I showed them.
- Showed them what?
I'm as good as they are.
I have to go.
Good luck with what's his name.
Where are you going?
Where do you think?
Back to Porpoise Spit with Mum.
- We're catching the bus out tonight.
- I don't want you to.
Well, you should have thought of that
before you gave up on me.
I couldn't pay all the rent without you.
I couldn't even do the shopping.
I needed help.
I needed a friend.
I mean, I don't want you
to go back by bus.
I bought you two plane tickets.
Go to hell.
I already gave 'em to your mum.
You're right.
You are a new person, and you stink.
Mariel Van Arkle stinks!
And she's not half the person
Muriel Heslop was.
Rhonda, your mum just told us
you're moving back to Porpoise Spit.
- lt'll be just like old times.
- Don't worry about Rhonda, Mrs E.
We'll push her around.
- Are you rich?
- My parents own it.
- They didn't come to the wedding.
- No.
They paid for it.
They're in Johannesburg.
Kitchen, lounge room, gym.
You can use everything
but the weights.
Bathroom, my room.
Your room.
I'm going downstairs
for a swim.
It wasn't just the money, was it?
What kind of person
marries someone they don't know?
You did.
I want to win.
All my life I've wanted to win.
Me too.
$84.20. $84.20.
Ninety-nine cents.
Ninety, one hundred.
Thanks, Mrs Heslop.
Have a nice day.
You can see she's not right
in the head.
- Look, I'll see what I can do, Bill.
- You're a mate. I won't forget it.
I'll be in touch.
I meant to pay.
I need help--
around the house, and--
3:00 news update.
Not comin' back.
I want a divorce.
I'm marrying Deidre.
You know what they say?
They say that I wasn't elected
to the state government that time...
because my family
wasn't up to scratch.
That's what they say.
Look at this place!
I never had a bloody chance!
Get out!
Get out and find yourself a job!
Get out, you layabout,
and stop embarrassing your father!
- You're an embarrassment!
- You're the embarrassment!
You mad bitch!
Oh, no.
Mariel Van Arkle speaking.
- Hello?
- Muriel?
- Mariel.
- Mum's died.
- What?
- We're all at the hospital.
Dad says you have to come home.
Yeah.
The funeral's tomorrow.
Are you coming?
Russell's gonna be there.
Yeah. I invited him.
He says he's gonna bring Alan.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Mariel?
Is that you?
Not sure.
It was a heart attack.
Joanie found her.
She was lying on the bed,
looking peaceful.
She didn't suffer.
She made the ultimate sacrifice
for your father.
Judge will be lenient on him now.
He's got kids to support.
She'd be glad, in the end,
her life amounted to something.
Deidre, I finished up
in the bathroom.
You were right
about those cupboards.
Let's start on the laundry then.
It's a big job.
- What happened?
- Mum burnt it.
Why?
Because she got sick and tired
of waiting for Perry to mow it.
Hi.
What am I gonna do without her?
Her photo album.
She took pills-- sleeping pills.
They were next to her
when I found her.
And when Dr Farrell come,
they were gone.
And when I asked
what happened to 'em...
Dad said he didn't want anyone
to know.
Dr Farrell said
Dad had been through enough.
I don't know. Maybe he has.
The Lord is good to me
His word my hope
Secures
He will my shield
And portion be
As long as life
Endures
I have a telefax to read.
Keep your eye
on them journalist bastards.
"To Bill Heslop and Family...
Hazel and I were sorry
to hear of the passing of Betty.
We are thinking of you
in your time of sorrow."
Signed, the honourable Bob Hawke...
former prime minister
of Australia.
- What are they doin'?
- They're, they're writin' it down.
I'll bet they are. Put that
in your papers, you mongrel bastards.
I've still got friends.
How many families get telegrams
from former prime ministers...
when somebody dies?
I'm not forgotten.
Betty Heslop lived
for her family.
She was very happy about
her daughter Mariel's marriage...
and attending the wedding
in Sydney...
was one of the highlights
of her life.
Her life, during her last days
on earth...
made me think of--
Mariel.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was so different--
a new person.
But I'm not.
I'm just the same as him.
Heslop.
On The Beach Motel.
One.
I can't stay married to you, David.
I've got to stop lying now.
I tell so many lies.
One day I won't know
I'm doing it.
I don't love you.
I-I don't love you either,
but, uh--
I don't know. I-I think I could like
having you around.
I'll give you the money back.
It's yours.
Good luck in the games.
You too.
I don't understand it.
Why'd she burn the back yard?
We've got to stick together.
You've got to help me
with the kids.
What about Deidre?
She'll lend a hand.
I don't think she's keen to marry me...
now that livin' with the kids
has come into it.
Someone's got to look after them.
And it has to be you, Dad.
You owe me, Muriel.
Now, this isn't all of it...
but I'll pay the rest off
when I get back to Sydney and get a job.
So you're not gonna help me out.
Is that it?
You owe us, Dad.
We're not useless.
We never were.
Now you're looking after the kids...
and you're gonna tell them
they're not useless.
How about that telegram
from Bob Hawke?
How'd you get that?
I phoned his office.
I was nearly
in the state government.
Fourteen votes I needed.
Nobody knew who'd won for three days
till the postal vote came in.
For three days,
I was almost there.
Couldn't win a chook raffle now.
Resigned from the council.
I'm unemployed.
Got to go on the dole.
Imagine the faces
when I walk into that dole office.
You reap what you sow.
You'd think I'd have learned that
growin' up on a farm.
You reap what you sow.
Dad, the cricket's started.
Hi, Joan.
- Muriel's goin' back to Sydney.
- Are ya?
I thought you were stayin' here
with us.
Keep in touch.
Bye, Dad.
Do you want me to open you
a can of beer?
That would be lovely, Joanie.
With you in a sec.
I'm giving it another chance
with Chook--
as soon as he gets out
of the correction centre.
They've accused him of raping
a Japanese tourist, which is ridiculous!
Chook hates the Japanese.
We better fly.
We're meeting Rose Biggs for lunch.
Rose Biggs?
Are you friends with her?
Once we got to know her,
we found out she was just like us.
But Rose Biggs sucked
your husband's cock.
- Rhonda!
- Oh, she did.
- I know.
But w--
I sucked her husband's cock,
and it made me realize...
we all make mistakes.
Hi.
- Mariel.
- Muriel.
What a surprise!
Rhonda, Mariel--
Muriel's come to visit you.
Actually, I've come to ask Rhonda
if she wants to come back to Sydney.
I've got a taxi outside
and two plane tickets, if you want to.
- What about your husband?
- We broke up.
I knew it wouldn't last.
What makes you think
I'd go anywhere with you?
Because I'm your friend.
Muriel, you can't come bargin' in here
without warning...
trying to turn Rhonda
against the people who love her--
against the people who were there
for her when she needed them.
Yes, she can.
Sorry, Mum. You know I love you,
but you drive me crazy.
And you three--
what a bunch of cocksuckers.
Who do you think you are
to call me that?
I'm married. I'm beautiful!
You can dance
You can jive
Having the time of your life
Ooh, see that girl
- Watch that scene
- See you, Mum.
Diggin' the dancing queen
Friday night
and the lights are low
Looking out for a place to go
Mmm, where they play
the right music
Getting in the swing
you come to look for a king
Bye, street.
Bye, mall!
Goodbye, beach!
Goodbye, tourists!
Bye, plaza!
Goodbye, Surf Club!
See you, surfies!
- See ya, high rises!
- And when you get the chance
Bye, Fun World!
Goodbye, Porpoise Spit!
Young and sweet, only 17
Split & Resync: Xenzai[NEF]
***RETAIL SUB***
I was so afraid, Fernando
We were young and full of life
and none of us prepared to die
And I'm not ashamed to say
the roar of guns and cannons
Almost made me cry
There was something in the air
that night
The stars were bright, Fernando
They were shining there
for you and me
For liberty, Fernando
Though we never thought
that we could lose
There's no regret
If I had to do the same again
I would, my friend, Fernando
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org