Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
No.
Hey! Where's Howard and
the rest of the apprentices?
Left at the bottom to find their own
way up. You gotta learn sometime.
You wanna be a troubleshooter,
you gotta know the mine.
All clear down there?
Yeah, we won't
need these anymore...
but I wouldn't go
lightin' any matches.
Damn methane. Gonna blow this place
to shit one of these days.
We ain't that lucky.
Hey, come on, now!
Knock it off!
- Howard!
- Hey, Howard!
Hey, enjoy your walk up?
Yeah, real cool.
Why didn't you guys wait?
Look, Landers, you better
get a lot of exercise...
if you're gonna grapple
with Gretchen.
Oh, yeah? I got a valentine for her
that she's never gonna forget.
Right to the heart, huh?
It's gonna be a hot time
on Saturday night!
Stavisky, you do anything else
with that...
except throw it
over your shoulder and burp it?
Aw, get lost, Axel!
Bunch of clowns. Things haven't
changed a bit. Same as always.
Bet you wish
you never came back.
Especially now since Sarah's
goin' out with Axel.
No skin off my nose.
I don't give a damn.
Come on. Last one into town
gets the brew! Let's go!
Okay. Let's go, guys!
Quittin' time!
Casanova is here!
- Gretchen, it's me.
- Howard, stay away from me.
- Hi, babe.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- How are ya?
- I'm fine.
- How are you?
- Good to see ya.
Hi, sweetie.
You big lug.
I missed ya.
- Anything I should do?
- No. Of course not.
Gretchen, I want you to be my date
for the dance. Okay?
Dry up!
Gretchen, you know what'd
look really good on you?
- What?
- Me.
Suck it in
and zip it up, will ya?
Gretchen, why fight it?
Let the good times roll!
All right!
Hi, fellas.
Mabel, this is the best thing that's
happened to this town in years.
Your decorating committee
has done one hell of a job!
Well, after all, the first
Valentine's dance in 20 years...
has to be something special.
Yeah, well--
Of course, you're right, Mabel...
but we'd all be better off
if you played down the fact...
that it's the first
Valentine's dance in 20 years...
if you know what I mean.
Let's just concentrate on having
a good time Saturday night...
and put all that
other business to rest.
My thoughts exactly, Mayor.
- Hi, guy.
- Aw, come on, you clown!
Help Miss Osborne
pick those things up!
What the hell are you kids
doing in here?
You're supposed to be decorating
the room, not each other.
Where you goin', son?
I always go this time of day...
for another beer
and a real good nose pick.
I'm sorry, T.J.
I don't think he likes being back
in the mine very much.
Well, that's too bad. Nobody told
him to go out to the West Coast.
It's not my fault
he couldn't make it on his own.
But now that he's back, he's my son
and he's working in the mine.
Put those things back...
or I'll turn you both
upside down, especially you.
This is my date, Chief.
That meeting in Centerville is
at 7:00. We should hit the road.
Then let's go.
I'll see you kids later.
Bye, Mabel.
Keep up the good work.
See ya, Chief.
I might as well go too. All of this
will have to be rewashed.
I'm really sorry, Mabel.
This is station QPID,
940 on your radio dial.
- Oh! Mayor!
- Country-fried QPID...
from Valentine Bluffs, where the
heartland meets the sea.
Mayor?
Mayor, somebody left this for ya.
- For me? Who was it?
- I don't know.
It was inside when we got here.
Maybe you got a secret admirer, huh?
- You in on this, Mabel?
- I'm afraid not, Mayor.
Oh, no. No, no.
Don't look at me. I didn't
have a thing to do with it.
Well, hell.
I've been looking for an excuse...
to get off this miserable diet
Mrs. Hanniger has me on.
Thanks, Howard.
If there's one thing I like
better than Christmas candy...
it's Valentine's candy.
- Have some.
- Hey.
Who sent it?
"From the heart
comes a warning...
filled with bloody good cheer.
Remember what happened...
as the 14th draws near."
It can't be happening again.
It's a bad time,
this time of year.
There's bad things coming,
my words you hear.
Beware of the 14th
if you value your life.
Here we go again. How many times
is he gonna tell that story?
Oh, let him tell it.
I love fairy tales.
This ain't no fairy tale,
little girl!
If you don't take it seriously,
you're a fool!
Ow!
Hurt yourself?
Axel, are you okay?
Oh, no! Let me see.
I know what I'm talking about.
I'm telling you now.
This town is accursed.
It all started 20 years ago.
It was the night
of the Valentine's Day dance...
at the Union Hall.
The biggest event of the year.
It'd been a tradition
for over a hundred years.
Everybody was there,
except for...
seven miners who were out
at the Hanniger Mine.
Five of them
still down below.
Two supervisors were waiting
for the men to come up.
Anxious to get to the party...
they left before the men
were safely out...
failing to check the methane gas
levels in the tunnels down below.
The five men were buried alive...
as the town
continued its party.
For six weeks we dug 'round
the clock to try to save them.
After we broke through,
one man was found alive.
I was the one
who found him.
Harry Warden spent the next year
in the state mental hospital.
Exactly one year later,
on Valentine's Day...
he came back to town.
He killed the two supervisors...
who had left their posts
the year before.
Then he cut out their hearts...
and stuffed them
into heart-shaped candy boxes.
That night at the dance,
we found the boxes...
blood dripping out the sides.
Inside was a note--
a warning from Harry...
never to hold a Valentine's dance
ever again.
Every February 14th,
Harry comes back to town...
his pickax stained with blood...
waiting in the shadows
of the Hanniger Mine...
just for someone to kill...
should they not heed his warning.
It could be you!
I know what I'm sayin'.
Forget about having a party at all
on Saturday night...
or you may not live
to see daylight.
Laugh now...
but you'll be sorry
you didn't listen to me.
Uh-oh!
Come on, Hap!
Lighten up!
It's a stupid legend.
It gives me the creeps.
All right, you guys.
Who ordered the Moosehead?
I did, you gorgeous slab
of female fleshiness.
There is a young barmaid
named Harriet
Who's never been robbed
of her cherry yet
Oh, try as she may
This girl can't get laid
A Valentine virgin
named Harriet
Why did you hit me
in the ribs like that?
- Hey, where ya goin'?
- I just want to put on some music.
Be my guest.
Excuse me.
It's your own fault.
You know that, don't you, T.J.?
Never said it wasn't.
Then why can't you
accept things the way they are?
Thing is, I don't like
the way things are.
Excuse me.
Yes. All right.
Thank you very much.
I have to call in the morning.
The administration office
is closed at night.
The nurse that's on duty
doesn't know a thing.
She's got to know
whether he's there or not!
I just hope this is
some kind of joke, and the kids...
are just trying to scare us.
If it is a joke, I want every one
of those kids strung up...
starting with
that damn Howard Landers!
Well, it's a human heart, all right.
Ayoung woman.
About 30 years old.
What are you guys doin'
with a loose heart?
Looks like a butcher
ripped this thing out.
What's goin' on
over in Valentine Bluffs?
You remember Harry Warden?
Oh, God, of course I remember.
Those were terrible murders.
God. I thought they locked him up
in Eastfield 20 years ago.
- They did.
- Are you sure he's still there?
We'll find out in the morning.
I'm checking on it.
Well, gentlemen, I'd say
you have your answer.
It looks like Harry Warden's
back in town.
Well, now.
I wonder who sent this.
Jake?
"Roses are red,
violets are blue...
One is dead,
and so are you"?
No!
No! Get away!
Get away!
No, don't!
Get away! No! No!
No!
This is gettin' really good.
Don't put your nose in it.
Hey, this is what I really call
"junk food."
How much longer, Hollis?
I'm freezin'.
Relax. This thing
ain't no microwave.
How 'bout rewin' it up?
- Man, have I got the munchies.
- Yeah, me too.
A little protein patrol, eh, boys?
- Don't go pokin' my meat.
- Oh, come on.
Probably cooked.
- Don't stick your nose in the food.
- It's his. He can do what he wants.
Is that turkey?
I asked for roast beef.
Turkey for the turkey.
Here.
Come on.
Shove over.
- Sure is cold tonight.
- Yeah.
I guess we got ourselves
a problem, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess so.
What are we gonna do about it?
Well, there ain't nothin'
to do about it.
Sarah's goin' with me now...
and that's all there is to it.
I ain't gonna back off
for you, T.J.
Nobody asked you
to go away, T.J.
Come on, Axel. Don't give me
any of that horseshit.
You're beginning to sound
like my old man.
Too bad, man.
Look, you left.
You went away, and we didn't
know where you were...
or when you were comin' back.
I ain't gonna back off for you.
You stay the hell away from Sarah!
All right, all right!
You want a fight, then you got it!
'Cause you and I
both know who Sarah wants.
You're kinda hard on him, Teej.
Can't exactly blame him.
Sure it's not his fault.
It's nobody's fault.
I don't know what to do.
You know, I really do like
that son of a bitch.
Hey, remember?
Remember how we used to
tear this place apart?
Eh? Get drunk,
race out to the bluffs.
That was great.
I guess things change, huh?
Nothin' stays the same.
W-A-R-D-E-N.
Harry Warden. He was
committed under court order...
approximately 20 years ago.
Well, I'm afraid I have no records
of a Harry Warden, past or present.
How can that be?
He was committed there,
under court order!
I'm sorry. I have
no records on him.
In 20 years, any number of things
could have happened.
Now, if this Harry Warden
was committed, as you say...
then he's simply
no longer here...
and if I have no records on him,
I have to assume...
that he's transferred,
he's released, or he's on the slab.
One of three,
take your pick.
One out of three?
Now, look,
Mrs. Raleigh...
you're gonna have to do
a little bit better than that.
Now, I have to know
what happened to this man...
and I have to know
what happened to him now!
Now, have you
checked everything?
Everything, except the microfilms
over in central file...
and it will take
several days to check that.
I need answers fast.
I'll be waiting for your call.
Dr. Peyton, 3-5-3.
Jumpin'Je-- They don't even know
what the hell happened to him.
What more do we need to know?
It's gotta be Harry.
Maybe we oughta
cancel the dance.
Just decide which one
you really want.
And now for the big moment.
Will it be number one
or will it be number two?
Patty, will you be serious?
This is important.
- You can't have 'em both.
- I don't want them both.
- Oh, no?
- No.
Just what I thought.
Oh, I don't know.
T.J. won't talk to me.
He just sulks
all day long.
He ends up making me
feel guilty...
when he's the one
who owes me the apology.
And Axel is not behaving
any better.
Oh, Patty, I don't even want to go
to the dance on Saturday night.
Oh, but you gotta go.
It'll be all right.
Stay with Hollis and me. Besides,
you gotta see the dress I got.
Cut down to here, slit up to there.
I may not get out alive!
Mabel?
Mabel, I gotta talk to you. We got
a problem concerning the dance.
Mabel, you back here?
Okay. Little John, I want you
and Mike to check the wall.
T.J., take care of the sump.
You get a pump down there,
or I ain't doin' it.
You do it, or you get your ass
outta here for good.
I'll do it.
What's buggin' him today?
Son of a bitch is after my ass
'cause of Sarah.
- Keeps it up, I'm gonna nail him.
- I said move it, Hanniger!
Oh, yeah.
Come on, man.
Anytime, loser.
Hey, that's it!
Break it up, you two!
T.J., you get your ass
up top to 217!
Let go!
There ain't gonna be no fighting
in my section, Palmer! Understand?
What an awful smell.
This is like it was
20 years ago.
I can remember those murders
just like it was yesterday.
Jake, you gotta
get help from Granville.
No, not yet.
Call in Granville, we'll have police
crawling all over this place...
and we'll have a hell of a panic
on our hands.
You just mention
that Harry's back...
and this town won't be worth
the powder to blow it to hell.
Just a minute, boys.
I want you to bring
the ambulance around back.
Load her up from there. I don't
want anybody in town seeing this.
You remember. Mabel Osborne died
of a heart attack, and that's all.
Breathe one word
of this to anybody...
and you'll have to answer to me.
Wait a minute.
What's this?
Take her away.
"It happened once,
it happened twice.
Cancel the dance,
or it'll happen thrice."
Well, that's it.
The dance is canceled.
Let's tear every poster,
every banner, every decoration...
down and out of sight!
I don't want to see a single
Valentine's heart anywhere.
As long as this town
is decorated to the hilt...
Harry's gonna
keep on killing and--
And get that damn
Union Hall locked up!
All right, Mayor.
No, I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do about it.
What's goin' on?
The mayor has canceled the dance,
and that's all there is to it.
In the light of Mabel's death,
he had no choice.
There'll be no parties either.
We owe her that much respect.
Mabel would have wanted us
to have the dance.
- She worked so hard on it.
- Yeah, you can't cancel it now.
He's looking for an excuse
to cancel the dance.
That's the way it is.
There'll be no dance
tomorrow night...
and no parties either.
Do you understand me?
Hanniger!
- We have something to settle.
- You bet we do.
Howard, you gotta chew it.
You don't blow bubbles with it.
I'll take care of myself.
How did you ever get
to be so stupid?
Come on.
Let's take a shower.
T.J., will you stop this?
I don't wanna go with you!
Are you listening to me?
Nope.
Remember this spot?
Of course
I remember this spot.
Why didn't you write me, T.J.?
Why didn't you call?
I wanted to, believe me,
but I couldn't.
I mean, I really
fell on my ass out there.
I made so many mistakes.
But I learned something.
Look. Give me a chance.
If you still want me
to go away, I will...
but I have to tell you that
I love you and I want you back.
How was I supposed
to know that,Jessie?
I honestly didn't think
you were ever coming back.
You just left me here.
Sarah, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm so damn sorry.
That's what I am
And, girl
I don't expect you to understand
I just play my song
And right or wrong
Now music's all I need
to get along
Women and wine
don't thrill me like they used to
- And I don't feel--
- You seen Sarah?
Ain't my turn
to watch after her.
Damn it, Sarah, why do you
do this to yourself?
How am I
gonna tell Axel?
Sarah!
- Chief Newby.
- I'm sorry I startled you.
It's all right.
- Is something the matter?
- No, I'm--
I'm just making
my nightly patrol.
Right.
- Good night, Chief.
- Good night, Sarah.
- Just a-diggin'in my mine
- Beer, Hap.
- I'll take my time makin'you mine
- You hear about Mabel Osborne?
- I'm a part-time lover
- She got it just the way I said.
- Mmm, you're a full-time fool
- Heart attack, my ass!
If we aren't gonna have
a Valentine's dance...
what are we gonna do?
Why don't we have
a Valentine party?
A party!
Where? Newby's got this whole town
locked up, bright guy.
- How 'bout my father's mine?
- T.J., are you crazy?
- Come on.
- The mine!
In the mine?
That'd be great.
- It would! What a blast!
- In the mine, that's exactly...
- what it would be.
- It'd be great!
Come on. We got
everything we need down there.
Let's see. We got a rec room,
we got a pool table, everything.
Yeah, in the mine. Where people
get killed and eaten.
Beware of Harry Warden.
Shut the fuck up!
Beware of what you make fun of,
you little asshole!
- Who?
- You!
Forget about having a party at all
tomorrow night, or you'll be sorry.
Lighten up, Hap.
Piss on Harry Warden
and that damn old legend.
We're gonna
have ourselves a party.
Don't you go
tellin' nobody.
Don't say
I didn't warn you.
That settles it, then!
We're goin' to the mine.
We're gonna have ourselves a party.
- All right!
- Whoo!
You're a full-time fool
Assholes.
Yeah. Damn kids.
I'll show them.
Piss on Harry Warden, will they?
Well, I'll give 'em a scare
they'll never forget.
Lights!
Come on!
It's cold out here!
- Hey, it's party time!
- This is great!
Hey, Hollis!
...Saturday night and we'll stick
around till the mornin'light
Let the good times roll
Yeah, let the good times roll
Let the good times roll--
Well, I work all day
just pushin'dirt
Got grease in my hair
coal on my shirt
Hi, Ben. Anything happen?
- No. It's been quiet all evening.
- Good.
That came for you, though.
Oh, my God.
- Get me a coffee, will ya, Ben?
- Yeah, sure, Chief.
Mabel.
Yoo! Does anybody
want a beer?
Hollis, check this out.
You asshole!
Hey, who busted the lock?
I got the keys right here.
- Howard did.
- Uh-oh!
- Howard.
- Harry Warden did it.
And whoever parked
the red Volkswagen out front...
I want it parked out back
with the others, like I said.
I don't want Newby
snoopin' around here.
Let me show you.
That's pretty crude!
Quiet. You're making
too much noise!
- Hey, whoa, Mr. Party.
- Whoa.
Johnny's got a catch there.
Hey,Johnny, where you going?
Sylvia's gonna get it!
Talk to you
in a minute, okay?
So, you're looking pretty good,
baby face. What's the occasion?
I figure it will get
Newby off my back.
Besides, I wanna get out
of this town pretty quick.
You know, I think
he really likes you.
I've got the munchies.
Hot dogs.
Here, Spot.
No! Who is that?
I got a feeling
about the mine, Ben.
I'll check back
with you, all right?
Make sure you call me on the radio
if anything comes up.
Will do.
What the hell is that?
Go on!
Get the hell outta here!
"You didn't stop the party."
Stop the party?
What damn party?
Stavisky, you couldn't clean
that table with a broom!
Aw, Hollis,
you don't even know--
Hey, guys, check this out.
Check this out. Gretchen.
What are you doing, man?
- Eww!
- Oh, wow!
The first time I tried
to snort Coke, and I almost drown.
Next time,
try harder.
- Axel, please.
- Oh, come on.
Axel, please, don't.
- What's the matter, baby?
- Axel, please, don't.
- Oh, come on!
- Will you please stop it?
Guess you better
back off there, Axel.
You back
the fuck off, man.
We were doing just fine until you
decided to come crawlin' home.
In case you haven't noticed,
things are changed around here.
She don't want nothin'
to do with you.
Do you mind?
I have my own mouth, thank you.
Then why don't you use it?
Tell him.
Tell me what?
She wants to come back
with me.
- Bullshit, man!
- Why don't you both just back off?
You're acting like
a couple of jerks.
Oh, well, you just
love it, don't you?
That's it.
You son of a bitch!
Hollis, do something!
Hollis! Let go!
- Damn it!
- Let go!
Shit! You guys,
knock it off!
- T.J., are you outta shape.
- Get outta here!
Sure you're okay?
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
T.J., please stop it.
I just don't care anymore.
Just leave me alone.
Come on.
Okay, listen. I showed you how to
do it with the right nostril, right?
You take the straw, you put it
up the neck-- the left nostril...
and you snort it.
Oh! Come on!
Loosen it up!
Let's have fun. We're at
a Valentine's party, for God's sake!
I'm getting
a little punchy myself.
How do you
get those down?
- Pull the rope.
-Just pull it?
Yeah, yeah.
Release the hook and let it go.
Mm. You know what we need?
Yeah, I got one right here.
No, I meant
a couple of beers.
- I'll go get 'em.
- I'll go with you.
No, you stay here,
and I'll be back in a flash.
- Okay, but don't take too long.
- Back in a minute.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
- Hey, T.J.
- Hey,John, how ya doin'?
I'm doing great.
Is something the matter?
Same old shit.
Howard really makes me gag.
- You're not kidding.
- I kinda like Tommy.
Oh, I agree.
- Hi,John.
- Hi, girls.
Yuck! What is this?
Oh, wow. One of those idiots
really thinks he's funny.
It's probably Howard.
John, is that you?
John?
John, if you're trying to scare me,
you're doing a good job.
Help! Help!
No!
Sorry I took so long, babe.
Sylvia?
All right.
Hey, all right.
All right. Sylvia?
I know you're in there,
and I'm comin' in.
Sylvia?
Come in, Mobile One.
Mobile One here.
Jake, you just got
a call from Eastfield.
A woman named Raleigh.
She said it was urgent.
All right.
Mobile One coming in.
How 'bout a little trip
down to the mine?
- The mine?
- It'll be great.
It's like a roller coaster,
isn't it?
It's 2,000 feet down.
That's okay. It'll cheer her up.
Come on, Hollis.
- Mike, let's go.
- What?
-Hollis, you goin' down to the mine?
-Well--
Yes. Come on.
- All right!
- Come on.
- Chicken.
- Chicken?
- Why don't we go down to the mine?
- All right.
One quick ride down
and right back up.
What about gear?
Yeah, get that six-pack.
This is gonna
be great, baby!
Watch your step.
Come on.
This is ridiculous with you girls
in those dresses.
Hollis! Where do you
think you're going?
We're going for a quick ride
and coming right back up.
You can't. You know the rule.
No women in the mine.
We're gonna come right back
up again. Believe me.
Watch your step.
Howard, don't be
a pain in the ass.
"Pain in the ass"?
What "pain in the ass"?
- Watch your step, okay?
- Be careful.
Down we go!
Come on, you guys.
Hop in the cars. I'll be right back.
- Yeah, we made it.
- You just let me know!
Here, Sarah,
put this around you.
Michael, here you go.
And a blanket.
And a blanket?
Hollis, you got one for me?
Here's one for you.
I'll be right back.
Can you believe we're
really doing this?
It's so dark
down there!
On second thought, I think
I'm gonna stay right up here.
No, you don't. If I'm goin' down
there, baby, you're goin' with me.
- Oh, great.
- Hold on, everybody.
Here we go!
Keep your hands inside.
- Pass me that beer!
- All right!
Come on. Pass a couple
up this way.
- Where's the lantern?
- Right here.Just stick with me.
Look out below!
Hold on.
Get ready for bumps.
Hey, Hollis, pass me a beer.
Want one, Mike?
How far down
does this go?
- Come on, Sarah.
- Here you go.
Wow!
All right!
Little bitty free ride.
There we go.
- Stops all by itself.
- Great, Hollis.
Let's go. Yeah, I hope you kids
enjoyed yourself...
'cause we're goin' right back up.
- That was great. Let's do it again.
- Howard usually walks.
Let's do it again.
Come on.
Where does that go?
That leads to an abandoned part.
We don't go down there anymore.
- Take us on a tour, Hollis.
- Yeah!
- Yeah, let's show 'em around.
- All right, all right.
Just because we're here.
Come on.
Keep those blankets wrapped
around you. You're gonna get filthy.
Okay, Daddy.
It's cold down here.
All right, boys and girls.
This is called a tipple.
So that's a tipple.
This is also
called a tipple.
Hey, Howard, come on!
- Comin'.
- Howard, come on!
I'm comin'! I just heard something.
Probably some rats.
Rats? You never
told me there are rats!
This is the old engine room.
Boy, what a nice view back here.
We'll meet you in ten minutes
over at the main shaft!
All right. No longer.
We're going straight up.
How do you like my pad, huh?
I can't believe you work here.
Yep.
- He's in there!
- What is it? What's the matter?
He's in there!
- What's going on? What's going on?
- His face!
She's dead.
- He killed--
- What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Dave is dead!
And Sylvia!
Somebody's killed her!
It's Harry Warden!
He's here!
Everybody, get the fuck out!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on! Come on!
Son of a bitch must've
cut the phone lines!
Listen to me. I want you to make
sure everybody gets out of here.
I want you to get the chief and tell
him to get here, and fast! Now go!
Sarah, she's in the mine
with the others.
- What?
- Her, Hollis and Patty.
They took the railcars down there.
They're in the mine right now.
- We gotta get them out.
- That's where he probably is.
He'll kill them!
I'm gonna get them out.
Come on! Come on!
Go! Go!
Come on!
If anything happens to Sarah,
it'll be your fault!
You never should've let them
go down there!
Let's worry about getting them out.
I'll take the abandoned section.
You take the level above.
We'll meet in the main shaft
by the elevator.
I hope to God we get there
before Harry does.
Good luck.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
Boo! Gotcha.
Damn you, Hollis.
Where the hell were you?
I thought you were right behind me.
You must've taken the wrong tunnel.
Oh, sure we did.
You did that on purpose.
Me?
Come on.
Watch your head.
Watch your step as well.
This is the oldest part
of the mine.
Oh, gosh!
These tunnels were built
in the early 1800s.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's all abandoned now.
We haven't worked down here
in years.
Not since Harry Warden.
Howard, what do you think
you're trying to do, you jerk?
Easy. I got a hangover.
- Boy, did you guys jump.
- I'll get you down.
Oh, Howard, you goof.
- Get down out of there.
- Wait. I'll go the other way.
- For Pete's sake.
- I know what I'm doing.
God, you guys.
- Come on. Hold it.
- Ooh, that feels so good.
- Get your light.
- Got it.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- You all right?
- Come on.
Get down! Stick with us
and quit clowning around.
- I was just having some of fun.
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, you guys,
where's Mike and Harriet?
- Maybe Harry Warden got 'em.
- Stop it!
- Howard, come along and behave.
- Yeah, let's go.
- My blanket!
- Come on.
You'd forget your head
if it wasn't tied on with rope.
- It's freezing down here.
- Who's leading this tour?
I feel so good.
So do I.
Where are we going now?
This leads to the main shaft.
We're going up.
How come the walls are
so white around here, Hollis?
I told you, it's lime powder. They
put it here to contain explosions...
and they put it on the wood
so it doesn't get dry and crack.
Hey, you guys, how come Mike
and Harriet haven't come back yet?
What's that?
I thought I heard something.
It's probably only rats.
That ain't no rat.
Come on. Let's go find Mike
and Harriet and get out of here.
Come on.
Tommy Whitcomb, what's the matter
with you? Where's your brains?
- How many times have I told you--
- Chief, listen to me!
You have to go to the mine.
We were having a party, and Harry
Warden started killing everybody!
Harry Warden is at the mine. There's
a bunch of kids trapped below.
Axel and T.J.
are trying to get them out.
He killed Sylvia and Dave!
Get back in that car
and get home and stay put!
Go on!
- Mobile One in.
- Go ahead, Chief.
Yeah, Ben.
Call the mayor right away.
Then round up every available man.
Meet me back at the mine.
I think there's some kids
trapped down below.
Out.
- Howard, would you get up front?
- I'm trying to get up in the front.
- Do we know where we're going?
- I can't even see.
Just stay beside me.
- Why don't they answer us?
- Stavisky!
We never should have
left them in the first place.
- Maybe they're down there.
-Jesus!
- What are you trying to do?
- You scared me!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, we're fine.
- What's the matter with you?
- We gotta get out of here.
Harry Warden is back.
- He's killed Sylvia and Dave.
- Are you kidding?
What are you saying? Harry's dead.
Harry died a long time ago.
Will you shut up
and listen to me, goddamn it?
Now, they're dead,
and he's down here somewhere.
If you want to get out alive,
you do exactly as I tell you.
What are we gonna do?
This better not be
your idea of a joke, T.J.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Come on. Let's go.
Wait a minute, now.
What about Mike and Harriet?
The last time I saw them,
they were in the engine room.
You check the main shaft. I'll take
tunnel six and meet you there.
Howard, you stay with the girls...
- and wait for Axel.
- Me?
- Stay with Howard. Stay there!
- No, Hollis, please!
Hollis, wait a minute!
Howard, you watch the girls!
I don't even know
my way around here.
Oh, shit!
Michael and Harriet, this isn't
any time to be doing anything.
Oh,Jesus!
Oh, God, Hollis.
Oh, it's not fair.
Hollis, please--
Come on.
He's dead. He's dead!
- Come on! Come on!
- Patty, come on.
Come on! He's dead!
Now come on!
- Howard, you bastard!
- He's dead! Now come on!
You can't leave us like this!
Please, help me!
- Leave him alone!
- Let go of me!
Patty, we need the light,
damn it!
Okay. Come on, Patty.
Don't do this to me.
We have to get out of here!
Stop it!
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Where are the others?
We saw him.
He was standing right there.
Harry Warden is down here!
- Come on. Let's go.
- Come on.
Let's go! Come on!
Where the hell is T.J.?
He went looking
for Mike and Harriet.
He told us to stay here.
Come on. The cage
is right up ahead. Let's go!
- Keep moving. You're gonna be fine.
- Axel, please, no!
I don't want to leave him there.
Please, let's go back and get him.
- Oh, please, Axel, no!
- Keep moving.
- Patty, stop it.
- I don't wanna leave him there.
You'll be fine.
You're gonna be just fine.
- Where are you taking us?
- Keep moving. We're almost there.
- I can't--
- Keep moving. You're doing fine.
That's it.
Oh, God, where are we going?
I can't make it anymore!
Shut up! Yes, you can!
- Come on. Let's go!
- I can't!
Let's go.
Oh, God.
It's T.J.
- Aw, shit!
- What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were Harry!
Do I look like Harry?
- Where's Howard?
- He ran off.
That jerk. He's never gonna find
his way out of here alone.
Hollis is dead.
Look, we gotta get
Sarah and Patty up top...
get some help
and come back for the others.
- Come on.
- Okay, let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Let's keep going.
Mobile One, come in.
Mobile One.
Come in, Mobile One.
Watch your step.
I can't even see.
- We're almost there.
- Keep your voices down.
Come on.
- Please hurry.
- Keep your voices down.
He smashed the control panel.
We're not getting out of here.
What?
What are we gonna do?
Climb.
Come on.
Watch your footing, now.
Axel, please slow down.
Patty, you're okay.
I'm right behind you. Keep going.
Come on. Don't look down.
Keep looking up.
Patty, just do as he says
and you'll be fine. I promise.
I don't want to go any further!
Please, can we stop
and go another way?
There's no other way!
Now move it, damn it!
Axel, you have to go slower.
I'm right behind her.
She keeps stopping.
Go slower, okay?
I'm scared of heights,
you guys.
I'm not going any further.
I'm stopping right here.
Sarah, give her a hand!
It's okay.
I'm right behind you.
Come on.
- Stay close.
- Okay. I'm right behind you.
Good girl.
Keep moving. Good girl.
Come down!
Come down, quick! Down!
Don't look.
Don't look at him.
Come on!
Patty, over here.
Now he's up top. That bastard's
really playing games with us.
We can beat him if we
can get to the railcars.
I know a shortcut through the sump.
It's over there.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Nice and slow.
Let's go. Slowly.
T.J., take the girls over, and give
me a yell when you're across, okay?
Go!
Watch your step.
Okay, Axel, we're clear.
Come on over.
T.J., do something.
There's nothing I can do.
It's 60-feet deep.
Gosh!
We've gotta get out of here.
- We can't just leave him here.
- Move it!
It's too late for Axel.
Come on.
Okay, you just hug along
the left side of the wall.
Just keep going.
Go on. Continue.
- But why--
-Just do as he says.
Answer us.
Let's go this way.
Careful.
Okay, there's gotta
be some way out of here.
Come on. Keep going.
Come on.
It's okay.
I just got hit.
Come on.
We've gotta hurry.
The elevator isn't working.
We're gonna have to go in
this way. Let's go!
Jump!
Everyone, watch this thing coming!
Oh, my God.
Sarah, move it!
Get in. Get in!
Watch out!
Why?
Come on.
He's in there.
Are you two all right?
- It isn't Harry Warden.
- Yeah, I know, T.J.
I got a call from Eastfield
late this evening.
They said that Harry Warden
died five years ago.
Well, then, who is it?
- It's Axel.
- Oh, my God.
Get where you're going.
My God.
It was on Valentine's Day that
Harry Warden killed Axel's father!
- Let's get in there.
- Yeah.
He's alive!
Oh, my God!
T.J., I have to see him!
Hanniger, I'll be waiting
in hell for you!
Harry, I'm coming!
This whole fucking town
is going to die!
We're coming back,
you bastards!
Sarah, be my bloody valentine.
Daddy's gone away
Harry Warden made you pay
Once upon a time
on a sad Valentine's
In a place known as Hanniger Mine
A legend began
Every woman and man
Would always remember the time
And those who remain
were never the same
You could see
the fear in their eyes
Once every year
as the 14th draws near
There's a hush
all over the town
Oh, the legend, they say
On a Valentine's Day
Is a curse that'll live on and on
And no one will know
as the years come and go
Of the horror from long time ago
Twenty years came and went
And everyone spent
the 14th in quiet regret
And those still alive
know the secret survives
In the darkness
that looms in the night
Oh, the legend, they say
On a Valentine's Day
Is a curse that'll live on and on
And no one will know
As the years come and go
Of the horror from long time ago
In this little town
When the 14th comes around
There's a silence
and fear in the air
Remember the morn
That the legend was born
All the shock
and the horror was there
Oh, the legend, they say
On a Valentine's Day
Is a curse that'll live on and on
And no one will know
As the years come and go
Of the horror from long time ago
And no one will know
As the years come and go
Of the horror from long time
Ago
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org