I'm about to tell you what does matter.
You're about to listen
like your life depended on it.
A month ago, an undercover
officer was murdered off West Grand.
They beat him up, put a gun to his head
and put a bullet through it.
I don't want to hear about
what you don't know or didn't do.
You ain't got the nut sack
for that size. You didn't kill him.
His name was Michael Calvess.
Take a gander at that.
Hold on a minute. You
motherfuckers come up in my crib.
Throw hot sauce
and blind my fucking ass.
- Want me to help you?
- Street name Jimmy Fredericks.
I know you know him.
My bets.
I know this motherfucker.
I might have let him suck on my dick.
You want to be bounced
back to County, keep it up.
I'll have you
braiding some nigger's hair.
Piece of shit!
Fuck. I think I'm bleeding.
Act like a punk,
you gonna get played like one.
Listen very carefully. They found
smack at the murder scene.
You took some of the same stuff ten
months ago. It nearly killed your ass.
You don't have the chemistry
or the sense God gave goats.
You didn't do the cook.
Dowd is dead. Who sold to you?
Whatever.
You gonna tell us? No?
You're a fucking smart ass.
We're tossing every inch of this place.
- Where is it?
Oh my God. This must be one of
those refrigerator safes that locks.
What's all this?
Bagels and guns. What do you know?
- Tell us. Who sold you?
- Come on. Fuck all this shit.
You're unbelievably so dumb.
Are you kidding me?
This is the last time
I'm going to ask you. Who sold you?
I don't know.
- It was Darnell.
- He's got a cop ID.
It's got a shield.
You all right?
Let me see. Where you hit, neck?
Let me call it in.
I'll call the paramedics.
Hang in there. I'll be right back.
...I've used a mild sedative for him.
But I'm worried about
his history of drug abuse.
I need to go and pick up my son,
but I'm going to be back.
He didn't do it.
I don't know if you're not listening or
you don't want to, but he didn't do it.
We've compiled enough evidence
to support the contrary.
What does that mean?
What evidence?
We're closing it.
There's no way
Sheps killed Calvess.
If you're closing because of that,
you're way off.
Neither of us believe he did it.
He didn't have the capabilities,
the cold blood.
This guy did not do it.
He had no compunction when
faced with arrest for trying to kill you.
This is someone of
questionable mental stability.
- With a history of drug use.
- That you can pin motive on?
That can ride the rap after the fact.
You are jazzed up cos this piece
of shit we killed, Sheps, was white.
The racial card gets cooled and
you can forget about the dead cop.
Henry, ease off.
We initiated and backed this effort
from the very beginning.
Irrefutable is the following. A
known criminal with over 40 offences.
A drug tie linking him to Calvess,
in possession of stolen weapons,
narcotics and identification
belonging to another slain officer.
Richard Tekulve
was stabbed three years ago.
Homicide got a confession
and conviction. That's irrelevant.
- It denotes illicit criminal activity.
- This is unbelievable.
Sheps came into possession
of the ID as a result of
participation in the murder
or association with the murderer.
This guy was
105 pounds soaking wet.
The injuries that Calvess sustained
only could've come from two men
of considerably more strength.
That's not even taking into account,
there's no murder weapon.
What are we talking about?
This matter is no longer mine,
gentlemen. I apologise.
- You're serious?
- It's the Commissioner of Police.
- That is so fucked up.
- Yes, it is fucked up.
This is so fucked up.
We're done.
You're so wrong, pal.
Fucking bullshit.
I'm sorry, Nick.
I want you to stop now.
This is done.
It's not.
It has to be.
You know I wasn't happy,
and that was fine.
But this is where I hit the wall
cos I've seen you like this before.
Before I was willing to put myself
through it, but I can't do it anymore.
We didn't get them.
We didn't get the guys that did it.
We fucking
didn't do it
cos we, I... I lost him.
I lost him.
You're running at this
for all the wrong reasons.
You think catching him
is going to make you less like them?
Purified, just like Calvess?
That's bullshit.
That's not what he was.
That's not what you are.
I love you. I do.
With everything that I am.
But I'm still going to leave.
I can't be with you like this.
I'm not trying.
I'm done trying.
Tellis, you've got
something on your desk.
Look at this.
- Where did you get a warrant?
- Friends where friends count.
I ran that name
Deacon gave us, Darnell.
Darnell Beery. Possession. His last
arrest was pulling a gun on an officer.
- Look who he was booked with.
- Eugene Sheps, Latroy Steeds.
Steeds nor Beery were never
questioned about Mike's murder.
'They all used to work at Titan's Auto.
It closed down six months ago.
'I want to check this place out.'
Hey!
Freeze!
Do not fucking move!
Do not move!
- Get down!
- Fuck you.
Fucking tried to blow my head off.
Is this Darnell?
Let me fucking see you.
Come on. We've got
some fucking shit to talk about.
Get me my lawyer. I don't see
no badge. I don't see no warrant.
I didn't do this shit, man.
You, shut the fuck up.
I'm Det. Lt. Henry Oak of the Detroit
Metropolitan Police Department.
This is Detective Sergeant Tellis.
We already know who you are,
which is why we are here.
You've been hiding from us
cos you killed a cop.
That cop's name was
Michael Calvess, Jimmy Fredericks.
I'm going to give you the opportunity
to come clean on this and confess.
If you choose in your limited wisdom,
to fuck around with me
and force my hand,
you're both going out of here in a bag.
Fuck that. What you're doing is illegal.
Give me my fucking phone call.
You need more than a phone call.
You've got a hell of a jacket.
Multiple counts. Assault, B & E,
felony possession, grand theft auto.
Add to that murder of a decorated cop
and you've fucked yourself for life.
I didn't murder no fucking cop.
I'm going to toss this place.
Anything you want to tell me?
No?
Fine.
This is next.
Whose ride is this? Yours?
This must be your car, Darnell.
Huh, Big D? Is this yours?
Give me the keys.
- Fuck this. No keys.
- Say "fuck you" again.
Say "fuck you" again to me.
Your ride? OK.
- Take us in.
- Going to fuck around with me?
- No.
- Huh?
No!
Fuck! No!
This ain't right, man.
Lieutenant!
Look at that.
Fuck.
You brothers throwing a coup?
You selling this shit to the Serbs?
Police issue.
That's from the impound. Let's hear it.
What you been doing? Huh, Holmes?
Been sneaking into the impound?
You're in a lot of trouble.
This is it.
This is Calvess' gun.
This is Mike's gun.
What are you doing
with a dead cop's gun?
Answer me! What are you doing
Answer me!
I don't know nothing
about no dead cop's gun.
A police issue revolver.
It belongs to a slain officer.
- That was not in there.
- What?
- That gun wasn't in there.
- Shut up!
- What you fucking doing with it?
- That's bullshit. It's a throwaway.
- What?
- You planted that.
I planted it?
Blood on the barrel.
Dried blood on the trigger guard.
Who the fuck planted that?
Come on.
Listen to me.
You better get a groove going.
You're in a life and death struggle.
Right fucking now.
- My lawyer.
- What?
- I want my lawyer.
- There are no lawyers.
It's just me and you.
I am in your shit for the duration.
You planted that.
Say one more fucking thing.
Please say one more thing.
In the fucking trunk.
No, I didn't do it. In the trunk.
What did I tell you?
They get dumber every year.
Nice and easy.
OK? We'll get this over real quick.
You're going to tell me
loud and clear what happened.
Two months ago,
a walking tunnel off West Grand.
You found out
there was an undercover cop.
You confronted him.
You overpowered him
and you beat him.
You took his pistol off of him.
You took it. You pointed it in his skull.
You pulled the trigger and killed him.
He died instantly.
A fucking lie.
I lied?
Remember Jimmy Fredericks?
Look at him.
You fucking remember him?
He was a junkie.
What'd you say? He's a what?
- Junkie.
- You're bullshit.
We saw that motherfucker
three or four times a day.
You found out he was undercover.
You tried to sell him a bad score,
hoping it would kill him.
He didn't use it, so you shot him.
You're bullshit.
You dealing motherfucker.
Fuck you. I'm gonna kill him.
Where do you think
we got them cop guns from?
That motherfucker used to swipe it,
sell it and get high regularly.
He was a cop.
A cop you killed. He had a wife.
He had kids.
No, not like this. Stop.
We bring them in like this,
lawyers will crucify us.
Put them under duress,
this bust gets bounced at arraignment.
These two colour us Klan
and walk.
They fucking walk for good.
We're too close.
There's a kit in the car.
We get it, we roll prints off the pistol.
You grab it. I'm going to call a wagon.
No. Don't call it in.
We're going to get
the confessions on tape.
Then we call it in.
I want some time
alone with these two. OK?
All right.
But grab the kit, all right?
We've got conclusive guilt.
We've got the murder weapon.
It's top heavy for conviction.
I'll go upstairs.
I'll bag whatever evidence I can find.
Let them get their shit straight.
It makes no sense
to knuckle down on them right now.
A brief reprieve, all right?
So suck it up.
Why you gotta lock the door?
- Are things gonna get worse?
- Shut up.
If anything happens to my daughter.
- Look me in the eyes.
- I know you.
I know you way before this shit.
You killed Elvin.
- How do you know?
- How you think?
Calvess just blow his own game?
Blow his own spot, man?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Who snitched you out
to Dowd about being a cop?
Do you think
that shit fell out of the sky?
He came after you
after Calvess told him you was 5-0.
He's a cop. He's one of me.
What the fuck
you think we making this up for?
We ain't got nothing to gain.
They're both dead.
You think Calvess is
some kind of a fucking saint?
That's something
he's about the furthest thing from.
Listen to me. We have seconds.
Make every single one count.
Before he left, he yelled.
You said he knew who killed Calvess.
- What does that mean?
- Your fucking partner, Oak, is dirty.
- He's fucking lying to you.
- What?
- He's lying to you.
- What's he lying about?
About what went down
in that tunnel, who killed that cop.
Everything. Why you think
we still up in here?
He was there.
Where?
In the tunnel.
That morning, Calvess came around.
He wanted to get some get high,
six in the morning.
I told that motherfucker this shit better
be worth my while, some big money.
You knew him by his real name?
He came off for a couple weeks,
said his name was Fredericks.
- Jimmy Fredericks. Yeah, go.
- But he got strung out.
Turned straight bitch. Blew his cover.
You knew?
Everybody knew,
just like everybody knows
you and a handful of
motherfuckers was cops.
He kept us out of his reports.
Tipped us off
to who was getting raided.
- We kept him high.
- You said he supplied you with IDs.
With police IDs?
All kinds of shit. Badges, IDs, guns.
Whenever he had
no money, he'd trade.
What was his condition that morning?
He wasn't looking too good,
talking crazy shit.
'Hands looking shaky. We show up
in the morning. He's got no money.'
Nothing to trade.
What was I supposed to do?
I told him to fuck off.
I ain't giving him shit.
This motherfucker starts tripping,
talking he's gonna arrest us.
Take us in if we don't comp his ass.
Then Oak showed up.
- Where?
- On the other side of the tunnel.
Did he say anything?
No, man.
When we saw him, Calvess seen him.
This motherfucker just flipped.
Talking about arresting us.
- Reaching for his gun.
- What'd you do?
I hit him.
- Cos he's reaching for his gun.
- I ain't trying to get shot by nobody.
Especially no junkie
trying to be a cop.
- What then?
- He fell.
Latroy hit him in his face once.
I kicked him to keep him down.
We ran,
and then Oak started shooting.
- Lieutenant fired? How many times?
- Three, four times.
The lieutenant fired on you
three or four times, you didn't get hit?
Quickly, tell me what happened then.
When we was running,
we heard Oak yelling at Calvess.
What the fuck are you doing, Mike?
That's when he did it.
Did what?
That's when he killed him, man.
What did you just say to me?
Fucking Calvess was a junkie.
He blew his cover.
- Oak killed him.
- Give me a straight face and say that.
You think he ain't capable of that?
You think he ain't got it in him?
He see his partner strung out.
That motherfucker flipped out.
You guys think
this is my first walk in the park?
Huh?
You cop to selling to an officer,
assaulting an officer.
You won't cop to killing him.
You want to spin bullshit.
You fucking wasted him.
It's over.
- What?
- It's over.
It is over. It is fucking over!
I gave you a shot to set it straight,
Darnell, and you pissed it away.
Both you pissed it away.
All this shit coming down.
You brought all this on yourselves.
You must be suspicious.
If you wasn't, why you lock the door?
The only thing
you need to know about me
is I'm going to bag
the motherfuckers that killed Mike.
Where we grow up, you kill a cop,
they will crown you King Kong.
Ain't nobody here
talking about killing no cop.
Oak come in here trying
to stick this shit to some niggers.
He knows that anytime
you stick shit to niggers,
it's gonna stay stuck.
When did you find that gun in there?
That gun Oak found.
Calvess'. You were the first one in
that trunk. Did you see a brown bag?
No. It came up when your back
was turned. Don't you see?
Tellis, open the goddamned door!
Why don't you dust for prints
and we'll see whose come off of there.
I'll bet you all the prints belong
to Oak. He planted it. He put it there.
You got ten fucking seconds.
Play it back for the record, now.
Goddamnit. Open the door.
Tellis!
What the fuck was going on in there?
Why'd you lock me out?
I asked you a question.
Were you tailing Calvess
the day he was killed?
You heard me.
Did he compromise his cover,
and were you tailing him as a result?
You talked to them?
The Mossberg off the floor.
Tekulve's ID and badge.
You heard them.
They're claiming Calvess supplied
them with police issue for junk.
- Can you explain that?
- How long after I left
did you let those liberal stirrings
in you spill all over the floor?
I don't like where you put me
to ask these questions.
Were you following him?
It's not an indictment.
If you did, I need to know now.
No,
I was not tailing him.
But you were there before he died.
You were there.
Tell me I'm wrong.
You want to fucking talk?
We'll talk.
Mike was making a bust that morning.
He had enough to make an arrest.
He needed backup.
- Off roster.
- Why?
He wanted to bring them
in on his own.
So I stayed back. I waited.
And the buy went bad.
How come you couldn't identify
those guys in there?
Because they shot him and ran.
They shot him or you shot them
as they fled the scene?
What? What did they say to you?
'Oak started shooting.
He shot Calvess. He killed Calvess.'
You must be out of your mind.
Much as he meant to me, you call up
my integrity, my commitment.
You're going to let
these pieces of shit smear that?
We're bringing them in.
You're fucking with something
you can't possibly understand.
I'm taking them in. It's over now.
Joke. You know that?
You're a fucking joke.
Your whole career's a joke.
A complete washout.
You popped that needle freak.
In the process you hit that woman
with a stray bullet, costing her a baby.
Enough!
Stop!
- Shut the fuck up!
- You're a lie.
You fucking lie.
I got this from child welfare.
Kathryn Tunney.
Mother deceased.
Removed from the custody
of her stepfather,
Myron Cobb, November 1985.
Placed with foster parents.
Did you know
that little girl, Lieutenant?
I think you do.
I've seen the records till she was 18.
I know you wanted to adopt her.
She was in and out of trouble,
in and out of foster homes.
Handful of arrests, drug-related.
You had them squashed.
You bailed her out of rehab.
You needed a doctor
to sign the release.
Who did it? Your old pal, Harlan.
He signed her out of those clinics.
I saw the signatures.
You made sure Harlan
was the active ME on Calvess.
Calvess?
I thought we were closing that.
So he could doctor the autopsy, alter
the lab reports, make them look clean.
Make Calvess look clean.
He's as dirty as you.
A filthy, fucking, needle-ridden junkie.
And you fucking knew it,
you motherfucker.
I'm calling this in right now.
Your gun and your shield
on the ground, now.
I am so far from fucking with you.
- You threatening my life?
- I'm going to take your life.
- Gun and shield on the ground.
- You're a fucking lie.
You wanted me to back your bullshit.
Sell your story
so you could railroad those pricks.
You pulled her out of all that shit.
You couldn't afford
to break her heart again.
I get it, man. I get it.
He was a fucking addict.
How long before
he'd start pimping her out?
Hopeless, right?
Everything he did was hopeless.
You took this case
so you could bury it.
Kill me just like you killed him.
Come on, buddy.
I'm going back in there
and finish this up.
Come on.
Go home.
Bullshit's over. You destroyed his life,
his family. You fucked it all up.
So now you two are
going to tell me that you killed him.
He identified himself,
attempted to make an arrest.
You overpowered and shot him.
Say it.
Say it and you get out of here.
You think I'm fucking with you?
Ready to talk?
This is Calvess' gun.
This is the gun you used to kill him.
See it? Take it.
Take it in your hand.
Grip the gun.
You are going to tell me.
I've got two bullets left.
One for this head.
Lieutenant, drop your weapon!
I will shoot you where you stand.
I killed Calvess.
Shut up.
Don't you leave me with this.
I need to know.
There was no bust. You were there
to kill him. That's what you did.
You knew what he was.
You planted the gun
cos he was a junkie.
You killed him. You've got to tell me
that. Look me in the eyes and tell me.
- They ruined him.
- Who?
They made him that way.
They made him a junkie.
The department. It takes everything.
The pension, everything.
The family gets nothing.
Kathy gets nothing.
It's not that way. Tell me the truth.
Tell me the fucking truth.
Look at me.
Do not fucking go. Tell me.
- Give me the gun.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
What the fuck you doing? I'm taking
you out and getting you help.
I don't want help.
You are not taking me anywhere.
I'm not going out.
Do you have any idea
what you're doing to Kathy?
To the girls?
You know what they mean to me?
You're pissing away
your entire life. I won't have it.
I heard about this
and I waited. I ignored it.
Why Kathy didn't tell me,
I have no idea. But that's it. It's over.
I'm sorry I took
so goddamn long, but it's over.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Mike.
Mike.
Mike...
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.