Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
uh, John, you know.
He was more puny-like.
But all the time
I was workin' for him...
I was just so scared.
Inside, you know?
Just scared.
Haven, do you think we could
get Connie out to the rally?
Connie White and Barbara Jean never
appear on the same stage together.
Connie can replace Barbara Jean,
but that's it.
As for Haven Hamilton, well,
I'll appear wherever
Barbara Jean appears.
I got a good mind
to take you outside.
With my wife in the hospital,
you puttin' that shit on me?
- Calm down, enjoy the show.
- Barnett's angry.
Okay.
Walk with me, Joshua
- And I will say that I am lame
- I think she's, uh...
I think she's having an affair here.
I really do.
The child that we have made
- But I'll never let him mention
- Oh, God.
- Your name
- Are you off. You're way off.
You are way, way off.
Are you kidding?
Some people take
And never give
- I love you.
- But all men die
And so must live
For a while
And life is short
- I love you.
- A precious gift
This thing we have
- Please don't let it drift away
- I love you.
Honey, won't you
let me be your friend
I love you.
Honey, won't you
let me try again
let me be your friend
For another day
When we've been there
Ten thousand years
Bright, shining
As the sun
We've no less days
To sing God's praise
Than when
We'd first
Begun
And on the profession
of your faith,
I baptize you, my sister,
in the name of the Father
and of the Son...
and of the Holy Ghost.
Amen.
I'm newborn again
Been a long time talkin'
'Bout my trials here below
Free grace
Free grace, sinner
I'm newborn again
And He walks with me
And He talks with me
And he tells me
I am His own
And the joy we share
As we tarry there
None other
Has ever
Known
He speaks
and the sound of His voice
Is so sweet
The birds hush their singing
And the melody
That He gave to me
Within my heart
Is ringin'
You know, my wife Esther is on
the same floor with Barbara Jean.
- And He walks with me
- Oh, and Esther and I had a son...
- And He talks with me
- in the service too.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, not the army. It was the navy.
And He tells me
I am His own
We lost him in the South Pacific.
We don't know how.
- And thejoy we share
- I'm sorry.
- World War II.
- Yes, sir.
As we tarry there
None other
Has ever
Known
I'm wandering in a graveyard.
The dead here have no crosses,
nor tombstones, nor wreaths
to sing of their past glory,
but lie in rotting,
decaying, rusty heaps,
their innards ripped out
by greedy, vulturous hands.
Their vast, vacant skeletons...
sadly sighing to the sky.
The rust on their bodies...
is the color of dried blood.
Dried blood.
I'm reminded of...
of an elephant's
secret burial ground.
Yes.
Cette aire de mystère.
Cette essence de I'irréel.
These cars
are trying to communicate.
O cars, are you trying
to tell me something?
Are you trying to
convey to me some secret...
What... Excuse me?
Oh, excuse me.
I thought I was completely alone.
How embarrassing.
Oh, you're a musician!
The economy's depressed, not me
You may say that I ain't free
But it don't
Worry
Me
Let's have some applause
for Miss Maisie Hoy.
Miss Albuquerque?
Hi, Frog.
This is with gestures.
Miss Jill Brown
on the track in number 78.
The youngsters will be eligible...
to apply for a gas-powered mini-bike
and a helmet.
You wanna talk about yesterday?
Get up, goddamn it!
Fucker.
You wanna talk about yesterday?
Do you wanna talk about yesterday
or not? What, are you...
Shit.
Come out of there!
You leave me alone!
Come on!
Look, I know what's...
For Christ's sake, what...
Now, you...
What are you doing? Do you wanna
talk about yesterday or not?
Oh, that's terrific.
Hey, that's great. Hey, terrific.
Oh, thanks. My turtle.
Thanks a lot.
Look, just relax!
Look, I know what's goin' on.
Great.
House detective.
Bill, hi.
I'm John Triplette.
Am I early?
I called you this morning.
Oh, yeah. The guy from TV.
Come on in.
Sure.
Just... We're just
cleanin' up here.
You know the...
- Sunday morning blues.
- Would you hold this?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Let me just move this over here.
- Is this your new album?
- Yeah. That's our only album.
It's a very good one, though.
I've heard it. It's terrific.
- I'm really sorry about the mess.
- Oh, that's all right.
You oughta see my room.
We had a little party last night.
Had a pretty good time too.
Uh, I wanted to, um,
tell you a couple things about what
we're trying to do with this show.
- Can I get you a drink?
- No, no, I'm fine.
I don't wanna take up
much of your time.
I just wanna tell you a little bit
about what we're trying to do.
I know you're astute politically,
and I'm certainly not here
to sell you a bill of goods.
- Don't care about politics.
- No politics? Okay, great.
Well, then, I've got a problem
that could work to your advantage.
As you know, this redneck music
is very popular right now.
I've got an awful lot of these
local yokels on the bill singing...
- Your basic country folk.
- Country crapola. Right.
So I think, uh...
What I'm going for
is a broader appeal.
Which is where we fit in.
I want to give it more
than just this Southern thing.
And I think that
a really hip group like yours...
could walk off with the evening.
Yeah. Probably the only
rock group on the...
- Absolutely.
- Sounds good.
- Sounds inviting.
- Yeah.
And you do get a big audience
from these country guys.
Is this just network, or...
It's better than network.
It's syndicated.
They'll be showing it
for a year and a half.
- Your glasses, sweetheart.
- Oh, thanks.
This is my wife Mary.
This is John Triplette.
Nice to meet you.
Go ahead.
He's, uh, he's the fella
from the television show...
that they're doing
for Hal Phillip Walker.
That political thing going on.
He's offered us a spot.
You're doing some great promotion.
All those buttons and...
- Oh, yeah, thank you. I'm trying.
- Bumper stickers.
Anyway, we got a great time spot
on this gala,
and we're gonna walk away
with the show, John says.
We can't vote for him.
We're registered Democrats.
Besides, he's a little crazy,
isn't he?
Well, they're all
a little crazy, Mary.
- I'll drink to that.
- That's the name of the game.
But I think the thing that you
should consider is your future.
It would give you a great shot.
But it doesn't make any difference.
We're registered Democrats.
Well, I'm a registered Democrat.
The only reason
we're registered Democrats...
is because your father's
a registered Democrat...
and his father's
a registered Democrat.
Well, Tom's a registered Democrat,
and he wouldn't do it.
It's not my way
To take your hand if I'm...
- Hi, Tom.
- Hi, Norman. How you doin'?
Good. I'm sure glad you called.
Is there anything I can...
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Whew.
- You have any speckled birds?
- What?
You know, L.A. Turnarounds.
Uppers.
Uh, no, no, I, uh...
But I know where
to get some grass.
- No, thanks. I don't need any grass.
- Okay.
- Uh, can I ask you a question?
- Mm-hmm.
Is there something...
Are you angry at Bill?
- No.
- Oh.
'Cause I, I, uh...
You know, I, uh...
Bill and Mary
and you and, uh...
Well, Bill, uh...
I mean, Bill seems to be, um...
Uh...
- I'm just confused.
- Mmm.
- Uh...
- Here.
- Why don't you write yourself a hit.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Can I talk to Cherry, please?
She's in bed with R.Y.
You wanna talk to R.Y.?
- I'd rather talk to her, if I could.
- Who is this?
This is Frank, one of the cooks
at the restaurant.
Are you a Jehovah's Witness?
Does it
make sense that the churches...
should remain untaxed
on their vast holdings of land...
and corporate investments?
Does it make sense that
a multimillion-dollar income...
should go untaxed
year after year?
No, all will not be easy,
but we will bask
in the satisfaction...
of having done
what we should have done.
And if we don't
get it done today,
we may run out of tomorrows.
The buses!
The buses are empty...
and look almost menacing,
threatening,
as so many yellow dragons
watching me...
with their hollow, vacant eyes.
I wonder how many little
black and white children...
have yellow nightmares,
their own special brand of fear
for the yellow peril...
I can't have...
I can't start...
Damn it, it's got to be more...
positive.
No, more negative.
Start again.
Yellow is the color of caution.
No.
Yellow is the color of cowardice.
Yellow is the color of sunshine.
And yet I see
very little sunshine...
in the lives of all the little
black and white children.
I see their lives, rather,
as a study in grayness,
a mixture of black and...
Oh, Christ, no.
That's fascist.
Yellow! Yellow, yellow, yellow.
Yellow fever.
We'll be able to talk about it.
They're checkin' out now.
- Get with him before he leaves.
- What about the place?
- It's not bad at all.
- Think it'll work out?
It's got this bizarre stage
that drops out of the ceiling.
They're gettin' out this mornin'.
- The place is very confused.
- Bye-bye!
- Is the place out there okay?
- Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Wait a minute.
Here we go.
Uh, Barnett!
Phone's for you.
- Is it important, or what?
- Bye, girls.
- Hello.
- Hello, Barnett. John Triplette.
- Who?
- Hello! Are you going home?
Mr. Green, how are you?
I'm goin' home.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- Thank you. How is Mrs. Green?
She's fine, and she's gonna be
thrilled to hear I saw you again.
Give her my very best.
And is she takin' her vitamin E?
- Got 'em right here.
- All right. Good for you.
You take care, darlin'.
Bye-bye.
All right, come on.
Let's get her on there.
- Lucky for you. Whoo!
- As long as I'm done
- Gonna buy me a pistol
- All right, get in.
We gotta go with those
white horseshoes, huh?
We're gonna live with those
for infamy.
Take that cortege
on the other elevator.
- Didn't the doctor get ahold of you?
- No more calls, Delbert.
I'm really sorry
I have to tell you this.
Mrs. Green expired this morning.
What?
Mrs. Green died this morning.
Wait right here.
Let me go get the doctor.
Mr. Green?
Mr. Green, you know,
my mama saved her life.
They used to live next door to each
other. My mama put out the flames.
She always loved Barbara Jean
more than anything.
She's still keepin'
a scrapbook on her.
The only thing she said to me
when I joined up was,
"When you're doin' your travels,
I want you to see Barbara Jean.
Don't say nothin' about me.
Just see Barbara Jean. "
So that's what I been doin'.
Now I'm gonna go over to Opryland
and hear her sing.
Give my best to your wife, now.
Wait a minute. Don't laugh.
Let me just... I have a theory
about political assassination.
You see, I believe
people like Madame Pearl...
and all these people here
in this country who carry guns...
are the real assassins.
Because, you see,
they stimulate other people...
who are perhaps innocent...
and who eventually
are the ones who pull the trigger.
- Ma?
- Kenny? Where are you, Kenny?
- I'm in Nashville. How are you?
- I was so worried.
- There's no reason to worry.
- Well, I haven't been able to sleep.
I had to take some of that Ny Quil
so I could go to sleep.
- Puts you right out.
- Did it help?
Yes, it did.
Where are you staying in Nashville?
- I'm staying at a rooming house.
- Who you talkin' to?
- It's my mother.
- Who are you talking to, Kenny?
A girl that lives
in the rooming house.
Who owns that rooming house?
- Her uncle.
- A man owns the rooming house?
Well, it can't be very clean.
- Don't be silly.
- I bet the sheets aren't clean.
In the South
you can pick up this parasite...
- Joan, put that down, please!
- Kenny, listen...
- Just a minute.
- I wanted to look at your fiddle.
Kenny! You can get this
parasite fungus in the South.
It's very difficult to get rid of.
When are you coming home?
I don't know.
A couple of weeks.
You left your blue suit
hanging in the closet.
I don't need my suit.
I would really like you to
get home as soon as you can.
Mother, just listen to me.
Kenny, don't you talk to me
in that tone of voice.
I love you too, Mama.
I really do.
I'll see you soon.
Bye-bye.
Let's find Barnett,
hope he's not in a bad mood.
Hi. How are you?
- Hey, Barnett!
- I'm obliged to give them...
- Hey, Barnett.
- What do you want now?
This guy wants me to do four shows.
What do you want?
Don't let her do too much.
How you hangin'?
- You feelin' better now?
- Yeah, I feel swell.
We gotta talk to you.
We're gonna do a show.
Okay, now, John's doing this show.
Haven's gonna do it.
We want Barbara Jean to headline it.
- Unbelievable.
- Now wait a second, man.
I wish they wouldn't rush us.
Get a shot.
It's national TVfor this candidate
Hal Phillip Walker.
We don't want her to make
any political statement.
What do you think
her bein' there's gonna be?
- Ain't that a political statement?
- People haven't seen her.
No, fellas.
Don't take it personal.
No politics, no government,
no nothin'.
- All right? Okay?
- All right.
- I heard you all out.
- Hello, boys. How's it goin'?
I believe I met you before
in the hospital.
Look at that. Didn't Jewel
show you how to do her hair?
- Come on, darlin'.
- How do you do, honey?
- No pictures.
- I'm all excited.
- How do you feel?
- I feel great.
I told the band you'd start off
with the cowboy song.
- Forget it.
- No, John, just leave it to me.
He can take a flying leap.
I'm gonna stay after him
like a rodent, man.
He's got a tape deck
in his tractor
And he listens
to the local news
He finds out where
the bass are bitin'
While he's plowin'
to the country blues
He was a cowboy
and he knew I loved him well
A cowboy's secrets
you never tell
No, there's nothin'
like the lovin'
Of a hard-drivin'cowboy man
He's got a tape deck
in his tractor
While he's plowing up
his daddy's land
He's got more horse sense
Than I ever seen in any man
He was a cowboy
and he knew I loved him well
A cowboy's secrets
you never tell
No, there's nothin'
like the lovin'
Of a hard-drivin' cowboy man
On Saturday nights
we go dancin' in town
And all the boys'll
order up another round
In the summertime
We look forward
to the rodeo
On Saturday nights
we go to town
And all the boys'll
order up another round
When he rides saddle bronc
I wait to hear
that whistle blow
He's got a tape deck
in his tractor
I can hear him
when he's comin' home
Then he holds me
in the rocking chair
And sings me the love song
He was a cowboy
and he knew I loved him well
A cowboy's secrets
you never tell
No, there's nothin'
like the lovin'
Of a hard-drivin' cowboy man
No, there's nothin'
like the muscles
Of a hard-drivin' cowboy man
Thank you.
It's that careless
Disrespect
I can't take no more, baby
It's the way
That you don't love me
When you say you do, baby
It hurts so bad
It gets me down, down, down
I want to walk away
From this battleground
This hurtin' match
It ain't no good
I'd give a lot to love you
The way I used to do
Wish I could
Mm-hmm-hmmm
Well, you got
Your own private world
I wouldn't have it
No other way
But lately you been
Hidin'your blues
Pretendin' what you say
It hurts so bad
It gets me down, down, down
I wanna walk away
from this battleground
This hurtin' match
It ain't no good
I'd give a lot to love you
The way I used to do
Wish I could
Mmm-mmm-mmmm-mmm
Have you been in Vietnam?
- Huh?
- Writin'it down
Kind of makes me feel better
Yes, you have.
I can tell by your face.
It keeps me away
from them blues
I wanna be nice to you
Treat you right
But how long can I pay
These dues
It hurts so bad
It gets me down, down, down
I wanna walk away
from this battleground
This hurtin' match
It ain't no good, no
I'd give a lot to love you
The way I used to do
Wish I could
Mmm-mmm-mmmm-mmm
Was it awful?
- Ooh-oooh, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
- It was kinda hot and wet.
Ooooh
Oooh
Oooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-oooh
Ooooh
I
Wish I could
Mmm-mm-mmm
Thank you.
I wanna tell you all a little secret
which you might not know,
and that is that last night
I thanked my lucky stars...
that I could be here at all
to sing for ya.
I heard on the radio...
This little boy... 9 years old.
Sometimes a deejay'll play a tune...
and ask everybody to phone in
and say how they like it.
I was listenin', and this
little nine-year-old called in.
The song had voices
in the background,
like the way they use
backup voices these days,
soundin' like little munchkins.
He called up, the deejay said,
"How old are you, son?"
The boy said, "I'm nine,
and I think it's gonna be a hit. "
The deejay said, "Why?" "Because
it had those chipmunks in it. "
And I thought that was so cute,
because, well, I can sing
like a munchkin myself.
I'm real fond
of The Wizard of Oz.
Plus, I live out, you know,
just a ways off of Interstate 24...
on the road to Chattanooga.
So you can see why
I kinda related to that.
I think me and the boys are gonna
strike up another tune for you now.
Let's go, boys.
I think there's a storm...
seems like it's a-brewin'.
That's what my grandaddy used to say
before he lost his hearin'.
Once he got deaf,
he never talked much no more.
'Cept sometimes he'd say "Oh, gosh"
or "Durn it" or "My word!"
My granny'd go around clickin'
her teeth to the radio all day.
Boy, was she a lot of fun,
and cooked my favorite, roast beef.
She was a sweetheart.
She raised chickens too.
She, um...
Did you ever hear a chicken sound?
You know how chickens go?
Here, chick, chick, chick.
Anyway, I guess we'd better strike
up this tune before it's too late.
Okay, boys.
The first job I ever really got...
Grandma... She's the one who clacked
her false teeth to the radio.
She taught my mama how to sing,
and my mama taught me.
One time she took me, 'cause we
was gonna get a new Frigidaire.
She took me to the Frigidaire store
where the man was advertisin'.
This record was goin' 'round, and
Mama told him I knew how to sing.
He said, "If she learns this tune,
I'll give y'all a quarter. "
So Mama and I went home...
And then what happened?
Let's see, I think... Uh, yeah.
We went home and I learned both
sides of the record in half an hour.
We went back and told him that
I'd learned 'em, and he said,
"Let me hear," so I sang both sides
of the record instead of just one.
So he gave us 50 cents, and we went
across the street and had us a soda.
Ever since then
I been workin'. I don't...
I think ever since then
I been workin' and doin' my...
- Come on, come on.
- Supportin'myself.
- Anyway...
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
- Am I all right? Am I all right?
- Oh, you're fine, darlin'.
- It's the microphone.
- I ain't done.
- I know, I know.
Get us a glass of water.
Boys, help her off, all right?
- You'll come back. Okay, darlin'?
- Thank you!
All right. Watch the wire.
All right, now! Okay!
Aw, come on, now.
Have a heart.
Thank you!
Come on, now.
It's just too soon, now.
All of you must know... Aw, come on.
You didn't mean that, did you?
She just come out of the hospital...
Oh, no. Hold it down, boys.
You know that little girl
just come out of the hospital.
That little girl's in there
cryin' her eyes out...
'cause she didn't want
to disappoint you.
Get outta here!
Y'all show up at Centennial Park
tomorrow at the Parthenon.
You'll see her for free
as our guests. How's that?
All right?
Okay, let's hear a get-well welcome
for Barbara Jean.
Let's hear it. Come on!
Ingrates is all they are.
A bunch of no-talent...
I got trapped out there,
and you guys know it.
- I want some ground rules right now.
- You name it.
She's gonna sing first and be off
before that man even shows.
Fine.
Whatever you want.
- Never shoulda brought her here.
- Any way you want it.
No paraphernalia, no literature
being circulated. You understand?
And never, at any time, is she to be
associated with Hal Phillip Walker.
- Hello?
- Hey.
Guess who.
- Linnea?
- Yes, it's me.
Hi. This is Tom.
I'm playing a gig tonight downtown.
You wanna come and meet me?
It's at a place called
the, uh, No Exit, or the Exit.
Exit Out, or somethin'.
Anyhow, it's right across the street
from Friday's, on Church Street.
You know where that is,
don't you?
Anyhow, I'll be there at 8:00,
and, uh...
Why don't you meet me there?
- Okay?
- Um...
Well, it's sad but true
The pilot light of our love
Has flickered out
- Mary...
- Driver, may I have more champagne?
- That's Norman.
- Oh.
Norman, yes.
Norman. Of course.
He doesn't like to be known
as a driver.
Thank you so much, Norman.
What used to come
from the warmest heart
I have to get from a cold can
Since my baby's cookin'in
Another man's pan
Have you ever been
to the ladies' restroom here?
No.
I'm stuck here at the Exit Inn
with no place left to go.
Well, if makin'love
Were margarine
Then she is
the high-priced spread
- I'll have a cider.
- Apple cider?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Put it on my bill.
- Oh, no...
- Yeah.
Uh, all right. And would you
put it in a wine glass, please?
Put it in a wine glass
and put it on my bill.
Traveling in cozy, close quarters,
I mean, you sort of
have to camp in one room.
- Well, Mary and I camp in one room.
- Obviously!
- Yes, I...
- Tom camps in a lot of rooms.
My name's Wade Coolidge.
What's yours?
Um, Linnea is my name.
Well, shall I say
that Tom and I, um...
Oh, la-dee-dee!
So you sang together.
No, I mean, we sort of
got to know each other, um,
in the biblical sense,
shall we say.
- You went to church?
- I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
This is dreadful.
But he is so attractive,
I was wondering...
I shouldn't be asking you,
I should really be asking Mary.
You went to bed with him,
right?
Oh, yeah.
I thought you understood that.
Well, I shouldn't...
Where'd you go to bed with him?
Listen, uh, we got
a special treat tonight.
A friend of mine
is in town cuttin' an album.
- Tom Frank is in the audience.
- That's you.
Tom? Speak of the devil.
He's agreed to come up
and do a couple of numbers.
Let's make him feel at home.
Tom Frank!
Come on!
Goddamn it!
I haven't seen him for
more than two minutes in three days.
Thank you.
- I used to be part of a trio.
- Used to be?
I been hidin' from 'em all week, but
it seems they found me here tonight,
so we might as well have them
up here to sing too... Bill and Mary.
Lovely!
Yes, you must!
I've been watching it all week.
You may say I ain't free
But it don't worry me
- It don't worry me
- My favorite song.
- We don't need to sing at all.
- You guys can do it for us.
- You may say I ain't free
- Good choice.
- But it don't worry me
Since you've gone
My heart is broken
Another time
Oh, railroad train
Has taken him
From me
All my luxury
Has turned to misery
He's all I ever wanted
Why did he run from me
Since you've gone
My heart is broken
Another time
Since you've gone
My heart is broken
Another time
I didn't know
That you were leavin'
- Till you were out the door
- Out the door
I didn't know
The love you gave
Was a real love
I didn't know
A lot of things then
Lord, I know them now
Since you've gone
my heart is broken
- Another time
Mmm.
Since you've gone
My heart is broken
Another time
Since you've gone
My heart is broken
Another time
When this is all over, I'm gonna be
taking them back to someplace.
What I could do is, I could
show you a little bit of Nashville.
I can tell you things that'd
send you around the corner.
I'm not kidding. I know...
Well, I know, for instance...
- What is your name? L...
- Norman.
Norman.
Please, Norman, I...
I make a point
never to gossip with servants.
Thank you.
Okay, fellas,
I think you know...
you've got a good man
to get behind.
I don't wanna take
a lot of your time,
'cause we do have
a little entertainment for ya.
You got pledge cards on the table.
You can pledge anything you want to.
I'll make sure... I'll make you pay,
whatever you put down there.
If you got a check,
don't be afraid to write it out.
I'll get that to the bank quick,
before you can stop it.
Any cash, anything at all,
don't anybody be humble or shy.
And while you're writin',
so you don't get bored or anything,
there's somethin' comin'
to keep you occupied.
Just keep your eyes up,
'cause good things come from above.
Hi, y'all.
- Hi!
My name's Sueleen Gay,
and I'm here to sing you a song
about a girl that never gets enough.
I never get enough
Of the love I'm hungry for
I always want more and more
Even if we stay together
Our whole lifetime through
I'll never get enough
I'll never get enough of you
She's the worst singer
I ever heard.
I ain't greedy for
that mansion on the hill
She cannot sing a lick, can she?
I never was that kind
Don't need my pockets stuffed
With hundred-dollar bills
Hey, you forgot your jacket.
Excuse me.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
All right, if you want more
it's gonna have to be me alone,
'cause it seems
I'vejust been deserted.
I'm gonna play somethin'that, uh,
I wrotejust recently...
- and came here to record.
- All right!
I'm gonna dedicate this to someone
special who might be here tonight.
This is a song called
"I'm Easy. "
It's not my way to love you
just when no one's lookin'
It's not my way
To take your hand
if I'm not sure
It's not my way
to let you see
What's goin' on inside of me
When it's a love
you won't be needing
If you're not free
Please stop pullin'
at my sleeve
If you're just playin'
If you won't take the things
you make me wanna give
I never cared too much
for games
And this one's drivin' me insane
You're not half as free
to wander
As you claim
But I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Give the word
I'll play your game
As though
that's how it oughta be
Because I'm easy
Don't lead me on
if there's nowhere
For you to take me
If lovin'you
would have to be
A sometime thing
I can't put bars
on my insides
My love is somethin'
I can't hide
It still hurts
When I recall
the times I've tried
But I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Take my hand
and pull me down
I won't put up any fight
Because I'm easy
Don't do me favors
Let me watch you
from a distance
'Cause when you're near
I find it hard
to keep my head
And when your eyes
throw light at mine
It's enough to change my mind
Make me leave my cautious words
and ways behind
That's why I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Say you want me
I'll come runnin'
Without takin'time to think
Because I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Take my hand
and pull me down
I won't put up any fight
Because I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Give the word
I'll play your game
As though
that's how it oughta be
Because I'm easy
Do it to it.
- Hi.
- Hi!
I'm gonna sing you all
a song Barbara Jean wrote.
Just wanna get comfortable.
It's called, uh,
"One, I Love You. "
Oh, you got that right, babe!
When I feel my life perishing
I call you on the phone
You always fix me up
When I get broken
'Cause every time
that I got hurt
And went out of control
You knew the fears I felt
Before I spoke 'em
Boo! Come on, now!
- What is this, some Walker rip-off?
- One, I love you
Two
I'm thinkin'of you
Three
I'll never let you go
Boo! Come on! Take it off!
And four, I miss you
Five, I wanna kiss you
Six
I won't leave you no more
- Did you tell Trout what you wanted?
- Did I? It was your job.
- I know.
- I assumed he knew what...
Well, I didn't think
it was gonna be any problem.
Four, I miss you
- Five, I wanna kiss you
- Take your clothes off!
Six
I won't leave you no more
Let's see some tit!
Come on!
What is this?
Come on back here, baby!
- What's the matter, hon?
- I don't understand what's goin' on.
Didn't Trout tell you
you're supposed to strip?
I'm a singer!
Listen.
Listen, listen, listen.
Go finish the show
like you told Trout you'd do,
and I'll set it up
so you can sing at the Parthenon.
You can sing in the Parthenon
with Barbara Jean.
- Go finish the show...
- I get to sing with Barbara Jean?
Yes, you are...
Yes, you will.
I'll take care of it. Go finish the
show like you told Trout you'd do.
Okay?
These fellas really like you.
I'm gonna be as big a star
as Barbara Jean is one day.
- I know you are. You can't miss.
- Go on, now.
Come on, let's do it!
Start the show!
Whoo! Hey!
All right! All right!
You're my mama!
All right!
Whoo! Hey, hey, hey!
But I'm easy
Yeah, I'm easy
Take my hand
and pull me down
I won't put up any fight
Because I'm easy
Want to learn how to say
something in sign language?
Yeah.
How do you say "I love you"?
Well, you could say...
Shorthand for it is...
This is shorthand.
Or you could say, "I,"
you could say, "love you. "
- "I love you"?
- Mm-hmm.
Or you could just say,
"I'm happy I met you. "
- I'm happy I met you.
- Right.
Say you want me
I'll come runnin'
- Without takin'time to think
- Phew.
- How can you smoke those things?
- 'Cause I'm easy
- It's easy.
- Yeah, I'm easy
Let me have a drag.
- Do you smoke?
- No.
Well, what do you want
to do that for?
Yeah, I'm easy
Give the word
I'll play your game
- Doesn't look good.
- No?
- Mm-mmm.
- So what?
Because I'm easy
- Tom, I have to go.
- Oh.
Can't you just call him,
tell him you're hung up?
No, I can't.
- Couldn't you stay another hour?
- No.
I just can't.
This is the long-distance operator.
- You want this charged to your room?
- Yeah, please.
- And your room number, please?
- 112.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- How you doin'?
- Oh, wow.
Listen, I'm real sorry
I left the way I did.
Oh, wow.
It's really nice to talk to you.
It's okay.
It's nice to talk to you too.
- What are you doing?
- I'm thinkin'about you.
You are? Well...
Listen, can you come down here?
- When?
- Tonight.
- Oh, Tom, I can't do that.
- Why not?
We have an opening at the museum
tomorrow. I can't leave my job.
Why don't you quit?
I'm makin'bread here.
We tried that before.
It doesn't work. I need to be busy.
I'll wait for you here.
When are you coming back?
About a week.
Okay, well, just...
just come on back.
Move back in.
It's fine.
I miss you.
I really do.
New York's really been nice.
It's missed you too.
The weather's been terrific.
I went sailing.
- Yeah.
- What's that?
That's just room service.
There's 50 cents on the desk there.
Just pick it up.
- Big tipper.
- Yeah, well, times are hard.
Right, all that money. You couldn't
afford to bring me down there.
- Yeah. Well, see you in a week.
- I love you, Tom.
This it, honey?
Be careful gettin' out.
Hey.
Hey! Hey, wait just a minute.
Just hold it, will ya.
Now...
I know you don't do that
all the time, I...
I wanna tell you
that I just... I mean...
Me personally, boy, I...
You know, I'd just like to kiss you
all over, every place.
You know what I'm telling you?
- I think you...
- Sueleen?
You okay?
Shit, man.
Didn't your mama
teach you no manners?
Who was that?
What's the matter with you?
Ain't you gonna talk to me?
Did it go all right?
- Oh, Wade.
- What?
I had to do me a striptease tonight
in front of all those men...
in order to get to sing
at the Parthenon with Barbara Jean.
Oh, shit, Sueleen, I...
That's dreadful!
That's terrible, girl!
I mean...
I don't know how to tell you this,
but I been meanin' to...
you can't sing.
You may as well face the fact
you cannot sing.
You ain't never gon' be no star.
I wish you'd give it up.
They gon' kill ya. They gon' tear
your heart out if you keep on.
They gon' walk on your soul, girl.
- What are you talkin' about?
- You can't sing.
- Do you understand that?
- Yeah? You wanna make a bet?
You wanna come to the Parthenon
and watch me sing with Barbara Jean?
- I am leavin' for Detroit Wednesday.
- You just come and watch, Wade.
I'm leavin' for Detroit, and if
you wanna go you just come on.
- They gonna kill you in this town.
- Well, you come and see.
- They gon' use you. You know that.
- Bye, Wade.
Dumb bitch.
I don't know why I stick around.
She just makes me so goddamn mad
I could spit.
Little more than a year ago,
a man named Hal Phillip Walker...
excited a group of college students
with some questions:
Have you stood
on a high and windy hill...
and heard the acorns drop and roll?
Have you walked in the valley
beside the brook,
walked alone and remembered?
Does Christmas
smell like oranges to you?
In a commencement speech such
questions were fitting, perhaps,
but hardly the material with which
to launch a presidential campaign.
Even those who pay
close attention to politics...
probably saw Hal Phillip Walker
and his Replacement Party...
as a bit of frost
on the hillside...
summer, if not late spring,
would surely do away with all that.
Well, now that summer,
along with presidential primaries,
is heavy upon us...
and the frost is still there,
perhaps we should take
a closer look.
Hal Phillip Walker is,
in a way, a mystery man.
Out of nowhere, with a handful
of students and scarcely any pros,
he's managed to win
three presidential primaries...
and is given a fighting chance
to take a fourth... Tennessee.
A win in that state would
take on added significance,
for only once in the last 50 years
has Tennessee failed to vote...
for the winning
presidential candidate.
No doubt many Americans,
especially party liners,
wish that Hal Phillip Walker
would go away,
disappear like the natural frost...
and come again at
some more convenient season.
But wherever he may be going,
it seems sure Hal Phillip Walker
is not going away,
for there is genuine appeal...
and it must be related
to the raw courage of this man...
running for president, willing
to battle vast oil companies,
eliminate subsidies to farmers,
tax churches,
abolish the electoral college,
change the national anthem...
and remove lawyers from government,
especially from Congress.
At this point it'd be wise to say
most of us don't know the answer...
to Hal Phillip Walker,
but to answer
one of his questions,
as a matter of fact, Christmas has
always smelled like oranges to me.
Our country cries
For peace today
There's trouble in
The U.S.A.
Watergate
Is the sound that rings
Wonder what
This year will bring
- You're going the wrong way!
- Wonder what
This year will bring
- All y'all goin' the wrong way!
- Will there be sadness
Tears or pain
Or will the sun
Refuse to shine
Wonder what
This year will bring
Down in Nashville
I heard today
A shortage of food
Is on its way
While up in Denver
Gas shortage rings
Lord, I wonder what
- This year will bring
- You may have to sit out here.
That's all right, John.
- Give me time to work on my speech.
- Okay, thank you.
Hi. How are you?
Good to see you.
Or will the sun
Refuse to shine
- Delbert, how's it going?
- Hi, John. How are you?
- Can I say hello?
- He's working on his speech.
- We'll do that later.
- Right.
- He's gonna wait there?
- He'll sit out there for a minute.
- Anybody here yet?
- Yeah, some of the people.
- Barnett?
- He oughta be here quick.
This building was originally here...
It was made out of lumber
and plaster of Paris.
- Oh, yeah?
- This whole big building...
See, they built it for
a centennial celebration,
and people liked this,
they didn't want it torn down.
Nashville got to be called
the Athens of the South.
- They sorta took to that.
- Because of this building?
- Yeah, right.
- Oh, that's good.
Then they had to rebuild it. This
was built right before I was born.
Whoo!
Gonna be a scorcher.
The park police control all this.
What's all these chairs?
We don't need all these chairs.
- This ain't no band here, right?
- What's the matter, man?
I don't...
I don't believe it!
What's the matter?
Are you guys jerkin' me around?
Do you see what I see, or am I...
What the hell is that sign
doin' up there, Triple?
We had some ground rules.
No political signs,
no advertisements, no noth...
What the hell are you doin', huh?
Go about your business.
I have abided by all the ground
rules you laid down, Barnett.
I have Walker sitting out
behind this place like an idiot!
Well, he can sit out in the sun
and parch for all I care!
My wife ain't well! I brought her
out of a hospital bed to be here!
You gave me some truth! You're
full of it, just like your man!
- I have abided by every ground rule.
- Except what?
She ain't gonna appear here
with that sign up there!
- I have busted my ass for you!
- I'm gonna bust your ass too!
I am through with it!
Take your wife and take a walk!
I'll tell these people
she's not going to appear again!
- Well, go on and do it!
- Okay, take a walk, and I'll do it.
You'd do that, huh? You'd put
a knife in my wife's back like that?
You're putting the knife in
her back, buster. You're doing it.
I have not got time to take the sign
down and put it back up again!
What are you hollerin' about?
You tryin' to embarrass me?
I'm tryin' to be heard.
Well, get these chairs off
and we'll talk about it.
- I'll take care of it.
- Delbert... Where is that rat?
What are you hiding for,
you little rat?
And grant us so
to serve thee by day...
that we may find
eternal fellowship with them...
through Him who died
and rose again for us all,
Jesus Christ, our Lord.
Amen.
Mr. Green, it's not over.
- I'm going to find Martha.
- What for?
She owes some respect to Esther.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Barbara Jean and Haven Hamilton.
When I feel my life perishing
I call you on the phone
I always fix you up
When you get broken
'Cause every time
that I got hurt
And went out of control
I knew the fears you felt
Before you spoke them
You tell me
One, I love you
Two
I'm thinkin' of you
Three
I'll never let you go
And four, I miss you
Five, I wanna kiss you
Six
I won't leave you no more
When I feel my life vanishin'
Like waves upon the sand
With nothin'to replace it
But invention
So I make
my rhymes and I sing my songs
Still they don't understand
You can't find her here.
I'll find her.
- I'd sing ya
- One, I love you
Two
I'm thinkin'of you
Three
I'll never let you go
And four, I miss you
Five, I wanna kiss you
Six, I won't
leave you no more
One, I love you
Two
I'm thinkin'of you
Three
I'll never let you go
And four, I miss you
Five, I wanna kiss you
Six
I won't leave you no more
I won't leave you
No more
Six
I won't leave you
No mo-o-ore
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Mama and Daddy
Raised me with lovin' care
They sacrificed
So I could have
a better share
They fed me and nursed me
And sent me to school
Mama taught me how to sing
Daddy lived the Golden Rule
When I think of the children
alone and afraid
Abandoned and wild
like a fatherless child
I think of my mama
And how she could sing
Harmony with my daddy
Our laughter would ring
Down the highways
On the beaches
Just as far
as memory reaches
I still hear Daddy
singin'his old army songs
We'd laugh and count horses
As we drove along
We were young then
We were together
We could bear floods and fire
And bad weather
And now that I'm older
Grown up, on my own
I still love
Mama and Daddy best
And my Idaho home
Mama grew up
On the prairies of Kansas
She was tender and sweet
The dust and tornadoes
blew 'round her
But they left her
straight up on her feet
My daddy grew up on his own
more or less
His mama died
when he was just 11
He had seven sisters
to raise him
But he dreamed
of his mama in heaven
His daddy drank whiskey
and had a sharp eye
He sold chicken medicine
farmers would buy
Together they hunted
the fields and the farms
When his daddy died
my daddy rest in my mama's arms
Down the highways
On the beaches
Just as far
as memory reaches
I still hear Daddy
singin' his old army songs
We'd laugh and count horses
As we drove along
We were young then
We were together
We could bear
floods and fire
And bad weather
And now that I'm older
Grown up, on my own
I still love
Mama and Daddy best
And my Idaho home
And now that I'm older
Grown up, on my own
I still love
my Mama and Daddy best
And my Idaho home
For Mama and Daddy.
Thank you.
Thank you so much,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Thank you.
- Wonderful! Wonderful!
Let's hear it for Barbara Jean!
Wonderful!
Get that gun!
I'm all right.
You get her. You get her.
- Dad?
- Bud, help her off. I'm all right.
- Get Walker out of here!
- Get Walker outta here!
Get off your asses!
Watch her head!
Y'all take it easy now.
This isn't Dallas, it's Nashville.
This is Nashville.
You show 'em what we're made of.
They can't do this to us
here in Nashville.
Okay, everybody, sing!
Come on, somebody, sing!
No, I'm fine. You sing.
You stay here and play.
- Somebody sing. Somebody sing.
- You've been hurt.
- I'm gonna get somebody to help you.
- Somebody sing.
Sing!
I think you've been hurt.
Watch your step there.
Come on, easy, easy.
- I can't stop that blood, man!
- You got a car or somethin'?
They say this train
Don't give out rides
It don't worry me
Martha! Martha!
And all the world
is takin' sides
- It don't worry me
- What happened?
Can you please tell me
what happened?
'Cause in my empire
life is sweet
Just ask any bum you meet
- Life may be a one-way street
- Is there anybody who can help us?
But it don't worry me
Come on, everybody sing.
It don't worry me
You may say I ain't free
Come on!
It don't worry me
You may say I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It's not gon' worry me
The price of bread
may worry some
It don't worry me
Tax relief may never come
- Economy's depressed, not me
- I need you. Come on.
- My spirit's high as it can be
- Come on down here.
You may say I ain't free
It don't worry me
No, it don't worry me
You may say I ain't free
It don't worry me
Ohhhh, it don't
Worry me
It don't worry me
You may say I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It don't worry me
It don't worry me, no
It don't worry me
You might say
that I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It's not gonna worry me
- It don't worry me
- Now, if we don't live peaceful,
- there's gonna be nothin'left...
except Clorox bottles
and plastic fly swatters...
But it don't worry me
- It don't worry me
- Why not?
It don't worry me
You may say I ain't free
Well, it don't worry me
Come on, everybody!
- It don't worry me
- That's right.
It don't worry me
You might say I ain't free
You may say that I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It's not gon' worry us
It don't worry me
You may say that I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It's not gonna worry me
Ain't gonna be nothin'
left in our graves...
except fly swatters
with red dots on 'em.
- That's right!
- You may say
That I ain't free
- But it don't worry me
- It don't worry me
It don't worry me
You may say that I ain't free
But it don't worry me
It don't worry me
You may say that I ain't...
The price of bread
May worry some
But it don't worry me
And tax relief
May never come
But it don't worry me
Economy's depressed, not me
Spirit's high
As it can be
And you may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
They say this train
Don't give out rides
But it don't worry me
And all the world
Is takin'sides
But it don't worry me
'Cause in my empire
Life is sweet
Just ask any 'bo
that you might meet
Life may be
A one-way street
But it don't worry me
It don't worry me
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
It don't worry me
I ain't gonna be worried.
No, not me
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
I got a smile on my face
It don't worry me
I'm gonna walk
with my head held high
It don't worry me
You know why
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
Let me hear you sing it
It don't worry me
No
I'll be smilin', smilin'
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
Hey, hey, hey, yeah
It don't worry me
Oh, no
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
Sing along, singin'
It don't worry me
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
It don't worry me
I'm gonna walk
with my head held high
It don't worry me
Ohhh-ohh-ohh
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't worry me
Nice and easy
It don't worry me
I'm smilin'
No more cryin'
You may say
That I ain't free
But it don't
Worry
Me
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org