Get off that truck, son. Oh, i'm sorry
I put a dent in it...
Right up byThe light there;
I'm sorry.
You son of a bitch.
Okay. Okay, come on.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Give it your best shot.
Go ahead.
What the hell's eatin' you?
Your mama.
You wish. I wish i may,
I wish i might.
Wish i was a thousand miles
From here tonight.
Well, take off. Might just. You didn't
Get me a beer, did you?
You're gonna have to support
Your own bad habits.
You are a selfish
on of a bitch.
What are you lookin' at? Turn around
And feast your eyes.
I'm dreamin'. Well, you can go ahead
And keep on dreamin', son.
Would you look at him?
- Can i have a bite?
- Bite?
- I'm just dyin' for a cone.
- Dyin'?
- You're not from
Around here, are ya? No.
You got a name? It's mae.
Mae. Well, That's a nice name.
I mean, it's pretty.
- Where you from, mae?
You ever heard of sweetwater?
It's down near snyder,
Isn't it? Texas.
- Who you out here with?
- Friends.
- Boyfriend?
I'm just stayin' At the trailer
parkDown by the highway.
Oh, yeah?
I need a lift home.
My name's caleb.
Now that's
A real nice name.
Yeah.
You sure are pretty.
I guess everybody
Tells you that, huh?
- You got a boyfriend?
- Sometimes.
What about other times?
What about 'em?
I mean, i don't have
A girlfriend. Exactly. That's too bad.
You plan to stay around
For a while? Not long.
You're not leaving tonight? No.
You think maybe-
There's a show down-Shh.
What? Here? Stop the truck.
Yeah. Now. -
There's somethin'
I want to show you.
There's somethin' You want
to show me? Yeah. The night.
What about it? It's dark.
I noticed. It's also bright.
It'll blind you.
I can't see.
Well, listen.
Do you hear it?
I'm listenin'. I don't hear nothin'.
Listen hard. Do you hear it?
Hear what? The night.
It's deafening.
Well, i'll hold your ears.
Listen hard.
I sure haven't met
Many girls like you.
No, you haven't met
Any girls like me.
Look up.
Stars See that one?
First one i laid my eyes on.
The light that's leavin'
That star right now...
Will take a billion years
To get down here.
You want to know why you've
Never met a girl like meBefore?
Yeah. Why? Because i'll still be here
When the light from that star...
Gets down here to earth
In a billion years.
That sounds like fun.
It is.
I'd like
To be there too. Maybe.
How?
Well, who knows?
I sure haven't met Any girls like you
No. No, you sure haven't.
- You ain't in Any hurry, are you?
Never hurry.
I see. You want
To listen to the radio?
See if i can
Find somethin'.
How's that?
- Where we going?
You'll see.
I don't like
Surprises, caleb.
Oh, you're gonna
Like this one. Trust me.
Ma'am.
I'm gonna introduce you
To a friend of mine. All right?
I want you To close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
Keep your eyes closed.
What's wrong, boy?
What's the matter with you?
Horses just don't like me.
No kiddin'. Why not?
They just don't.
That's all right.
- You're pretty strong.
- Yeah. Stronger than you.
Damn!
What is it?
What's wrong?
What time is it?
I don't know.
What time do you
Got to be home?
Honey, dawn
Is a long ways off.
We got plenty of time.
Take me home, caleb.
What's the rush, mae?
I have to go.
Hurry, caleb. Hurry!
What is it?
I don't understand
What's goin' on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Okay.
- Just a couple more miles. I can get there.
They'll never know.
- I didn't notice the time.
What is buggin' you anyway?
It's your daddy, right?
You don't get home on time, He's gonna give you a
Don't you worry about it. I'll just tell him
The car broke down.
Just get me home!
Maybe i will. But you're gonna
Have to kiss me first.
Come on, mae. Just a little touch.
I ain't askin' for much.
Mae. Mae!
Sure was some kiss.
Hey, dad, there's caleb.
About time he came home.
- Daddy, he looks sick.
What'd you say, darlin'?
Look!
Shit.
Gotcha!
Caleb!
Howdy.
I'm gonna separate your head
From your shoulders. Hope you don't mind none.
You put a hurtin' on us, Mae, but good.
It was sort of an accident.
Nah, that was sloppy, mae.
Real sloppy.
Let me do it, jesse.
Let me tap dance on him, Won't ya?
It'll be so good. Do it, fast.
- All right!
Yeah. Let the good times roll.
- Whoo!
- No!
- Him? - what the fuck
Is goin' on?
It ain't what's goin' on, Son, it's what's
comin' off Your face, clean off.
- well, you might as well
Just kill me then too.
- How you figure that? 'cause he's been bit
But he ain't been bled.
Ah, shit! He's turned by now.
Son of a bitch, jess.
He's turned. He comes with us.
It's all right.
You see these tire marks?
That's four hours And nine minutes ago.
Meanin', If they're on the highway
At a steady 55,
That puts 'em clear
In the next damn state.
I wanna know what you boys
Are doin' about that.
Look, i'll take care of it.
You can't, mae.
I turned you, I taught you.
Well, i turned him
And i'll teach him.
What's the matter, homer,
You jealous?
A little too little
To be jealous.
You have any idea What it's like
to beA big man on the inside...
And have a small body
On the outside?
You have any idea What it's like
to hear About it every night?
It's risky as shit, jess.
He fucks up, it's our ass.
It's our ass, mae, It's your ass.
You wanna give him a week?
Then it's decided. We give him a week to
see If we can call him one of us.
Cut the shit. I know you're awake.
I can smell it.
You slap me if i'm sleepin',
Cause i wanna wake up.
Guess what?
Who the hell
Are you people?
I'm jesse hooker.
I believe you already Met mae.
Diamondback.
I'm you're worst
Fuckin' nightmare.
Severen.
And i'm homer.
That's h-O-m-e-r.
Mispronounce it And i
wouldn't wantTo be you.
Oh, baby,
You are beautiful. Hmm?
Whoo! All right!
Hey, jesse, remember that
Fire we started in chicago?
- Let's get a move on.
I think it's burnin'.
Whoo!
Bombs away, little buddy.
Come on, jesse.
I don't feel so well.
I know.
No, you don't.
Look, i don't understand
What's goin' on here.
I like you.
I really do.
But i gotta get home.
I'm sorry.
Let me go.
- You won't get very far.
- We'll see.
I'll be seein' ya.
Before long.
Excuse me.
When's your next bus
To fixx, oklahoma?
Where the hell is fixx?
Well, the nearest
City's lauden.
Gate 12, 15 minutes, $14.
Right.
Um, i only have 11.
I got a bus ticket for 14.
Can you give me a break? I gotta get home.
You're three bucks shy.
What seems to be The problem, kid?
No problem.
I'm just $3.OO short
For a bus ticket home.
Can you help me out?
Well, i got this.
Great.
Come this way, please.
What's the problem? You.
You're not looking
Too good, kid.
I ain't feelin' Too good,
sir. What are you on?
You wouldn't believe me If i told you.
Let me see your eyes.
You got blood on you.
Yes, sir.
I got cut.
Look, i only got $11.
And i need three more
To get home.
Can you help me out?
Get home.
And be a good boy.
Mm. Stop the bus.
I got to get off.
I'm dying.
You're just in time.
Drink this.
I asked you once If you listened
to the night. Now listen to me.
Look, the night.
It's so bright...
It'll blind you.
Huh.
Sarah.
- Morning, daddy.
- Morning, baby.
- You sleep some? - i sleep some
You sleep a little?
A little. Bad dreams.
Me too.
Not much, loy, But the highway patrol found
What might be your winnebago.
It was left in Some fill and torched.
Nobody was inside.
Probably switched cars. Could be
your boy's fallin' inWith some trouble.
- What are you Doin' about that?
- All we can.
Well, it's not enough, Eakers.
Loy, you're just gonna
Have to bear with us For a bit.
Yes, operator,
I'd like to reverse charges...
On a long-distance call
To oklahoma.
Caleb.
Caleb. Caleb.
Look, caleb.
I wanted to go home too.
You know, i called, mae.
Ain't nobody home. Nobody was home.
Jesus! This is fucked, mae.
I'm scared.
So was i, but don't be.
Just feel it. Feel what's in you.
That's what scares me.
I feel it.
Look, you're in my hands.
You'll be fine.
What'll we do now?
Anything we want...
To the end of time.
But y ou have
To learn to kill.
I don't wanna kill.
You wanna die?
Mae, i ain't no killer.
Well, just don't
Think of it as killing.
Don't think at all.
Just use your instinct.
It's just something that you do Night after night.
It's only Ever a question of how.
- Instinct.
Evenin'. Whoo! Evenin'.
It would be my pleasure And honor to invite
you two Lovely ladies for a drink.
All right. All right.
It's making me shaky.
That's because you have to.
Kill. That's right
. The night has its price.
Where are we, diamondback?
Hat road is this? You got me.
Isn't that where
I had the flat tire?
You pulled over.
And there you stood
By the side of that road.
And i just knew
You were trouble.
And you were right.
How many years ago
Was that?
Just remember, hon. You don't remember
the dateOf that night neither, do you?
Oh, jesse.
Look. You see what i see?
Hey, whichever way You're headin',
I'd appreciate a lift.
Sure thing. Climb in.
- Turn off the car.
- Hey, asshole, my pal here...
Told you to turn off the car.
Now, you mind if iDance
with your wife?
She's a real...
Look at this one. Ooh, yeah.
You're not Gonna look so good...
With your face ripped off.
Lord, did we Get lucky tonight.
She is so beautiful.
And he is so fuckin' stupid.
You kids,
Y'all running from home?
Sure. Hey, that's okay by me.
Sometimes home is bad.
Me, i got a truck For of home.
Nice setup you got here.
How do you fly it?
Hey, you drive
A truck before?
I've driven a semi.
Semi... that's five.
Five gears, brother.
This got thirteen.
You got two to the rear
And the rest go forward. Anyone smoke?
Yeah.
Got a light?
What about the rest?
Rest? Shifting.
You know how
To shift, don't ya?
Watch this.
Come on, baby,
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Talk to me.
Come on, there.
Show me how to
Brake and stop it.
Okay, now this is The most important thing
When you wanna brake a truck.
You got to remember
You got two brakes.
And one brake is for the cab.
This one over here.
And the other one
Is for the trailer. This one right here.
When you want to brake The truck,
you gotta Brake the trailer first.
Come on, baby.
Then, you got To brake your cab.
Or else. Or else what?
Or else you jackknife.
The trailer hits the cab,
No more truck.
No more truck,
No more truck driver.
Hey, uh, you okay?
You got a problem, kid?
What's the matter, boy?
You can't drink and drive?
You want to be the captain
Of a boat this big, boy,
You gotta be able
To stand the water, huh?
What's the matter, boy?
You really sick? Huh?
Caleb...
You could kill me
If you drink too much.
Shh. Honey.
Let's you and me go make A phone call.
See if anybody Knows anything. Okay?
Sheriff eakers?
Loy colton here.
You did?
A positive make?
Where was he?
Hope, kansas, bus station?
Cop said
He was goin' home?
Well, you checked the house? He
should have been there By now.
No, i'm in waco, texas.
I guess i'm headin' In the wrong direction.
Think i'll turn around
And head north.
Real brave boy.
Jesse, he needs
More time. Please.
Look, one more night.
One more night.
Then i'm gonna get
My wet dream, boy!
Why wait? We're gonna do it
anyway. He ain't one of us.
You don't belong.
Besides, you're so damn ugly,
It makes my gums ache.
I wonder about you, mae.
I should be wondering About you.
It ain't right for mae
To be carrying you, caleb.
He makes a kill tonight!
I don't care how you do it.
You do it, or you're done.
And done means dead
Without guile.
It means you be
Real uncomfortable...
For a long, long time.
That's your mama
Talkin', boy.
Well, i'll be goddamned.
Shit-kicker heaven.
Hey, come on, caleb. Let's belly up to
the bar And get us some refreshment.
Park your carcass.
Hi. Howdy.
Bartender, give me A couple of shots,
Whatever donkey piss
You're shoving down These cocksuckers' throats.
Hey. Hey! You spilled my drink.
Well, why don't you Lick it
up off the bar, Meatball?
Why don't you
Lick it up yourself?
Hey, i ever tell you
The one about buffalo bill?
Ah, hell You're all right.
Go on, give him another one.
Tequila. Beer in a glass.
Now pay the man. -
Oh, bartender?
That'll be a double shot...
Of your very best
Watered-down shit Right here.
There are two ways you can
Leave these here premises.
Is that a fact?
That's a fact.
On your feet
Or on your back.
That's pretty tough words
For a bartender, huh?
Gee whiz. If you're not
gonna Serve me a drink, well...
I'll just Have to drink his.
How can you Drink that shit?
Go on, hit him a couple Of times.
I'm tryin'To show the boy somethin'.
Now you hit
Him back, caleb.
You son of aOhh!
Phew!
Did i do that?
"did i do that"?
Good times.
- Just the glass. The glass.
- Just the glass?
You're shakin' all over.
You nervous? I would be too if
i were you. But then again,
I'm not you.
You know, Your skin is as soft
As a preacher's belly.
You know that?
Don't you want the beer?
No, honey The drink's on me.
What you people want?
Just a couple more
Minutes of your time,
About the same duration
As the rest of your life.
? Oww!
Oww, oww, oww, hoo-hoo-hoo!
Oww, oww, oww!
You know what?
What? This is the best
time I've had...
Since i nailed your mama
In the back Of your daddy's truck.
He was there Watchin' too.
I didn't see nothin', man.
To tell you the truth,
I think he liked it.
I'm cool, man.
I know she did.
Don't fuck with me.
You know what
I said to your mama?
You know what I said to her?
I said, "shh.
This ain't gonna hurt. "
I said...
"shh!"
I hate 'em when
They ain't been shaved.
Whoo! Mmm!
It's finger-lickin' good.
Hey, jess, I think i smell like
A dead polecat.
Well, this is a kick, Ain't it?
Holy shit!
Holy shit! Jess.
Am i alive?
Hey. You look like
40 miles of rough road.
Why don't you
Sit this one out?
I'll take it from here.
Oh, yoo-hoo!
I got a new name for you.
Mr. Pig knuckle.
Are you havin' a little trouble
With your hog-leg there?
Ohh!
There's a fly
On the ceilin'.
Come on.
Won't you dance with me?
It's all right. Come on.
? Now i just found a game
That i can't play?
? And this is where
The cowboy rides away?
? And my heart is sinkin
Like the settin' sun?
? Settin' on the things
I wish i'd done?
? It's time to say good-bye?
He's for you, caleb.
? This is where the cowboy
Rides away? - No!
Go.
Bartender, set 'em up.
Yo!
Here. Whoo!
This'll do. All right.
Allow me.
Please. Wait. Please.
Get in here!
- You fucked up
For the last time, boy. - Sorry.
Yeah? Why don't you do
Your sorry ass a favor? Take care of him later.
Black out them
Bulkheads and fantail. The sun is on the rise.
We should leave your boyfriend
In the road and let him Get himself a suntan.
- good idea.
- We better move our ass. Here she comes.
Come on, little boner.
We got five minutes Before sunup.
And we ain't found us
A place to stay yet.
That goddamn kid you let go
Is goin' straight to the law.
And they're gonna be
Combin' the area For this shitbox.
You both fucked up.
Gonna keep talkin', jess,
Or you gonna get us Out of the sun?
Okay.
I'd like to rent
One of your bungalows, sir. Huh?
One of your bungalows.
Oh.
The key.
Uh, here's...
You were here once before, Wasn't you?
Lots of years back?
Yes, i get through here
About once every 50 years.
Make me a reservation.
It's the police.
Honey, wake up.
Jesse, wake up.
Wake up.
Come out with your hands up!
Fuckin' daylight!
God!
Daylight! No!
Please, no!
Pull yourself together,
Old man!
Leave him alone, jess. Shh.
I'll give you this end of it.
Give him the piece, severen.
Severen, Give him the gun!
Don't shoot
Your pecker off, boy.
Back!
We got the place surrounded!
Come on out!
This is your last warning!
Checkout time.
Aah!
How you doin', jess? Like shit!
How you doin'?
I'm down to
My last inch of skin!
Now, boys, it ain't over
Till it's over!
Goin' after the van, jess.
That's a good one, shit bug!
You go outside, they're gonnaBe servin' you in a
- you got a better idea?
- It's the only chance we got.
Give me the keys, grandpa.
Go ahead.
We'll cover you, son.
Shit bug's gonna
Get himself killed.
What have we got to lose?
Just a pretty face.
- Get a move on.
We'll cover you. - See you in hell!
You did it!
Goin' home.
Let me in!
Let's get out of here!
Whoo-whoo! -
Jesse.
Come on, you little boner. Hurry your ass.
Wait! Get up here!
Wait up. Wait up!
Back there,
You did good.
Thanks.
Catch.
All right.
Shake?
Thanks.
You bought yourself
Some time, son.
Jesse, there's somethin'
I've been meanin' to ask you.
- Yeah? What might that be?
- How old are you?
Let's put it this way:
I fought for the south.
The south?
We lost.
Hey, caleb, let's go out
And look at the night.
All right.
How about a little five-card
Russian roulette?
Why not, severen?
It almost feels like
You're one of us now.
Yeah, it does.
So what does that make me?
I ain't exactly sure.
It's good, right?
I guess so, yeah.
Do you miss the sun?
It's been so long,
I can't really remember.
How long?
Spring, four years back,
And i was in high school. Mmm.
Homer said he was in fifth grade
And he needed help With his homework.
Little weasel.
- Do you miss he day?
- The day?
Nah. I can see better at night.
Here we go.
I don't want this.
Three cards.
How many you want, Little boner?
How many for you,
You old saddle bum?
Three. Three. There you go.
One for her.
Three for the dealer.
Are you cheatin', Severen?
I ain't cheatin'.
What's this then?
Deal the cards.
I fold. I'm gonna taste the air.
Watch the time, boy.
Deal the cards.
It's impolite to stare.
Howdy.
My name's homer. What's yours?
Sarah.
What are you doing down here
All by yourself?
I do what i wanna do
When i wanna do it.
Wanna watch tv?
- What's on?
- Whatever you want.
Is it a color television?
Uh-huh.
Beautiful morning
Coming up here.
Looks like
Another sunny day also. And folks...
I'd like to introduce you
To... Sarah.
Boy, you people
Sure stay up late.
We keep odd hours.
Who ordered pizza?
Homer, sweet darling?
I tell you what.
I'll play you for the pizza.
Homer, you look at me when
I'm talkin' to you, now.
What?
Deal 'em.
Sarah, you here
With your family?
- Just my daddy.
- And what room are you Stayin' in, honey?
Uh, number three.
There'll be something else on.
There'll be something. Wait.
No, that's okay. I better be going now
No, wait! Wait, sarah.
Sarah. I oughta punch
Your lights out.
I guess you oughta. Oh!
Oh, god, honey.
She's my sister.
What the hell's she doin'
Up at 5:OO in the morning?
I tried callin' you.
We've been out a lot
Drivin' in the truck,
Tryin' to track you down. Dad.
Son.
Son?
'Round and 'round
And 'round she goes.
And where she stops,
Nobody knows.
It's about time For that big old wheel
To stop rotatin'.
Who are these people?
I'm with them now.
Jesse, you let them go.
It's my family.
Go on, now.
You comin'?
Caleb.
No. But you're goin'.
No!
She's mine.
You're gonna have to Give her back, son.
She's not yours.
- I'm gonna nip her.
- You can't do that.
I chewed mae.
She went off
And chewed on you.
Now i'm chewing
Your little sister.
That makes us even-steven.
You let her go or
I'm gonna have to hurt Your body, homer.
- You're gonna have to hurt My body first.
- Hold on a second, pilgrim.
Remember which side Of the bread
Your butter's on.
Goddamn, this is my family!
Let 'em go!
The question is whether
They'd let us go.
They've been trackin' us.
Now they know our faces. I say kill 'em.
I've had about Enough of this shit.
Let go of my boy.
And y ou, let go
Of my little girl.
Daddy, put that away.
Ain't gonna do no good.
What do you mean, It ain't gonna do no good?
I'd listen to your son.
- I'd stop right there
If i was you, mister. - Not likely.
For you.
Shit!
- Go on, daddy! Go!
- What the goddamn hell's Goin' on, son?
I can't expect y ou To believe it.
I can't believe it myself.
I ain't a person anymore.
I don't know what i am. I'm sick!
- We're gonna get you to The hospital right away.
- You do and i'm dead! No!
Caleb, Those people back there,
They wasn't normal.
Normal folks, They don't spit out bullets
When you shoot 'em.
I got bit.
I got a bite.
We're gonna get you to
The hospital right away.
No! Goddamn,
You want me killed?
I ain't goin' to
The goddamn hospital!
Hospitals fix this?
Damn it, daddy,
Take me home!
Daddy? Daddy?
You ever... You ever transfuse a person?
Daddy?
I'm all right.
Oh, god, honey.
Whoo!
You okay? Yeah, i am.
Sarah, i'll tell you
About it one day.
Just promise you won't
Ask me about it till then, All right?
Okay. Wanna go ride a horse?
Okay, let's go!
Knock it off.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's gettin' cold.
You can almost feel The fall comin' on.
Yeah, the days
Are gettin' shorter.
Nights are gettin' longer.
I'm tired.
You pick your dishes up And i'll be upstairs
To read to you.
I want caleb To read to me.
Go on upstairs. I'll be up in a minute.
Hey, don't forget
To brush your teeth.
You know... Look, i...
I'm gonna go out
And oil that swing.
That can wait.
No, it's all right. I can use the air.
Hi, caleb.
Why did you leave?
You're warm.
Your skin's warm.
I belong here, mae.
This is my family.
I miss you.
What's it gonna be?
Mae!
Sarah!
Shit!
Son of a bitch!
I'd sell him.
Goddamn. Where's my sister, severen?
- Hey, let me give you
A hand there, old buddy. - Asshole.
Hey, caleb!
I hate to be an indian giver,
I really do,
But you disappointed me,
And now you're gonna
Have to pay.
First, you're gonna
Give me back my spur.
Then i'm gonna knock
Your tonsils out your asshole.
What do you think
Of them apples, huh?
Stop! Stop!
Hey, mister...
Get the hell off my truck!
- Keep goin'
Before you get killed. -
I'm gonna give you
Till the count of five!
One, two, four...
Bull's-eye!
Mister? Jesus.
I'm sorry. Damn you.
Now come on!
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
- Oh, shit.
- Hey, caleb?
Fasten your fuckin'
Seat belt!
Son of a bitch!
No! -
Whoo-hoo!
It's time to pay The fiddler.
Where's my sister, jess?
I taught severen
Everything he knew,
But not everything I know.
The last sound that you hear
On your way to hell...
Is gonna be your guts
Snappin' like a bullwhip.
This ain't got nothin'
To do with my sister!
You leave her out of this
And let her go!
Jesse, let him come back.
It's too late for that, Mae.
Goddamn, jesse,
Where's my sister?
Everything is gonna be
All right.
Don't be scared.
- I'm gonna take her back.
- Sure you will.
Caleb, look out!
Jess!
Hey!
Go, caleb.
Make a run for it.
Come on, jesse!
Get in the car! Mae, come on!
Hurry up!
Get in the car!
Go on! Aah!
Go on, honey. Go on. Run.
Run, sarah!
No!
Block that sun out!
Mae!
No, homer!
No!
Caleb!
Wait, sarah!
My god.
Jesse.
Roast.
Fun times.
Caleb, what's happening?
I brought you home.
I'm afraid. Don't be.
It's just the sun.