Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Ma'am, we gonna rebuild a new school
at no cost to you.
No cost at all, ma'am.
Perhaps someplace else. They'll be back.
No, see, we done already decided.
We're gonna rebuild it right here.
A brand-new school
where children can learn in...
and we can be proud of,
right here on Mont Royal.
And them devils come back here...
we're waiting on them.
-That'd be right.
-Right.
lt might all be just a terrible mistake...
but this school is very welcome.
Mrs. Main.
There's a telegraph for you, ma'am.
lt's from George Hazard.
lt says that Constance...
has just been murdered by Elkanah Bent.
Madeline, please stop and reconsider.
Perhaps you didn't read it all.
lt says that this happened on Friday.
The funeral is this morning.
You can't possibly....
Oh, God.
He left on Thursday.
He'll never forgive himself.
Damn Elkanah Bent.
-You know him?
-lndeed l do. He's a madman.
l think that he is capable of....
You're thinking he killed Orry, ain't you?
Yes, l think he did...
with Ashton.
-l must get to George.
-Miss Madeline?
-We in here, Titus.
-He needs me.
Madeline, please stop.
The message ends, ''Please don't come.''
And it's signed simply, ''George Hazard.''
Miss Madeline, the log float done arrived.
l never seen so many logs
in these parts before.
-lsaac says it's best you come.
-You have duties and responsibilities here.
We need you.
Dear George,
we're all so worried about you.
You must mingle more. There are so many
people here to thank for coming.
Not now.
lsabel, George is grieving.
The people will understand.
The most important men
to the future of America are all here.
lf you're going to join them
in the House of Representatives...
you should take advantage
of the situation.
She's really a very caring woman, George.
You see qualities in her
that elude me, brother.
You may be happy with your position
at the Freedmen's Bureau, but l'm not.
Sweetheart. Go comb your hair, darling.
l have plans for our future
and for our fortunes.
Secretary Stanton...
General Grant. Why, Senator Stevens.
-How very delightful of you all to come.
-Mrs. Hazard.
Stanley, good to see you.
Stanley, please allow me
to congratulate you...
on your fine work
with the Freedmen's Bureau.
The Republican Party is proud
of the progress of emancipation.
Stanley is capable of much greater things.
Excuse me.
We must see to the other guests.
Mr. Jackson.
l try hard to guide
and improve your career...
and you make no effort.
l'm sad for George.
And l grieve Constance as well, lsabel.
She cared little enough for us, God knows.
-George is my brother.
-And would do very little to help you.
We must start
helping ourselves, Stanley...
-and to that end, l'm traveling south.
-South?
-Your war profits.
-All the Hazards profited from the war...
and thanks to me,
we have some funds in the South...
that can be invested
in some very cheap land.
-Your bureau can aid us.
-That is privileged information, lsabel.
-That land is for ex-slaves, not rich, white--
-Stanley, darling.
The ex-slaves can't buy up all of the South,
can they?
Why don't we go upstairs and discuss it?
We haven't seen each other
in a very long time.
Good afternoon, Edwin.
Mr. Hazard sent for me.
The General is in the library, Mr. Ouinlan.
You're to go right in.
Good afternoon.
That lrishman is offensive.
Excellent foreman, though.
l'm placing Hazard lron
completely in your hands.
That's absurd.
All my correspondence
is to be transferred to you.
You're to handle Mrs. Main's accounts
with the Charleston Bank.
Anything she wants or needs,
see that she gets it.
You're to treat everything as your own.
-George, l'm just a foreman.
-l know you can do the job, Jack.
Besides, you're the only one
l can trust right now.
Surely your brother can be trusted?
lt's the vulture he's married to
that can't be trusted.
lf she makes a move on anything,
you let me know immediately.
l'm counting on you, Jack.
l can't make any decisions right now.
Food chokes me.
l can't sleep.
And when l do,
l wake and keep asking why.
Why wasn't l here?
l don't know what to do
with her things, Jack.
-Sir, the Pinkerton detective is here.
-Send him right in.
Agent Jupiter Smith.
-Gen. Hazard, sir.
-The war is over. ''Mister'' will suffice.
This is Jack Ouinlan, my associate.
Take a seat.
l've just come from the local police.
They suggest that you inform me...
of the particulars
of Mrs. Hazard's murder, sir.
Elkanah Bent is a brutal, vicious man.
He's a butcher of men, women,
and children alike.
And he takes great pleasure in it, too.
He and l were together at West Point...
along with General Orry Main,
late of the Confederate Army.
l have no doubt he killed Orry, too.
He knifed him down,
just like he did my Constance.
Did they tell you Bent came after me?
Spent weeks lying in wait
for me to return.
And what would his motives be, sir?
Orry and l got him dismissed
from West Point.
He blames us
for ruining his military career.
He also swore a vendetta against Charlie.
-Charlie, sir?
-Charlie Main, Orry's cousin.
He served under Bent just before the war.
He's seeking revenge
against both of our families.
So then he may return
to try again for you, sir.
No, he won't.
Because before that can happen,
your organization's going to find him first.
And when you do, he is mine.
You think there's lndians tracking us?
He's got a nose for it.
He kind of feels them.
-ls that true?
-lt sure is.
Kind of feel them, huh?
Well, l don't see any tracking us.
When you see them,
it might be a mite too late.
Now, we're going to hole up soon.
We'll do a little work
on that jug of corn whiskey.
-Might be the last chance we get.
-Yeah.
-You are an optimistic cuss, ain't you?
-That's me.
Good night, Jimmy.
Well, are they out there?
Not tonight...
but they're there.
This is their land. They know we're here.
Give me the password and do the shake.
Wesley, have you lost your damn mind?
l've knowed you since both of us was kids.
l know, but you still got to give
the password and do the secret grip.
Damn. Liberty, Wesley.
-Evening, lsaac.
-Hey, now.
Good to see you.
Gentlemen.
Can l have your attention,
please, gentlemen?
l call this meeting...
of the Union League Club,
Ashley River District to order.
Now, Mr. Andrew Johnson
is our President...
since Mr. Lincoln was shot.
And Mr. Johnson
is a Southern-loving Democrat.
He'd like to see you cut right out
of your hard-earned rights...
political and land-wise.
He doesn't want to see you vote.
He has pardoned the very men...
who have oppressed us for so long a time.
But the Republicans, and that's all of us...
we want to see you rise up so high...
you'll have to walk down steps
to reach heaven.
-Who are your friends?
-Republicans!
-And who's the enemy?
-Democrats!
Liberty, Lincoln, League!
Now, my friends...
there are still slaves...
because there are still those
who would be masters.
How many here
still work for their old masters?
Own up.
Stand up and own up now.
You get paid for your efforts?
We'll be paid. Miss Madeline promised.
-Besides, she give us more than pay.
-More than pay?
What's more important
than cash money for your labors?
Don't you people know that the
Republicans delivered you from slavery?
What's more important
than cash money for your labors?
Pride.
We gots pride.
Well, sir, all l can say is--
We done heard everything you had to say,
Mr. Klawdell.
Now you going to listen to me.
Y'all sit down.
You can't see how it is down here...
because you're from up North.
But you best take a long, hard look
and listen.
What we do now...
what we gives...
we do and give 'cause we want to.
lt ain't like it was before the war.
lt's different now.
We's free now.
And free men choose.
What point is it in being free...
if you can't choose?
Hold on there. Hold up.
Now, l don't know about the rest of you,
but this man....
-Sir, what is your name?
-lsaac Kano.
What you say is true.
Y'all know we've come together
to choose delegates...
to the January convention
down in Charleston.
l, for one, think we've found
our first delegate here in Mr. Kano.
What say the rest of you?
What is that you're doing?
This is a sample of earth
l found at Mont Royal.
l'm taking it to the bank.
They'll have a survey done, and when
that's complete and a loan is secured...
we'll be rich once again.
But Madeline owns Mont Royal.
Madeline is living there,
but not for much longer.
She is not blood.
Mont Royal belongs in our family.
-Cooper--
-Don't sass me.
Don't ever sass me.
What are you becoming, Cooper?
Strong once again.
l'm sorry, Cooper.
Do you understand the potential value
of what you're holding in your hand?
Yes.
And l also understand that...
you have no legal claim as yet
to Mont Royal.
Cooper, l can't loan you money
on something that you don't own.
You're late, ma'am.
Champagne. How glorious.
-Did you hear me, Ashton?
-Yes, of course l heard you, Fen, dear.
l was only a tiny bit late.
No need for concern.
Champagne, please.
Thank you.
Oh, my!
My darling husband.
-Do you want me.... l can demonstrate it.
-Please.
lt's only the first model, you understand,
but there will be more in time.
These pianos will stand in every cathouse
and saloon all over the world...
and no one is going to be able
to resist her.
Just like me.
-That's why l named it so.
-Champagne for everyone.
To my remarkable genius of a husband
who is going to make me...
us all very rich.
To the Ashton piano.
How did you manage to buy that dress?
l put a little bit of money away
every now and then.
You save any more back,
you give it to me.
l'm not some slave, Fen.
No, you're a slut,
and you look every inch of it right now.
Not everybody thinks so.
So you know everybody?
l'm warning you.
lf you ever want to see Mont Royal again...
you cut back your spending.
lt took everything we had
to start this business up.
We're flat broke right now.
We are going to be very rich...
and l just wanted to be beautiful
for my husband.
We're not married yet.
You're hurting me.
-You scare me.
-l scare you?
-l saw you kill a man in cold blood.
-He was a disgusting pig and l hated--
That's not enough reason
to kill somebody.
You behave yourself,
or you'll never see your mansion again.
You don't know me.
l know you.
You are vicious and greedy and vain.
But you amuse me sometimes.
Let's go out for a fine dinner.
You can show that wicked dress off.
Come along.
lf you insist.
-Can l help you?
-l certainly hope so, my friend.
l'm trying to locate
an old comrade of mine from the war.
-His name?
-Charles Main...
late of the Confederacy, but most recently
reported to this division.
l see you're admiring this.
lt's unusual, l know.
lt belonged to my dear, departed mother.
l'm afraid of losing it.
l'll see what l can discover
on your old comrade.
l appreciate it.
Excuse me, sir. l think l found it.
Your friend was here
under the name of Charles May.
He deserted,
but President Johnson pardoned him...
on the request of Brevet Brigadier Duncan.
Brigadier Duncan?
You have any more information?
Brigadier Duncan corresponds
with him still. You want the address?
l'd be indebted to you, sir.
Appreciate it.
-What did that man want?
-He was searching out a friend, sir.
l gave Brigadier Duncan's address
in St. Louis for further reference.
My God, Private,
l think you've made a grave mistake.
Run a message
to the Pinkerton Office in town.
All aboard, please.
This for me?
-Thank you, Jim.
-lt's a present, Charlie.
Why, there's a nice one.
My son Gus used to collect these.
That's a real nice one. l thank you.
l'm going to keep this with me, all right?
Makes me happy.
l owe you a debt
for your patience to Jim here.
lt's not hard. He's a good boy.
Besides, my debt beats yours all to hell.
You never did tell me
how you two met up anyway.
Kind of like l met you.
Bunch of bullies was beating him up.
-Cheyenne?
-lt could be wolves.
lf they're Cheyenne, l hope
they're only after our horses and mules.
So do l. You don't plan on
giving them up, do you?
lt's either that or give them our hair.
No, please don't hurt me!
For better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer...
in sickness and in health...
till death do us part.
With the blessings of the Lord,
l give you a man and his wife.
Well, kiss her.
-Jane.
-l'm so happy.
Madeline, is something wrong?
No, everything's fine.
lt's just that Maum Beatrice is taking care
of little Orry, and l should get back.
You go back inside.
Wouldn't it be a shame if someone was
to bolt the door on them fine people...
-and set the whole thing on fire?
-Damn shame.
Could be done, you know.
lt's real tempting.
That's not why you're leaving, is it?
This has brought back memories.
You take the buggy. l feel like walking.
Wait a minute. Who's that?
Well, now.
-Howdy, Mrs. Main.
-Girl, you know what we plan to do.
Why don't you settle down
and put your mind to it?
You're disgusting.
Come on, you haven't had it in a long time.
You ought to enjoy it.
Leave me alone.
Come on, Gettys. Nobody around.
Let's get that stuff.
l'm being whooped here.
Gettys, you fool, come help me!
Gettys, don't do this!
-Come on.
-Don't!
This lady took a stumble and fell down.
We was just helping her up.
-See, we live close by and--
-You're just being neighborly?
Yes, sir.
Do it someplace else.
-Jenks is the name, ma'am.
-l'm Mrs. Main.
-You sure you're all right, ma'am?
-Yes, thank you.
Are you on Mont Royal to see me?
No, l'm a geologist
running a survey for phosphates.
Who sent you?
A Charleston bank
employed my services, ma'am.
Mr. Jenks, thank you.
-l thank you very much.
-Certainly, ma'am.
-Did you say 10 cents?
-l believe l said 1, ma'am.
But you can have it for 10.
Can l have this ribbon for my hair, Mama?
lt's been a hard year, Sophie.
Ma'am, l'll tell you what.
l could use some hay to carry along
for my mule.
l'd be glad to trade you for it.
She'd look real pretty in that ribbon.
-l have to go get my husband.
-Could you do that, ma'am?
Appreciate it.
-Papa's in the far field. l'll go fetch him.
-All right.
Appreciate it.
You want me to tie that up
into a bow for you?
What do you say...
about showing me where that hay is,
little lady?
All right.
Come in.
Mr. Cooper?
Forgive me for marching on in, but there's
someone here l'd like you to meet.
lsabel Truscott, Mr. Main.
Miss Truscott is interested
in investing hereabouts...
and when l related
your discovery of phosphates, she--
Thank you, Mr. Keyes.
You've been quite gallant and useful.
When l have discussed matters
with Mr. Main...
l shall call on you again at the bank.
Very well.
When you need my services,
l'll be gladly available.
Have you remarried, lsabel?
No, but because
of Stanley's political hopes...
l feel it best to use my maiden name
in my business dealings.
After all these years,
you're still a fine figure of a man.
l understand Northern investors
are not always welcome in this house.
lt's not a rigid rule. You're quite welcome.
How did you come to learn...
about my phosphates?
When it comes to my money,
l always do scrupulous research.
l know all about your phosphates...
and that you're searching for money
for some of your other holdings...
such as Mont Royal.
Exactly what sort of investment
were you thinking about making?
Substantial enough
to open a full mine operation...
and a fertilizer plant.
-My terms--
-l'm afraid that you're in no position...
to accept anything but my terms.
1 for me, and the balance for you.
-That in exchange for full financial backing.
-My, my.
Would that extend
into my other companies, as well?
Now, my dear Cooper, don't be piggish.
This operation will be so successful that
you'll be able to invest your own money...
in whatever way you wish.
There is one problem, though.
Since Mont Royal is not fully yours,
and Madeline has enterprises of her own...
she will no doubt be interested
in the profit that you make.
You may split that with your sister-in-law
however you see fit.
There's one other consideration.
What other consideration?
Labor can be such a difficulty.
The workers must be bound to us...
and the best way to do that
is with a store that we control.
The workers buy everything on credit...
and it's convenient for all.
-A company store.
-Exactly. Do you know of such a place?
l know the perfect place...
and the perfect man for the job.
Somebody must have put a nail in the log.
Damn fool woman!
Good morning. Good to see you, Cooper.
How could you be so foolish
to rebuild that stupid school?
l'm not. The local sharecroppers are,
for the children.
Don't play with me, woman.
You know exactly what--
Tell me, was it you, Johnny, Gettys...
or that crowd of rabble
that call themselves the Brethren...
that tore up my saw-blade?
Your saw-blade has been ruined?
Won't that distress George Hazard
all to pieces?
George doesn't know.
There's a great deal that he doesn't know.
Such as?
Such as, with the aid of his sister-in-law,
lsabel Hazard...
l intend to open a mine for phosphates
right here on Mont Royal.
Mont Royal belongs to me.
For as long as you make
the mortgage payments, it does.
But since your sawmill isn't operating,
how do you intend to do that?
l shall.
But if l should fail...
l wish you all the best.
Why would you wish me that?
Because l bear you no malice, Cooper.
-You're a fool.
-Perhaps that's my lot in life.
You are no gentlewoman.
Were you ever?
l never claimed to be.
Damn you.
How does he get down the chimney?
Well, he just does. He's Santa Claus.
What if he gets stuck?
Santa Claus never gets stuck.
He has got magic powers.
-What if--
-lf, if, if!
lf you keep asking questions,
we'll never get our shopping done.
Go, Gus.
What are you doing here?
That was nicely done, Charlie Main.
You come around here like a specter,
and frighten the girl and the child.
Come on in.
Whoa, now.
Nothing?
Mr. Tackett said the blade ain't ready.
He wouldn't even give us
so much as a glance, Madeline.
l smell the odor of the Brethren in this.
-Anything else unusual?
-Stopped by Gettys' store.
Prices are way up, higher than ever.
You can get anything you want...
as long as you put your name down
or makes your mark.
Trouble is,
you got to pay him $12 a month.
And we only get paid every six months,
so they tack on something called interest.
They don't use cash money...
just paper l ain't never seen the like of.
Something called scrip.
That way, they can never clear their debt.
lt's more slavery.
Sound familiar?
Unfortunately.
Soldiering's the only thing l know.
The Army needs civilian scouts.
Many of them have, shall we say,
dubious backgrounds.
-And what do l know about scouting?
-You've been there and survived.
You walked out alive.
That's something of value.
lf l decided on that,
you'd put in a word for me?
Yes, of course.
-Now, what about Elkanah Bent?
-George Hazard's wires reached you?
Someone should have put a bullet in him
long ago and saved us all that grief.
He'll be caught.
But until then, you watch your back.
-The man's insane.
-l'm dedicated to that.
-lf he wants to come after me, let him.
-What about Willa?
-How can you treat her like that?
She adores Gus.
She spends a lot of time with him.
-l never asked her over.
-She does it for Gus...
-and because she's in love with you.
-l never asked for that, either.
Go and talk to her.
''We are such stuff
As dreams are made on
''and our little life
ls rounded with a sleep.''
Sam's forming a traveling company.
Maybe we can meet
on the road somewhere.
l don't think so.
l'm not very good at this.
l can't see you anymore and l'd appreciate
it if you wouldn't see Gus, either.
Charlie, come up to my room
with me now.
-We can have some privacy and talk.
-We wouldn't just do that, would we?
We can just hold each other.
Charlie, l love you.
You have to give me a chance.
l don't know why l'm here.
Yes, you do.
Tell me.
Out West....
l just don't know anymore.
Let me help you.
God, l missed you.
See that?
When l was out on the prairie,
a little boy named Jim gave me this.
lt made me think an awful lot of you.
l got this one. Now l got two of them.
One to think of both of you with, Gus.
You're a good boy.
l'm mighty proud of you.
l hate to intrude,
but could l speak with you for a minute?
l secured a placement for you
as a civilian scout.
-Out West?
-Fort Leavenworth, Kansas.
All right. That's all right by me.
The pardon still stands
even though Johnson's having trouble?
lt does.
As long as l can hunt down
that damn renegade...
l don't have any problems at all.
You're leaving again, aren't you?
-When will you be back?
-l don't know.
Doesn't this mean anything to you?
What happened to you out there?
Please tell me.
No, l told you this is the way it is.
-l've got a debt to settle.
-You're a bastard.
You used me, Charles Main.
l'm sorry for that.
All right,
you just make your mark right there.
May l see one of those labor contracts?
Why? You thinking of signing up
for some work?
You can see mine, Miss Madeline.
No, l'm sorry. That is not allowed.
Put your mark there.
Seeing as how you're pretty strapped up
to Mont Royal...
maybe you'd like
to buy these things on credit.
-All these people are buying with credit?
-Sure.
All the Negroes are getting credit
for work done.
For a year's contract?
-We'll pay with cash.
-Wait a minute.
You're sure you don't want to join
the rest of your folks, Madeline?
Like l said, cash.
Come in.
Mr. Cooper, Mrs. Main to see you, sir.
How are you, Cooper?
What do you want?
l've come to discuss the labor contracts
for the workers at your mine.
That is none of your business.
You are deliberately placing hard-working,
decent men...
into bondage once again.
-Do you mean the Negroes?
-Yes.
You, of course, are sympathetic to them.
Deeply.
You know perfectly well they can't read...
and l'm sure you haven't explained
the contract to them.
Then your teacher and your school
should be educating them.
l have a contract with you
and rights to Mont Royal.
l will not permit this to happen.
You have the right to live there
as long as you pay the mortgage.
Some of the finest legal minds
in Charleston determined that.
lf you wish to continue to live there...
then you see
that the payments are made properly.
And if you wish
no more further trouble from me...
then you stay out of my business!
What do you mean, no further trouble?
-Cooper, what's happened to you?
-l am regaining...
what you and others
sought to take away from me.
Pride.
California is the most beautiful place.
lt's sunny and warm all the time...
with the most magnificent mountains
and the ocean.
And in some of the streams,
they say there's gold.
Have you ever got any yet?
No, not yet. But l'm going to keep trying.
Gold is very precious.
But not as precious as you are.
-Can we really come visit you, Aunt Brett?
-Nothing would make me happier.
-But that really is up to your father.
-Can we, Papa?
What?
You'll have to excuse me.
Yes?
Everybody's worried about you.
George, we have trouble at the ironworks.
l hired two Negroes...
and six of our best men
threatened to walk. White men.
-Fire them.
-What?
-Fire them and keep the two.
-That's your responsibility, not mine.
Come here. l want to show you something.
Look at this.
We were able to track Bent
all the way to Chicago.
From here in Pittsburgh
to Canton, Ohio, to Columbus.
Where they saw him
with a pierced earring. Remember that?
-l know it was Constance's.
-George, please.
Six days later,
Pinkerton loses him in Chicago.
George, stop it. You're obsessed.
Please let me take the children
back to California till it's over.
lt'll never be over
while there's a madman running loose.
lt'll never be over till you let it be over.
Bent will just keep going
until you stop chasing him...
because it's what he wants.
You're scaring me, George.
Just think what it's doing to your children
to see you like this.
The children are safe here with me.
You're welcome to stay
as long as you like.
But where my business is concerned,
this business...
you may not intrude.
-Agent Jupiter Smith, sir.
-Show him right in.
l'm sorry to come unannounced...
but l'm heading out West
and wanted you to have this report.
-Tell me what's in it.
-We picked up Bent's trail again...
in a small farm in southern lllinois.
He attacked a young woman there, sir.
She's alive, but barely.
So much for my obsession.
We believe he's headed for St. Louis next,
and from there, who knows?
My bet is he's after Charlie Main.
Look at the cards. Same old cards, right?
l want somebody to pick me a card.
Who decides to pick a card?
All right, pick your card.
Show it to everybody.
Come on, now. Look at the card.
Don't show it to me.
Put the card back in there.
Watch me shuffle it for you.
Eyes are closed. Check out the eyes.
Do you see the card in there?
Please look.
Are you sure you don't see the card?
Tie me up.
Let me know when it's good and tight.
ls it good and tight yet?
Can you see that? You get over here.
Get on over here so you can see this.
You want this?
You men there.
Hey, you coloreds.
We'll have none of that at this camp.
You let them be. They're doing no harm.
-They're acting up. lt's not soldierly.
-They're just having some innocent fun.
A soldier's life is tough enough.
Don't you agree, Lieutenant?
What the hell would you know
about soldiering?
A damn sight more than you ever would.
Why don't you find yourself something
useful to do right now, Lieutenant?
Excuse me.
l want to thank you for that, sir.
No need for it. He was wrong.
And don't call me sir. l work for a living.
Name's Charlie.
You a scout? They call me Magic Magee.
Yeah, l can see why.
l got my tent set up over there
by the stables.
When you get settled in and all,
stop by and we'll pull the jug awhile.
l hear the South in you.
Are you sure you want to drink with me?
Stop by.
l hear we'll be fighting lndians.
When we have to.
Mostly we'll be riding escort
for wagons and stages...
hoping our presence will keep
the hostile ones on the reservations.
Mind you, l have sympathy for them...
save one in particular.
No. One or two is enough for me.
l don't want any trouble
with officers or NCO.
-You read and write, Magee?
-Yep.
Given that and seeing how
you can do tricks, why did you join up?
There ain't a lot of folks
looking to hire colored magicians.
Besides, it's better than
emptying a spittoon in a saloon.
That was my last job
before reading about young men of color...
putting on the army blue.
You learn to ride and shoot like that,
you'll rise fast.
You know they plan on promoting
from the ranks.
You mean officers?
For now, noncommissioned officers.
lt would be men like yourself.
So why are you scouting for the Army?
-l'm just looking for a friend of mine.
-Sounds like something personal.
His name is Scar and it's very personal.
-Boy.
-Sir?
-l'm looking for Brigadier Duncan's house.
-Right there, sir.
Gussie, naptime, dear.
Welcome.
My name is Francis Cardozo.
l have the good fortune
to have been born free...
and l am deeply honored
that those of you who were not...
have chosen me
to conduct our proceeding.
Any man who wishes to speak may do so.
Below me, a clerk is at the table.
lf you can't write your name,
give it to him and he'll write it for you.
And you make your mark beside it.
Do not hesitate to say
what's on your mind, please.
lsaac, you go.
Welcome, my friends.
We have gathered for a high purpose:
to prepare an address...
to the white inhabitants of South Carolina.
We do not claim
superior wisdom or virtue...
but merely ask in a conciliatory spirit...
for rights...
due us...
as men.
l now declare
this convention of colored people open.
Until recently,
the masters owned the land.
Now we got the right to own land.
But until we get the land
and can farm for ourselves...
the old masters
can hire us out for nothing...
or starve us if they want to.
Give us the land, l says.
That's all l got to say.
Our next speaker, lsaac Kano.
l ain't by no right no kind of speaker.
But l've been doing me some thinking,
real recent-like.
l've been thinking a lot
about being a freed man.
That's something l never knowed
as a child.
Now as a married man...
l've been thinking
a lot about having a family.
about the rest of my life.
l've been thinking some about dying, too.
l reckon this here proclamation
ought to show some of them white folks...
that we are just like them.
Not different.
Show them how we feels like them.
We loves like them.
We bears babies like them.
Lord knows, a lot of their daddies...
give some of us their blood.
And a lot of our mamas done fed...
a whole lot of them their milk.
And l've been figuring...
somebody ought to tell
some of them white folks...
that when they dies, and when we die...
we all gets put into the same dirt...
and how when we get to heaven...
we all gonna share...
the same good Lord.
l reckon enough has been said
about all them differences.
l thank you.
Listen to them, Mr. Kano.
Just listen to them.
l just said what l thought.
So pure and simple...
every man's heart soared.
God bless you, Mr. Kano.
-Thank you.
-For what?
You called me ''mister.''
That ain't never been done before.
Them were some real powerful words
back there.
You helped make them
real and powerful, lsaac.
-Maybe.
-No maybes about it.
And what that make us?
We's Americans.
Get down, niggers.
l said get down!
You heard him. Get you down.
Your horse done run off, gentlemen.
But since you're here,
why don't you dance for us?
Dance for us, boys. Come on.
They ain't gonna dance.
Been to a nigger convention,
acting like white folks...
they forgot how to dance.
Make them dance, boys.
Madeline, come quick.
Something's wrong.
Prudence, get the gun.
Last chance to dance, boys.
Run, Titus!
Get him !
Stupid nigger!
God, no!
Help me!
Give it to me. Jane, get on with me.
You critters can't dance,
but you can fight and you can run.
You think you're Americans.
Never can be, and you never will be!
Pull him up, boys.
Oh, God.
Jesus, take care of Jane.
Yeah, now that's what l call dancing.
Let's hang another one.
Get him over here. Come on.
Here. Put it on him.
Let him go!
Who's giving orders out here?
General Orry Main's widow
and this 12-gauge shotgun.
Now let him down.
You four, get out of here now!
Oh, my Lord!
No!
lsaac, please.
Please don't.
No, don't leave me.
-That'll be all, Colonel.
-Sergeant.
Troops, to the right, halt.
Brigade Corporal, dismiss your men.
Troops dismissed.
-Settling right into the life, aren't you?
-lt beats emptying out spittoons.
How you doing?
But you know l'm an entertainer...
and l've been teaching
some of the boys about drama.
A bunch of the boys in C troop
would like to see some stage playing.
They've got sort of a theater in town...
but they don't sell no tickets
to colored folks.
-ls that a fact?
-Sure is.
There's a lot of facts changing these days.
Come on, my old dears, one more time.
Why is this beard on me?
l didn't see that before,
my beard and hair are so long and white....
Tickets.
-Change for $10.
-Thank you.
-May l help you?
-l sure hope so.
Do you sell tickets to colored?
Absolutely not. lf we did,
we wouldn't attract decent customers.
ls Sam Trump inside?
-You know Mr. Trump?
-You might say.
He's very busy, and so am l.
What are you doing?
What the blazes....
You.
Get out. You've hurt her enough.
l'm not here for Willa, Sam.
l'm here for tickets.
Tickets? See Mr. Thurlow, not me.
No, Sam,
the tickets are for colored soldiers.
-Colored?
-Yes, colored.
Sell him the tickets.
-Our policy will not allow Negroes.
-Then we won't play Leavenworth.
For God's sake, man, sell him the tickets.
All right, but no white people will attend...
and you people will suffer
at the box office.
Shut up.
Care for a taste?
You going to save some for me?
You're supposed to be sober, Sam.
l will be thanks to you.
All right, my old dears, once again.
Why is this beard on me?
Thank you for helping with Sam.
Thank you for backing me on the tickets.
Did you settle your debt on the prairie?
No, not yet.
''Then must the Jew be merciful.
''On what compulsion must l? Tell me that.
''The quality of mercy is not strain'd...
''lt droppeth as the gentle rain
from heaven Upon the place beneath:
''it is twice bless'd
''lt blesseth him that gives
and him that takes:
''lt becomes The throned monarch
better than his crown
''But mercy is above this sceptred sway...
''lt is enthroned in the hearts of kings...
''lt is an attribute to God himself...
''we do pray for mercy...
''And that same prayer doth teach us all
to render The deeds of mercy.
''l have spoke thus much
To mitigate the justice of my plea.''
First you change the play.
Then you change my staging of his play.
William Shakespeare
wouldn't have any mercy on you.
l had something to say.
And you said it, regardless.
Cooper finally has the excuse
he's been waiting for.
l can't make the mortgage payment
this month.
Get the money
out of George Hazard's account.
-Go to his man.
-No, l won't.
The sawmill is dead.
lf you don't go to him, you're condemning
your Negroes back into slavery.
George is in business for profit.
You think he doesn't know
what lsabel's doing?
You mean the same man
who worked alongside of our lsaac?
-lt's finished, Prudence.
-Never.
All right, forget about them. Let Cooper
win and gloat. What do you care?
You're a stubborn, spoiled, selfish...
Southern lady.
lf he pushes me off onto Jack Ouinlan,
if he shows me...
one ounce of pity...
l swear....
-What the hell's going on?
-Just following your orders, George.
You asked me to tell you
if lsabel tries to move in on your interest.
She has, in South Carolina at Mont Royal.
l need your help.
Please.
Where is the partnership agreement
between Cooper and lsabel located?
-l don't know.
-lt is important, Madeline.
l'm sure it is, but--
Wait, l'm sorry.
l'm sure we'll find it, wherever it is.
This whole thing
has just got me so furious.
What is this?
l've been tracking Elkanah Bent
with the help of the Pinkertons.
l want to thank you for coming.
l just had to. You have
a sizable investment at Mont Royal.
That's not the only reason you came, is it?
No.
No, it isn't.
-Edwin.
-Excuse me, sir.
Mrs. Main will stay the night with us.
She and l will need two train tickets
to Washington, earliest tomorrow.
Very good, sir.
Jack, l'll need you to find the specifics...
of a partnership entered into
in South Carolina.
Thank you, Mrs. Main.
You've done what no one else could.
Company, halt.
Lieutenant, we got a war party
about half a mile out.
Lead the way, Mr. Main.
Column, left turn forward. At a gallop!
Open fire! Fire at will!
Keep walking. Steady.
There they are, Lieutenant.
Charge!
What are you doing?
You ruined the whole thing.
We would have had them
if you hadn't interfered.
Sorry, Colonel. We had no idea
it was a trap. lt appeared to the scout--
Shut up.
Yes, sir.
This is your scout?
Yes, sir. Mr. Main.
Sound recall!
The main village is on Cottonwood Creek.
We were trying to bait out the warriors
and strike the village.
Now it's all been ruined, thanks to you.
Bring up my mount!
Main, not only are you
a despicable traitor...
you're a damn deserter, as well.
l only hope l see you hang!
You go to hell.
You say a word, boy, l'll hurt you.
Running Wolf, you remember me?
l don't speak Cheyenne.
Where is Adolphus and the boy?
Man-ready-for-war and his dog soldiers,
they've killed them.
-l did not know.
-You know where Man-ready-for-war is?
Would you kill him?
Yes, l would.
He was here three, four days back.
He's gone. You may search.
He's gone.
He and his bunch
attacked a wagon train 3 miles east.
-You may search.
-l believe you, Running Wolf.
The soldiers will be coming, understand?
They'll be looking for him.
This is my woman.
We are old, with children and women.
We are not at war.
No, l know.
Come on, sound the charge!
Venable.
Damn you, Main!
These people breed like rabbits
and make more warriors.
Damn the red devils, and damn you!
Let it go!
Keep fighting!
Kill the horses!
Use your sabers.
Kill them !
Sergeant, good work.
Cordon the men up at the end of
the village. Let's get ready to move out.
Yes, sir.
You son of a bitch.
-Form columns in twos, Corporal.
-Yes, sir.
l would not advise that, sir.
l would advise
you getting out of here, now.
Sir.
Charlie, come back! You don't have to run.
Charlie, what about your boy?
What about Gus?
Charlie, come back!
Damn!
English
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org