Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
(bird hoots)
Norman! Come here! Come here!
Norman!
Hurry up! The loons!
The loons!
They're welcoming us back.
I don't hear a thing.
Just look at this place!
- It's a mess, isn't it?
- Just take a second.
It'll be all shipshape again.
And warmer!
Hah!
Phone works!
At least, I think it does.
Hello!
Hello?
Who the hell is that?
Who the hell's in this picture here?
Who the hell is it?
Hello? Who's this?
The operator?
Oh, what do you want?
You called, you must want something.
Oh, wait a minute.
I did call you, but you never answered.
Well, how are you?
Yeah, I'm nice.
Listen, this is Norman Thayer Jr.
over on Golden Pond.
I've something I want you to do.
Call me up. Can you do that?
I want to check the phone,
see if it still rings.
Hasn't rung all winter.
May have lost its whatsie.
Do you have my number?
I've no idea.
It's got a nine, that's all I know.
It's in the book. You must have a book.
Norman Thayer Jr.
Let's give her a try, shall we?
- Who the hell is that?
- (knock at door)
- Someone's at the door!
(Woman) It's me, you old poop!
Well, look at you!
Hm... Look at me.
Quite a sight, aren't l?
Oh, Norman!
It's so beautiful!
Everything's just waking up.
Little tiny birds. Little tiny leaves.
I saw a patch of little tiny flowers
over by the old cellar hole.
Uh... I forget what they're called.
Little tiny yellow things!
Well... Want to help me
with the dust covers?
- I don't have anything else to do.
- Come on.
What were you doing out in the woods?
Norman, what do you think I was doing?
I was getting wood!
Hey, I met the nicest couple.
- Mm? Where?
- In the woods.
A couple of people?
No, a couple of antelope.
Of course a couple of people!
Their name is Migliore, I believe.
Migliore? What sort of name is that?
I don't know, darling.
Italian, I suppose. They're up from Boston.
- Do they speak English?
- Of course they do!
They're a nice middle-aged couple.
Just like us.
If they're just like us,
they're not middle-aged.
- Of course they are!
- Middle age means the middle of life.
People don't live to be 1 50.
Well,... we're at the far edge
of middle age, that's all.
We're not, you know.
You're old and I'm ancient.
Oh, pooh!
- You're in your 70s and I'm in my 60s.
- Barely on both counts!
Do you want to spend the rest of the day
quibbling about this?
We can if you like.
For the Lord's sake!
The Migliores, whatever their age group,
have invited us to dinner sometime.
Wouldn't that be nice?
I don't know. I'm not sure
my stomach's ready for rigatoni.
Oh, no!
Poor Elmer! He's had a terrible fall!
Poor little Elmer, the life you've led.
He was my first true love, you know.
Known all along I wasn't the first in line.
No, you were a rather cheap
substitute for Elmer.
- And now he's had a fall.
- Maybe he wanted to kill himself.
He's probably got cancer
or termites or something.
- Shut up, Norman!
- Not a bad way to go, huh?
A quick front flip off the mantel, a bit of
a kick and end up in the fire. Nothing to it.
- Norman, will you shut up?
- When my number's up, do that for me.
Prop me up on the mantel
and point out which way is down.
I might try for a full gainer
with a half twist.
Norman Thayer Jr,
your fascination with dying...
..is beginning to frazzle my good humour.
Not fascination.
It crosses my mind now and then.
Don't you have anything else
to think about?
Nothing quite as interesting.
What's stopping you? Why don't you
take your dive and get it over with?
And leave you alone with Elmer?
You must be mad!
(laughs)
For pity's sake!
Come on, help me
get the canoe off the porch.
Norman, are you paddling?
Of course I'm paddling.
Then, you're not steering.
- Do you want me to take the stern?
- I certainly do not.
(loons call)
- Norman!
- Good God, what is it?
Oh, look, I've spotted the loons!
Oh, they're so lovely!
Here, here.
Look.
- Can you see them?
- No.
Oh!
Oh, my goodness! There they are.
Oh, they're so beautiful!
They're huge.
I never saw such big loons in my life.
Those are boats, you poop!
Come in closer.
(Woman)
A husband and wife.
I think they're looking at us.
Yeah, they are.
What the hell's the matter with them?
Hey, buzz off!
Buzz off!
- Ethel, what are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- Don't do that!
- Why not? You did it.
Never mind, I'll explain later.
(Ethel laughs)
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11!
How about that? Right on your man!
Where were you?
Where was l?
Oh, come off it! Don't give me that.
- 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
- Damn!
Yes, damn it! Good night, sweet prince.
5, 10, 1 5... and 20.
- Well, mother!
- (Ethel laughs)
Do you want to stay and watch the boat
while I run into the store?
I think I'm qualified to watch the boat.
- Come with me if you want to.
- No, thank you very much.
- Hello, Sumner.
- Morning, Mrs Thayer.
- Will you fill her up, please?
- Sure.
Norman will help you.
That'll be $38, please, Mr Thayer.
God... Do you know how much
gasoline cost when I was your age?
12 cents a gallon.
Is that a fact?
I didn't know they had gas back then.
What are you? A couple of nitwits?
Think it's funny being old?
My whole goddamn body's falling apart!
Sometimes I can't even
go to the bathroom when I want to.
But I can still take on both you punks...
Norman! Here we go.
Thanks, boys.
I'll drive home.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
If I make the wrong turn
and wind up in Michigan, let me know.
(knock at door)
Someone's at the door!
(Ethel)
It's me, you old poop!
- Where have you been?
- Picking strawberries.
There were oodles of little strawberries
along the old town road.
What on earth you're doing in here
on a morning like this is beyond me!
I've been busy looking through
yesterday's paper for gainful employment.
- Here we go again.
- Very good prospects, I think.
Chauffeurs, yard work.
Dairy Divine wants a... ice cream dipper.
I think I could do
something like that, don't you?
What are you gonna do if you call and
they say, ''Come and start tomorrow''?
- I'll start tomorrow.
- Oh, for the love of God!
Norman, what on earth's
the matter with you?
Look, give me that stuff.
Take these buckets and go pick us
another quart of strawberries...
..and I'll fix us a scrumptious
strawberry shortcake for lunch.
Go on!
- You want me to pick strawberries?
- Yep. Do I have to put an ad in the paper?
I'm not sure I know
how to pick strawberries.
It's very simple.
You bend over and you pick 'em.
Bend over? Where are they?
On the ground, where they belong.
We picked blueberries on a bush.
We didn't have to bend over.
- Strawberries grow on the ground.
- (boat horn)
Oh. Here comes whatshisname.
He'll have the paper, you know.
I can't miss any career opportunities
off picking strawberries.
I'll pay you, Norman.
It may be the beginning of something big.
You may become
a major strawberry picker.
Not if I'm bending over all the time.
- I think you're trying to kill me.
- I've thought about it.
Don't bother.
I'm living on borrowed time.
Will you take your cheery personality
and get out of here?
I hope you'll massage
my bent back this evening.
With pleasure.
Well, maybe I can...
lie down to pick the berries.
- Morning, Ethel!
- Hi, Charlie!
Come and have some coffee.
You can take five minutes.
You got a letter from Chelsea!
- The rest is just bills and junk like that.
- Sure. Go on in.
Ohh!
Uh-oh! I think I broke your door.
No, no. It's been that way for months.
Norman's supposed to fix it,
but it's not high on his list of priorities.
(breathes heavily)
(panting)
Hi, Norman.
Norman, are you back already?
You barely left!
So? I move fast.
Ran all the way
and picked without stopping.
- Let me see what you got.
- I'll just dump 'em in with yours.
Not a single berry!
What's the matter with you?
Must have eaten them all.
No mail today, Charlie?
Holy Mackinoly, I left it on the porch.
How about bringing it in?
Can you do that?
You bet!
- Glass of milk, Norman?
- No.
I see you broke the screen door, Charlie.
It's just missing
its little thingamabobbers for the hinges.
- I could bring you a couple tomorrow.
- Just be careful next time.
Here it is, Norman.
- Drink it.
- Thank you, nurse.
Finish your coffee over here.
There you go.
- What you got there, Norman?
- I have no idea, I can't open it.
Here, bite this, please.
Oh, just his medicine.
Oh, goody. What a swell surprise!
Nothing serious, just for his palpitations.
That's right.
I have occasional heart-throbs.
Norman, we got a letter from Chelsea.
Look at the goddamn Orioles!
Baltimore's always been a sneaky town.
Norman!
She's coming for your birthday.
- Oh? How nice.
- Yep.
And she's bringing a friend.
She has the nicest boyfriend!
Oh?
They're coming together,
then they're going on to Europe.
Oh, really? I don't want crowds of people
coming on my birthday,...
..watching me turn older.
Wait a minute. It's not that Freddie person.
This is a different boyfriend altogether!
What the hell's going on?
Detroit's disappeared! Good God!
- What is it, Norman?
- Detroit's gone!
What happened to her husband?
What is it, Charlie?
What happened to Chelsea's husband?
He didn't work out.
Hey...
She's...
(laughs)
She says...
She says she's in love with a dentist.
Does her boyfriend know about this?
This is her new boyfriend.
Her new boyfriend is a dentist.
That's who she's bringing here, a dentist?
Yep.
Good God, he'll be staring at our teeth
all the time!
Well, should we ask him not to come?
No, we should have representatives from
all walks of life at my last birthday party.
Oh, lorks! I think this medicine
should be put away from all this hot air.
- Why didn't you marry Chelsea?
- You wouldn't let me.
No? If you'd have married somebody else,
I'd have allowed that.
I didn't want anyone else!
How old will you be?
- When?
- On your birthday.
103.
Miss Appley was 97 in May.
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah.
- She died, you know.
- No.
Yeah. Last Tuesday.
We got a call in case any mail comes up.
Gave you a forwarding address
for Miss Appley?
(Ethel)
What's so funny?
One of the lesbians expired.
- (Charlie laughs)
- Oh, no.
- Which one, Charlie?
- Miss Appley.
Well, she had a good full life.
Charlie said she was 97.
97! Isn't that wonderful?
Puts us all to shame, doesn't it?
There's something to be said
for a deviant lifestyle.
(Charlie)
Well, thanks for the coffee.
You still make
the best biscuits on the lake.
Thank you, Charlie.
You must come round
when Chelsea comes.
- Hey, I haven't seen her in a long time.
- No.
- Well...
- Norman.
Charlie's leaving.
Good. Bye.
Goodbye.
Watch out for that screen door.
Norman!
The loons are teaching their baby to fly.
Isn't that exciting?
Listen to this.
''Retired people sought for handbill
delivery. Some walking involved.''
I should call. I can walk.
Is that why you came rushing back here?
To read those goddamned ads?
You wanna know
why I came back so fast?
I got to the end of our lane...
I couldn't remember
where the old town road was.
I went a little way into the woods.
There was nothing familiar.
Not one damn tree.
Scared me half to death.
That's why I came...
running back here to you.
To see your pretty face.
I could feel safe, I was still me.
You're safe, you old poop.
And you're definitely still you,...
..picking on poor old Charlie.
After lunch,...
..after we've gobbled up
all those silly strawberries,...
..we'll take ourselves to the old town road.
We've been there
a thousand times, darling.
A thousand.
And you'll remember it all.
Listen to me, mister.
You're my knight in shining armour.
Don't you forget it.
You're gonna get back on that horse...
..and I'm gonna be right behind you,
holding on tight.
And away we're gonna go, go, go.
I don't like horses.
You are a... pretty old dame, aren't you?
What are you doing with
a dotty old son of a bitch like me?
Well,...
..l haven't the vaguest idea.
(Ethel hoots)
Yoo ho hohooha!
(loons call)
Hooha ho!
I don't think you should do that
in front of Chelsea's companion.
Oh, pooh!
I was just talking to my friends.
Hey, look at you!
My, oh my! You have on a tie!
Yes, I know. I put it there.
Do I look all right?
I haven't overdressed, have l?
You look sexy.
I'm gonna have to do some fast
manoeuvres to catch up with you.
I have some other ties.
You could come as Miss Appley.
Thank you!
''Welcome home, Chelsea.''
I see my birthday party
wasn't cause enough for celebration.
I just wanted our little girl
to feel welcome, that's all.
Norman.
Wouldn't it be nice
if we could all get along this time?
Hm.
Where the hell are they?
I'm getting older by the minute.
They said they'd be here
when they get here.
- Is that what they said?
- Yup.
That's a hell of an attitude.
No wonder we don't have
any grandchildren!
- What would we do with grandchildren?
- Toss them on our knee.
We're the last of the Thayers, you know.
End of the line for a damn good name.
Yup. And we're gonna take it out in style.
(car horn)
Oh, my...
They're here and I'm not even dressed.
- I look like an old character.
- You are an old character.
Go on upstairs and change
if it will make you feel any better.
- Be nice to them!
- Sure.
I'll explain the risks involved in being late
to an old man's birthday party.
(Woman)
Anybody home?
Too late. Look.
Move that flower vase
to the other side of the table.
- Why?
- Just do it! For once, just do it!
Hey! Oh, Mommy!
Oh, darling!
What a treat! Let me look at you.
Oh, you're great!
- Where is he?
- Just inside the door. Go in.
He's waiting for you.
Hello, Norman.
- Well, look at you!
- Happy birthday.
Look at this little fat girl.
Oh, Norman!
You're as thin as a rail.
- Isn't she?
- Sure.
My darling, I'm so glad you're home.
- Give me these things.
- I didn't think we'd make it.
We rented a car
that explodes every 40 miles.
- Rented a car?
- In Boston.
What sort of car is it?
I don't know.
- Green, I think.
- Ooh! A green car.
I meant what sort of make is it.
- I don't know.
- She doesn't know, Norman.
- It doesn't matter.
- Of course it doesn't. I was just curious.
Well, I guess I should have looked.
Let's see.
It's very ugly and it breaks down a lot.
Ugly and breaks down.
Sounds like a Nash.
Yes, well...
Where... Where's your friend?
You did bring your friend, didn't you?
I knew I was forgetting something.
- That's still on, huh?
- As far as I know.
Come on in. No-one's gonna bite you.
Mommy, Norman, this is Billy Ray.
(Ethel)
Oh!
How are you doing?
You seem awfully young to be a dentist.
This is Billy Ray Jr.
Oh. I'm Norman Thayer Jr. Where's...
His father is trying to park the car.
This is a great surprise. You can call me
Ethel and you can call Norman Norman.
(laughs)
I like your logic, Mommy.
I'll go see if Bill has driven into the lake.
I'll put away some of these things.
I hear you turned 80 today.
- Is that what you heard?
- Yeah.
Man, that's really old.
You should meet my father.
- Your father's still alive?
- No, but you should meet him.
Isn't this fun!
Norman, let's put Billy
in Chelsea's old room.
Then he can look out
at the lake in the morning.
Let's put him out on the float.
He can look at it all night long.
- I'd like that.
- You'd be eaten alive by all the bugs.
- So?
- Norman, take him up.
- Show him where everything is.
- Come on, boy.
I just had a birthday, too.
I turned 13 two weeks ago.
Oh? We're practically twins.
I'm so glad you're here!
He'll be right in. He actually thinks
you have to lock your car.
Mommy... Norman looks so old.
Oh, I don't know...
You look great, though.
Thank you. So do you.
- I love your hair.
- Thanks.
How's his mind?
Is he remembering things better?
- Is he...
- Oh, he's all right. He's all right!
Come on, Billy!
I'll show you the bathroom,
if I can remember where it is.
Well, at least he hasn't changed.
No. He's still impossible. It means
so much to him to have you here.
Sure. Now he's got
someone he can pick on.
Oh, come on. Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
(man)
Chels!
Well, you've finally made it!
- This is my mother. This is Bill Ray.
- Hi.
- I think I saw a bear.
- You couldn't have at this time of year.
There are some rather nasty moths
flying around, though.
No, no, this was a little big for a moth.
If you really wanna be scared,
wait till you meet my father.
- Hey, Dad!
- Hey, Billy!
Dad, they do have indoor plumbing here.
Oh, great!
Chelsea was just bullshitting us.
I like to paint a rustic picture
of life on Golden Pond.
Ooh, it's rustic, all right!
It's lovely, though. Lovely rusticity.
We've been peeing indoors for 40 years.
- You must be Norman.
- Yeah, must be! Who are you?
- Bill Ray.
- The dentist?
- Yes, sir.
- Want to see my teeth?
- (chuckling)
I'd just like to tell you, sir,
how glad we are to be here.
Chelsea's told me so much
about you and your lovely wife.
We're pleased she's brought us here.
I'm surprised Chelsea could find the way.
Well, she's here, Norman,
and that's what's important.
Do you visit your parents?
No, sir. My parents both passed away.
I see. Then, you have a good excuse.
(Chelsea)
Norman, please.
(Ethel)
Norman! Why...
Am I not allowed to speak to our guests?
Is that it?
They're afraid
I'm gonna embarrass them.
Well, I'm gonna go say hello to the lake.
Anybody coming?
Uh... me.
I've never seen anyone
say hello to a lake before.
- Mommy, you coming?
- Yeah.
(Ethel)
Want to take the boat?
- A boat, all right!
- Bill, aren't you coming?
What, outside?
That's where the lake is.
Coming, Norman?
No, I think I'll just sit here
and enjoy the quiet.
- I'll stay, too.
- With Bill.
- The screen door's broken.
- Really?
Norman will fix it.
- I love your house.
- Thank you.
It's not for sale.
I don't want to buy it, I just like it.
It has uh...
It has a charming ambience.
Well, how does it feel to turn 80?
Twice as bad as it did turning 40.
I know what that's like.
I turned 40 five years ago.
45 now.
- Norman.
- Huh?
Do you mind if I call you Norman?
- I believe you just did.
- I don't want to press.
What should I call your wife?
How about Ethel? That's her name.
Ethel Thayer.
Thoundth like I'm lithping, doethn't it?
Almost kept her from marrying me.
Wanted me to change
my last name to hers.
- What was that?
- I don't remember.
Well.
Well...
I think I'll... start a new book.
See if I can finish it
before I'm finished myself.
Maybe a novelette. Maybe something
from 'Reader's Digest' abridged.
Here's 'Treasure lsland'.
- Ever read it?
- Oh, yeah.
That's a great book.
I'd highly recommend that one.
No need for that. I've read it myself.
But my mind is going, so...
it'll all be new to me.
That son of yours ever read this book?
I don't think so.
Your son hasn't read
Treasure lsland?
No, but I intend to have him read it.
His mother's been the real force
in his life lately.
But l... I intend to eradicate...
..some of the... dishevelment.
Actually, uh...
Actually, things are...
..coming together
very nicely for me lately.
I'm beginning to feel
very good about myself.
Meeting...
Meeting Chelsea was a major...
..thing.
We have a...
We have a very kinetic relationship.
It's very positive.
I'm sure you'd be pleased.
- What do you charge for a filling?
- Hm?
You're a dentist.
What do you charge for a filling?
Oh, it's generally $40.
$40? Good God!
Norman.
We'd like to sleep together if...
..if, you know, it's all right with you.
What do you mean?
We'd...
We'd like to sleep together
in the same room.
Same... same bed.
You know, if it's not offensive to you.
All three of you?
No, just two.
You and Billy?
No.
Not Chelsea and Billy?
That leaves Chelsea and you, then.
That's right.
Why would I find that offensive?
You're not...
..planning on doing something unusual,
are you?
No, no. No, no, no. Just um...
You know, just...
Ah... Doesn't seem too offensive.
As long as you're quiet.
Thank you.
- Chelsea always slept with her husband.
- Yeah, sure.
Ethel and I, we sleep together.
Been doing it for years.
No, I guess I'd be...
..delighted to have you
abuse my daughter under my own roof.
Would you like the room
where I first violated her mother?
Or would you prefer the master bedroom?
Ethel, your boy and I
could sleep out back.
You could do it in the hearth.
Like that idea?
You're having a good time, aren't you?
Huh?
Chelsea told me all about how you like
to have a good time with people's heads.
She does too, sometimes.
Sometimes I can get into it...
..but sometimes not.
I think you should know I'm pretty good
at recognising crap when I hear it.
You know, it's not imperative
that you and I become friends.
But I thought it would be nice.
I'm sure you're a very fascinating person.
And I thought it would be fascinating
getting to know you.
That's obviously not an easy task.
You just go ahead and be...
..as poopy as you want, to quote Chelsea.
And I'll be as receptive and as pleasant
as I can be.
But I want you to bear one thing in mind...
..while you're jerking me around,
making me feel like an asshole.
I know precisely what you're up to.
And I'll take just so much of it.
OK?
What is the bottom line
on this illicit sex question?
Very good! That was a good speech.
Bottom line. You're a bottom-line man.
All right, here's the bottom line.
OK.
Hm?
You seem like a nice man.
Bit verbose, but nice.
And you're right about me.
I am fascinating.
Let's get back to sex.
Anything you want to know, just ask me.
No, I just um...
I just wanted to clear up
that little question.
Chelsea and I can sleep together, right?
Sure, please do!
Just don't let Ethel catch you.
(door opens)
Dad! Dad! I paddled the canoe!
A canoe! It's a boat!
Just like the lndians had.
Actually, the lndians used
a different grade of aluminum.
Chelsea wants you to come to the lake.
- She and Ethel are going skinny dipping!
- Skinny dipping?
Go ahead, permissiveness
runs rampant here on Golden Pond.
Let's go.
Oh, um...
Are there any bears around here?
Oh, sure. Black bears and grizzlies.
One came along here last month
and ate an old lesbian.
Dad, come on.
He's just bullshitting. Come on.
Oh, yeah!
- Hey! Where are you going?
- Skinny dipping with Chelsea.
No, no. You're going back inside
and talk to Mr Thayer.
Bullshit!
Dad, I'm not going in there
with that old turkey man. He's creepy.
What if he dies?
Now, listen to me.
If you don't behave yourself, I'm gonna
send you right back to your mother.
Is that what you want?
Now go back in there and talk to him.
Maybe you'll learn something.
Go on, go on!
(laughing)
Remember when I was nine years old and
I caught you and Norman skinny dipping?
No. I don't remember that.
Don't you remember I had that big light?
I shone it on Norman on the diving board
and he was naked!
He screamed at me. He called me a spy
and sent me to my room for a year.
It took me so long to get over that.
It took Norman a long time before
he could go skinny dipping again.
He wouldn't even get out of the water until
I went up and made sure you were asleep.
I was so bloody mad at him
for yelling at you...
..that I let him float around
down here for an hour or so,...
..freezing to death.
(laughs)
Good!
Are you going skinny dipping?
Huh?
- Are you going skinny dipping?
- Nah. You?
Nah.
I try to be selective about
who I flash in front of, you know?
Oh?
Chelsea says
you're a real heavy-duty fisherman.
She calls you The Old Man Of The Sea.
Aaah, I've caught a few.
You fish?
Nah.
What do you do out there in California?
I mean, what does one do for recreation
when one is 13 and not at school?
We... cruise chicks.
- Mm?
- Cruise chicks.
You know, meet 'em. Girls.
Try to pick 'em up.
What do you do with 'em
when you have 'em?
Suck face.
I beg your pardon?
You know, kiss. Suck face, you kiss.
Ever read this book
Treasure lsland?
No.
Go read it.
Now?
Take it upstairs! Read chapter one.
Give me a report in the morning.
I thought you said
we were gonna have a party.
I'll call you when the party's under way...
if it ever is. Go on!
(gasps)
Oh, I... I'm sorry.
Chelsea's still in the water.
You should go on down.
No-one should skinny-dip alone.
Uh... Oh um...
- Yes?
- What uh...
What is that over there?
That's a lawn chair.
(chuckles)
Go on!
- Right down to the pond.
- Right. See you later.
I thought you'd be nude.
(chuckles)
No. Sorry.
I didn't want to overwhelm our guest
on his first night.
He's nice, isn't he?
- Hm. $40 a filling.
- $40!
That's enough to keep you off sweets.
He'd be a good catch, wouldn't he?
- He said they wanted to sleep together.
- Well, why not? They're big people.
Yeah.
You and I did, didn't we?
- Did we?
- Oh, Norman!
Have you been picking on him?
Yeah. He finds me fascinating.
(laughs)
Well, why not?
Norman.
- Norman.
- Hm?
Chelsea... wants us to do something...
for her.
She wants to leave Billy here
with us for a month.
Which Billy?
Oh, Billy, Norman! The little one.
Bill is supposed to have him
for the summer.
The kid would be miserable in Europe.
Bill seems very nice and...
..Chels needs someone nice.
Couldn't we do that for her?
What would we do with the boy?
What would I say to him?
Oh, you'd think of something.
Let's do it!
Let's say we'll do it
and give Chelsea some happiness. Yes?
All right.
The three of us will have
a splendid time, won't we?
I dunno. We might.
You know, Norman,...
..you really are
the sweetest man in the world.
But I'm the only one who knows it.
-  Happy birthday to you
- (all join in)
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Norman
(Billy)
And many more!
I suppose you expect me
to sing something now.
Well,... I'm not about to.
I've been trying all day to draw some...
..profound conclusion about
living four score years.
I haven't thought of anything.
I'm surprised I got here so fast.
But I'm... glad I got to spend
so much time with this beautiful woman.
What's your name again?
I want to thank all of you for coming
all the way here from Disneyland...
..to witness this historic event.
Now I'm out of hot air, I'm gonna need
some assistance to get these candles out.
Come on, everybody.
(Billy)
Whoo!
Come on!
Chicken.
Ohh!
Charlie!
Well, holy Mackinoly!
Look at you!
- Chelsea Mackinelsea!
- Charlie Mackinarlie!
Boy, it's good to see ya!
You've held up good.
Thanks, so have you.
Bill, this is my old friend, Charlie!
- He's the mailman.
- Hi. How are you?
Hello.
- Want a ride?
- I'd love one.
(Chelsea)
Oh! It's so good to see you!
Great.
You actually deliver the mail on a boat!
What an incredible tradition.
Oh, Charlie's a legend on this lake.
He gets the mail through, no matter what.
- Right, Charlie?
- Yeah, I guess so.
Must be a bitch in the winter, huh?
Yeah. In the winter I have a hell of a time!
Course, there's nobody on the lake
to deliver to, so I get done a lot faster.
(laughing)
You've got a great setup here.
You're a lucky man.
You're a lucky man, too.
Yeah, I guess I am.
Um... what uh...
What do you usually do
at a time like this?
Well, generally I just fall into the lake.
Just uh...
(Chelsea laughs)
Whoa!
All right, come on, Dad.
Big rolls here. You can beat him. Big rolls.
Two threes. What does that mean?
That means doubles,
which always means you get 14, you see?
You send me home,
you get 20 more, for God's sake!
- All right, Dadders!
- Good, huh?
Excellent. You're a natural.
I'm starting to regret
teaching you this game.
Chels. Hey, Chels. Parcheesi pro.
Chelsea doesn't like playing games.
We don't know why.
Probably doesn't like losing.
I tend to panic
when the competition gets too intense.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
We play serious Parcheesi around here.
I let Norman win sometimes
just to keep his spirits up.
Ha ha ha!
What I'd like to know
is why you enjoy playing games.
Huh?
You seem to like beating people.
I wonder why.
You got another chance, Bill.
Another roll.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org