DECLARES THE MAFIA INFORMANT
REPORTING OF THE MAFIA KILLED
ONE IN THE BEDROOM
HOLY BIBLE
CLOSED
OPEN
After the fall of communism
in Eastern Europe,
public order collapsed.
He was replaced
by organized crime ...
and is not as if there were
been present.
But then again
an open hunting
for anyone looking for a handful
euros, including me.
When a mob family has
problems with another, I call me.
I solve for the right price.
Those are the services quickly.
But that's not the only reason
for my presence here.
DEPUTY OF THE FAMILY
CRIMINAL TAVANIAN
Hey. How long, Demyan.
How are you, brother?
- Liev, nice to see you. I'm fine.
- Vlad is waiting above.
- Hello?
- Yes, Nicholi. Yes.
We are ready.
Everything is ready
for shipment.
Perfect. We deliver
in the next 48 hours.
HEAD OF THE FAMILY
CRIMINAL TAVANIAN
What I can say, Vlad?
It was a pleasure.
CZECH DRUG ZAR
I'll call you when I come.
Welcome back, my friend.
It's good to be back, Vlad.
Your absence was too long, you know?
I had to drink alone.
Surely it was no problem for you.
- Let's drink together.
- Come on.
Thank you, Nadia.
Tell me of Grozny.
This treatment went well for care
our interests.
I see, but I was referring to the city.
I learned that almost have
rebuilt brick by brick.
Grozny remains.
Remember to Sergei?
He killed that bitch only
for having messed up the boot.
It was a crackpot.
Many of our brothers
died in Chechnya.
By Sergei.
You know, someone should go back
and destroy it again,
for old times.
Vlad, the war ended long ago.
Not here. Not for me.
- Vlad?
- I'm busy.
It Mikhail Suverov.
Mikhail, good to hear.
You and I set limits.
You have deleted the.
HEAD OF THE FAMILY
CRIMINAL SUVEROV
What do you mean?
Nicholi do business with Dvorak
without my permission.
Lie.
Who the hell told you?
Someone who knew.
I do not know who is this person,
but whoever he is,
is lying.
Try to deal with.
My problem with that
is that not only I learned from him.
You know how it is.
Where there is smoke without fire.
Not what you think.
Nicholi came to us.
Of course, my friend.
You try to take my business.
My price low five points.
You killed three years of peace
between ourselves
by a handful of bills, Vlad.
And I just kill you.
No, wait ...
Vlad ¿? Demyan ¿?
Tell me.
We are trapped. Has a man
armed with a caliber. 50 in front,
shooting through a window.
When you find him,
asesínenlo.
Front. Walk.
Come on.
- Come on.
- No, no.
Devils.
Are you done?
DEPUTY OF THE FAMILY
CRIMINAL SUVEROV
Get rid of that.
What do you expect? Do it.
And make sure it disappears.
We do not want fighting.
Hey, stop.
I said high.
Turn around, dammit.
I said you knew back.
Some say it is
a blessing to know who you are
and which are destined to do
in life.
For me, it is rather a curse.
How I ended up here?
Through a series of events
random by fate.
You do not know.
But here I am.
The money is good,
but you pay a price
anyway.
HOLY BIBLE
Isaiah 43:18:
'Remember not
other times
nor dream and more
the things of the past. '
If I know something is true in life,
is that the past is the devil.
You can not escape it.
He's always behind you.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Janice.
CLOSED - OPEN
YELLOW APPLE
Yes, arrives tomorrow.
Me too, my friend.
Call with news
as soon as you receive them.
Until then.
Bobby.
- How was it?
- Well.
Dying to receive the shipment.
- I went to Damascus?
- No.
Astrakhan came just an hour ago.
Should arrive in three hours.
How about returning?
Must be in Colombia
tomorrow night, late.
Let's say two hours to download,
recharging, refueling
and 23 hours of trip
back.
We should be ready
the end of the week.
Very good.
Go get the car.
Call to negotiate
conditions.
Who the hell is this?
Mikhail, my father always told me:
Do not say something
if you already know the answer.
You make me waste time.
You thought he was dead, right?
Demyan.
Look, Mikhail,
I'm in charge now
and, fortunately for both,
We are on the restart.
I thought it best to negotiate
conditions quickly
while there is still blood
in water.
I listen.
Live Lie low in the tomb of Vlad,
or you seek, I will kill you
and I bury myself.
Those are my terms.
Now what?
Paste them stronger
us to them.
I'll raise hell.
Go.
You should think twice,
intelligently.
I will destroy it.
Yes, but go to war
with Demyan
and we can not do
by Leo.
That your cleaner will not remove
Demyan addition to Vlad
what caused the problem
first.
But it is the only independent
of the city.
What do you suggest?
Have you heard Wolf?
It is a fairy tale.
The things I say
not a fairy tale.
Perovsky Ari has his number.
Silence.
- What?
- Are you who is called the Wolf?
Aleksey prefer, but the same.
Can you be tomorrow in Prague?
It is very short notice.
Will double your fee.
Send me an e-text. To
then do not bother.
Excuse me.
Now that you owe money
Slim Jimmy ...
They sent a dog to fetch
their leftovers.
Actually sent to a wolf.
Ve
Can you pay?
- Will you pay?
- Yes
- When?
- Stop it, damn it.
It's in the other room.
Well, well.
It's in the safe behind the bar.
One for the customer ...
and the rest for me.
Good dog.
I have long been watching her.
We are like two trains on the same route
going to crash.
I have resisted deal
thereof.
But sooner or later
if I do,
will take care of me.
The time is coming.
Is that you, Leo?
The usual place, tomorrow,
at 8:30.
Listen, it's my ...
Apology.
Hello, Ray.
Missed one.
Yes, I said.
Mikhail was the one who asked
you to give an example.
If you did not like the terms,
You should not accept
work, Ray.
You're right.
He should not have used
a woman as a shield.
She was a prostitute.
We work with results, Ray,
no excuses. You know.
End with Demyan.
I can promise you.
It's too late, my friend.
Already hired another
for the job.
Where does that leave me?
I doubt sincerely
that Mr. Mikhail Suverov
again request my services
because of this fiasco.
They are angry, Ray.
Who can blame them?
There are a million and Suverov,
igualitos to it.
Why do you think I called?
Another contract in my city no
I like just right, Leo.
In addition, seem to bite
the hand that feeds us.
Not if his hand stopped.
Demyan wants revenge
and is willing to pay
much more than Suverov.
If we remove the two brothers,
We pay extra.
Ray? We have started a war.
Wars are good
for business.
You can take advantage
or fold.
You decide.
What do you want?
Looking for Bobby Suverov.
Who the hell are you?
Aleksey Andreev.
Who?
Fuck, that's my name.
Thank you very much.
How are you?
Hungry, thirsty and tired.
Aleksey.
Ven. Ven.
What do you want?
Well do not know.
What would you recommend drinking
in a moist heat like now?
A large glass of ice water
with drinks, sir.
Would you look good drinks?
In fact, I prefer.
Appleton Estate Jamaica Rum
aged 30 years, sir.
I believe this would be perfect, sir.
I like your offer, boy.
I will try.
Then, my friend, how
start?
The presentations would be fine.
Mikhail Suverov.
Bobby Suverov.
Aleksey.
I would prefer not to use
my unfortunate nickname.
It's a fucking cliche.
Yeah, whatever.
Aleksey, tell me,
What do you think of the current situation
in our Golden City?
I guess it's business as usual.
Two parties with different opinions
faced by trivialities.
- I like the way you think.
- No.
I think not. I just do.
What are you doing exactly?
I play chess with the old
in the park
Every Tuesday and Thursday
afternoon.
Restoration of the 70 cars,
game machines 90,
and if I pay enough,
probably mate
anything that breathes.
Probably?
Except innocent people.
Children ever. Women
are no problem.
But they only shot.
Use your hands
or a knife to a woman
is weak and in bad taste, you know?
Is fine.
What do I do?
Cause chaos.
These are Demyan Ivanov
his deputy, Grigory Rikoniev,
and his second.
And Nicholi Dvorak,
Czech local trash.
Nicholi was the one who started this,
so he will be the first.
Hello, Nicholi.
Who are you?
A trained monkey.
But they pay me well
to put my touch.
What are you doing, Ray?
Time to go, really.
I have not finished drinking.
Ends and you pay.
Get me another drink now.
Sorry, we're closed.
Drank enough. Go.
Yeah, bitch?
Then I will take with me.
- Thou shalt not take anything ...
- Take your damn ...
Release.
Okay, I'm leaving.
All right. Let go, please.
According ...
- All right, Janice?
- Yes, everything is fine.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no, no.
Water does not move past the mill.
You are American.
Yes.
- Give me one second, okay?
- No need.
No, let me handle this.
Just for a second.
A little soda with salt never fails.
First kill Vlad,
Demyan then becomes chief.
But rejoices
this rise accidental?
No. The bastard
does not appreciate anything.
They were together in Chechnya.
Vlad was shot by Demyan.
- They were blood brothers.
- So what?
Am I less a man for not killing
dogs with them in Grozny?
What about me? First am
Deputy Chief Deputy Chief,
and the death of the head,
Where does that stay?
I'm still a fucking chief.
Life is a waste.
When you drink, you're always
pessimistic, Grigori.
By the way, my glass
is empty, Liev.
Tell me, if I have always
to serve your damn drinks,
What am I then?
A deputy.
Two on the table two,
a table in three,
four in the table six,
three in the table eight.
Two magazines of 17 bullets
each added 34.
10 men, three rounds each,
and four wrong.
Hey.
Which of you, poor fools,
is Gregory?
Who the hell are you?
The left has only
three in the magazine,
and the right ...
One in the chamber.
It was beautiful, right?
Remember what killed Elvis?
This would make it safely.
Well, if Elvis killed could kill
and may not want to take it.
Calm down, baby.
It's just an expression. Come on.
It sounds great.
You should think of another.
Just take it, dammit.
Shut up.
I told you, right?
Heaven?
What really killed Elvis?
That? Pills or something.
I do not know. Rays.
- You.
- Get out.
You ... were working for us.
Not anymore.
Whatever you are paying,
Mikhail double it.
Yes? The triple.
No, wait. I mean ...
I'm his only brother.
He should have had another.
It's Bobby. It's Bobby.
- What do you mean? What?
- Is anybody there.
Is armed.
Yes?
What the hell, Andrei?
What happened to my fucking news?
Yes, Leo ...
The Leo man removed
Last night, Bobby.
And Mikhail?
They say they arrived seconds
that do the job.
This is beautiful.
Yes, love it here
Mikhail affected.
Of course. It was his brother.
What has life care.
Maybe this time it should have
slightly more care.
I ...
I have bad news.
What exactly, Andrei?
Nicholi killed Dvorak.
What?
Police found him floating
in the pool
shot in the head.
Not the end of the world.
Find another with whom
do business.
Andrei, is it?
Are you the bad news?
Nicholi is not the only dead.
What do you mean?
Who else?
Someone attacked the center of betting.
They killed them all ...
all the boys.
Grigori ¿?
Grigori, Liev.
They all died.
What about my money?
Not sure.
What the hell do you mean?
I found out recently.
There were many policemen.
- I could not stay, but ...
- But nothing.
Find my damn money, Andrei.
Yes, boss. I understand, yes.
Give me time to do
one called.
Give me 20 minutes and call it.
Just 10.
- Hello.
There you are.
Forgot your jacket.
Clear. How did you find me?
I found this in your pocket.
My address. Clear.
By the way, I cleaned.
How much do you owe?
No, no, no. I made it myself.
No need.
Luckily for me, the direction
was correct on the envelope,
because it had your name.
My name is Ray.
- Only Ray?
- Ray Carver.
I'm Janice.
Sorry you've been well.
Just wanted to thank you.
You went so fast that I ...
No, I'm glad you did.
I guess I owe you one.
Ah, okay?
Agreed.
In such a case ...
God willing, we'll talk soon.
God willing.
Goodbye.
Devils.
Did you stay outside without keys?
Not so good. See you.
Agreed.
So what?
Am I on the payroll?
What would you like to do?
What I would like
this city would be arrasaras
and salaras earth.
But I promised my brother
be smart
and think things through.
Come with me.
Mikhail.
Leo.
Hello, Aleksey.
I knew you were in town.
It is very expensive, but worth it.
Do you know?
Let's say we move
Similar circles.
Why am I here, Mikhail?
Your boy, whoever he is,
did not finish the job with Demyan,
but had much success
when he killed my brother.
What boy talk
exactly?
Bobby's girlfriend
saw the black bastard.
Come on, Leo, be honest.
How many monkeys in the city?
Playing for both sides
is very dangerous, my friend.
I know your name
and where to sleep.
Come on, Mikhail,
you are mocking.
What kind of charge would
if you do not stop to give
the names of my operations?
Disrespect me.
You're lucky to be alive.
You accepted the contract for my brother.
It involves you directly
in his death.
You should consider yourself lucky
that you ask.
My black bastard and not mine,
not since I took
sustain you.
Come on, Mikhail.
You're my best customer.
So I look stupid?
If I lie,
cut off your fucking head.
No doubt, Mikhail.
I've known you a long time.
Tell me everything you know about him.
I'll tell you one thing:
If you're looking for,
I find him first.
I swear.
That is not him.
It took over 10 minutes.
Excuse me. I had to call
a friend in the police.
It was not easy.
So?
Police took the money.
I have proof
in the center.
But I found
there was a survivor,
one of the makers
betting that saw it all.
According to him, this giant
crossed the front door,
called Grigori,
removed two 9 mm pistols
and opened fire.
Does one only?
It's a lie, Andrei.
The appearance he described
is even more insane.
What do you mean?
It measured six feet high,
wearing garish Hawaiian shirt
and a white hat.
Frank Sinatra said it looked like
after taking steroids.
The Wolf.
What?
Mikhail hired an outsider,
Wolf.
But Wolf is just
a ghost story.
No. No, it's very real.
It must have been the same
Vlad also eliminated.
What do we do?
What do you think? The wolf hunt.
All bleed, Andrei.
Spread the word: I will pay big money
who find it, right?
- Okay, I understand.
- Well.
Meet me at 5:00 am
in the betting parlor.
Do not be late
and bring me something, dammit.
- A good thing.
- Agreed.
Leo, this is my third message.
What the hell's going on?
How did he would be there?
Call me.
Caramba.
Not bad.
Can I get you anything?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
You know, your accent, being
U.S. and all ...
I guess I remember the homeland.
Did you miss?
Yes, but I had to leave.
Why?
Too many bad memories.
Now sometimes I think I hide
in this city, you know?
Very afraid to return.
Clear. What scares you?
My dad was killed.
Never found who did it.
Was masked.
But I saw it all.
I was just a girl
but never forget.
Sorry.
That is terrible.
I do not know why I tell you.
Sorry, I must attend.
Do I read?
Sorry, old but harm you.
What?
We complicate things, Ray.
What you're saying, Leo?
I'm leaving town.
You must also do so.
Go to Prague.
Mikhail pressured me.
And I gave you.
I gave your name, where are you,
your home, everything.
Sorry, dude.
If he did, was history.
Sorry.
Hey.
This was my dad.
I carried it everywhere.
Why are you here?
Tell me.
Here are pictures of me.
This is my life.
What? Why?
Did you have to do with his death?
Answer me.
Tell me. Tell me.
Yes.
Why?
Because I was hired to do.
And you've come to kill me?
No. I try to protect you.
What is supposed to believe you?
Do I reach a bad time?
I threw out the window.
Rebounded very well.
What about the grenades?
I found a nice touch.
Who the hell you think you are?
The villain.
How funny.
I thought I was.
Just back from the black house.
Is it over?
Is he dead?
I think not.
What happened?
There was great disorder but no body.
We thought this would be interested.
It's the same girl in every picture.
YELLOW APPLE
What Aleksey?
I called him.
He told me to fire him.
Devils.
Guess what?
Deslúmbrame.
We received anonymous information
on the new man of Mikhail.
He's right, is the Wolf.
Staying in an expensive hotel
the center.
We will end this.
Right now.
Hi, this is Janice.
Leave a message
and call you when I can.
Thank you.
Janice, it's me again.
You call me, please?
But I ...
Just call me.
- Ready?
- Demons.
I mean, yes.
All bleed.
Come on.
You know,
some call it sixth sense;
other, intuition or hunch.
But in reality,
the little things,
as the terrible ventilation
Forgive me.
Fans.
BANK
Yes?
Ray, how the hell are you?
Do I read?
Yes, yes, I am.
Why call me the phone
Janice, Leo?
I came as soon as I could,
as requested.
How many are waiting for me?
Yes, yes, yes.
She is here.
She's lovely, Ray.
You should have told her.
We are intoxicating.
Can you get out?
No, no, no, impossible.
At the moment is busy
taking an order.
The place is packed, Ray.
On my way.
Hey, go for drinks before
out of here, right?
Clear.
Do I got over?
It depends on if he comes or not.
It will come, believe me.
Will not be disappointed.
You never looked better, Leo.
Are lizards
with only one arm, Ray.
Where is she?
With Mikhail. He
would return to the club.
I'm sorry, Ray.
It seems that I returned to certify thee.
They say that after the second time,
you give flowers
or a box of chocolates.
Walk.
I wish I had something to give.
Maybe even you.
Thank you, Ray.
Jeremiah 8:20:
'The harvest is past
and the summer is ended,
but we are not saved. '
Finally, we must all pay
for our sins.
I know that.
That awaits us all.
CHURCH OF LUST
Chief, I can not reach
with none of the men.
What?
With none?
Silent.
Who's next, dammit?
Enough.
Back.
Throw it away or dies.
Let her go.
Tonight you will die.
The question is whether it
you will die.
Do I reach a bad time?
Ray?
Come on. Come on.
You must go.
You must leave Prague.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for everything.
You have to go.
I spent much time
traveling from far away
to ask you a question
extremely short.
Why not kill you?
Nobody paid me to do so.
But the next question
logic is
What the hell you doing in my house?
I never liked to be handled
by those imbecile criminals
so I said:
'Aleksey, there are many idiots
with deep pockets.
Instead of winning with them ...
Why do not you take off? '
Why not?
Maybe I call you sometime.
Why not, my friend.
Lamentations 3:26:
'It is good to wait quietly
the salvation of Yahweh. '
No matter where you go,
always end up where it all began,
yourself.
We may never know how I ended up
where I did.
I do know that the price
I must pay
is never to be saved,
but at least it will be.