Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Run you crook!
Above, Laura!
Orphanage "Good Shepherd"
Tell me.
It's all prepared.
She is now playing.
Even he knows nothing.
Laura will be very happy
In his new home.
Do not worry.
Until this afternoon.
Your friends are going to throw you
Much less, Laura.
Do you crook!
Mamaaaaaaa!
Mamaaaaaa!
Mamaaaaaaaa!
Mamaaaaaaaaaaa!
-- And I go,
I am coming to me.
Mamaaaaaaaa!
-- Since going.
-- Simon.
-- Are outside, listening.
-- Go to sleep.
Sorry, honey, no.
Sure. Watson and Pepe
Have fallen
... Playing until very late,
And now they can not
Go right?
... Come to the inside.
Let's see, the son ....
Do not you think that you are a bit
Greater for these things?
-- When you lived here
Girl, had we not afraid?
-- No child. It was impossible
Be afraid in this house,
If we were a bunch
In the room.
And the lighthouse us
Lit up all night.
-- Was there a lighthouse?
-- And still, what happens
That is not working now, son.
Tomorrow when alight
To the beach, you teach.
-- And why not
Faro works?
-- Will I guards
A secret?
-- Yes.
-- In fact, if it works.
But light is invisible
And we took care of all the dangers.
-- How the light that is invisible?
-- Look, sees a
Thing, see.
Look toward the window.
It out.
There, eh. No.
You move.
Okay?
What?
Have you seen?
-- The children who go to these come,
Why can not
Stay at home?
-- Honey, they are
Very special children,
Who need them
Care a lot, a lot.
And they can not go and
Come every day,
Because they are very
Away, do I understand?
-- If
Can I sleep with
You tonight?
-- You what you have
Morro much.
-- Is Dad is not going to come with
Us to the beach?
-- Do not going to go down Watson and Pepe?
-- They can not.
With the jaleo tonight
They have not stuck eye.
-- But what have nose!
It seems to me that you
Accounts with friends
... Only if you are interested.
Come on, ready,
Take the pill.
-- The "S" of Simon.
-- Anda, ascends to your room
And go by the bag,
... Which then will go to dad
The beach with us,
Okay?
Some of the two
Have a talk with Simon.
I refer to the issue of
Friends invisible.
-- That is normal,
Do not worry.
He was alone and bored.
And watch where
Reach the other children,
Forget the
Friends invisible.
Everything is going to come out very well.
We are going to mount a
Super residence.
I am very happy
We are here together.
-- Pirate!
-- Pirate.
-- Cave ...
-- Cave.
-- And lighthouse.
-- And lighthouse. Let's see ... Erase una
After a pirate very bad,
That hid their treasures at
A cave near a lighthouse.
-- And what treasures?
-- The treasures that robbed. But
To enter the cave
.... Do not think it was easy to enter, he ...
(Sound of the Sea)
-- Hello.
Hello.
-- Is Simon?
Simon, let's go!.
Simon!.
-- What is your name?
I Simon.
Want to play?
Well, would you like to come
After playing to my house?.
-- Simon. But
What you do there?
-- We are playing.
-- But if Watson and Pepe not
Went down to the beach.
-- Not them, is another child.
-- Well, you say that games
Another site. That it is dangerous.
Come on, come on.
-- Can you come home to play?
-- Yes.
-- Why breathe pulling
Shell, son?
-- It is a path for
My friend will follow us,
And come home to play.
-- Échalos in the middle of the road.
-- In this step will not need
Home for more children.
-- Hello.
-- Good afternoon.
I am sorry that I
This unannounced
... But I had been impossible
Locate your phone.
My name is benign Escobedo.
I am a social worker.
-- Well, I feel that there
Made the trip in vain, but
... Had not reached any
Interview for today.
-- Does Interview? Not. I
I am here by Simon.
-- That room! It'sa
Beautiful house.
-- Y. .. How gave her?
I grew up here. This was
A small orphanage.
I always wanted to return.
So we did
The idea of residence
-- Are residence?
-- A residence for
Disabled children.
I thought that was why.
-- But you need a lot of people ...
To be able to handle everything.
-- It is not that type of residence.
With 5 or 6 children we
Would be satisfied.
-- To do otherwise, it would be very
Complicated. Right?
-- What I wanted
Simon count?
-- Yes. Yes, of course.
-- Yesterday I sent
His file,
And I thought I should visit
And introduce if
Need something.
Do you think so many
Reforms at home?
-- Sorry, but I do not understand very
Well the reason for his visit.
-- But this is information
Of long ago.
-- I know, but I
Have commanded everything.
There are new treatments.
This is a pilot program.
We need to make an application and
I thought that maybe you
Were interested.
-- My husband and
Know, is a doctor.
And we are very up to date
On progress
In the treatment of
Simon's disease.
And now I ask him to leave.
Simon does not know
It is adopted.
And much less anything
About his illness.
Besides these issues
I like to treat them ...
When my husband is at home.
-- Jack
-- And I go,
I am coming to me.
-- Who Goes there?
(Noise of metal falling)
Who is there?
Carlos!
-- What's going on?
-- Will you machacarle head
The old with that stick?
Sleep tonight
With Simon.
If reappears by
The house, call the police.
-- Mom, Mom
Already I awaken?
-- You are awake now
You can raise children.
-- Is Wendy is getting old and dying?
-- Wendy ages, but Peter
Pan comes every year
.... To take his daughter to "Never Never."
-- And why Wendy
Not going with them?
-- Well ...
-- And if Peter Pan came to me,
You vendrías me?
Not. I am too old for
Go to "Never Never", son.
-- Do you, how old are you?
-- 37.
-- How many in
Years you will die?
-- Anyway ...
What question is that?
Well, I die
In much, much,
... When you and you too old.
-- I am not going to be higher.
I am not going to grow.
-- What will you be?
How Peter Pan?
-- Like my new friends.
-- Now, do you have
More than one?
-- Son 6.
-- And they also
Going to grow?
-- They can not grow.
-- What are these things
Carried in their hands?
-- They are treasures to play.
-- Ya. Is that played between them,
Invisible friends?
-- Well, of course. You remove the treasure.
Something you want much
And you have to find it.
-- That's it, that's the game.
Find something you have removed.
-- Yes. But following
Tracks.
If you find it
Grant you a wish.
-- Oops.
Y.. Do you have a treasure?
-- The currencies of mice. A
Grandfather were left in the park.
I think we are
Gold. Very valuable.
Want to see them?
Do not look yet.
-- Where did you get
You all this?
-- I find it.
-- And this?
-- It is the first ice that I took
After operarme of angina.
-- The currencies of mice.
-- Are These are the coins?
... Are your baby teeth.
Where do you find those?
-- Do not you realize?
They are the first clue.
There have been my coins.
-- Do you want us to play treasure?
-- No, the game has already begun.
You have to remember where
Save my baby teeth.
If you find my treasure,
I ask for a wish.
-- Guess which could have sand.
-- That has prepared
You, right?
In the beach?
-- No, not worth, has
To be at home.
-- And this?
-- The sewing!
-- Simon, wait.
Come on, run.
Come!
This key rings me. But
If it is the key to the kitchen!
-- My treasure!
-- Those are things dad.
I now have the treasure!
Now I ask one wish!
-- Simon!
These are things
Daddy and me.
And you do not have to have
Hiding anything. Is that clear?
-- I have not been myself.
They have been.
-- Look, do not stand
That tell lies.
-- I do not relax.
You are the liar.
You are saying that you
My mother and you are not my mother.
-- What do you mean?
-- You are not my mother.
-- Where did you
Drawn that?
-- My friend has told me.
-- Who is your friend?
-- Thomas, Thomas I
Has told the truth.
That I am like them.
That I do not have
Father or mother.
That I will die.
You are not my mother!
You are a liar!
-- We thought wait
That you were a bit
.... More higher
Talk of certain things.
-- If you have something that
You want to ask, whatever ...
-- What of the Magi,
Will also is a lie?
-- Simon Watch: Escuchaste what mom
Was talking to this lady,
Dressed what was in the envelope
And we invented the game
Because they were afraid to ask
You'd discovered.
-- What if one day
I am not the volume?
-- Do not pass anything.
How long without tomármelas
Have to go to I die?
-- Many, many days. Many.
Weeks whole, right?
Look, you do not worry, because
We will take care of you,
... You will no ill
Let alone to die.
All right?
Simon, low son!
Simon.
-- Simon, hurry up already
The children come first.
-- We can still download
... I have to teach you something.
-- Really? What you
That show?
-- The house of Thomas.
-- But not now, darling.
Tomorrow when we
Teach me alone, okay?
-- No.
-- Now may not be Simon.
-- Now!
-- Lower immediately
I said you!
-- Do not give me the win!
-- Slow!
-- I said that to come
See the house of Thomas!
-- OK, but you want to get off,
Stay on board. Nobody forces you.
-- See Where is the mask?
-- Is this where you wanted?
Simon!
Honey!
Is Honey?
Simon!
Is Simon?
Simon, son.
(Shout)
Carlos!
But what is
Happening?
Is Honey?
Is Simon?
(Laughter children)
Simon!
(Noise of metal falling)
Simóoooon!
Cariñooooo!
Lauraaaaa!
Noooooo! (Shout)
Simon!
Simóoooon!
Noooooo! Simóoooon!
-- It's there, Carlos!
-- That there is nobody, Laura.
I am saying that you
Hence there is nobody.
We could not be more here.
-- That is my son.
Sim -...!
Carlos is here.
He spoke with police
And now wants to talk with you,
If you feel forces.
-- How are you?
It is not in the cave.
-- But I saw someone, Carlos.
-- He had to imaginárselo,
Excitement of the moment.
Rest assured,
His son was not there.
My name is Pilar.
I know that it is
Going wrong. But ...
I want to know
We are going to do
Everything in
Our hands
To locate his son,
As soon as possible.
-- Pilar is a psychologist.
It cooperates with the police.
They are working hard
To find Simon.
-- I would like to ask
Some things.
Her husband told me
Regard to the adoption
And the illness of his son.
Being Simon adopted ...
There are possibilities
We can not rule out.
-- Like what?
-- A possible abduction by
Some biological relative.
I understand that
Discovered the other night
... A woman loitering around your house.
-- Benign Escobedo.
From Social Affairs.
She appeared at home a few days ago.
-- There is no woman
Social Services under that name.
Could you describe that woman?
-- I was about 70 years,
White hair, blue eyes,
... And a very thick glasses.
-- Please be assured that
Let's give this woman.
He does not fit any doubt.
-- Who is going to leave to care for her son,
... If I am not able to take care of or mine?
-- We do one thing.
Stay with medal
San Antonio from my grandmother.
You know that I love you.
It is a sort of
Good luck charm.
-- But if you do not think
In these things.
-- For the same reason. Contigo
Going to be much stronger.
It is not a gift, eh.
It is a loan.
When again with
Simon, I am the return.
(Shout)
Is Carlos?
(Strike a strong metal)
Carlos!
(Newsletter): As time passes ...
Parents of small
Simon Sanchez feel
Most destitute.
Yesterday  met 6 months
Since the small 7
Years
Disappeared from his ...
Home without trace .
The situation is even more dramatic
Because Simon is sick
And needs medication
Daily for treatment .
Parents ...
(Laura): My son has disappeared
6 months ago. His name is Simon.
The city is empapelada
Poster.
Probably so
Seen his photograph.
We have tried everything.
Not a clue.
Neither the lower track.
My son had some friends
Playing with imaginary
And never wanted to give them importance.
But I have the feeling
They are at home.
-- I saw my daughter. One year
After his death.
It was night, and
We were sleeping.
I woke up. And without knowing
Why I went to her room.
And there she was.
Smiling and calm.
And I think that was
His way of saying:
I am fine. I am safe.
Do not suffer more for me.
-- It is not strange feeling
Somehow
The presence of a loved one
After his death.
Any of those
We are in this group of mourning
They can
Similar stories.
-- I am not being understanding.
My son is not dead.
We have led
His friends invisible.
I myself saw the one
Day he disappeared.
She was in the house.
And llegaré where needed
.... To recover
My son. I am not mad.
Believe me.
I know what I see.
(Sound horn)
-- It is!
It is the woman who was at home.
Are Benign?
(Shout)
(Gritos)
Señooooor!
-- We have been in
Benign house,
We found
Photographs
And old Super 8 movies.
I would like them echase a glance.
Does any of these faces
He is familiar?
-- This is Antonia, the school's director
And some are children of the orphanage.
They were my friends.
This is Martin. He liked
Martin known to him.
Rita, Victor. I think this
Child was named Guillermo.
She was named Liliana, it was
Blind ... and it's me.
Are Benign?
-- A woman who was in her house.
It was one of the caretakers of the orphanage.
-- But if it is impossible.
I agree.
-- Not too long he worked there.
He had a son: Thomas.
Apparently the little had
Born with a malformation.
That's why we kept
Separated from the others.
Nobody knew him.
For the townspeople
Was a real surprise
When they found his body.
-- What does it mean?
-- Apparently, he disappeared, playing ...
Shortly after that
You were adopted.
One of the small,
Confessed later,
Who had attempted
Gastarle a joke.
It was loaded with
Tomas in the caves
And then removed him for the sack
See if they dared venture outside.
There never left
There. It drowned.
They found his body
When the tide went down.
The children never accused ...
Of the crime. Only
Were playing.
-- This child was in my house.
-- We ask all present
... At the festival opening.
Nobody remembers seeing
A child with a sack
... In the head while walking through there.
(Laura): - You do not know what is
Sleep at a stretch all night.
I can not stop thinking.
Remember as llamábamos
Simon knew what when?
Two kilillos. My two of kilillos
Moreover, you said. That weighed.
Doctors said that it was
Very little for their age.
But, of course, to you and to
I seemed enough.
And that we knew that ...
Had many chances ...
Not a person
Normal like us.
But when we met her ...
When we saw for the first time
His smile, and his eyes, ojitos ...
Simon made us strong, Carlos.
Together we are strong.
Together.
And if you ever lose forgives
Nerves. But it is difficult.
Charles, there is someone in the bathroom.
-- What's going on?
-- Someone has put in bed.
Carlos, I do not look well,
Tócalo, it is still hot.
-- Of course it is hot,
I just lift.
-- Someone has put in bed.
I am convinced.
This is what Jung stating
... Which is in the subconscious
To really
Cohabiting with the living dead.
In Germany, have another
Name for the emissary
... From death.
It is a being who represents ...
As the image of a
. That is a double.
Crossing the gaze with him
... Or any of them like that
I taught mean,
Irredeemably
... Secure a passport
The other world.
-- How long does it take
Her son disappeared?
-- Nine months.
In my house are occurring
Strange things,
Things related
Disappearance of my son.
And I no longer know
-  is Not so simple
It is not going to get you a
Exorcist in the yellow pages.
-- What the child arranqué
That was my son.
The police assured that leads
Died more than 30 years.
Someone has my son.
I do not know for what purpose.
But I assure you that I will not
Stay home waiting.
-- Is there anybody in this
Field who if I fio.
Of course, I am speaking for my instinct.
Do you agree Visit
From a medium in your house?
-- This was not a dormitory children ...
When it was an orphanage, right?
-- No, the bedroom of
Children are there in the background.
-- So it is right that
Begin here. Enrique!
-- Perfect, I am hour.
-- I would like some object
This old house.
Something related to its past,
And if possible,
Some clothes thereafter.
We are not alone.
(Bell)
-- There is a psychologist who is
Working with the police,
Pilar, which is keen
In attending the meeting,
If there is no objection.
-- Perfect, perfect.
The police Mola.
-- Could you explain to
Need this doll?
-- Aurora needs an object
To motivate trance.
The clothing and other objects he
Help to get into a situation,
So we can start back.
-- A regression?
An invocation of mind.
The past, present
And the future
Overlap and intersect.
It would be something like a trip back in time.
I know that like
Is a witchcraft,
But I can assure you that
There is nothing to fear
... Parallel to the perception.
If there is something to do, Aurora will see.
-- If there is something to do, I hope
That what we all.
-- Are you ready, Enrique?
-- All ready, when you want.
-- Dawn, can you hear me?
-- Perfectly prepared.
-- Let there.
Everything around you
Begins to fade.
The dark forms a
Circle around you
And increasingly close.
Everything fades.
We are no longer here.
Now you are by yourself in
Midst of the darkness.
And the darkness
Starts to disappear.
I will count backwards
From the number 10,
When you finish
Go anywhere.
And you can also see anyone
To hide in this house.
10 .. 9 ... 8 ... 7 ... 6 ...
5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ... 1
You can open your eyes.
-- Uff ... it's cold. The
Window is open.
-- Aurora, I want
Look around you.
Is there somebody else you
In this room?
- I hear someone .
I hear .
I hear something .
The sound comes and goes .
And what I hear  .
It seems that I lost .
I hear something .
(Murmullo)
I am sure that children are
... On the other side of the aisle.
I think it is the other side .
I can not open  .
Is closed .
But there is someone  .
(Crying Child)
- Why are you crying?
-- We are sick ....
Who they are?
- I do not come to harm them.
Do not be afraid .
Ábreme the door. No.
Be afraid. It opens the door .
(Crying Child)
-- I want to get out.
(Cry of a child)
What have you done?
(Gritos children)
-- Aurora, I need that I
Tell what you are seeing.
- Are very sick. They
Crying. Oh! What happened?
- Who would want envenenarlos
(Voice of girls): He wants to kill us all!
-- Is there my son?.
-- Aurora, are you Simon?
- (Aurora): Is Simon here?
-- Aurora! Aurora! Will I
Listening? Let's look.
Aurora, it is necessary that you
Stay in the middle of the room.
I am going to count to 10.
10 ... 9 ... 8 ... 7 ... 6 ...
5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ... 1
-- I was in this house,
But it was very different.
The beds,
Toys, decoration
... Was much older.
The light from the lighthouse fall
Through the windows.
-- Is it safe
Simon saw no?
-- It was very dark, sorry.
I could not recognize anyone.
But there were children.
-- So you saw
To children. Is that so?
-- That's right.
-- We are saying that
This house there are ghosts.
-- What is a ghost Carlos?
In this house there is something
And all we saw today.
-- When something terrible
Happens in a place,
... Sometimes leaves a footprint
A wound that serves as a hub
Between two lines of time.
It's like ... like an echo that
Is repeated over and over again,
... Waiting to be heard.
As a brand, uy! Forgives.
As the mark of a pinch,
Which seeks caress relief.
Laura ...
Those who are
Close to death ...
We are more receptive
This kind of message.
-- Trying to tell me that my son
Could see these children
Because ...?
-- Well, Laura, I think
That enough is enough.
Recojan their things and
Go, please.
-- Jack, we can not fail
That these people were going well.
-- Laura, all this is a farce,
... A trick show.
-- I am not what I believe. And why?
Let's see, what purpose?.
What we said
It was true, right?
We have asked for money.
-- From time.
-- And what intends to do?
Let's see, tell me what it intends to do?
Throughout this time the police
I had not a single sign,
... Neither one of which may be my son
... Dead or alive.
What is supposed to
I do?
Do Cruzarme arm?
Let's see what I can ill
Listen to these people?
-- Laura, please, enough already.
-- No, you let me.
Tell me Pilar, in this
Bad people death ...
How many cases like that of
My son has brought you?
Búsquese other occupation
If it is boring,
Not because I invited her to my house.
-- What is supposed to
I do?
-- You are a strong mother.
Their plight gives you strength.
And you will be, but only
Do you know where ...
Is able to get to
Find her son.
-- Is that I no longer know what to do.
-- You will hear, but not heard.
This is not
Seeing is believing,
... But to see to believe.
Create, and then you will see.
-- What are you doing?
-- I do not think that we should continue
Living in this house.
We should leave
Here at least one time.
-- But the kids are in the house.
Aurora has seen.
I can not quit.
You've heard voices.
-- That guy, Enrique,
... Has been one hour to top
Moving cables.
Did not you realize that everything
This can be a montage?.
-- That is the theory of Pilar, right?. That everything is a complete fabrication.
That is its scientific theory.
-- Pilar just trying to protect ourselves.
-- Do Protegernos what?
-- Something Protegernos
As of tonight,
... Anyone who
No amount enter
... In our home and jodernos life,
Moreover, that.
-- But only if
Want help.
-- How to Help
But what you have paid attention
To what they were saying?
At any time have
Even mentioned ....
The possibility of
Simon back?
No! What these people want to do ...
Is contact with the dead, Laura.
If Simon is alive,
... I do not see this as
People can help.
And if it is not, they do not
We will return.
I do not want nor can I follow
Suffer more.
Vámonos this
Home, Laura. Please.
-- I am not going to stop
I leave you nor,
Pilar nor anyone else ... or Carlos, no.
-- Laura, we can overcome this.
Many couples lose
A son and continue forward.
-- I just
I want to be back
... With Simon, do not you understand?
I just want to be with him.
If you want to go, I
Not what you can prevent.
I just want ... to be with him.
Where are you now? I am afraid I do not.
Want to play.
Are you playing with me?
Benign!
-- There are 5, right?
-- Yes
-- All my friends. Martin,
Rita, Alice, William, Victor.
Benign killed them.
Therefore returned to the shed,
Getting their bodies.
What I have been thinking.
Kids playing killed Thomas,
And are now playing
With Simon and me.
Do not you understand?
Simon is in danger.
I no longer know how to play.
We no longer know how to play.
-- Laura, that is the history you
You have mounted on your head.
-- Jack, I have seen
With my own eyes.
How do you explain it this afternoon?
Who rode all these tracks?
-- Simon invented this game
To call your attention.
-- Who? Dímelo.
Come on, tell me who.
-- I made the suitcases. No.
I want to continue here.
-- Well, I can not go yet.
-- I am not going to continue to live in this house.
And you do not you will be here alone.
-- I can go from one day to another.
Too many memories, Carlos.
I need to say goodbye.
Two days. Sola.
I need it. Please.
Please.
(Tap bell)
Well, what else do you want from me?
What else should I do?
I do not have time. I do not have time.
Do you want to continue playing? Right?
That's all I want.
So, we do a deal.
I play a little more with you,
You and I say where is Simon.
All right?
1,2,3, touches the wall.
(Sollozando): 1,2,3, touches the wall.
A ...
1,2,3, touches the wall.
1,2,3, touched the wall!
1,2,3,
Wait! Wait! Wait!
... Wait, I will not hurt you
Really, I just
I want to find Simon.
-- Is Simon?
-- Mom,
Why are you weeping?
-- Oh, my life. Are you OK?
You are Ice son.
You do not worry about anything.
Do not panic
... I will take you from here.
(Sound of metal) (voices of children)
-- Stay to play with us.
-- No love, we
We can be playing.
(Children laughing)
I want to be if you, Simon.
I want you to think
Only we, you and me.
All right?
Think of the days before
It reached this house.
Do you remember, son?
Well, just think about it, okay?
Think only that.
And dad, and the upcoming Christmas.
And all the things
We remained to be done together.
So much my love.
Close your eyes!
God! Very strong! Strong!
Strong! But more!
Think. Think you would like to be mayor.
What would you like to be
Most, my love?
And the colleges to which you go.
All children who are you going to know.
Y. .. y. .. and think only for a moment,
... Thomas and the other children,
Are all a fantasy.
That this is crazy, my life.
That, this ... this is like a great dream.
That has been very long.
Long. Larguísimo, okay?
Close your eyes. Please
Have been gone. Please.
Close your eyes, my life.
Continue playing with me, okay?
Continue playing, sweetheart.
Okay?
(Recalling): - What do you have to show me? --
The house of Thomas.
Noooooooooo!
Nooooooooooooooooo!
I saw you at a fair price.
I saw you.
I wish to re Simon.
Mom, Mom, did I wake up?
Of course, if my life.
Of course it can.
Mom, mom found
The currencies of mice.
Now I ask my lack desire.
I want to keep
Care for all of us.
Laura.
It's Laura!
Hi, Laura.
It has become old as
The Wendy's story.
It is Laura.
Come, you site.
The house, the beach and the lost children.
Yes.
Once upon a time, one house
I was on the beach,
Where they lived ...
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org