Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
# And they called it puppy love
# Oh, I guess they'll never know
# How a young heart really feels
# And why I love her so
# And they called it puppy love
# Just because we're 17
# Tell them all,
please tell them it isn't fair
# To take away my only dream
# I cry each night
# My tears for you
# My tears are all in vain
# I hope and I pray
# That maybe someday
# You'll be back in my arms once again
# Someone help me, help me,
help me please... #
We're gonna be husband and wife
in less than an hour.
# Is the answer up above
# How can I...
Oh, how can I tell them
# This is not a puppy love
# Someone help me, help me,
help me, please #
Here, mate? You marrying that bird?
- Sorry?
- I said, you marrying that bird?
Yeah.
- Let me smash her back doors in.
- Grow up, you silly little wanker.
You wanna keep that cunt on a fucking
leash or she'll be eating through a straw.
- You shouldn't have said anything.
- You should have said it for me.
Oh, fuck.
What's the matter?
Shall I call the police?
They won't do anything.
Fuck. Fuck.
Come on.
Fuck.
- Oh, fuck. Fucking hell.
- What? What? No...
- It's gonna be all right, it's all right.
- Gene...
I'll go and talk to 'em.
Fucking hell...
Listen, boys. We ain't done nothing.
What do you want?
What do you want, money?
Want a bit of dough?
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Leave him alone! Stop it!
Stop it!
Oi!
Do it.
You can't shoot me.
You ain't fucking got it in you.
'Controversy in Whitehall
after a leaked government file
'which shows the extent of Gulf War
Syndrome was made public.
'The report concludes that several
hundred troops returning from Iraq... '
- Do you wanna lift?
- Pilates. You look terrible.
- So would you if you'd had my dreams.
- Seen my red Prada wash bag?
No.
- Love you.
'Troops feel as if they've been betrayed
by their own country
'and left to rot
when returning home from the war. '
All right, lads?
- Hello, soldier.
- Oi-oi.
Fucking wanker.
Look at him, the pikey.
- Hello again, soldier.
- Nice bag, mate.
What do you fucking want?
Look at me, chief.
You what?
- Want some, eh?
- Come on, boys. Let's slip.
I would have had him.
I could have taken him.
I should have taken him.
I do. I have my phone, I have my key...
I don't have my keys.
- Thank you very much.
- Have a good day.
You too. Look after my boy.
Look after Mummy.
See ya.
- See ya later.
- Bye.
- Good morning.
- All right?
You know, my wife says the reason why
you won't come in and have coffee
- is because we're black.
- What?
She says it proves
that all police are racist.
I'm joking, Walter.
Lighten up.
'... knives during robberies,
muggings and attacks on strangers.
'Ln other news, the trial of feared
criminal Terrence Manning continues.
'Manning's accused of heroin trafficking
and manslaughter... '
Mr Monroe.
How are the witnesses looking?
They're looking good, Sergeant
Greaves. If they all turn up.
I hope so. They're all we've got.
Don't you worry. You won't be seeing
Manning for a while.
Well done. I'm counting on you.
- There is something about him.
- Course there is.
He's ten years younger than me and
he's made Sergeant in the Flying Squad.
What am I?
All due respect,
I'm driving a barrister around.
- What are you saying, Walter?
- Most police couldn't lie in bed straight.
Do you want a coffee?
Ribena. I'm going to the gents.
- See you in court three.
- Yeah, OK.
How long's she got to go?
I beg your pardon. Who?
Your wife. I noticed she's pregnant.
I'm sorry, but if you're making
some kind of threat towards me...
You're fucking right I am.
Walk away from the Manning case
or the kid won't see his first birthday.
I'm af... I can't just walk away.
Don't bother buying candles, then.
If I could draw your attention to pages
16 and 17 of your bundle, Your Honour,
you should find two diagrams depicting
the layout of Mr Manning's club
labelled H and J.
There's been a suggestion
made by the prosecution
that the room to the right...
Critics of the government have raised
new concern over yob culture
after teenagers that attacked Cambridge
politics student Sandy Mardell
were released from Belmarsh prison
before Mardell had left hospital
having had several months
of corrective facial surgery.
Laurence Forest,
Jamie MacDermott and Tommy White
were released today having served just
six months of a one year sentence
for grievous bodily harm
against Sandy Mardell.
Mardell was beaten to within inches of
his life in a horrific, unprovoked attack.
'I think they thought I was gay
'because the last thing I remember
is one of them spitting on me,
'calling me a queer so-and-so... '
His assailants were released early on
the grounds that it was a first offence.
Mardell's father, a retired army captain,
called this...
"... a sad day in the breakdown
of law and order in this country. "
Excuse me.
You scared the life out of me.
Room 313. Where is it?
Um... Back down past the lift.
Second door from the right.
Thank you.
I wish I could, but I'm only the agent.
- 'OK. Let's do it. '
- Great. You won't regret it.
I'll email you the contract
and tell Bertle he's on his way.
'Your round soon, eh?
I'll get those tickets to you. '
- OK. I'll speak to you soon.
- 'All right, bye. '
OK. Bye.
- What's that, then?
- Honeymoon in the Maldives.
- What are you doing tonight, Frank?
- Dunno. Not much. Might go boxing.
Hello, Intelligent Solutions.
Frank speaking.
Oi, Dekker.
I heard you just closed Bertle.
Sling me a bone. He's my pal.
It's my deal.
Fucking won't be.
I'll pull him out.
I'll think about it.
It's on you, Dekker. Watch your back.
See you later.
Elizabeth Emanuel wedding dress,
the one you liked.
Two weeks at the health spa
in the Maldives, the one you liked.
How weird's that? This is the same place
where I had that dream the other night.
It says here I should order this now.
Unless we fancy driving into town
at the weekend.
Here, mate. Is that an M3?
Fucking hell. Fuck this.
- What's wrong with you?
- Sorry.
- Listen, mate. I'm so sorry.
- What's the matter with you, cunt?
Sort your fucking driving out, you cunt!
- State of him...
- Baby?
OK, OK, OK...
Morning.
Just in case.
Listen. What do we really know
about Manning?
About the people around him.
Is he capable of getting to me?
- Ease up. What's the matter with you?
- Just call it professional curiosity.
I just need to know
about these people.
And if there's something you think...
What does it matter what I think?
I'm just a driver.
But if you have your suspicions,
shouldn't you tell someone?
Who? The police?!
Cedric?
You back, babe?
Put down the knife.
We just wanna talk to ya.
Tell your husband to back away
from the Manning case.
Tell him yourself, you coward!
No! No!
Get off me! Get off me!
- No! Get off me!
- Give me the fucking knife!
Get off me!
I must point out the room has never
been used as an office by Manning.
But instead as a storage space
to house our client's extensive collection
of vintage model racing cars
numbering in excess to 1,400.
You getting in?
I've seen inside your room, sir.
Yeah? What did you see?
Would you like a cup of tea?
AK-47 s, Remingtons, Glocks, Sigs.
I'm guessing you were in the army.
You can't get that on the street
unless you're friendly with the Taliban.
I wanted to be in the army. They
wouldn't let me. Got a criminal record.
In the TA for a while.
Got kicked out of there.
Got a bit heavy with one of the NCOs.
Fucking Black thought he was Rambo.
Came unstuck with me, though.
Here, talking about Blacks, guess what's
happened to an old barrister of mine.
No?
Someone's only gone and stabbed his
pregnant missus in the stomach.
Killed their baby. How sick's that?
People like us...
We wouldn't stand for it, would we?
I'd kill them with my bare hands.
What did you do?
Didn't do nothing. He was my barrister
years ago. Something about football.
- I just heard about it.
- No, I mean, what do you do?
Here?
Head of security. Good job. I like it.
Here, look, I wanna show you
something. You're a soldier.
You'll like this.
Rigged it all up myself.
No one else knows about it.
Both got a secret, you and me.
It's a dirty fucking world.
I've seen things happen in these rooms
you wouldn't have seen as a soldier.
Trust me.
You could stay here if you wanted.
I'm married.
I'm not a queer if that's what you think.
I just meant you could stay here.
Use the camp bed
whilst you sort yourself out.
It's up to you.
What's the matter, mate?
You look really upset.
I pissed you off?
- No.
- Is it me? Have I pissed you off?
It's all right. I'll be fine. I just need
to get my head down, all right?
Maybe I'll see you soon, eh?
I could call your missus for you,
if you want.
Let her know where you are.
- 'Hello, Mardell speaking. '
- Sir. It's Bryant.
'Bryant. How are you? '
I need to see you, sir.
'OK, well, come over in the morning. '
Yes, sir.
Goodnight, soldier.
It's beautiful, sir.
Beats Kandahar.
Now, what's on your mind, Bryant?
Is everything OK at home?
Yeah.
Then why did you come here?
It's just... I don't know.
I don't see the point, sir.
You know? Being over there
and then coming home.
It's almost worse here.
You're a soldier. It's your job.
What do you want, sympathy?
No, but I wanna do something,
you know?
I don't wanna be
just another face in the crowd,
otherwise what was I doing out there?
I wanna... I wanna be remembered.
That'll be Sandy.
How is he, sir?
He never even
made it back to Cambridge.
Talk to him, Bryant.
He liked you.
What would you do to them
if you could find them, Sandy?
They go around wrecking lives.
And when they get caught, they get
a slap on the wrist. If it were me, I'd...
Help me.
Thanks, Sarge.
There was a man, Walter.
He followed me into the toilet and he
threatened me. Told me to walk away.
I can't prove it.
So it will never come to light.
And Manning was in the same room as
me when this happened to Marcia.
So how are we going to pin it on them?
We can't.
I mean, I should know. It's my job.
It was my wife.
They tried to kill my wife.
And they killed my baby.
Oh, God...
She's gonna pull through, Cedric.
She's gonna be all right.
Yeah.
Can I help you?
My name's Hillier.
You represented me a while back.
- How did you know where I live?
- I work in security, remember?
These are for your loss.
Thank you very much, Hillier.
That is... very kind of you.
Listen carefully. I know a man who can
help you with what's just happened.
You call us on this number if you want
to do something. It's up to you.
City boy.
Yeah, it is a long time no speak.
Really?
Come to the hotel tomorrow at 5:00.
Don't knock on the door.
OK.
That was the geezer
I went to school with. Complete nutter.
- He knows people.
- You're gonna get them done?
I'm gonna do something.
Oi, Dekker.
Have you thought about our little deal?
Dan, please. Look at the state of me.
You've got a week.
Otherwise you'll get ironed out again.
Right.
He'd be on the list as well.
You watch, Frank.
He'll get served.
They didn't fuck about with you,
did they?
That's why I'm here, Simon.
What do you need?
I dunno.
Yeah.
You know me, Gene.
I'll get whatever you want.
How much?
What are you doing?
Put it away. Don't work like that.
Put it away.
If you're gonna do anything,
don't do it on your own.
I know people.
Mate of mine.
Fucking hurt there.
Can I meet him?
Yeah.
But if I set it up,
I don't want you fucking about.
Hmm? Me and my mate,
we go to work properly, understand?
So what now?
- 'Hello? '
- How can you help me?
- 'Come to the hotel I work at, 3:00am. '
- Where is that?
- 'Look in your files. Under Hillier. '
- I'll be there.
Good. And don't knock on the door.
- 'How can you help me? '
- 'Come to the hotel I work at, 3:00am. '
'Where is that? '
What am I doing here?
I'm a barrister, for Chrissakes.
You've got nowhere else to go.
I am really sorry.
I have to go. I can't do this.
- I am supposed to uphold the law.
- But the law's failed you.
Thank you for seeing me, Mr Bryant.
You know where I am now.
- When did you get down here?
- Day before yesterday.
Took Dad's car.
It's good you came.
You should be proud of yourself.
Proud I can drive? Look at me.
Think I'm having
a get-together this week.
Just a few like-minded people,
you know?
Should er... Should come along.
To do what?
Nothing special. Maybe a bit of keep fit.
Good for you.
Even if you just say hello.
- I'm gonna go.
- No, stay, it's OK.
I don't wanna be like this all my life.
I'm so sorry, Mr Monroe.
There's nothing more we could do.
Come in.
What are you doing here?
Eh?
I said what the fuck are you doing here?
Why have you come here?
To learn how to fight.
Says who?
- Hillier said you'd teach us how to fight.
- I can't teach you how to fight.
Because you already can.
It's already in you.
- Where are you going, Monroe?
- I can't do this.
I...
Sorry to hear about your wife.
For fuck's sake, Monroe.
Think you wandered in here by mistake?
Deep down, you wanna stay,
because you've been abandoned
by the powers that be.
There's nowhere else to turn. Get
your shoes off and fall back in line.
Get AIDS,
or jump on a bus
with a rucksack full of explosives,
the government will dish you out
a free car,
but keep your head down,
be good and walk without a limp,
and you get zip.
That's why you're all here.
You count for nothing.
And your cries fall on deaf ears.
Same as me.
The only difference between us is
I've got the confidence to fight back.
So how do we fight back?
I don't know yet.
But if you want to spend your life getting
bullied and raped by cunts like Blair,
and having paedophiles
wander the fucking playgrounds
while you smile mutely
and pay your fucking taxes...
...then get out the door.
I wanna learn how to fight back.
So do I.
Me too.
Good.
No, you're wrong. You use
the inside of your hand, not your fist.
Smack 'em on the nose, sends the
nose bone straight up into the brain.
That will kill 'em instantly.
Reckon you could do it?
I'd rather let Bryant do it for me.
And that will save you
getting a 23 rec in prison.
How do you prefer to kill people, yeah?
Up close and personal, bare hands,
or sniper rifle, 300 yards, bingo?
I'd rather get you to do it for me.
I'd be happy to.
I'm going to the toilet.
Try not to kill anybody while I'm away.
What did I tell you, eh?
Fucking out-there.
- He's completely insane.
- Maybe. But he speaks sense.
Same again for everyone?
He's a fucking mug, huh?
If someone killed my family and I found
'em, I'd send 'em a fucking nail bomb.
No, it's a letter bomb.
That's what you'd send.
Excuse me.
Why don't you look where you're going,
you black cunt?
Do yourself a favour and fuck off before
you get opened up like a tin of beans.
- What kind of fucking nutter are you?
- Fuck off.
- What happened?
- Nothing. Can we leave?
- I spilt the drinks. I'd like to leave.
- Who started on you?
- It was just some lads.
They called me a black 'C' and...
Could we just leave?
- Who was it?
- Doesn't matter.
Who is it? Eh?
It's the one with the dark hair
and blue T-shirt.
- You call my mate a black cunt?
- Who are you, you fucking mug?
- Wanna make one?
- I'll fucking make one!
- I'll fucking make one.
- Outside, all of you. Five minutes.
We'll fucking be there.
He's gonna go, this cunt.
We're gonna fight 'em.
- Excuse me?
- Come on, this is it.
For fuck's sake, Bryant. No way.
Come on, stand with me.
We can do this. Don't fall away.
This is it. We can do it!
I'm with you, boss.
Right, come on.
Come on.
Now we're talking bollocks.
Watch these smudges up here.
Come here.
- I'm going right through him.
- Come and stand over here.
Eh? Fucking stand with me.
Fucking stand with me.
You come here cos of them smudges.
Don't you fucking wanna...
Let's go. We're gonna get nicked.
Fucking saucy cunts.
Come on. Let's go.
What?
You fucking know what.
- I was shitting myself.
- So was I.
But at least I stood.
And Lord hold Marcia
underneath your wing.
Guide her with your loving hands
through the passages of heaven.
Amen.
Come here.
Are you religious?
I stopped believing
when I realised no one was listening.
Your lip's swollen.
I fell.
I've been listening to everything that's
happened over the past few days.
- That's illegal.
- So's what you've been doing.
- Where's Danny Bryant?
- How the hell should I know?
Well, find him and tell him
I wanna meet with him.
Otherwise I'll have you all nicked
for assault.
I thought you were different.
Do you mind if we talk alone?
Para?
I was Engineers. Where did you serve?
Falklands, Afghanistan, Iraq.
What the fuck does it matter?
If you wanna arrest me, get on with it.
Do you mind?
You know, two weeks ago,
some kids from our street...
They set fire to a 79-year-old woman
because she called the police.
After they tried to rob her, three times.
And do you know what the police said?
Paperwork.
I'm here to help you.
I heard what you said in the sports hall.
I wanna help ya.
I can get you sleeves on all Manning's
people, the ones that hurt Monroe.
The ones that killed his family.
The law failed him.
We won't.
You get that right and I'll
feed you paedophiles, dealers,
bullies, junkies, scum,
cunts, dogs... the lot.
And on top of that,
I'll try and keep you
one step ahead of the law.
Yeah?
This is my job. This is what they gave
me after serving 25 years on the force.
I get to drive high-risk
prosecution and collect CCTVs.
You wanna know why?
Because I play it by the fucking book.
You wanna hurt people like Manning,
get the people around him.
What about the people
that attacked Mardell?
You're on.
'Fuck you! You fucking fuck! '
We're one short tonight, gents.
Not everybody's got the appetite for it.
Glad to see you do.
Now.
I'm gonna walk out that door in a minute.
There is no training tonight.
The next time you see me, it'll only be if
you're serious about doing this properly.
About putting something of substance
together. Legitimate targets.
I'm talking about people that hurt you.
I'm talking about fucking violence.
So go home and make a decision.
You're either with me or you're not.
If you are,
I'll be at the hotel at midday tomorrow.
If you're not, forget you ever met me.
That's them.
Two IC1 s heading towards you.
Intercept and wait for me.
How are you, man?
Go on.
Enough, Bryant.
Enough!
- Apple bag, please.
- Give me the money and then pick it up.
You work for Terry Manning, don't you?
So what if I fucking do?
- I have a message for him.
- What's that, then?
OK, go! Go! Come on, go!
Do you live round here?
Two drug dealers left for dead.
This is gang related. We've yet
to study the CCTV footage but...
Move along, just move along.
The investigation's ongoing
so I'd rather not comment further.
Sir, the caretaker called me up.
The monitors are on the blink.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And you'd know about that, would you?
You'll find that I did serve five years
in the Royal Engineers.
Indeed you did.
Shall I have another go, sir?
You do what you want, Lewis.
As long as you find out
who did this, huh?
Before you smile, watch this.
Camera 2 picked you all up
making your getaway.
Be careful. I may not be there next time.
Four cameras were watching.
We got two of 'em.
Fortunately, only one of them
matters this time. Now...
These are two more faces
on the Manning payroll.
Tomorrow, they transport laundered
drug money to a safe house.
Cos they had the police in their pocket,
there's no reason for 'em to suspect.
But be careful. Faces like this
don't go down like junkies.
- Isn't it robbery?
- Hit 'em quick and hard. They'll fold.
- What about police traffic?
- I can only do so much.
Give me your fucking keys, now.
Get down on the floor!
Down on the floor. You stay there.
You stay there. Come on!
Get down. Don't you move!
Get on the fucking corner!
- Stay there!
- Get down, you cunt!
Come on!
Keep down! Don't move!
Go, go! Get in! Fucking idiot!
Get in, you fucking idiot!
Fucking idiot! What did you do?
Me? That black bastard
pushed me out the way.
- Who you calling a black 'B'?
- You, you mug.
You pushed me out of the way.
You fucking mug!
Leave it! Leave it!
- We got something, didn't we?
- Not the point.
You're fucking useless, all of you.
Couldn't take money
when it's sitting on a plate.
I didn't know the police
were gonna be driving by.
Shut up. You're as bad as him.
Like fucking kids.
Extraordinary events
in a London suburb this morning.
What appeared to be a robbery
ended in thieves emptying sacks of cash
over the streets for the public.
'Extraordinary scenes indeed.
'Lt seems that the gang took the money
from known drug dealers
'slit open the bag and then let it go
from the back of their getaway van.
'Eyewitnesses reported that
the masked raiders waved at police
'as the money was distributed
into the streets. '
We're famous.
Someone's taking the piss, someone
under our roof. I've got too much to lose.
- Yes, sir. Clearly.
- Talk to the ghosts, see what they have.
Who are these fucking people?
Good afternoon.
We believe we have evidence
linking the robbery to the attempted
murders of the drug dealers this week.
We believe the same gang
is responsible for both crimes.
And we are treating this
as a priority case.
We also believe the gang have made
connections within the police force.
We will leave no stone unturned
in our attempts to bring police corruption
to justice.
'These gang members are nothing more
than mindless outlaws.
'And while certain members of the media
'will always find disillusioned members of
the public to lionise these street gangs,
'this footage shows the true horror
of what we are dealing with.
'The gang are armed.
'And the public should not approach them
under any circumstances.
'Lt's our duty
to bring organised crime to justice
'as the safety of the British public
is our priority. '
'The public is being failed
by both the government and the police.
'The poll,
commissioned by the Home Office... '
'The craze is the latest
in a string of violent incidents
'said to be provoked
by the outlaw gang. '
'Police criticised the media
for "hero worshipping" the armed gang
'after several tabloids called them
a "Robin Hood-style" organisation. '
'... who they are
and why they've taken to the streets.
'Later, you can have your say
in our text vote
'as to whether you see the gang
as heroes or villains. '
Bullies. I put them top of my list,
you know?
I hate 'em.
There's a few that are gonna get served
one day.
Why stop there?
We can do what we want.
- Know where to draw the line.
- What line?
What are you gonna do? Punch every
traffic warden you come across?
No. I'm talking about your nonces and
that. Your Gary Glitters, your grasses.
Sickos, Muslims.
Hang the fucking lot of them.
Lan Huntley.
He'll be the first to fucking go.
I'm a Muslim, Hillier.
Do you want to kill me?
You ain't a Muslim. You're black.
So I'm not allowed to be a Muslim
because I'm black?
Here, boss. What was that thing
you said about suicide bombers?
You don't have to be a Muslim to blow
yourself up. I'm talking individuals.
- You gonna kill the Irish cos of the IRA?
- Yeah, I would.
You're such a Philistine
sometimes, Hillier.
No, I'm British 100%, me.
Listen. I'm here
because my wife and child are dead.
That has nothing to do with race
or religion.
OK?
Get to a landline and call me back
on 02074960209.
- What's wrong?
- I think Greaves is on me.
Don't worry. This is swept.
Listen. I've found the CCTV
from the court toilets with Monroe.
'Your man's called Furlong. Lan Furlong.
'He currently resides in a bail hostel
in the West Country. '
Text me his address to Dekker's phone.
Why's he on bail?
Shoplifting crayons, apparently.
CPS document said he was originally
charged with sexually assaulting a minor.
But they buried it, down to his
cooperation with certain police officers.
The geezer's a fucking nonce.
Put him down.
You're a good man, Walter.
Thanks for everything.
Yeah. You too, son.
So where are you from?
You married?
I'm supposed to be getting married soon.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. I don't even know if I want to.
Stop talking.
There's the target. Bring the car round
and meet me on that corner.
Oi, Furlong.
Is it not true
that you work for Terry Manning?
And in a bid to bend a jury,
you murdered
the prosecution counsel's wife.
But you did threaten the counsel's
unborn child with murder
if he didn't walk away from the case,
did you not?
And lastly,
were you or were you not cleared
of sexually assaulting a minor
on the grounds of your special
relationships with certain police officers?
Guilty. Kick the barrel away
and let's get the fuck out of here.
For Christ's sake...
You have to stop this. This is murder.
What about your wife and kid?
- They're not the point.
- What is the point, then, Barrister?
If we do this, we become murderers.
And I don't want any part of that.
How do we know if he really did it?
Cos that's what we think?
Is that proof? Is it?
I do this for a living.
We need real proof.
Beyond a reasonable doubt.
This ain't murder. It's punishment.
Don't you do this.
Do it? That's what we're about.
This is who we are, now.
No!
Christ, you...
What did you fucking do that for? Eh?
You ain't seen the last of him.
I'm the boss, Hillier.
Don't you ever forget that.
Listen, it's worse than I thought.
Manning's got Greaves in his pocket.
They're doing all sorts together.
Manning will get bailed this week.
The case will collapse. Find him.
He's the one to go for next.
- What about Furlong?
- Fuck Furlong. He's already gone.
It wasn't that easy.
You let him go. For fuck's sake,
you don't know what you've done.
Hang up now.
Yeah, don't call this number again.
I'll contact you.
Furlong.
What you gonna do now... boss?
Fuck off.
Off you go, eh?
Better off without me, is that it?
Yeah, you carry on walking away
when things get tough.
Leave all the real work to me.
You're a joke.
Fucking outlaws?
What a load of old bollocks that is!
You ain't got it in ya. None of ya.
Not a fucking one of ya!
And all you do, boss, is give orders.
I've never seen you once back it up.
Not once.
No wonder your missus
started fucking about.
Who's coming? Who's staying?
'According to Scotland Yard,
the gang,
'referred by the tabloids as the Outlaws,
'are still at large, although the police
are searching in the West Country
'after an anonymous tip-off
said the gang were seen... '
'The CCTV footage
doesn't positively ID the suspects,
'although they say, without a doubt,
this has the stamp of the Outlaw gang. '
I need cigarettes.
Only a matter of time, eh?
Says on the TV them outlaws
have started killing each other.
'Lewis was found executed
in his own home last night.
'Police want to question this man
in connection with the murder,
'Danny Bryant.
'Recently court-martialled
from the forces,
'he's said to be the mastermind
behind the Outlaws.
'Police say Bryant fell out with Lewis
because he was loyal the police force.
'Bryant is extremely dangerous and
not to be approached by the public. '
Stop the car.
Dekker, Monroe. Get out of the car.
- What for?
- Just get out.
They've killed Lewis
and put me in the frame.
They don't know who you are.
You can still walk away.
- What if we don't wanna?
- You should want to.
If they kill their own, you don't stand
a fucking chance. Now walk away.
Dump your phones and start again.
Forget we ever met. Don't make contact
with each other, whatever you do.
Now, go.
- I said walk!
- Where?
You fucking walk away now!
- Now go!
- Why?
I said go! Go on, fuck off!
For your own good. Go on.
This is where you were beaten up.
What do you wanna come here for?
Don't matter.
'My client Terrence Manning
has fought tirelessly to clear his name.
'And can return to being an
upstanding member of his community.
'Mr Manning would like to thank his family
and friends for support throughout,
'in particular his wife Joanna,
who has been his rock.
'Mr Manning would like to thank members
of the press who respected his privacy
'around and about the family home.
'Finally, my client
would like to thank the judge
'for the fairness and justness
of his ruling today. '
We're in the papers again.
Says they nearly had him.
Pinned him down somewhere in Essex
and he slipped the net again.
Do you think they'll catch him?
Did he kill anyone apart from Lewis?
He didn't kill Lewis.
Greaves and Manning did.
You know where Bryant is, don't ya?
Frank? Drop it.
You can make a lot of money with that
information. He's on the wanted list.
- Have you spoke to him?
- Stop fucking driving me mad.
- I'm only asking.
- Where you been, shithead?
Therapy?
It's a shame you lot
never got round to him.
Bryant would have loved
to have dealt with him.
I would have come with you, but it would
have looked weird if we'd both gone.
Hey.
To the groom.
- What a fucking way to go out, eh?
- I can think of worse ways.
You know what you were saying
in the office about Manning?
You know my brother Andy?
He knows someone
who does a bit of running about for him.
- Said Manning's lying low in the country.
- Who the fuck have you been talked to?
- I told you earlier, friend. Drop it.
- I haven't spoken to anyone, I swear.
- It's just my brother.
- Where in the countryside?
Dunno. I can find out.
Leave me alone.
# Sometimes it's faded
# Assassinated
# For fear of growing old
# We hang on
# Though we try
# It's gone #
- Manning made bail. Where is he?
- Kill me and you won't fucking know.
Somebody'll talk. They always do.
'He said Manning's lying low
in the country... '
I will.
'The only difference between us is
'I've got the confidence
to fight back. '
Be faithful to her
until death do you part?
No.
Yes? Yes?
There's a phone call for you, Cedric.
Who is it, Lucy?
He didn't give his name.
He said you'd know who it is.
How are you getting on?
I've been better.
You?
Do you wanna do something?
I know how to get to Manning.
Come on! Get him! Get him!
Come on, get back! Back!
What did I tell you?
- Put the gun down, please.
- What... did I tell you?
- You told us not to make contact.
- For your own good.
What were you talking about
at the restaurant with Monroe?
Somebody say something about
Manning? I heard you say Manning.
Tell me what you know, Dekker.
He's in the countryside. I know where.
- How do you know?
- I just do.
What were you planning?
We don't know what else to do
any more.
We'll dump the vehicle and go on foot.
A tree line runs into the garden.
The file says
he drives a black BMW 735i.
And that's our entry sign.
And once we're inside?
Any other questions?
It won't work. What do you think,
he's gonna be waiting for you alone?
Even if you do kill him, they'll find you.
You know where we'll be
if you change your mind.
What about you two?
You've still got lives to go back to.
You could slip under the radar,
forget we ever met.
He's probably right.
Chances are, we won't make it.
Come on.
Something's wrong.
Upstairs.
'Or spend the rest of your lives
getting raped by cunts like Blair?
'Or having paedophiles
wandering the fucking playgrounds
'while you smile mute
and pay your fucking taxes?
'Neither do I.
'I wanna learn how to... '
- Get down on the floor.
- Drop the weapons.
Go! Go!
Come on. Come on.
Over there. Come on.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's just a surface wound.
I'll live.
- What?
- What were you doing with that gun?
You were closer to hitting me than them.
What? I was the one
who shot the marksman, wasn't I?
Bollocks.
You didn't have your safety catch off.
- Rubbish.
- Rubbish, he says. Eh? Rubbish!
You know, Monroe? You know
something? I've never heard you swear.
Takes a lot of doing
for a man in your shoes.
If we go up that way, we're dead.
Make your targets!
Keep it sharp, lads!
Armed police! Stand still!
Get the murdering little fucker! Stop him!
Do it! Kill him!
Shit.
Thanks, Mr Manning.
You ain't got the bollocks, son.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org