Rock of ages cleft for me
Let me hide myself in thee
Let the water and the blood
From thy wounded side which flowed
Be of sin the double cure
Save from wrath
and make me pure
"Judge me, O Lord,
for I have walked in mine integrity.
"I have trusted also in the Lord,
"therefore I shall not slide.
"Examine me, O Lord, and prove me.
"Try my reins and my heart.
"For thy loving kindness
is before mine eyes
"and I have walked in thy truth.
"I have not sat with evil persons,
"neither will I go in with dissemblers.
"I will wash mine hands in innocency.
"So will I compass thine altar, O Lord.
"That I may publish
with the voice of thanksgiving
"and tell of all thy wondrous works..."
- Loggins' funeral?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Ain't related, are you?
- Related?
We're looking for the child's kin.
Thought I saw some resemblance.
No kin?
None we know of, except in Missouri.
Seems you got the child's jaw.
No, just a friend of her mama.
If ever a child needed a friend...
"...will I bless the Lord.
- "Amen."
- Amen.
Amen, Essie Mae.
I just know your ass is still warm.
Would you like some water, Addie?
We'll get the child some water.
Bless you, child. I wanted
to pay my respects to your mama.
- I have to go. It's a long way to St Louis.
- St Louis, Missouri?
Yes, ma'am. I sell the Good Book.
Just spreading the Lord's good news.
Addie, don't you have your Aunt Billie
living in St Joseph, Missouri?
Her poor mother's sister.
- Her only known relative.
- That so?
If you're driving your chariot to Missouri,
you could take her.
- I wouldn't call it a chariot, Reverend.
- I'll write the woman a letter tonight.
I have to think upon this. I may
have to make a few stops along the way.
- I never travelled with no child before.
- The child's got no place to go!
Well...
...in the eyes of the Lord,
I have no choice.
- Hallelujah!
- God works in mysterious ways.
Come on, Addie, better get your things.
This nice man's taking you to your aunt.
How come you're taking me?
- How come you're taking me?
- 'Cause I'm going that way, honey.
Although I do want to make just one stop
before we leave town.
- Got a little business to do.
- You know my mama real good?
Oh, pretty good.
You just stay out here.
Don't you say a word unless I ask you to.
- Mr Robertson?
- That's right.
- I'd like a minute of your time.
- Not buying today.
- Just want you to meet somebody.
- So what?
- Tell him your name, honey.
- Addie. Addie Loggins.
You done real fine. I'll be out in a minute.
- Ain't she a sweet child?
- No, she ain't.
Maybe not now, because she's sad,
with her mama dead and
your drunken brother hitting that tree.
What are you trying to pull? Get out!
- I'm going. I'll tell you where.
- I don't care!
To see J T Faraday.
You know who he is?
One of the biggest lawyers in Kansas.
He don't favour the man with the money.
Know what's going to happen
to your brother? A lawsuit against him.
Everything's going to be tied up in knots.
His money, his house, all he owns!
Including half this plant.
Don't think that poor child ain't entitled,
'cause she is.
Now, I was thinking,
$2,000 would be acceptable.
I'll give you 200.
- $200?
- $200.
It's a deal.
There you are.
That'll be $67.54.
- You sure these tyres are new?
- $67.54.
Now, we'll have you to St Jo in no time.
- When's the next train to St Joseph?
- St Joseph? Let's see.
That'll be the 4.14. Change trains in
Kansas City and into St Jo at 9.52 a.m.
One child's price ticket.
$11.45.
Send a telegram to Mrs Billie Roy Griggs,
Cosmo Row, St Joseph.
"Train arriving 9.52 a.m. And bringing
love, affection and $20 cash."
Make that $25 cash
and sign it just Addie Loggins.
Ten words, that will be 85 cents more.
That will be $12.30.
$12.30?
You'd better say in that message,
"Love, affection and $20 cash."
Here's your ticket,
and $20 for your Aunt Billie.
We got till 4.15.
I don't suppose you can wait here
by yourself, can you?
You hungry? Want a Nehi
and a Coney Island?
- Ain't you eating?
- I ain't hungry.
You worried about going on the train?
You'll like it.
You'll soon be at your aunt's
and all your troubles over. So, eat up.
- She don't know me.
- She will.
- She ain't going to want me.
- She ain't seen you yet.
Never even cared for my mama.
And she was her sister.
- Your mama was fine.
- Everybody says she weren't!
- Everybody don't know your mama.
- How good you know her?
Enough to know you can be proud
of the happiness she gave.
Eat your Coney Island.
You meet her in a bar-room?
- Where would you get that question?
- I hear talk, wondering if you was my pa.
Well, don't the world have a wild
imagination?
Eat your Coney Island.
You my pa?
Course I ain't your pa.
I'll get you some relish.
Coney Island ain't no good without relish.
Look, I know how you feel. I lost my ma
and pa. I don't know where my sister is.
I wish I could tell you I'm your pa,
but it just ain't like that.
You met her in a bar!
Just because a man meets a woman
in a bar don't mean he's your pa! Eat up!
Then if you ain't my pa, I want my $200!
I want my $200. I heard you
through the door, talking to that man.
It's my money and I want it.
- You hold on a second...
- I want my money. You took my $200!
- Will you quiet down?
- I want my $200!
- Hold on. Let me explain something.
- If you was my pa, that'd be different!
- Well, I ain't! Get that out of your head.
- I look like that.
You don't look any more like me
than you do that Coney Island! Eat it!
- We got the same jaw.
- Lots of people do!
- It's possible!
- It ain't!
- Then I want my $200!
- All right!
We got the same jaw. I know a woman
that looks like a bullfrog.
- That don't mean she's its mother!
- You met my mom in a bar.
You think everybody gets met in a bar
gets a baby?
- It's possible.
- Anything is. Possible don't make it true.
- Then I want my money!
- Will you quiet down?
The trouble with you is
you got no appreciation.
Maybe I did get a little money
from that man and you're entitled to that.
I'm entitled to my share for getting it for
you. Where would you be without me?
Think them folks would spend a penny to
send you east?
Who got you a ticket?
Who got you a Coney Island?
And threw in $20 extra, not to mention
85 cents for that telegram.
You wouldn't have had that without me.
I didn't have to take you, but I took you.
I think that's fair enough.
We're both a little better off.
You get to St Jo. I get myself
a little better car. Fair is fair.
Now, drink your Nehi
and eat your Coney Island.
I want my $200.
I don't have your $200 no more
and you know it.
If you don't give me my $200, I'm going
to tell a policeman how you got it
and he'll make you give it to me,
'cause it's mine.
But I don't have it!
Then get it.
How we doing, angel pie? Going to have
dessert when we finish our hot dog?
I don't know.
Daddy, why don't we get Precious
a dessert if she eats her dog?
Her name ain't Precious.
I want my money back on this ticket
and send this telegram, "Trip delayed,
"but I'm coming real soon!"
Lie quiet.
Folks don't take to children
when they're doing business.
- Yes?
- Ma'am, is Mr Morgan at home?
Mr Morgan?
My name is Moses Pray,
Kansas Bible Company. He'll know.
I'm sorry. Mr Morgan has passed on.
Oh, ma'am, I just...
I don't know what to say.
- What were you seeing him about?
- He ordered this here Bible...
- Rudolph ordered a Bible?
- The de luxe with the lady's name on it.
- Lady's name?
- I expect a special gift to a family friend.
Under the circumstances, I'll give you
back his dollar deposit with no obligation.
Ma'am, I don't know how
to put into words the sorrow I feel.
What name is on it?
I don't really know what name Mr Morgan
had put on it, ma'am. Let's see.
It's here somewhere. I've got it.
Here it is...
- Pearl.
...Pearl.
- I'm Pearl.
- He must have got this for you, ma'am.
Yes, he bought it for me.
- Of course. You're not obliged to take it.
- Of course I'll take it.
There's one thing. I told him
I could sell him a cheaper Bible,
but he wanted the best, being the de luxe
with the lady's name printed in gold...
- Oh, he would.
...bringing a balance due of $8.
$8?
Well, that's $8, minus the dollar deposit,
- making it $7.
- I'll go get my purse.
- You're not obliged to take it.
- Of course I am. He ordered the de luxe!
Cold or not,
it's good to be back in Manhattan.
Jack, you've been here since Thursday.
What have you done?
I've had a lot of fun, Don.
I saw some shows, went to nightclubs.
Last night, I was invited
to Fred Allen's apartment for dinner.
- Fred Allen?
- We're good friends.
I'm glad to hear it.
Has Fred got a nice apartment?
How could I tell, Don, with all that
laundry hanging in the living room?
- Ain't you going to go to sleep?
- Don't you want to hear Jack Benny?
No!
I don't want to sound catty...
You're too young to smoke! You're going
to set this whole place on fire.
I now owe you $103.72.
74.
Roosevelt said we're all feeling better.
- He did?
- Made me feel good saying that.
- Better than I've felt in a long time.
- Bet old Frank wishes you was 21.
You don't like me, do you?
No, I don't like you!
- Yes?
- Ma'am, is Mr Bates at home?
Mr Bates is dead. He died a week ago.
Passed over? I was just talking to him
not less than a month ago.
- What was it you wanted?
- My name is Pray, Kansas Bible Co.
I have this Bible Mr Bates ordered.
- Bible?
- Who is it? What's the trouble?
- It's about Benjamin buying a Bible.
- Bible? What kind of Bible?
Says he talked to Benjamin a month ago.
I'm not sure of the dates.
Benjamin didn't go near that shop
for more than a month before he died.
I may be mixed up on the dates.
What company are you from?
Kansas Bible Company, out of Wichita.
- I ain't never heard of it.
- Daddy?
Can't we go? I want to get
to church and pray for Mama.
Yeah, sure we can, honey.
Daddy was just fixing to leave.
This is my little girl. It's just the two of us.
- My mama's gone to the Lord.
- So has poor Mr Bates.
Here's his deposit. Let us know
if there's anything we can do.
Hold on there! Wait one damn minute.
- He actually ordered a Bible?
- He did. Here it is.
- In gold, for somebody named Marie.
- That's her. She's Marie.
She meant a lot to him.
He wanted the de luxe edition.
- How much?
- That's...
- It's the $12 one, Daddy!
- $12?
Honey, we have to have a little goodness
in our hearts in the circumstances.
If it'll make that woman happy,
I'll take it.
You owe me $85.74.
I mean, we're going to Washington
on the Q T.
Molly, she says we can't go on the Q T,
we got to take The Pennsylvania.
I'd better go! Where's my suitcase?
- I don't know, McGee. You had it last.
- I know. It's in the hall.
He's going to open the closet.
He'll say he's got to straighten it out.
Got to straighten out that closet
one of these days.
- Would you like to do business with me?
- Instead of paying me back?
I'll pay you back. While we head east,
how about we do business together?
You're looking at me
like I'm out to cheat you. It's business.
Take it or leave it. Turn off that radio.
You'll drive us all deaf with it.
... in an average way, of course.
OK. Remember one thing,
I decide on the price.
Maybe you don't know French,
but there's finesse!
I never sold no Bible for $12.
That man was a law officer!
- We got it, didn't we?
- I don't care if we got it!
Don't you go making the decisions!
You just got to look like a pretty little girl.
You ain't got a ribbon in that cigar box?
I got my mom's kimono in my
suitcase, Chinaman with umbrellas.
That ain't what I had in mind.
You look real nice in that ribbon. First off,
I didn't know was she a boy or a girl.
- I'm a girl!
- Well, it makes all the difference.
- Ain't she got a sweet face? Somehow.
- We'll take a ribbon in each colour.
- How much is that going to cost me?
- That'll be 15 cents.
Bought my grandchildren ribbons
just like this, last holiday.
Grandchildren? I don't believe it.
You can believe it all right.
I'm just as old as I look.
Now, here you be.
That's one, two, three, four, five.
This wallet's about to bust inside. I give
you five ones, you give me that $5 bill.
- How many grandchildren you got?
- I got two granddaughters, nine and ten,
two grandsons near 16
and I got a grandson 35 years old!
Come on! Why don't you
just give me a $10 bill?
Here's the five. The ones are there.
It won't be so quick to break.
- Six children!
- I got a daughter 51!
I don't mean to be handing you no line,
but that's pretty hard to believe.
- You can believe it all right!
- I'd have to see it. Much obliged.
- See you again!
- Y'all come back!
It just don't seem quite right.
Somehow.
- Yes?
- I'm looking for Mr Stanley.
- Mr Stanley's dead.
- I'm looking for Mr Warren M Stanley.
Warren's passed on, sir.
I was just talking to him not more than
two weeks back. He ordered this Bible.
He spent money on a Bible?
- Yes, with the name Elvira in the corner.
- Why would he buy a Bible?
He took fast to the idea. He left a
balance to it. Not counting the deposit...
- This one's already paid for!
- Huh?
Mr Stanley paid for the whole thing,
don't you remember?
- Afternoon, ma'am. Mr Huff at home?
- Mr Huff passed away a week ago.
Gee, I was talking to him a month ago.
- What was it you wanted?
- My name is Pray, Kansas Bible Co.
He ordered this Bible for Edna.
- That's my name.
- You don't have to take it.
- I'll give you back his deposit and...
- Of course I want to keep it.
He bought me a Bible.
I told him I could sell him a cheaper one,
but he wanted the best,
the best being the de luxe
with the name printed in gold letters,
bringing up a balance...
Of $24!
$24. I'll get my purse.
What's your name, honey?
- Addie.
- What a sweet little name.
- Addie Pray, ma'am.
- Addie Pray, I'm going to get you $24
and an extra five
for just coming to my door.
- Praise the Lord.
Keep your sunny side up, up
Hide the side that gets blue
- Let's give 'em some money.
- No.
Just a little bit. We got $305.16.
It's a whole other business giving it away.
- They're poorly!
- The whole country is.
- Frank Roosevelt said to care for people.
- I don't care about Roosevelt.
- He says it!
- That so? He's taking care of himself.
You think he don't eat off silver trays?
He could eat off table tops. He don't.
Because that would make him look
common. He ain't running this. I am.
- You don't say what we give away.
- It's mine, too.
- $200 belongs to me, don't forget.
- You want it?
Put my share in my pocket and I'll take
you to a train station. You like that?
Find out where the nearest depot is. First
you overcharge, then you give it away!
- Where are we?
- Plainville.
$12 for a Bible! Then it's up to $24!
If I stay with you, I'll end up in jail!
- You can take me to the Lincoln depot.
- You bet I will!
- Where's Lincoln?
- There.
- You think I'm taking you over there?
- We'll hit one in Sylvan Grove.
- Where's Sylvan Grove?
- Here.
- That's through Lucas.
- You got to go some way!
- I'm not complaining!
- You got to go through Waldo, Luray...
Luray? Those are pretty good towns.
We could do some business.
- We won't. We're nearly out of Bibles.
- What? Why didn't you tell me?
- You look in the box!
- You've always got an excuse.
- You always blame me!
- You should have told me!
- We're running out of Bibles!
- We got to get new ones in Great Bend.
- Great Bend's the other way.
- We got to have Bibles, don't we?
We can veer down to Lucas and Wilson.
Veer off to Lorraine and Bushton.
We could veer off to Hoisington.
Just have to keep on veering, that's all.
I'm getting hungry. You getting hungry?
Sometimes I just don't know.
Keeping people with all the Doodley-do!
You go on back now.
I'll see you another time.
- Don't send me back.
- You got to go. Another time, I promise.
What you trying to keep secret?
You got diamonds and rubies in there?
- Go on, go on.
- Old Fido! Night-night, old Fido!
- Woof!
- Woof, woof!
There it is!
- Much obliged.
- Thank you, sir.
All right, boy, you're next.
I ain't a boy!
- Don't let it bother you.
- It ain't funny.
- There's no reason to get that sore.
- He called me a boy.
- He just got mixed up, that's all.
- He looked me straight in the eye!
- So am I and I think you're beautiful.
- You're just saying that.
You're as beautiful as your mama
and she put every flower to shame.
They feared she'd droop the tulips in
Holland, and you got all her looks.
- Then how come he called me a boy?
- I don't know.
- Maybe it's 'cause of what you got on.
- What's wrong with it?
Nothing. It just... don't exactly
make you look feminine.
Maybe we should get you fixed up.
Get you a new dress, a fancy new hat.
It wouldn't exactly hurt business either.
- You really think I'm pretty as Mama?
- Course I do.
- How much money's in the box?
- $405.16.
- Give me a twenty.
- What for?
- Come on.
- Where?
To get us new outfits
with your money from Aunt Helen.
- I don't have no Aunt Helen.
- Sure you do. Let me explain it to you.
- Yes, sir?
- An Ipana toothpaste and Sen-Sen.
- 20 and 5.
- 25.
- Yes, sir.
- There.
75 makes 1, 4 makes 5
and 15 makes 20.
Thank you very much. I don't need a bag.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you. Bye now!
- How much is this?
- 35 cents.
- 65 cents makes $1. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yes?
- A bottle of purple toilet water, please.
That'll be 25 cents.
There you go!
Lady, you made a mistake.
I give you $4.75.
- I gave you a $20 bill.
- You gave me a five.
No, ma'am, it was a $20 bill.
You give me a five and I give you $4.75.
It was a $20 bill.
No twenties in with no fives.
- What's all the turmoil?
- This girl gave me a $5 bill.
I gave her a $20 bill, I know I did. It was
a birthday present from my Aunt Helen.
She wrote "Happy Birthday, Addie"
on it. You just go look and see!
That's it, right there! That's my $20 bill
I got from my Aunt Helen!
- Give the child her $20 bill!
- I am.
- Give the child her $20.
- Yes, sir!
- And some candy.
- And pay attention to things!
- Yes, sir!
Get your cotton candy!
Sweet hot cotton candy!
- Five cents.
- Do you have change for this five?
There you are, little girl. Cotton candy!
Cotton candy!
Mister, this purse is full. If you give me
a five, I'll give you five ones.
- Get your cotton candy right here!
- Mister!
Unless you've got a $10 bill? I'll give you
the five back, along with the five ones.
There. Now, don't bother me any more.
Cotton candy!
Step up and get your cotton candy!
Get your tickets for a fourth of a dollar!
The show goes on in five minutes!
Six unusual ladies
unveiling the secret of passion,
found only a few years back in the
Egyptian tomb of Queen Neferetti,
and featuring
the luscious Miss Trixie Delight!
- I had my photo took!
- You did?
- Come get a photo with me?
- Not now.
- It'll only take a minute!
- Not now!
- It won't be here after tonight!
- I can't help that.
- How many times will you see it?
- As many as I like.
- You've seen it half a dozen.
- I might see it more. Go play bingo.
- I don't want to.
- Write another love note to St Roosevelt.
- Maybe I will!
- Stop standing around checking on me.
I ain't about to leave some poor child
stranded. I got scruples, too.
- You know what that is, scruples?
- No.
But if you've got them, it's a sure
bet they belong to somebody else.
And his name ain't Frank! It's Franklin!
Hey there, I wondered where you got to.
Where's your pa?
- Is my picture ready?
- Sure. Excuse me, folks.
Sit back in the moon there.
I'll be right with you.
Here it is. Hey now, I thought you were
going to sit in the moon with your pa?
He ain't my pa!
Hi! Get ready! Smile!
Hold it, hold it!
Beautiful.
I don't want you smoking
in the car tomorrow.
- What?
- I didn't say nothing. I'm listening to you.
There'll be two extra people riding with us
and one don't like smoke.
- What extra person?
- What?
A lady I'm taking to Topeka.
- I didn't know we was going there.
- You don't know everything.
What's the lady's name?
Miss Delight. Miss Trixie Delight.
She's a real lady!
I'm just giving her a ride!
That's what you're always talking about,
helping other people out!
Don't drop nothing, Imogene.
Take care of those breakables.
Yes, Miss Trixie.
Morning! Car is right over here.
You better ride in the back.
Come on, Imogene, you don't want
to keep these nice people waiting.
Then I danced in Tuscaloosa and the
Mayor said the nicest things about me.
The newspaper ran a big photo on me.
I got a scrapbook on me from all over.
Tell him about the time that man tried
to crack your head with a bottle.
Imogene, you silly old thing.
You know that's not true.
He wasn't going to hit me with no bottle.
He was horsing around.
Ask me nice and I'll tell you about that.
Tell him about the time
you almost got thrown in jail.
I don't understand it, Daddy. This little
baby has to go winky-tinky all the time.
- Don't worry. We'll stop here for dinner.
- We just stopped for her at lunch.
Right, and now
we're stopping for dinner. Come on.
I ain't hungry.
- Want one?
- OK.
- How old are you?
- I don't know, 15. Why?
- Just asking. Where are you from?
- Nowhere.
- You've got to be from somewheres.
- Down by Troy, I guess.
How long you work for her?
Ain't kept count. A year, maybe.
How old you be?
Nine. She really do all that dancing?
If you want to call it dancing.
All she do is waggle her hips
and shake her behind.
How come she leave that job?
The boss try to make her put out
for his friends.
- She don't put out for free.
- She put out much?
Like a gum machine. Drop something in
and she'll put something out.
- How much she charge?
- Most she can get.
But she always asks for $5.
She ain't putting out for your pa, though.
Says she's going to get all she can first.
He say he was my pa?
I heard him mumbling something like
he didn't want to talk about it. Ain't he?
I'm with him, ain't I?
How do you come to be with her?
She promised to give me $4 every week.
She ain't gave me nothing!
Except a nickel or dime.
Why don't you quit?
How I'm going to quit? And what if I do?
Ain't got no money to get home to Mom.
And what if I do get home?
They got hard times as it is.
My mama say, "Go work for a white
lady, she'll take good care of you."
Know what I think? You know that
white speck on top of chicken doo-doo?
That's the kind of white she is.
She's just like that little white speck
on top of old chicken shit!
I just love it, love it, love it!
All this white. It is absolutely the
proper thing for my kind of appearance.
You need a new dress. The right dress
makes all the difference in a face,
especially since you've got
the right kind of bone structure.
Oh my, oh my, Daddy,
but wouldn't you look handsome
behind the wheel of that?
Everything is in the bone structure.
A person can tell his whole life
by his bone structure.
I tried pushing her out of a window.
I think there are bugs all over. I just
hope there's no snakes round here.
I think we ought to go now, you know?
Thank you.
Now, hurry... Oh!
Come on, get those things in there.
Don't break anything, either.
- Let's go!
- Baby's got to go winky-tinky.
Don't worry.
Come on, we're ready.
- Come on!
- I ain't ready!
You don't look busy. Come on.
- I ain't coming!
- You listen here...
- No, I won't listen here!
- What's up with you?
I want to sit in front.
How come we ain't working no more?
We're on vacation. Miss Delight and me
are in front because we're grown-ups.
That's where grown-ups sit!
Children do not tell grown-ups
what to do with their lives.
She ain't my grown-up
and I ain't sitting no more in the back.
- Not for no cow!
- Keep your voice down!
Miss Delight ain't no cow.
She has a high school diploma!
And she's got to go to the bathroom,
so get to the car!
She's always in the bathroom!
She must have a bladder like a peanut.
I ain't getting back in that car
till she's out of it!
What's up? Daddy says you're
wearing a sad face. That ain't good.
How would you like a colouring book?
You like Mickey the Mouse?
Son of a bitch!
Come down to the car and let's all
be friends. You see me smile?
Let's see you smile like Aunt Trixie.
Come on down with Mademoiselle.
Kiddo, I understand how you feel.
You don't have to worry.
One of these days you're going to be just
as pretty as Mademoiselle, maybe more.
You already got bone structure.
When I was your age, I didn't have any.
Took me years to get bone structure.
Don't think that's not important.
Nobody started to call me Mademoiselle
till I was 17 and getting bone structure.
At your age, I was skinny.
Never thought I'd have nothing up here.
You're going to have them up there, too.
Tell you what, want me to show you
how to use cosmetics?
I'll let you put on my earrings.
You'll see how pretty you're going to be.
I'll show you how to make up your eyes
and your lips.
I'll see to it you get a little bra,
or something.
Now, pick your ass up, sit in the back,
and cut out the crap, you understand?
You're going to ruin it, ain't you?
I don't want to wipe you out and I don't
want you wiping me out, you know?
So I'm going to level with you, OK?
With me, it's just a matter of time.
I don't know why,
but somehow I just don't manage
to hold on real long.
So, if you wait it out a little,
it'll be over, you know?
Even if I want a fella, somehow or
other I manage to get it screwed up.
Maybe I'll get a new pair of shoes,
a nice dress, a few laughs.
Times are hard.
If you fool around on the hill up here,
then you don't get nothing,
I don't get nothing, he don't get nothing.
So, how about it, honey?
Just for a little while?
Let old Trixie sit up front with her big tits.
Hey, come on!
We're coming, and if you don't
find me a gas station soon,
this little old snowflake's
going to wet her pantaloons!
Oh my, I almost fell down!