GSW.
That's what the hospitals call it.
Gunshot wound.
Doctor has to report it
to the police.
That makes it hard
for guys in my line to get...
..."quality health care. "
Not many men know
what their life's worth.
I do.
Seventy grand.
That's what they took from me.
And that's what
I was going to get back.
They say, "Time heals all wounds. "
You'd think, after five months
of lying on my back...
...I'd give up
any idea of getting even.
Just be a nice guy, call it a day.
Nice guys are fine. You got to have
someone to take advantage of.
But they always finish last.
Help a cripple.
Thank you, sir.
Help a Vietnam vet walk again.
Help a cripple.
Thank you, sir.
What the fuck you doing?
Get the fuck out!
Shut up. I cured you.
Cocksucker.
- What do I owe you?
- Two ninety-eight.
Son of a...
Hey, my cigarettes!
Sorry, sorry. Pardon me.
Thank you.
One hundred...
...two hundred...
...three hundred.
Have a nice day, Mr. Johnson.
Excellent fit, sir.
And how will you be paying?
I'll give you $900.
Let me see that Magnum.
That's it.
$400 and the gun.
I'll need to see I.D.
Of course.
I'm sorry, Mr. Johnson,
this card's been canceled.
Impossible.
Do you have another form
of payment?
Try it again.
Old habits die hard, I guess.
If you don't kick them,
they kick you.
Ain't marriage grand?
Porter.
You're not dead.
What are you going to do?
Kill me?
Not now.
You're cleaning up.
Val still wants to talk to you.
Sorry, babe.
Shall I tell him
to call back again?
No, I'll talk to him.
Shut him up anyway.
Yep, same as always. You?
Yeah, good, good.
Why? Are you there now?
Don't sweat it, Val.
We all look alike to them.
Same crew. The Chows.
Twice a week.
Tuesday and Friday, between 11 and 12.
Always the same route.
Chinese money laundry.
How much in the case?
Anywhere between 340 and half a mill.
How much do you need?
We split it 40-40.
I mean, how much do you need
to buy your way back?
Into the syndicate.
How much?
- The Outfit?
- Whatever.
Jesus. You know everything.
Hi, sweetie.
130 grand.
The Chows won't go to the cops.
They keep everything in-house.
They don't feel pain.
You notice anything about those guys?
They look nasty.
Probably kung fu motherfuckers.
- Did I miss something?
- They weren't wearing seat belts.
We'll hit them on Friday.
Hubba, hubba, hubba!
Lookie here.
How's that pileup taste?
Daddy brought home the bacon, baby.
Val!
What?
After kicking a Chow's ass,
you want to do it again.
140 grand.
140 apiece.
Total.
Total?
That's 70 grand?
That's not enough.
Is for me.
I'm taking a few months off.
I'm up short. Sixty short.
Fucking slants!
Should have hit them Tuesday.
Fuck!
We got away clean.
And got something to show for it.
Be grateful for what you get,
rule number one.
Yeah, rule number one.
What?
Everything's cool.
Just not enough! All right?
Never is, Val.
Baby, just put the money
in the car, will you?
I can't fucking believe it.
You know what, Porter?
This is funny.
This will kill you.
It's always 140.
Someone ought to give me a Ph. D.
Jesus! Wait till I'm out
of the fucking way!
Everything's cool, baby.
You were great.
Everything's cool. Give me...
Okay, keep the gun.
That's it. Everything's cool.
It's just like we planned.
Come on.
Don't fall apart on me now.
There we go.
I bet you got a lot of questions
rattling in your head.
Lynn did not understand.
I don't know.
Wives get funny
when it comes to girlfriends.
What?
I didn't get that.
You got it.
Come on, Miss Porter.
I don't have all day.
Is Miss Porter here?
Mrs. Porter.
Yeah, whatever.
Motherfucker!
Get up. Turn around.
Come on.
What have we got here?
How much in here?
Two grand.
- What's in here?
- Helium.
What do you think it is?
It's heroin.
Shit. Oh, shit.
Val Resnick.
Where is he?
You want to know where he is?
He's right here.
Look. Fuck you.
Wrong answer.
God! You motherfucker!
- Fuck!
- Val Resnick.
I never heard of him, man.
Where'd you get the shit?
Come on.
They'll fucking kill me.
What do you think I'll do?
Worry about me.
Oh, come on. Okay, okay.
Stegman, man.
Arthur Stegman.
Where is he?
South End Taxi.
Farragut Road, man.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I'm looking for Arthur Stegman.
He ain't here.
Something I can help you with?
No, you can't. Where is he?
I don't know.
Take a guess.
What?
Take a guess about where he is.
Is he at home?
Go fuck yourself.
Here we go.
- This one's mine.
- Roll it.
Wait, that was mine.
There's somebody here to see you.
I'm looking for Stegman.
Who are you?
I'm Porter.
Porter, that looks like assault to me.
He looks like he likes
to resist arrest.
Fuck! Not in here.
Jesus! He wants to talk.
Am I right? Did I call it?
Are you Stegman?
Maybe. What do you want?
Your boy didn't make his delivery.
Why don't we talk outside?
You're a dealer?
Just forget about it, all right?
Don't touch my money either.
Come on...
This is heroin?
This is heroin.
Don't worry about it.
Take it easy.
Let's talk.
What are you looking at?
Play your game.
And you're bleeding
all over my couch!
Come on!
Steggie's been holding out on us.
I'll check it out.
Val Resnick.
- What about him?
- Where is he?
Even if I knew,
the answer would still be no.
- Where'd you meet up with my boy?
- At his drop.
Is he dead?
No, but she is.
O.D.'d on that crap you sent her.
So? What do you care?
I'm her husband.
You won't fucking kill me?
Not in front of these kids.
Where is he?
I don't know!
That's the truth.
It got delivered to me last night.
I won't see anyone till next month.
Why all the trouble?
He's afraid of the girl.
I mean...
...of Mrs. Porter.
I mean, that's how it looks to me.
I don't know nothing.
I know Val from the old days.
Three months ago he asks me
to do him a favor.
I make an extra grand a month.
I figure, what the hell?
Now you threaten to kill me?
That much a buddy of Val's I am not.
He's in the city.
That's all I know.
How do you know that?
- He said so.
- When?
When he came. Said he squared
himself with the syndicate.
Said he was back
in the big time for good.
He was very excited.
You tell him that Porter is back too.
And he wants his money.
I'll come back for you
when these kids are not around.
When would I tell him this?
Talk to me.
There's a young lady to see you.
Her name is Pearl.
She's got two very bad habits.
Right now I'm only interested
in one of them.
Send her up.
Apartment 718, ma'am.
Go right on up.
Send her up.
It's Haskell.
Sorry to call you at home...
Don't be sorry.
Just don't call.
I got a call from a cab guy
on the south end.
- What is it?
- It's this guy, Stegman.
Shit. Hold on a second.
On your knees, bitch.
I want satisfaction.
I'm on the phone, Pearl.
It's "Mistress Pearl. "
I'm on the fucking phone!
Make it quick.
This guy Stegman calls.
He sounded all nervous,
like something scared him.
He had to talk to you.
I said I'd see what I could do.
- What was it about?
- He said to tell you Lynn was dead.
He said some guy wanted you.
That's all he said.
I thought you ought to know.
You did right.
I want to talk to him.
Who, Stegman?
No, President Nixon.
Of course, Stegman!
Tell him Varrick's, by the bridge.
Make it...
Make it 20 minutes.
I'm working here!
Can't you see I'm working here?
Put it on my tab.
I'm looking for a girl.
She goes by the name of Rosie.
Do you know her?
She worked by telephone,
not freelance.
Probably connected
with the syndicate.
Out of my league.
I wouldn't know her.
Maybe you know somebody who would.
- Why you looking for her?
- I'm her brother.
I got cancer.
I want to see her.
You two look close.
Got a cigarette?
Your sister sounds expensive.
Try Michael,
bartender at the Regal Hotel.
That wasn't the name
I was looking for.
The only one I got.
I tried to call you, but you
must have changed your number.
I never gave you my original number.
What did this guy look like?
He had dark hair, blue eyes.
He was a Cro-Magnon-looking bastard.
If Lynn's dead, he did us a favor.
I know, except I'm out
a grand a month.
We can work something out.
Did you get a name?
He said he was Porter.
He said he was there for Porter?
No, he said he was Porter.
I wouldn't want that guy
after me either.
- I know how you must feel.
- What am I? A nobody?
I've got friends.
All I have to do is point.
I pick up a phone
and he's a dead man.
And he stays dead!
Try to keep it down.
All right?
It's okay.
What'd he say?
He said you owed him money.
Nothing else?
Nothing. Why?
How much you owe him?
None of your business.
I just got the feeling
he'd like to kill you.
Oh, Christ!
Porter.
What'd you tell him?
Nothing!
- What could I tell?
- You tell him about the heroin?
He had it with him!
I told him I delivered it.
Nothing else?
I don't know nothing else!
You gave him something. A name.
Someone who knows where to find me.
I swear on my mother...
Fuck your mother!
- That's not nice. Take it easy.
- What are you looking at?
Val, don't.
Not again. Don't do that, man.
Come on. Not again.
Don't.
- Forget it.
- Is there some trouble here?
We're just leaving.
You know what?
This one's on me.
You see me reaching for my wallet?
Sorry. He just got a promotion,
so he's a little tense.
Is there a Michael here?
That's him over yonder.
You're the man to see
about horizontal refreshment?
I'm looking for a girl named Rosie.
Prostitution is illegal
and you're speaking Greek.
Usually these matters are conducted
with more discretion.
Be discreet now.
What was her name?
Rosie.
- Who's looking for her?
- Just call her.
Rosie?
Give me the phone.
Take care of that.
Who the hell is this?
Porter.
Try again, honey.
Porter's dead.
I used to drive for you.
Provide a safe work environment.
Porter?
Why pour salt on old wounds?
I didn't need to.
I guess I had a soft spot for her.
Come in.
You look pretty good
for a dead guy.
How'd you hear about it?
People were talking.
Plus I heard your wife
was back in town alone.
She's dead.
I'm sorry, Porter.
Why?
Jesus. Surly Porter.
You're the same as ever, aren't you?
This doesn't look like you.
Yeah, well, people change.
Stay.
It's okay.
Come on, sweetheart.
Meet the nastiest dog
who ever lived.
What's his name?
Porter.
He took your job after you left.
He's just as tough,
but he won't leave me.
I need a favor.
A favor?
Maybe you're not the same as ever.
I'm looking for a syndicate boy.
It's the "Outfit. "
- We don't say syndicate anymore.
- Whatever.
Don't get touchy.
What's his name?
Val Resnick.
That son of a bitch.
You know him?
I met up with him once
a few years ago.
He can't use Star's service.
He beats up the girls.
He almost killed one.
You?
Does it matter?
You quit looking after me.
Would you know where he might be?
I suppose he's at the hotel.
- Which one?
- The Outfit hotel.
The address?
We're friends, right?
I mean, we used to be.
But I'm an employee too.
The Outfit wouldn't like me
telling you, would they?
How strong are you?
Personally, I think you are
the strongest man I've ever met.
But I wonder if it's enough.
For what?
You want this guy
for something he won't like.
I'm going to kill him.
That's something he won't like.
What if they grab you and ask you
how you found out?
You know I wouldn't turn you in.
- I wouldn't talk.
- What if they ask you hard?
I'll say it was
a cab dispatcher named Stegman.
The Oakwood Arms, Union and 17th.
Hi, Val.
Where's my money?
I took your gun.
It's back here.
You look like a pro.
Keep your mouth shut
and you'll walk out of here.
My 70 grand. I want it.
I don't have it right now.
- Where is it?
- I gave all 130,000 to the Outfit.
I gave it all to them.
Tell them you gave them money that
doesn't belong to you. Get it back.
I can't do that.
You don't know these...
You'll kill me
whether I get it or not.
All right, I'll get the money.
Just give me a few days.
What are you doing?
Noon. Tomorrow.
Say it.
All right.
This may sound crazy,
but no hard feelings?
I did what I had to do.
You can appreciate that.
I appreciate that, you...
No, no! Don't.
Please.
Allow me.
Jesus!
You bitch!
Let her work.
Me love you, baby.
Me love you long time.
No, no, wait.
Tomorrow.
Noon.
You and the money be at
7th and Franklin at the pay phone.
Where'd you get this?
Some hooker had it.
I recognized you.
I swiped it in case I could use it.
Did you hurt her?
The hooker,
did you hurt her?
What does that have to do
with anything?
I've got a few minutes.
So go boil an egg.
Phillip says you have a problem
you need help with.
Yes, sir.
Is it your problem...
...who breached our security
last night?
He breaks into my apartment...
There's an old expression
that has served me well:
"Do not shit where you eat. "
Or "live. "
"Do not shit where you live. "
I like that better.
I'm sorry, Mr. Carter.
There are three ways
we can handle this.
One: We help you.
Two: We allow you to help yourself.
Three: We have you replaced.
We have an investment in you, Resnick,
of time, money and training.
So assisting you would be...
...in a way, protecting our investment.
That is good business policy.
Yes, sir, Mr. Carter.
Thank you.
You won't regret it.
According to Phillip,
a man has come to kill you?
He's alone and he's
a professional robber. Correct?
Yes, sir. He does payroll jobs,
banks, stuff like that.
- What's his name?
- Porter.
What's his first name?
I don't know. He never called
himself anything but Porter.
Where did you get the $130,000?
That's why this man is in town?
The $130,000 you paid us back.
Yes, sir.
But only $70,000 of it was his.
We never asked you where you got it.
It's none of our business.
Now it appears
it has become our business.
Here's his file, Mr. Carter.
Do you understand your value
to the organization?
You're a sadist, you lack compunction.
That comes in handy.
But now, an area of your personal life
has become a danger to us.
A man in our organization needs
to be tough, self-reliant.
Were you to handle this problem
on your own...
...there would be no doubt...
...you're the man we want.
I want to.
I want to handle it myself.
Great.
Until it is handled, I want you
to move out of the Oakwood.
I don't have a place...
No more unpleasantness at the hotel.
Yes, sir.
It might be easier
if Resnick just disappeared.
I thought about that.
I'm not worried about Resnick.
He wouldn't last two minutes
without us.
It's that other mutt
I'm thinking about.
- What's his name?
- Porter.
Takes a lot of moxie to walk in
and whack our guys around.
Either that or he's shit nuts.
Frankly, I don't understand it
for $130,000.
It was $70,000, his share.
That's even worse.
I don't want
Mr. Bronson hearing about this.
He'll think I'm getting soft.
His principle has always been:
"If you don't understand it,
get rid of it. "
A stitch in time, so to speak.
Stitch this mutt up, Phil.
Any Polaroids or trophies?
No, not this time.
They cut me loose, Pearl.
Like I thought they would.
Hold on one second.
Shut up!
I'm on the fucking phone!
Yes?
Did your friends make it to town?
Last night, baby.
Did you tell them
Porter took their payroll?
I did.
And they want retribution.
All right. Here's what we do.
Yeah, that's Porter.
He has shit for brains.
Shit.
Shit!
Next time, Porter.
Porter's made some new friends.