Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Proctor, you've been singing
Christmas songs...
...for the entire five hours of this stakeout.
Christmas is a good four months away.
If you sing so much as one more note...
...I wiII shoot you.
Go ahead...
...make my Christmas.
Sir, can we caII it a day?
I've got a very good tip
that the WiIson Heights Gang...
...is gonna rob the jeweIry store
across the street.
I thought we might wait at Ieast untiI
they showed up before we caII it a day.
-Is that okay with you?
-Yes, sir.
I usuaIIy read the funnies
to my niece on Sunday.
Don't you understand?
It took me a year to get transferred...
...away from Lassard
and his band of misfits.
Now that I've got my own precinct,
I am not gonna Iet anyone screw with me.
It's my precinct.
I make the ruIes.
No one takes so much as a Ieak
without my say-so.
-I have a sixth sense.
-Sir--
-Let me finish. I have a sixth sense--
-But, sir!
WouId you Iet me finish?
I have a sixth sense
when it comes to crime--
-But, sir!
-Stop interrupting me!
I have got a sixth sense
when it comes to crime.
My instincts teII me this crime wave...
...is about to come to an abrupt end.
Hey, you! HoId it!
-HoId it!
-Freeze!
Captain Harris!
What are you doing here?
WeII, we're on a stakeout.
What's aII this about?
The WiIson Heights Gang struck again.
-Where?
-There, sir.
Right behind you.
When did you get here, sir?
-WeII, we--
-We've been here five hours.
-Shut up, Proctor.
-You were here during the robbery?
-Of course not.
-Yes, we were, sir.
They came a few minutes ago.
I tried to teII you.
-Shut up. Shut up! Shut up!
-Don't you remember? Inside the car.
GentIemen...
...you promised me you wouId have
this gang in custody two weeks ago!
Instead, they're making us Iook
Iike a bunch of....
The ones that are very funny.
The kings have them.
Bring me my f-- FooIs!
-Making us Iook Iike fooIs!
-Mr. Mayor, I--
Save it.
PeopIe are afraid. They're taking
their business eIsewhere.
The merchants are aII over me.
Some very important--
The ones that--
Feathers are being ruffIed here.
And now the governor is invoIved!
He wants this crime wave
stopped immediateIy.
And he is sending in a speciaI team...
...to see that the crime wave is stopped.
Mr. Mayor, Your Honor--
I think what Captain Harris
is trying to say...
...is his department wiII appreciate...
-...aII the heIp it can get.
-Yes. Good. Thank you.
But due to the possibiIity of a Ieak
in Captain Harris' department...
...the governor chose a team
outside the precinct.
He feeIs sure that they wiII bring
these scoundreIs to the--
You know, to the court thing.
Justice! Bring them to justice.
Oh, excuse me.
HeIIo. Yeah.
Oh, send him in, yes.
Thank you, Midge.
Captain Harris, Commissioner Hurst...
...I'm sure you know Commandant Lassard.
Thank you, Midge.
You-- Let me make sure
I understand this.
You are going to be working with me.
Side by side.
I feeI just the same.
We're very happy to have you with us,
Commandant Lassard.
I am sure, sure...
...that you wiII heIp us tree these swine.
Your Honor, I have just the men
for the job.
Now, who wants to go one-on-one?
No.
Heads up, peopIe!
It's Brad. He's such a chiId.
-HeIIo.
-Nice seeing you again.
-You Iook IoveIy.
-Thank you.
-Do caII sometime, we'II have Iunch.
-I wiII.
-HeIIo, dear.
-HeIIo.
-Hi, Mrs. Stanwyck.
-Hi, Jonesy.
Did you ever see such a bunch of stiffs?
EIaine, exceptionaI event.
Watch this.
What on earth is he doing?
Thanks, paI.
That shouId get me
through the next hour.
Excuse me.
-What do you think you're doing?
-I'm a poIice officer. It's my duty--
-Do you have any idea who I am?
-No, but I wanted to--
I'm WendeII P. Farnsworth.
My brother-in-Iaw's a counciIman, and I'm a
personaI friend of your watch commander.
So I suggest we forget aII about
this IittIe misunderstanding.
-Got me?
-But you were parked in a red zone.
-I have to give you a ticket--
-Let me make it cIear to you, girI.
Now, get out of here...
...before I have you busted down...
...to crossing guard.
-AII right.
-You toId her.
You got to know how to handIe peons,
you know what I mean?
What now?
-What's this?
-Citations for parking in a red zone...
...more than 1 8 inches from the curb,
bIocking a fire hydrant...
...expired registration sticker, no front pIate,
Iittering, attempt to extort an officer...
...and wiIIfuIIy destroying a court summons.
Oh, no! My car!
You can pick it up at the poIice impound
after you pay for your citations, boy!
-Morning, son.
-Morning, Dad.
PossibIe 21 1 in progress
in the Iiving room.
-ShaII we caII for backup?
-No. We can handIe it.
-Grandpa.
-Dad.
AII I took is a Iousy sandwich.
Good morning and weIcome
to the WiIson Heights Division.
Now, Iet's get to work.
This gang has been one step ahead of us.
Now, the governor feeIs that someone
in this department...
...may be Ieaking.
To guard against that possibiIity...
...onIy the peopIe in this room
wiII know our pIans.
Now, these boards...
...carry the onIy information we have...
...about these robberies.
We--
Captain Harris?
Commandant.
Thank you, Commandant Lassard.
Though we have dozens
of eyewitnesses...
...no one has been abIe to identify
any of these men from our mug books.
We can onIy assume therefore...
...that they have no poIice records.
Three sets of unidentified fingerprints...
...have been found at each crime scene.
But running them through our records
has aIso drawn us a bIank.
Whoever these perpetrators are,
they're pros.
But they have made one fataI mistake.
They chose...
...my precinct.
Yeah! Yeah! AII right! AII right!
-Ten-hut!
-Be seated.
-I've been briefing the men, sir.
-Thank you, Captain Harris.
Now, in the--
-Sir, are you okay?
-Get away!
In the absence of identifiabIe fingerprints
and photographs...
...we're gonna have to reIy
on good oId-fashioned poIice work.
Commandment, I thought you said
you had a seven-man team.
I do, commissioner.
Morning.
-Hi, there.
-Morning.
-HeIIo.
-Hey.
Nice day.
-Morning.
-Hi.
It's good to be back.
GentIemen,
you aII know Sergeant FackIer.
-Commissioner Hurst.
-HeIIo there, sergeant.
Now that our team is compIete...
...I know we shaII soon
triumph over our enemies.
Hi. Fern. Hightower.
-Hi, I'm Nick.
-HeIIo.
How do you--?
FackIer, get a mop!
Evacuate!
Evacuate this room now!
This is not a good combination.
Fire in the hoIe.
Come on, come on. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Where you from originaIIy?
You the president?
-You got the key for this?
-No.
Okay.
He Iifted you out of your chair?
And across my desk,
and he carried me into the vauIt.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. He got away
with approximateIy $ 1 90,000.
Thank you.
WeII, suggestions?
I suggest we canvass--
Canvass the entire area
with our modified poIice-artist sketches.
Who knows, we might get Iucky.
-The word--
-Word on the street...
...that might turn something up.
Listen to the stooIies,
maybe put a few men undercover.
WeII, Commandant Lassard?
The word on the street...
...might give us a cIue.
I think I just said that.
At his age, the memory comes and goes.
Hey, Debbie, take a Iook at this.
Thank you, DougIas.
WeII, at Ieast they didn't get
aII the money, huh?
They were too smart to take this.
It's an expIoding dye pack.
It's activated when you take it out
of the bank.
If you remember anything eIse at aII,
caII Captain Harris.
-Sir--
-What are you doing there, sergeant?
Sir, I found money the gang dropped.
-Thought I'd take it to Commissioner Hurst.
-That's aII right, I'II take it.
-I think a job--
-That wiII be aII.
AIrighty.
-Proctor.
-Yes, sir.
Keep an eye on these peopIe.
Commissioner.
-Yes, Captain Harris.
-It wasn't important.
Nick. Thanks, CIarke.
I think we got something here.
Go ahead.
The big guy was breaking open
the safety-deposit boxes.
The man with the guns toId him not to,
and then they argued.
TeII him what the guy said.
The big guy said, ''Why not?''
The guy with the gun said, ''Because
that's not what we're being paid for.''
They're just hired heIp.
There must be somebody pIanning
the robberies.
Somebody behind the scenes.
A mastermind.
-Ace.
-Yeah.
Who do you think the boss reaIIy is?
I don't know, but whoever he is...
-...he's certainIy weII-connected.
-Yeah.
We know what the cops wiII do
before they do.
-Ain't it something?
-Hey.
Check out Ox.
Ox, five minutes, your time's up.
You win the bet.
You gotta pay him.
I toId you.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
I am pleased to say...
...my plan is proceeding perfectly.
Together, we have brought forth
a wave of crime...
...such as this city has never known.
Every mind is filled with dread.
Every fear bears our name.
Only a few more robberies...
...and all will be ripe for Operation Chaos.
There will be panic, anarchy, destruction.
We shall bring this city to its knees.
Very funny. But we've talked
about this before, haven't we?
Oh, yes.
Bring them up here.
Come on.
You can have them back
at the end of the crime wave.
With aII due respect, Your Reverence...
...Lassard's peopIe
are incompetent fooIs...
...who are going to screw up
this whoIe investigation.
I certainIy appreciate
your difficuIty, captain.
I mean, after aII,
I want these swine captured...
...every bit as much as you do.
What can I do? My hands are--
The thing--
-With the ropes.
-Tied.
When I want your heIp, Captain Harris,
you may rest assured, I wiII ask for it.
After aII, this is the governor's show,
isn't it? I mean, my hands are tied.
However...
...if you shouId find any evidence...
...proving that Lassard and his men...
...are hurting the investigation
in any way...
...I wouId have no choice
but to go right to the governor...
...and have them removed from the case.
I wish you couId run for a third term,
Your Honor.
I wouId Iove to vote for you again.
-Me too.
-Thank you for that vote of confidence.
Now, I'm very busy this afternoon.
So if you don't mind...
...have a nice...
-...thingy.
-And you too, Your Honor.
Don't you touch another thing.
Before we Ieave...
...pIease aIIow me the priviIege
to congratuIate you...
...on your fabuIous coIIection
of modeI ships.
Thank you.
BuiIt them aII myseIf.
Of course, it's a Iabor of Iove.
Take that one you're hoIding now
in your hands.
I've spent a year on that IittIe baby.
Oh, no!
I can fix it.
I've got the whoIe weekend.
I'm very good with wood.
It's okay.
Trust me.
Commissioner Hurst is right.
We must start
with basic poIice investigation.
We shaII circuIate these sketches...
...by our very, very taIented poIice artist.
We shaII come up with many, many Ieads.
Sorry I'm Iate.
Did I miss anything?
-Yes, Nick.
-Sir, we got a tip...
...that an office at the Union Towers
is being used by the mob.
I think sending two
undercover poIice officers...
...to this Iocation may give us the break
that'II crack this case wide open.
-Sergeant Jones and myseIf--
-I'II handIe this assignment, sergeant.
I don't think an assignment Iike this
is appropriate for a man of your--
Nonsense, sergeant.
I was handIing undercover cases
when you were stiII trick-or-treating.
We'II have Captain Harris
and Lieutenant Proctor...
...take the undercover assignment
at the Union Towers buiIding.
-Undercover work is sure exciting.
-Shut up, Proctor.
Proctor, we're supposed to be undercover.
I know, I was trying to throw them
off guard.
-Just wash the windows.
-Sir.
Thank you, sir.
I think we need to taIk
about what the gang is gonna do next.
Yeah. This next job is gonna be
the cruciaI one.
It's gonna be--
What are you doing?
Sir, if you don't squeegee
these windows properIy, it Ieaves streaks.
Squeegee over there.
Thank you, sergeant.
This used to be my boys' cIub.
Come on.
It mostIy has changed.
Pardon the intrusion...
...but I have these poIice sketches
I'd appreciate you Iooking at.
WeII, certainIy, officer.
But first, why don't we aII shoot a coupIe
of friendIy games whiIe we taIk, huh?
SpIendid.
This aIways was a friendIy neighborhood.
-Come here, son.
-I'II--
Watch this. I'm gonna hustIe this oId fart
for everything he owns.
Do you mind if I ask you
a few questions?
-Let's shoot first.
-Okay.
HoId this.
-I'm not good with sports, you know.
-Hey, sarge.
This is--
I'II try.
-I'II go first.
-Yeah, yeah.
That's okay if you guys are tired,
I'II shoot again. This is nice.
Jeez.
That'II do it.
What wouId you Iike to know?
You know what I'm saying, B
-OG
-What's the matter?
Screaming almost damaged my ears
The people running in fear
The hour to devour is near
Pandemonium, chaos, total destruction
Tragedy portrays an eerie seduction
Gunshots, fistfights, even knives
People getting hurt
Others losing their lives
No doubt about it
And you can't deny it
What started as a quarrel
Turned into a riot
Bodies laid out all over the ground
Blood spattered everywhere
People getting beat down
Inner city juvie going out with a bang
Hi, we're--
CouId you teII us--?
Your beat kept me moving
From right to left
Your rap is, how you say, real def
But we need some help
And some information
About the gangs
In the Wilson Heights situation
What do you know?
She's a rapper and a cop
Man, everybody's rapping
Where will it stop
People give rap a whole lot of beef
But now old folks are rapping
Without no teeth
We're rapping about gangs
That go around banging
Robbing, stealing, shooting
Hanging on corners, polluting the nature
So give me your number
In case we get some information
-Word
-We believe you guys
We won't dispute you
But if you're lying to us
We'll come back and shoot you
Word
These guys are gonna be big.
Yeah. So where's The Gang
Iiving these days?
Captain Harris?
Oh, God!
I'II feed the poor! Oh, pIease, heIp me!
-Oh, pIease, heIp me! Mother!
-Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, you can do it!
Thank you, Proctor! I'II never forget--
Don't worry about the pants!
Save yourseIf, sir!
God, pIease don't Iet me die.
I'm so young. PIease....
--God, I'll help the homeless!
I'll feed the poor.
Oh, I'll be so good.
I mean it. I really, really mean it!
Thank you for your contribution,
Captain Harris.
Please, don't let me die!
I'm--
WeII, it wouId seem...
...that aII our oId-fashioned poIice work
has netted us zip.
We don't know who these men are.
We don't know where they're going
to strike next.
-Yes, sergeant.
-WeII, maybe we do, sir.
Maybe they'II strike
exactIy where we want them to.
Right.
A trap is onIy as good
as the bait you use.
Red Leader to perimeter. Report.
Checkpoint One. Nothing here.
WeII, heIIo there, IittIe feIIow.
Bet I got something for you.
AII right. Here we go.
Look at this. See, I'm gonna get you
some good miIk.
Here. There you go.
Let's just keep this
between me and you. Okay?
-Checkpoint Two?
-Checkpoint Two. Negative.
Airport. I'm in a hurry.
Take the bus.
I don't wanna take the bus.
I wanna take your cab. Now, step on it.
You'II take the bus and Iike it. Now, mister!
He took me to dinner, then to his pIace.
And we've been there aII of two minutes
when he says:
''Oh, baby, you're so fine.
How about some wine?''
-Checkpoint Five. Laverne, are you there?
-Just a minute, Di.
Checkpoint Five. AII quiet here.
So then I Iook at him, and I say....
-What's happening, Checkpoint Three?
-Checkpoint Three. Nothing unusuaI here.
Checkpoint Four, report.
Checkpoint Four. Yeah, aII cIear.
Thank you for caIIing K-D-O-Z.
K-Doz, the station where nothing happens.
Come on, now, chin up.
I'm sure we'II get robbed any minute.
Promises, promises.
Right here, Proctor.
When this trap is sprung...
...right here is where aII the action wiII be.
And I wiII be right in the middIe of it.
This is why I insisted
that I be given this assignment.
You sure know how
to throw your fat around, sir.
That's weight, Proctor.
-Weight.
-Oh, weight.
-What's that?
-I don't know, sir.
They're out there, Proctor. I feeI it.
They'II attack this truck,
our men wiII move in...
...and I wiII personaIIy put an end
to the WiIson Heights Gang.
It's quite simpIe, reaIIy.
-Do you think we'II get commendations, sir?
-MedaIs?
They'II give me the key to the city.
First, I'II address the city
on the 6:00 news.
''The city is safe. It was my priviIege
to serve you,'' et cetera.
-Sir.
-I think maybe a parade is in order.
I'II be the grand marshaI, of course.
I'II have to face aII those taIk-show offers.
-Sir!
-What is it, Proctor?
HeIp! PuII me up!
HeIp! No! No!
HaIt! HaIt!
-HaIt! HaIt!
-HeIp!
They can't hear me, sir.
Sir, running reaIIy is the best form
of aerobic exercise.
Is it bad?
They knew. They knew aII about it.
Somebody had to tip them off.
-But onIy our team knew about the pIan.
-No, UncIe Eric...
...the Ieak is not in the precinct.
It's one of us.
WeII, it seemed Iike a good pIan
at the time.
Oh, yes, yes. A fine pIan.
We Iose a priceIess diamond...
...this WiIson Heights Gang
puIIs off the crime of the century...
...and we Iook Iike a bunch of jerks
because we practicaIIy invited them.
Do us a favor, Sergeant Lassard.
The next time you have a briIIiant idea...
...pIease, keep it to yourseIf.
AsshoIe!
But now, Captain Harris,
if you'II take a seat.
Perhaps a different seat.
We've got to stop feeIing sorry
for ourseIves.
Now, so far...
...this gang seems to be confining
its robberies to our precinct.
-You got something, Nick?
-No, no. I'm just taking some notes.
Captain Harris, the mayor wants
to see you as soon as possibIe.
The mayor wouId Iike to see me.
WeII, don't keep him waiting.
If you'II excuse me.
Proctor!
I want a compIete report
on this sprinkIer system.
-SprinkIers?
-SprinkIers.
Good afternoon. How are you?
So nice to see you. HeIIo. HeIIo.
WeIcome to America. A great country.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Seven?
Harris. Don't bother to rise.
A whoIe Iot of gIue,
but not an ounce of Iove.
Have any progress to report,
Captain Harris?
WeII, actuaIIy, I'm afraid not, sir.
We're at a bit of a standstiII.
We are re-questioning aII of the witnesses,
but that, of course, is just basic procedure.
This is not what I want to hear,
Captain Harris.
I wanna hear that these crooks
have been--
-The thing when you put the cuffs on--
-Caught!
-Caught. That's exactIy right. Caught.
-I'm trying, sir. I reaIIy am.
But it's not easy with Lassard
and his men sIowing me down.
Yes, that business with the armored car.
That was a mess.
Do you have any other compIaints
against them at aII?
Not yet, Your Eminence.
But I know Lassard and his nephew
are up to something.
-And I am going to find out what!
-What?
-That's what I'm going to find out.
-AII right, Iet's get cracking!
-Yes, sir!
-Let's get this case moving!
-Go!
-Yes, sir!
Midge, find out why Harris
has got a chair on his ass.
Come on, Nick,
we've been here since noon.
-You haven't even toId us what we're doing.
-Look, you guys just have to trust me.
-May I heIp you, sir?
-I got my eye on that neckIace there.
It is beautifuI. ShaII I show it to you?
No, thank you. I'II get it myseIf.
AII right, aII right, aII right. Stay caIm.
Sorry about the mess.
Okay, now,
where do you hide your safe?
-CaII me when you're ready.
-Back room, behind the painting.
Thank you.
We'II just be a minute.
-Excuse me, coming through.
-I don't know them.
-How'd you know?
-I don't get it yet...
...but for some reason, the robberies
foIIow the oId number 51 bus route.
-Get back here!
-CriminaIs, ho!
Oh, crapoIa.
Let's go, Proctor!
Freeze! Freeze!
You're under arrest! Hands up!
Harris, you're in the Iine of fire.
Get out of the way!
Sure, you'd Iike that, wouIdn't you?
WeII, Iet me teII you something,
Sergeant Lassard.
I happen to be captain of this precinct,
and I am perfectIy--
Let's go, Proctor!
-AII units, attention. Robbery in progress.
-I hurt my hand. Let's go! Go!
That was very exciting, wasn't it?
-He shoots.
-Air baII.
As I was saying...
...I wanted to praise the cunning
and skill you showed...
...in evading almost certain capture.
What happened there?
That fool Lassard and his team
are getting too close.
You want we shouId
take care of them?
No. Leave them to me.
Watch it, it's FackIer.
Watch it!
-Thought we weren't meeting tiII Iater.
-Hurst caIIed a speciaI meeting.
-For what?
-It makes me nervous. Harris is too happy.
You're probabIy jumping to concIusions.
-I couId be wrong.
-Officers, be seated.
This is not going to be pIeasant,
so we'II get right to the point.
From the beginning, we've suspected
that there was a Ieak in this precinct.
This morning, acting on an anonymous tip...
...Captain Harris and I personaIIy
searched one of your offices.
I'm afraid we found
what we were Iooking for.
This jeweIry has been identified
as stoIen merchandise...
...from the WiIson Heights Gang's
Iast robbery.
The office beIonged
to Commandant Eric Lassard.
To teII the truth, we were shocked.
You're shocked?
We have no choice but to suspend
Commandant Lassard and his team...
...from active duty,
pending an investigation....
An investigation.
Good day, gentIemen.
Excuse me. And of course, Iady.
Ladies, two of them.
And good day to you, Your ExceIIency.
You are aII dismissed.
We're just gonna sit here and do nothing?
What can we do? We're suspended.
To pursue this case
wouId be disobeying a direct order.
-We couId Iose our jobs.
-Wait a minute.
A man's being faIseIy accused here.
Doesn't that count for anything?
She's right. We've got to cIear
Commandant Lassard.
-No one eIse can.
-He's the reason we have these jobs.
He'd do the same for us.
You're right. Let's go.
-So, what are we Iooking for?
-I don't know, some connection.
Why are these robberies taking pIace
aIong the oId number 51 bus route?
What's so speciaI about that route?
-ShaII I bring it up on the screen?
-Yeah, Iet's take a Iook at it.
Wrong fiIe.
These are the intercity RaiIink pIans.
They must have moved the oId bus routes
to a different fiIe.
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
Maybe this isn't the wrong fiIe.
I'II teII you what, try cross-referencing
the oId bus route...
...against the proposed RaiIink system
and see what you come up with.
It matches perfectIy.
Yeah, but why is the WiIson Heights Gang
robbing stores aIong the RaiIink?
What happens when a section of town
becomes a high-crime area?
-The property is devaIued.
-Right.
Why wouId somebody want
to devaIue the property?
-So they can buy it.
-ExactIy.
The property aIong the RaiIink system
is very vaIuabIe.
Now, whoever owns that property
is gonna be very, very rich.
Find out if anyone's buying property
aIong that route.
I'm way ahead of you.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Tonight our devious plan
becomes a fearful reality.
All that remains is for me
to give my final command.
Begin Operation Chaos.
You boys are awfully quiet tonight.
WeII, sir, this is probabIy going
to be our Iast officiaI meeting with you.
We wanted you to know
what a priviIege it's been for us...
...to work with a criminaI genius
such as yourseIf.
As a matter of fact, we got you...
...a pathetic IittIe something here
to express our admiration...
...our respect, sir, and our--
Just put it in the drawer, boy.
It's Cuban.
I thank you. I'm touched.
Why, this is the perfect way...
...for me to celebrate
this victorious moment.
Funny. Very funny.
It's no good.
I don't know the code word.
-The computer won't Iet me get at their fiIe.
-We're so cIose.
We've gotta do something.
Yes, sir.
Hey, brother,
you reaIIy are computer friendIy.
Okay. ''CIayton PIating.''
Radio-controIIed detonators.
Dynamite.
DougIas.
-Oh, no.
-What, another robbery?
No, it's worse.
They've got the bIueprints
and the firepower to shut the city down.
Party Guys to Birthday Boy.
The candIes are Iit.
Make a wish.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Make up your mind.
I'm out of here!
What are you doing?
We better check this out.
Ladies and gentIemen,
pIease just caIm down.
There's no need to be aIarmed.
Just take your seats.
Ladies and gentIemen, the MetropoIitan
PoIice Department proudIy presents me.
Sorry, DonaId. Ah, phooey!
-Okay, come on.
-There you go.
-Hey, here comes a portabIe.
-Yeah, right.
Yeah, give me that one.
Yeah.
Nice night, isn't it, officers?
Hey, baby. Rock 'n' roII is the answer,
baby. Because I know what you need.
Because I'm gonna give you
what you need.
Great.
Thank you very much. Good night.
Come on, Nick, Iet's go.
Officers need assistance.
The batteries are dead.
You better go on foot. Now.
Hey, baby.
Why don't you just put that gun away.
Maybe we can have ourseIves
a IittIe party.
Okay.
Who wants to go first?
Looks Iike she doesn't need us.
-She's good.
-AII right.
My....
What a big gun.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Oh, crapoIa!
He can be such a baby.
This is Sergeant Lassard, requesting
aII avaiIabIe units to GaIena and Main.
GaIena and Main.
Over here.
-What's up?
-The WiIson Heights Gang is down there.
-What's the situation?
-The gang is getting away.
So, what are we waiting for?
I'II just get a few things from my cycIe.
Tack, you ready?
-I'm ready.
-Let's go kick some butt.
-Let's check it out.
-AII right, be carefuI.
I'm gonna see where this tunneI goes.
Look who's here.
Here one minute, gone the next.
How about you?
I just thought I'd keep you company.
You into heavy metaI?
Now I'm mad.
Sorry.
You're under arrest!
Throw down your weapon
and come out with your hands up!
I take that as a ''no.''
You're weakening. I'm stronger.
No, it's your breath.
-Knock, knock.
-Who's there?
-Boo.
-Boo who?
Quit crying.
This wiII be over in a moment.
Fighting is one thing, but bad jokes
is where I draw the Iine.
This time it's you and me.
Leave the dog out of it.
Okay, Iet's see what you got.
AII right.
AirIine piIot, huh?
AII right, Iet's finish it.
Damn you!
What the heII are you made of?
Target: human.
Mission: destroy.
My God, you're a robot!
''My God, you're a robot!
My God, you're a robot!''
-PIease, don't kiII me!
-''PIease, don't kiII me!''
''PIease, don't kiII me!''
Rest now, human.
FurIinger Magnum SpeciaI.
Hey, you're pretty good.
I'm the best.
Cute.
You know, this has been a Iot of fun,
but I have to pIace you under arrest.
You wouIdn't shoot...
...an unarmed man, wouId you?
Welcome, Sergeant Lassard.
-So you know me.
-Oh, yes, indeed.
Whatever you're paying your informer,
it's not enough.
Your cohorts are causing me
very great annoyance.
As we speak, my associates
are finishing off your friends.
And now I'm going to finish you.
Poison gas?
Oh, come on, give me a break.
Yes, melodramatic, I know,
but effective.
Goodbye, Sergeant Lassard,
and take care.
That's a nasty little cough you have.
That's not gonna do it.
HeIp!
You okay?
As you were, sergeant.
Thanks.
Now, where's Mr. Big?
We better spIit up.
Man....
Come on.
You got anything?
I think we Iost him.
I think we found him.
This is Lt. Hightower. The perpetrator's
attempting escape, west on Foundry.
Sir, Lieutenant Hightower's chasing
the perpetrator our way!
WeII, what are you waiting for?
Let's get out of here!
Repeat: west on Foundry Street.
I am pursuing in a commandeered
civilian vehicle.
Tack!
Tack! Jones!
I got him! He's in the truck!
Come on!
Anybody know how to drive one of these?
Affirmative, sir!
We took one on our honeymoon.
Y'aII hang tight.
Paddy wagon wiII be by in a minute.
See y'aII Iater.
I don't see anything, Proctor.
WeII, this is Foundry Street.
I heard Hightower on the radio.
You must have been mistaken,
because there is nothing going on here.
I do not beIieve it!
Shoot. Don't say it, Proctor!
Just don't say it.
-ToId him so.
-I heard that!
What are you doing?
I'm picking up passengers.
Why?
WeII, I have to, sir.
They're on my route.
Let's go! Move it, move it, move it!
Let's move! Go! Go! Go!
Sit down! Let's go!
You know what you're doing?
ReIax, I do this aII the time.
Look out!
WeIcome aboard, cowboy!
He had a Iot of troubIe with that Ianding.
I'II give it a nine.
Look out for Gene & Roger's
Fruit Stand!
Get out of here, you maniac!
-Have a nice evening, sir.
-Yeah, sure.
You're much better
than the reguIar driver.
''You're much better
than the reguIar driver.''
-There go the Iights.
-AII right! Let's go!
What are you doing here?
WeII...
...we chased the mastermind
into this office, sir.
WeII, he isn't here.
So get out there and find him!
Yes, sir.
What are you doing here?
That man is an imposter!
Me?
No, he's the imposter!
Okay, make way! Make way here!
Move it, move it! Commissioner Hurst...
...they have vioIated their suspensions.
I demand they be brought up on charges!
-Oh, Harris, shut up!
-Oh, shut up, Harris!
WeII, one of these guys is the mastermind.
But which one?
There's onIy one sure way to find out,
and that's the Pinocchio test.
That was it. Sorry, commissioner.
HeIIo, guys and gaIs!
Oh, boy. I wish I had a picture
of your stupid faces.
Mr. Mayor!
HeIIo, Harris, you stupid twit!
Thanks for the information when you were
trying to catch me. I found that so usefuI.
Harris was the Ieak?
I didn't know! I mean, he was the mayor.
I mean--
-How was I supposed to know?
-Why?
For money, sir.
He knew the property aIong the
RaiIink route wouId be very vaIuabIe.
So he had his gang set up a crime wave
to devaIue the property...
...so he couId buy it up, cheap.
With the damage that bIackout caused,
weII, he was gonna own it aII.
He'd just sit back, stop the crime wave...
...retire from pubIic service
and watch his property skyrocket.
You mean this was aII
just a reaI-estate scam?
A biIIion-doIIar reaI-estate scam, sir.
Take him away.
Take me away? Oh, how rude! How rude!
Take yourseIves away. Try that!
As a matter of fact, you're aII fired.
Each and every one of you is fired. Fired!
And don't you touch my modeI ships!
Not one of you!
Don't touch them!
The IittIe men are so deIicate.
They'II crumbIe
between your big, fat fingers!
Your big cop fingers!
Eric, I owe you and your team an apoIogy.
I've been a fooI.
Yes.
But that's aII right, commissioner.
Consider yourseIf and your team reinstated.
And so it is with great honor
that I award these men and women...
...the Distinguished Service Medal
for serving this city in its hour of need.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our honored police officers.
I think I'II take your seat, Iieutenant.
You take mine.
Yes, sir.
UnIess there's some probIem.
Nope. No probIem.
Proctor.
Oh, Proctor.
Proctor!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org