Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Resync for 2cd version  by nEraNga
The pool hall is a great equalizer.
In the pool hall, nobody cares about
how old or young you are...
what color your skin is,
or how much money you got in your pocket.
It's about how you move.
I remember this kid once...
who could move on a pool table
like nobody had ever seen.
I mean, hour after hour, rack after rack,
his shots just went in.
The cue was part of his arm,
and the balls had eyes.
And the thing that made him so good...
was he thought he could never miss.
I know...
'cause that kid was me.
What they're doing
is forming this new league...
kind of like what they have
for golf and tennis...
but for pool.
They scouted all the best players
in the country...
for 50 spots on this new pro tour.
Then they made their selections.
Last summer, I was in Memphis
playing Bucktooth for that Chevy.
The tournament director himself
was in the room watching me play.
A guy by the name of Toupee Jay.
Anyway, after playing Bucktooth...
this guy Jay comes up to me...
and he says even though
all 50 spots in the tour are filled...
after watching me play, they'd have to make
an exception in my case to carry 51.
Can you believe that? They want me.
He even told Joe
he'd send the invitation himself.
Man, when I was out there playing...
we had no professionals.
All we had was hustlers.
I don't wanna be a hustler, Rags.
I want to be a professional,
and I'm gonna be.
I'm just waiting for my invitation.
What's going on here?
-We were just--
-We were just what?
You know who this is?
This is Rags, and he's a hustler.
Probably one of the best.
What'd you do? Make him win the first set?
-He's up $20.
-He's $20 up. Right, $20 up.
Then you'd be $50 up, then $100,
then you'd be broke.
Come on, Joe, let me play.
I can beat this guy.
Maybe you can and maybe you can't.
But we don't deal with maybes, do we?
You don't know all the angles yet,
but I do, all right?
He's bad news.
Even if you win, you can't win.
What do you mean, even if I win,
I can't win? I don't understand.
You don't have to understand.
Just listen to me.
If the kid wants to play...
why don't you let him play?
He may learn something.
The only thing he'll learn from you
is how to lose.
I'm trying to do something here.
I'm trying to educate this kid, all right?
So if you got something to say, say it to me.
Otherwise shut the fuck up,
because he's my kid, all right?
He's my fucking kid.
And I'm gonna make him a champion.
So you stay away from him.
-Mail came today, Joe.
-Thanks, Don.
-White boy's got skills.
-No, he can't.
Damn!
Now let me get this straight.
You're saying that
because you and me are friends...
that makes us niggers?
No, "niggas," all right?
There's a big difference.
That's what I just said. "Nigger."
-No. "Nigga."
-"Nigger."
"Nigga," N-l-G-G-A.
-What the fuck is that?
-Man and me, like, we're brothers.
You know, like if I say, "You my nigga,"
that means we're boys.
Like that man you're playing, right there?
That's my nigga Charles.
My nigger Charles, right?
Hold it. See, you can't say that.
-Only I can.
-Why?
Because, first of all, you don't say it right.
And second, you don't know Charles. I do.
-You do?
-I do.
I've known Charles
since he was knee-high to a duck.
See, me and Charles, nigga, we down.
-You're down?
-Yeah, down.
Of course you're down. You're down
about $5,000. Give me my fucking money.
You know what?
It is absolutely impossible
to have an intelligent conversation...
with your white ass.
Shoot pool, honky.
This is our night, Johnny.
This is our night. I can feel it.
I mean, you've got them animals in there
eating out of the palm of your hand.
You beat them, you take their money,
you call them names to their faces...
and they love you.
I don't know how you do it.
I never saw anything like it.
Beating a man out of his money, that's easy.
Anybody can do that.
But beating a man out of his money
and making him like it...
that's an art.
That's an art of a true hustler.
But it's getting late...
and I don't wanna be here
all fucking night, okay?
There's enough drug money in there...
that we're gonna need
a fucking wheelbarrow to carry it out.
So stop messing around.
I mean, you got a game
those people never seen.
And quite frankly,
I'd like to see it sometime myself tonight.
You're gonna go in there,
you're gonna bump up the bet...
and you're gonna
close this fucking night out.
So stop wasting my fucking time.
Just do it.
A bottle of Jack.
I'll be a three-legged dog
if I'm not looking at the Side Pocket Kid.
You don't remember me...
but I saw you play once
about 10 or 15 years ago.
I used to wear a rug.
Toupee Jay.
Yeah, that's me.
I saw this kid play one of the best games
I've ever seen in my life.
Couldn't have been more than
14 or 15 years old...
but, man, he could shoot the lights out!
Now look at him. He's all grown up.
You know, I always wondered
what happened to you.
Why you never made it down
to Johnson City.
Well, Jay, I've never been
much of a tournament player.
-There's no money in them.
-No money?
We just held the U.S. Open in Atlanta.
First prize was $100,000.
But you gotta be invited to those things,
don't you?
We did invite you. A couple of times.
I sent the invitations out myself.
I even called and spoke to a backer
you had in those days.
But he said you weren't interested.
Something about...
your parents wanting you to finish school.
What was the name
of that backer you had, anyway?
Was it Joe?
Bet $20,000!
What's the matter? Did I stutter?
Everybody got all quiet, and shit?
About a minute ago,
it was like an evening at the Apollo.
Now, all of a sudden, it's quiet as a church.
That's all right, Chico, I don't blame you.
I've been beating this motherfucker
all goddamn night. He can't win.
You better watch your mouth.
You watch my mouth, Chico...
'cause you sure as hell
don't want to watch me play pool.
Unless I'm blindfolded, handcuffed,
with a cue sticking out of my ass.
Maybe you'd bet the $20,000 then, right?
That's what I thought.
Come on, Joe, let's get the fuck out of here.
These guys wouldn't bet $5 they were black.
Hold this.
You got a bet.
But for $20,000, you got to play
my man Brad in the corner, over there.
What are you doing?
I only got $8,000 on me.
Don't play that guy. He's a pro.
I saw him at the pro tournament in Phoenix.
Don't you ever tell me who I play again.
I'll play anybody in the house,
you know that, Chico.
Do you wanna play this bad motherfucker
on my money?
I don't think so.
Seems you got
too much personal shit going on.
You know what? Fuck you, Johnny.
Charles, get the rack.
I'll play him myself.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-He's got $8,000 on him, but it's not enough.
What the fuck is going on?
You should have looked out for me.
I was just a kid.
I'll fucking kill you, you motherfucker!
Shut the fuck up!
Do you honestly think that I would let
a white boy walk into my pool hall...
and talk that much shit
unless he was trying to tell me something?
You missed the fucking signs.
You didn't listen.
Me and Johnny, we's niggas.
-I'm out of here.
-Peace.
What's this I hear
about you not having my money?
Get the fuck off me!
When I was 12, I walked into a pool room...
picked up a cue,
and I just knew how to play.
I guess, for some people,
it's baseball or music.
For me, it was pool.
But I never wanted to be a hustler.
I wanted to be the best.
But after 15 years with Joe...
the only thing I ever got to be
was the best hustler.
I guess, in life, things don't always work out
the way you want them to.
You wanted to see me?
I'd have to say you're the worst carpenter
I ever worked with in my entire life.
How did you get this job?
Jack Radosta hired me on.
I guess he thought
he owed me a couple of favors.
Jack's a good man.
Bad gambler, but he's a good man.
I know I'm no good at any of this stuff.
But Jack's been showing me some things.
If I work harder...
-and I try as hard as I can--
-Relax, you're not getting fired.
As a matter of fact,
I've decided to move you up...
and make you head of supplies.
That's a promotion, son.
-More money, nice bonuses.
-Thanks.
I figure, out of all the men here,
you're probably most qualified for that job.
Why do you say that?
You're the pool hustler, ain't you?
If I need a few truckloads of steel
to disappear off this site...
I know I can count on you
to make it happen, right?
You get taken care of, I get taken care of,
and everybody's happy.
And the heaviest thing
you ever have to lift around here...
is a clipboard.
Well?
I'm sorry, Bill.
I think you got the wrong guy.
-What?
-Tell Jack I said thanks, okay?
You don't do as I say...
then you and Jack will both
be looking for work somewhere else.
Then you can tell Jack I said we're even.
Johnny, you got a phone call.
Hey, Nick. What's up?
What?
Yeah, I want a game.
What I'm saying is that I bet you $200
I can drink both these pints of beer...
-before you drink those shots of Jack.
-Sounds good to me.
That is absolutely impossible.
-Then put up your money.
-No problem.
-Brett, can you spot me?
-Again? You already owe me $200.
I'll pay tomorrow.
No cheating. I know how you guys are.
You can't knock one of my glasses
off the table...
and tell me to lap it up to win my bet.
-Who the fuck do you think we are?
-I know, I just....
To be fair, you must at least
let me finish my first beer...
before you fire down both your shots.
And we can't touch the other's glasses.
-Deal.
-You're on.
-Fine.
-Sounds good to me.
Absolutely. Good luck.
$20, $30, $40.... $65.
How much more do I need?
If Tang wins his game,
that should be just enough.
Since when was he satisfied
with just enough?
Tang's right.
Plus I'll need more money for fliers.
You can play Moose a quick game.
He's good for $100.
-Say, Moose!
-Don't mess with me.
I was watching TV with your wife today.
Stupid bitch.
Took her two hours to watch 60 Minutes.
Look, I'm sorry. I made him.... Oh, my God!
-Say, "1, 2, 3, go."
-1, 2, 3, go.
-That hand's quicker.
-What difference does--
-Use your left hand--
-Shut up.
You can't touch my glasses
and I can't touch yours.
It's incredible what's going on.
How about that?
That's it, Danny, get your money up.
Race to 5 for $100,
and I wanna see the money this time!
No more playing for owesies.
Good Lord, Moose!
Will you calm down, get a throat lozenge?
Let me get my cue, will you? Hey, Nick!
Hand me my cue, will you?
-Is that legal?
-Of course it's not legal.
I'll get your money.
-What's he doing here?
-Never mind your brother.
He's playing Moose, for Christ's sake.
Concentrate on your own game.
-You've told me that since I was 15.
-I can't help it. This guy's tough.
He's a pro.
You didn't say anything about that.
This guy's a pro? What's his name?
I don't know. He's a new guy on the circuit,
for Christ's sake.
-I don't know. I haven't played in a while.
-Lf you're short on the money, I'll back you.
-It's not about the money--
-I know it is not about the money...
but you can't go on playing bums
all your life.
Sooner or later, if you're any kind of man,
you got to step up...
step out, and see what the fuck you got.
All right, somebody hand me a cue.
-You wanna play some?
-Maybe something cheap. I'm just learning.
-$1,000 sound about right?
-Fine.
-Did you see that last shot?
-Unbelievable!
-You see the look on that fucker's face?
-Fucking dog.
We gotta go to Mel's.
Waitress there has the sickest tits
I've ever seen.
-Jesus Christ, when did this happen?
-Weather's been crazy lately.
How often have I said,
"Stay out of the pool room"?
-A thousand?
-Exactly. So how come you don't listen?
It makes no sense. Every day
you say, "Stay out of the pool room."
But I come and win $200 or $300.
It's easy money.
-Enough!
-Coming to Mel's?
You guys are retarded. I'm not going.
-Let's go.
-Seriously, don't smoke.
If I catch you with him smoking,
I'll take your bar mitzvah money.
-Thanks, Mom.
-He wouldn't do that, would he?
All right, Mom, get in the fucking car.
Did you guys know
that the average penis size is 6.4 inches...
and that the average vaginal canal
is 7.9 inches?
Therefore, in this country alone...
there's over 17,000 miles...
of unused virgin pussy out there.
-Come on.
-What the fuck is the matter with you?
-This shit is true.
-Did you do the math on that?
-I did.
-You have too much free time.
Where do you get this shit?
-It's common knowledge.
-Hey, Danny.
-You still playing The Goat, Friday night?
-Yes, you girls are coming, right?
The guy who signed Stevie Ray Vaughan
is coming down to see my ass.
Sorry, I gotta work Friday night,
and it's Lanie's last night of training.
What is this, the Olympics?
Come on, take the night off.
I'll train her myself.
This is the universal sign for "check."
I need this.
If Sinatra made it big by paying off girls
to scream and faint when he sang...
I got to have a couple of hot girls
throwing their panties on stage at my gig.
-We'll see.
-I love you. Mean it.
-Are you kidding me?
-Man, that chick has got body karate.
Do you think her tits are real?
I hate chicks with fake tits.
Are you kidding me? Fake tits are
the greatest invention of the 20th century.
-Plus they're safer.
-Safer?
Do you know that 78 percent
of chicks that have fake tits...
who are involved in boating accidents
do not drown?
-Where do you get this shit?
-It's common knowledge.
Get the fuck out of here.
Now, slowly, give me your gun
and all the money in your briefcase, nigga.
You messed
with the wrong guy, motherfucker.
Payback's a bitch, ain't it?
My girlfriend, Tara, was a law school
student from the good side of the tracks.
Her parents had her living in this
fancy apartment for the last four years.
She didn't like me playing pool much.
And I didn't like me much when I didn't.
Now that I've picked up the cue again,
I just hope she understands.
Hi, baby.
I'm sorry that I didn't call. I was....
Fuck! Jesus fucking crap!
Did you forget something?
It's your boss's party tonight,
and I'm supposed to wear a suit, right?
It was my birthday last night, Johnny.
-It was?
-God damn you.
Why didn't you
say something about it last night?
What's this?
You're playing again, aren't you?
So that's what's more important
than me last night, the fucking game?
Aren't we through with all that?
What about your job with Jack?
What about my job with Jack?
It didn't work out.
Why?
Do I look like a construction worker to you?
Give me an Indian and a cop,
I'll sing you YMCA. Is that what you want?
You think I like living with you,
like a kept man?
Breaking my back for peanuts
while you pay the check?
I play pool, Tara. That's what I do.
You know I beat a pro last night?
First time I picked up a cue in forever.
I sent him to the ATM three times.
I've always done what other people
want me to do. You, Joe, everybody.
-Now I'm gonna do what I wanna do.
-Is that why you play? Is it for the money?
You know me better than that.
I'm not sure how well I know you.
But you'll start to get to know
my foot in your ass...
if you think that
you're gonna forget my birthday...
and make me feel sorry for you
in the morning.
I just turned 30,
and I will be damned if I'm gonna let you....
Oh, my God.
You rat bastard!
Mikey V, go get my stuff.
You hock that thing again?
I just needed a little cash
for last night's game.
-You pawn motorcycles?
-I pawn anything, you know that.
That's your guitar. You shouldn't pawn that.
He's got your pool cue.
You're not supposed to pawn that.
That's different.
-Why is that different?
-Because it is.
If you need something, come to me.
Don't hock that thing again.
That's not very practical.
You're never around.
I'll be around.
I'm playing at The Goat, Friday.
Think you can come?
Why you gotta say it like such an asshole?
Just ask me nicely, and I'll be there.
-What time?
-8:00.
-I'll be there at 8:00, all right?
-We'll see.
Looks like you're getting pretty good
at that thing.
I'm getting pretty good at a lot of things.
Watch yourself,
I'll be coming after you soon.
I'll be sure to keep my eyes open.
I made a score last night,
so just take some--
What're you doing?
Are you gonna embarrass me in front of V?
You're my brother, not my mother.
You start looking after yourself.
You're in here, too.
That's me. That's not supposed to be you,
all right?
I leave town for five minutes, and this guy
thinks he's a hotshot pool shark.
Yeah, well, I am.
-You're not.
-I am.
You should not be having
your hands like that.
Why should I not have my hands up?
Because someone could just,
I don't know....
My goodness, is that horrible?
You know something?
You really wanna see pool,
come to the state line with me.
Check out the pros.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen...
and welcome to the Olhausen Invitational...
$100,0009-ball shootout.
I see a lot of familiar faces here tonight.
May your hands be steady,
and your aim be true.
Good luck.
Look at this.
See that guy in the beard?
That's Robert Tobin.
Best bank shot in the game.
Big guy over there with bushy eyebrows.
That's Bruce Kaner, the champ from Russia.
But the guy they always chase every year
for the title is that guy.
-Bobby LeBlanc.
-The best in the game.
Look at him, watch the way he breaks.
Shit.
Three balls on the break.
Six-ball run, and he's out.
Is that what makes him so good?
With that break,
he only plays six while others play nine.
There's a lot more to his game
than his break.
Watch the way he strokes the ball.
Smooth, never out of line.
When God invented pool players,
He made that guy right there.
Hey, Johnny, is that you?
St. Louis Louie, how you doing?
It's good to see you.
You, too. What're you doing here?
I didn't see your name on the roster.
I'm not playing.
I'm just showing my brother
a real game of pool.
-He's never seen you play before?
-Like I said, a real game.
Don't let him fool you. Your brother
can move the rock with the best.
I don't know about that.
I'm gonna go up and say hello to the boys.
Y'all wanna come with me?
Sure. Let's go.
What's he mean by "the rock"?
That's the cue ball. Come on.
All right, fellas. Clear the way.
I'm coming through!
Sorry, Louis, there's no food in here.
Buffet's around the corner.
What're you laughing at, Shorty?
When you go to bed at night, how do you
keep your head from sliding off the pillow?
I want you to meet an old friend of mine.
This is Johnny Doyle,
his big brother, Danny.
Charlie Banks over here, Boston Shorty...
and the legendary Jersey Red.
Jersey Red? I've heard about you for years.
-What have you heard?
-Red's got more stories than the Bible.
I once heard you ran a rack of balls
with a nine iron.
It was a putter, son.
Took the sorry son of a bitch for $12,000.
-What was your last name?
-Doyle.
Used to be known as "The Side Pocket Kid."
I heard of you.
You're the kid who took Bucktooth's Chevy.
You remember that?
Remember it? That was my car.
Bucktooth stole it from me.
It's not funny. We were on the road together.
I pull off to take a piss.
He drives off, leaves me standing there
with my dick in my hand.
I loved that car. I was glad he lost it to you.
Let me buy you a drink.
-You want one, Louie?
-Not really.
I got a game, shortly, and I gotta stay sharp.
-Who's it with?
-Greeks. You all want in?
Greeks? Shit, yeah, count me in.
Malaka, you're professional.
Last time you play, you beat me $10,000.
I shoot ball three times whole game.
Yeah, but I had my eight hours of sleep.
-You know I don't play good when I'm tired.
-What about your friend?
We play partner. $2,000 a man.
Who, him? I don't even know him.
He don't wanna play pool, anyway.
Ask him.
Hey, kid, you wanna play some pool?
Sure, I'll play.
I'll see if he's got any money.
You are so beautiful, man.
You've got 'em so turned around,
they don't know what to think.
Red, let me borrow your cue for a second.
What?
Johnny, I thought you knew
what we were trying to do here.
I'm trying to set him up for Red.
I thought you knew the move.
No hard feelings, all right?
Of course not.
Go ahead, go do your thing.
What's this?
He doesn't have any money,
but just to show you how fair I am...
I'll take the old shaky man as my partner.
Fine, you take old man. Let's go.
Get balls!
I got your balls right here,
you Greek bastard.
You don't wanna play this guy, anyway.
He may be a jackass,
but he plays pretty good.
Here, hold my coat, will you? Thanks.
Here, stick around.
Play some cards or something, all right?
Take a cab home. I'm gonna get out of here.
-I wanna go with you, man.
-Just do as I say, all right?
I made a Freudian slip yesterday.
I meant to ask my wife to pass the butter...
but instead I said,
"You bitch! You've ruined my life!"
-That's lovely. Excuse us.
-My pleasure.
-You're late.
-You look fantastic.
You're still late. What took you so long?
You didn't tell me
the guy lived in Sherwood Forest.
It took me an hour to find the place.
I had to leave a trail of breadcrumbs
along the way, to find my way back.
You don't look so bad yourself.
-I can't believe I got you in a suit.
-Me, neither.
It's going back tomorrow.
I know how you hate these things.
Thank you for coming.
No problem.
Here comes the wicked witch of the world.
-Brace yourself.
-Be nice.
There you are. I want you
to meet some friends of mine.
Tara, this is Bernice and Laurence Winthrop.
Richard Illich, and this is Brian Schwartz.
Everyone, this is Tara.
And John. Hi, John.
I'm surprised to see you here,
what with your busy schedule and all.
-I can't believe you actually made it.
-I did, Beth, all right? So relax.
No, really.
What has been keeping you so busy?
I know you're always fashionably late...
but I would just love to know
what kept us all waiting for you today.
I've been here for about an hour already.
I just was outside,
helping the valets kick-start your broom.
They had trouble finding your keys.
I think that was the problem.
Beth, may I speak to you for a moment?
John, I must say my curiosity is piqued.
What kind of business are you in?
-I kind of move money around.
-Money management. Hard currency?
-Generally.
-It's a risky business.
What's your loss ratio?
Larry, I don't lose money that often.
Really? What's your technique?
Let's just say I kind of
take it out of other people's pockets...
and put it in my pocket,
you know what I'm saying?
Okay, excuse me.
Excuse me, handsome. You got anything
in this joint besides champagne?
I didn't think so.
Lawyers' party, big deal. Can't get a beer.
I'm going outside. Get some smog.
What do you call a thousand lawyers...
buried up to their neck in sand?
-What?
-Not enough sand.
-Hi, Mike Flynn.
-John Doyle.
I saw you come in.
-Good hair.
-You, too.
Are we related?
Only kidding.
I retired last month...
so my friends drag me to these things.
They try to keep me busy.
What do you do?
I don't know.
You could say I'm self-employed.
That's good. It's wise.
When I was a kid, I figured out right away...
most companies pay people enough,
so as they don't quit.
People work hard enough,
so as they don't get fired.
You know, what's that?
Bullshit is what that is.
You play pool, Mike?
A little. Why do you ask?
Because you got a crease on your pants.
I'm not sure I wanna be hanging out with
a guy who noticed a crease in my pants.
I didn't say "a crease in your pants."
I said "a crease on your pants."
It's horizontal, below the pocket.
Normally, I might think
that would come from bad dry-cleaning.
But a guy like you
doesn't get bad dry-cleaning, do you?
Comes from playing pool.
When you lean against the table
to take a shot...
table makes a slight crease in your pants.
Yours happens to be accentuated...
by a little bit of blue chalk,
something only found on a pool table.
You're right. I've been playing pool.
Losing my ass all night
on that stupid table they got upstairs.
You say they got a table upstairs?
Come here.
That's how we do it.
It's no fair playing a guy on his own table.
One more setup, Jack.
It's my party. You'll owe me.
That's it for me.
-Tapped out?
-Phil over here is a ringer.
Mike, you back for some more?
I'm just getting started.
Phil, that's a friend of mine, John Doyle.
Phil Stein. It's his house.
John, nice to see you. You shoot pool?
I play a little.
We've been playing a little. Doubles, 8-ball.
But everybody here seems to be tapped out.
-You and Mike wanna take him on?
-Sure.
Why not double the stakes?
Are you sure you could afford it?
You're down quite a bit right now.
I'd be careful if I were you.
I don't have a lot of money on me tonight.
It's okay, I'll cover us both.
Let's play, like children.
This one's for all the marbles, boys.
Maybe, if I just....
I guess even a blind squirrel can find a nut
every once in a while.
What are you trying to say, Phil?
I'm not trying to say anything.
I'm just saying that shot was luck.
You couldn't do that again
in a million years.
I don't have to make it again
in a million years. I made it just now.
I'm saying it was luck.
Nobody can make that shot. It's impossible.
I can.
What's that?
Set 'em up, I'll make it.
I'll even make it one-handed.
Did I stutter?
Everybody got all quiet, and shit.
About a minute ago, it was like an Elk's
Lodge meeting up in this motherfucker.
Now suddenly it's quiet as a church.
Who is this guy?
-You're not serious, are you?
-Of course I am. What's it worth to you?
You're down quite a bit right now, Phil.
I'd be careful if I were you.
One hand?
All right, I'll bet you anything you want.
Anything?
All right.
You have a young paralegal
that works for you.
She's about to take the bar.
Even though I'm sure she's great
at what she does...
I think she'll make an even better lawyer.
I say this: If I make that shot...
you gotta give her a job as a lawyer
in your firm.
One year. No special treatment.
-Just a job and a chance to prove herself.
-That's ridiculous.
We scout the top law school graduates...
from all over the country for that job.
It starts at six figures, plus benefits.
Tell me, what the hell
are you gonna put up against that...
if you miss?
How about...
my new Benz?
It's got a can't-get-lost system. It's beautiful.
I know you want it.
You can own it.
All right. You got balls, kid.
Set it up.
Thanks.
So what do you say?
Come back to my boat, a little wine,
a little dancing.
You should see the moon over the water.
-It's intoxicating.
-Will your wife be there?
Honey, you'll never believe
what just happened.
Excuse me.
Can't you see I'm talking to the lady?
Now you're not. So beat it.
Where've you been?
I've been looking for you all night.
Upstairs. I've got an unbelievable story
to tell you.
Can't you see
she doesn't want to talk to you?
Come on, Tara. Let's go.
-I'm not going anywhere with you.
-Who the fuck is this?
-He's a lawyer in our firm. He's a little drunk.
-I don't care who he is.
You talk to my girl again like that,
I'll take your teeth out with pliers.
Don't talk to him like that.
You'll get me fired.
-I can talk to him any kind of way I want.
-Good playing.
You had Phil shaking
like a dog shitting peach seeds.
Here's your end. And here's my card.
You come across action like that again,
count me in.
You know him?
You hustled my boss?
Of course you did.
Why should tonight be any different?
You can't do anything
without playing an angle, can you?
I'm sorry, Uncle Mike.
I shouldn't have brought him here.
-That's your Johnny.
-This is Uncle Mike?
-You don't understand, sweetheart--
-I understand.
You think about one thing.
You care about one thing, and it is not me.
Please don't go. Get the fuck off me!
Are you crazy?
Women. You can't even
live with them anymore.
So, what about you?
I'll give you the keys,
and you can stay overnight at the office.
Thanks, Nick.
What are you going to do?
Gonna give up pool
and try to go back to her?
I gotta tell you something.
I don't think you can give up the game,
because you love it too much.
I don't know. Joe messed me up good.
Joe had nothing to do with it,
for Christ's sake!
Your trouble is, you played so many bums,
you almost became a bum yourself.
And you're not!
You're suffering from
a minor-league syndrome, understand?
You've gotta pull your ass out of that.
Tang and Danny don't belong in this place.
They don't belong in the world of pool.
But you do, for Christ's sake!
You have one of the most natural talents
in that arm I've ever seen in my life.
And what do you do?
You walk around pretending,
"I don't deserve it."
But you do deserve it,
don't you understand that?
That's a waste!
It's one of the biggest wastes in the world...
because you have the ability to be the best!
You come here.
You go around...
thinking you're a loser...
and, boy, you'll become a loser.
And pretty soon...
the only people you'll be able to beat...
are those people who think
they're bigger losers than you are.
Think it over.
Don't you fucking move!
You're gonna shoot me, Joe? Go ahead.
You killed me a long time ago.
You ungrateful fucking prick.
You don't remember, do you?
Where would you be without me?
I found you on the street,
living above the arcade with the rats.
Your mother and father
didn't care about you.
But I did. I was your father.
I bought you shoes and clothes.
I cleaned you up.
I taught you a skill.
I taught you the game.
The car you drive, the women you're with...
-everything you are, you are because of me.
-And what's that, Joe?
A fucking con man, a liar?
Someone who knows how to fuck you
before you fuck me?
I don't want to be that anymore.
-You owe me!
-I don't owe you fucking shit!
Don't tell me how you did it for me,
because you did it for yourself.
You saw a meal ticket in me,
and you fucking cashed it.
But you sold me out cheap, man.
You never gave me a chance.
What, you think I'd get too big for you?
Like I wouldn't need you anymore?
I needed you, Joe. I needed you a lot.
Because, you know, you're right.
My father never gave a fuck about me.
I needed you to be my father.
You don't like the way that tastes,
go ahead and shoot me.
You're a tough guy. You can do it.
You were never good enough to be a pro.
At 14, they would've chewed you up.
You should thank me. I saved you.
-Maybe he's gay.
-I think he might be.
-Are you gay? That's cool.
-I am not gay!
A little loud.
I think girls are a little weird, that's all.
This weekend, I was at this chick's house,
28 years old...
and she still has stuffed animals on her bed.
-Don't you find that strange?
-All chicks have stuffed animals.
They're chicks, they're weird.
You can't let that bother you.
-Scoot over.
-Dude, what happened?
What the fuck did you do
to your fucking hand?
I was drunk.
I slammed it in the door of my car.
-You gotta go see a doctor.
-I'll go. It's all right.
-You want me to take you?
-I'm good.
-I came here to talk to Max, actually.
-What's up?
I figured with my hand broke up like this...
I should get a job,
'cause I won't be shooting pool no more.
-You are drunk.
-How can I help?
I figured since you're the only degenerate
here who's got a job...
maybe I might ask that you put in a word
with that Merv guy.
Merv? You fucking kidding me?
He's not the kind you'd want to work for.
-Why?
-He's kind of a fucking asshole.
So, how bad could it be?
Come on, he's a good friend of mine.
Then definitely no. You think I want
anyone else like you working here?
Next thing, it'll be mutiny at Merv's.
Then they'll find me face down
in a puddle of blue toilet water.
Don't you want a good salesman?
The sign in your office--
I know what the sign says.
Did you ever sell motor homes before?
Did you ever sell cars before?
Have you ever sold anything before?
Then why the hell should I hire you?
-Because I got ESPN.
-ESP.
What the hell are you two talking about?
You know, Dionne Warwick,
Psychic Friends, all that.
It'll be a great asset for a salesman...
to know what a customer's thinking
at all times.
-I don't believe in that shit.
-You don't?
-I don't.
-Then let me prove it to you.
-How?
-I don't know. Let's make a bet.
-What kind of bet?
-Don't. Remember what happened last time?
What happened the last time?
Nothing. Forget it. We'll go somewhere else.
I'm tired of people not believing
in my psychic abilities here.
I'll tell you what.
If I can tell you where you got your shoes,
you give me a job, all right?
If not, I don't know, you can have my ring.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org