Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-Do you know where you're going?
-This is it.
-Do we bring the bags?
-Yeah.
Flight 92 to Miami, boarding gate 1 .
After you pass through the passport
control, it will be on your right.
Muchas gracias, por favor.
She speaks English.
l don't know why you speak
refried Spanish all the time.
lt's a courtesy, Janet.
We're in their country.
Mary Jennings?
Yeah, that's my name.
Don't wear it out.
-What's the problem?
-Come with me.
Excuse me, but we've got a flight
that's just about to leave.
You two will wait here.
Follow me, please.
Seriously, what is the problem?
l don't want to miss this flight.
l have a special rate.
-Excursion rates, they're called.
-This way, please.
What the heck is going on here, boys?
Wait a minute. ls this some kind
of Candid Camera thing?
-Where's the camera?
-Shut up.
l beg your pardon?
Did you think we don't know about your
affair with a government official?
We know who you are...
...Miss Porter.
We are not fools.
Fools, no.
You wish you were foolish.
Foolish should be a goal of yours.
Let me ask you something.
Don't you get tired of acting like
a typical South American police thug?
Go ahead, hit me again.
l tell you, our side will always win.
We have more spirit
and resources than you.
All it'll cost us is money.
There isn't enough mommy in the world
to further your cause.
Fuck.
Will you shut up, Raoul?
You'd want your mommy too,
if you had to say all this.
-Cut!
-Oh, Lowell, l'm sorry.
End marker.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, Lowell.
You can't use any of it?
You hate me now, don't you?
No, it's funny. l don't hate you.
l hate myself for not using cutaways.
lt was terrific up to that point.
Let's go, folks.
Back to one. lnto position.
Do l have time
to go to the men's room?
You bet.
Back to one!
Don't hit your chest
because of the body mike.
l'm lucky to get through that speech
at all. lf l hit my chest, forgive me.
You'd hit my chest too.
Work with us, people!
Back to one as quickly as possible!
-Reloading.
-You can say that again.
-l will after the next shot.
-lf l make it all the way through.
Very nice, guys. Tom, take this out.
Back to one, please.
Where's my plane ticket?
You fuck up my movie, l'll kill you.
You know what l'm talking about
and so does everybody on this set.
l don't care what you do to your body
on your time, but this is my time.
l won't have some spoiled, selfish,
coked-up little actress ruin my movie.
Pull yourself together
and work with us these last days...
...or l'll kill you
before you kill yourself.
l'll do a better job. You're so
out of it, you'd botch that up.
Can you do the shot
straight through this time?
Yeah.
Okay, back to one.
Let's try it again.
What's your name?
-Cindy.
-Cindy. That's perfect.
Get your ass off this set
and don't come back.
lf l catch you on this set, supplying
her with drugs, l'll call the cops.
Shoo! Get!
ls that about everything?
Anybody else want to be arrested
or killed before we wrap this?
Let's do the shot.
l feel like l slept
under an elephant's foot.
Slugabed.
lt's almost 1 1 :30.
Suz.
Sleeping Beauty?
What was the name of that man
who slept for 1 00 years?
Rapunzel. No.
Rip van Winkle.
Mrs. Winkle,
this is your wake-up call.
Suzanne.
-Delivery!
-Excuse me?
Delivery. l'm dropping someone off.
l'm dropping someone off!
lsn't this an emergency room?
-Yes.
-Well, this is an emergency!
Are you a relation of hers?
Oh, no. No relation.
l barely know her. l found her
like this and l brought her here.
-Will she be okay?
-l don't know.
Where can we reach you?
l'll call. There's empty
bottles of pills in her purse.
l think that's what she took.
Thanks.
What'd she take?
-Pills. Demerol, Percodan, cocaine.
-Give me her vitals.
Blood pressure's 84/20
and she's tachycardic.
-What's she saying?
-Something about being foolish.
You can say that again.
-You want ipecac?
-She's too unresponsive.
We have to pump your stomach!
Do l have to be there?
Nasty dream?
Everybody has those.
You'll have them for a while.
Great.
l'm Julie Marsden, director of the
rehab unit. l'm here to admit you.
Excuse me?
Which part is confusing you?
l'm in rehab?
Yes, Dr. Feldman and your mother
had you transferred...
...from the emergency room last night.
l'm in a rehab?
You don't remember
having your stomach pumped?
Oh. That's what--
My mother knows?
She was here while
you were unconscious last night.
Great.
Oh, God.
Why did they pump my stomach?
You would have died if they hadn't.
Why can't l remember anything?
You were probably in a blackout.
And you don't remember
taking any drugs?
Oh, well, sure.
Some, but not, l mean....
How did l get to the emergency room?
A man dropped you off unconscious.
Who?
l'm not a detective.
l'm here to admit you
and, God willing, help you.
l'd like to ask a few questions.
A guy dropped me off?
Did you try to take your life?
-Oh, please!
-l'm sorry if the question offends you.
But having to have your stomach pumped
indicates fairly suicidal behaviour.
Well, the behaviour might be,
but l'm certainly not.
l want you to know
that l know you're scared.
And that this is
the place to handle it.
l don't really understand
how l almost died. That's not--
That's never what l wanted to do.
What did you want to do?
l don't know.
Good.
That's your first step.
l just feel like
if l don't do what you want...
...you're gonna leave me.
You'll punish me.
All right, all right.
Let's stop there for the day.
Good work, Carol.
Okay, everybody, before we go,
l'd like to introduce...
...a newcomer, Suzanne,
who's just out of detox.
Hi, Suzanne, and welcome.
Weren't your parents coming tonight?
My mother, you mean.
No, my mother's working.
She's coming if she can.
We should all visit with our
significant others for a few minutes.
Suzanne, could l talk to you?
Deal with your feelings
before they deal with you.
Do you always talk in bumper stickers?
Addiction isn't the problem,
it's the solution.
-You do.
-Until you remove the solution...
...you can't see what the problem is.
This anger's not about me.
Who are you angry with?
Hello, darling!
Hello, dear.
Hi, Mama.
Am l too late for the family thing?
Yeah, but it's okay.
l did not want to miss that. How did
it go? What's wrong with your hair?
-lt's all the rage in the rehab.
-Excuse me, Suzanne.
Can l meet your mother?
-Sure. Bart, this is my mom.
-l can't believe l'm meeting you.
-Since l was 7, l wanted to be you.
-Bart does you in his drag show.
-This is my lover, Allen.
-Hello, Allen.
What number do you do?
''Whistling Pines.''
My costume's like the one you wore...
...in That Marvellous Mrs. Markham.
The one with the corset?
That was so difficult to wear.
Sorry, boys.
-Nice meeting you.
-Very nice meeting you. See you.
Dear, sorry, but you know
how much the queens love me.
Whistling pines
Call out to me
Under the stars
You'll hear the trees
-She looks fabulous.
-Who do you think did her?
Dr. Klein. He does all of them.
l wonder what Allen does.
This is my new roommate, Aretha.
How do you do? How rude of me.
l was excited to see my daughter.
Aretha's an unusual name.
l know. l think my parents
were expecting someone black.
Are you black?
No.
lt's very nice to meet you.
Suzanne has told me so much about you.
l think l'll go
weave a basket or something...
...and let the two of you visit.
-She seems very unusual.
-Yeah.
l'm glad you're making new friends.
Thanks, Mom!
Have you talked to Marty?
Not yet.
-You should.
-l know.
You're supposed
to start that new film.
-l'm not doing it.
-Don't do it. l'll tell you why.
l'm not going to do it.
First: lt is not a pivotal project
in your career.
Two: You'll need time
to rest and explore.
And C: You should change agents. l
don't like what they're doing for you.
Careers need planning. Your big
problem is, you're too impatient.
You only want instant gratification.
-lnstant gratification takes too long.
-Don't think about that now.
l'll handle everything while
you're in here. No pressure.
l don't want anything
hanging over your head.
l want you to be absolutely clear.
l promised myself l would not
do this and look at me.
l didn't want you to see me get upset.
l hate getting upset.
l really hate that
you have to go through this.
l wish l could do it for you.
Ever since you were a little girl, l
had this feeling that l'd lose you...
...that you'd be taken from me early.
As opposed to later,
when it would be more convenient?
You are tough. You're just
like Grandma, always judging me.
-We don't need to go over this again.
-You never let me talk.
lt's just that l feel like
l'm not talking to you sometimes.
lt feels like l'm talking
to your drama coach.
You think you could try
not being so mad at me?
l'll rinse these.
l have Woolite in my purse.
-lt's handy for the road.
-Leave it!
l'll have some clothes
brought by tomorrow...
...and your tape cassette thing
for your music and a quilt.
Sunday afternoon, Mary will bring
your video machine and some tapes...
...and a plant.
lt's so blah in here.
l don't know how you stand it,
everything one colour.
Flowers for you, Suzanne.
Who died?
Both of us almost did, for a start.
Who are they from?
They're from the guy
who pumped my stomach.
Bullshit.
'' Hope your stomach is better.
You seem to me to be
what my mother warned me about:
A beautiful and overly
sensitive person.''
He can tell from
the contents of your stomach.
l have to be sensitive to need dope.
l'm tempted to marry him
so l can tell people how we met.
Lowell Korshack's on the phone again.
Tell him l'm detoxing.
He's a director l was working with.
l don't want to talk to him.
l'm embarrassed.
l don't have to, do l?
You don't have to do anything
you don't want to.
Except never take drugs and go to AA
meetings for the rest of your life.
Oh, l feel so much better.
What can l say?
The upshot of the whole thing is
that your being in the clinic...
...made you a high risk to do a movie.
They want me to do it.
l talked to the director.
The director is not the problem.
lt's the insurance company.
They won't cover you if you do drugs.
What can l say?
l'm not doing any drugs.
We know. These are businessmen...
...with no knowledge
of creative personalities.
Actors are not treated well.
And actresses are treated like...
...l hate to use the word, but, shit.
l remember when l was 1 5 years old.
Mr. Mayer called me in for a meeting.
He was on the toilet.
We had the meeting
with him on the toilet.
You can be sure he wouldn't have done
that to John Garfield. Correct.
She doesn't like me to talk.
Doris, you better let
Uncle Marty handle this.
She'll listen to you,
you're not her mother.
Suzy, what can l say?
Other actresses and actors...
...who have not come to work
due to a drug or alcohol problem...
...cost the insurance companies a lot
of money. Can you see their problem?
l do see. l'm being punished.
lf you'll let me finish,
you'll see this is not all bad news.
Your Uncle Marty talked to
the insurance company this morning...
...and they'll cover you...
...if you stay with a '' responsible
party'' for the run of the film.
What am l supposed to do?
Go to a halfway house
for wayward SAG members?
lf you calm down a bit,
you'll see it's not that bad.
They said they'd cover you if you stay
with one or both of your parents.
What can l say? l said
your father lives in New York.
-So, what about Doris?
-Excuse me?
She can't stay with her father.
He's worse than she is.
-Not that you're bad.
-Stay with my mother?
l'm not a teenager!
l lived with my parents until l was
23 years old. We all shared the--
Doris, please. Thank you.
Maybe it would be better to wait
a few months to go back to work.
-Go to your AA meetings--
-l want to do this film.
l can go to meetings and work.
l do better when l work.
She's exactly like me
when l was her age.
-l never stopped working.
-l feel l belong, l feel necessary.
lt was good therapy after
my divorce and my miscarriages.
ln those days,
the material was a lot better.
Doris. So you got it right?
These are the conditions
for doing this film.
For the run of the film,
you stay with your mother.
You can have your old room.
Great.
Okay, l'll stay with her. You.
You know what they say,
'' No pain, no gain.''
Well, no wonder l'm so hefty.
Hefty?
lf anything, you are too thin.
Now, me. My stomach, that's hefty.
Mom, l was kidding.
l don't get your generation's humour.
l don't have a generation.
Then l think you should get one.
l got it right here.
Morning, l'm Ted. Designed to make
your life a more annoying place to be.
l'm Suzanne, designed to be annoyed.
Then we'll get along just great.
-This, of course, is your--
-My hamster cage.
-Your resting place.
-My final resting place.
l dreamed it would end like this.
Alone in a tiny room with an AM radio.
lt won't end like this,
it'll just middle.
lt'll end in a larger room...
...with air conditioning
and an AM/FM radio.
l have news to cheer you up.
The producer's coming to see you.
One of them.
-How many are there?
-Three.
The Father, the Son
and the Holy Ghost.
Which one am l
endearing myself to today?
-Anybody home?
-Morning.
Hi. Joe Pierce.
Just came by to welcome you aboard.
-You ready for makeup?
-Soon.
Any more people in here,
we'll need a lubricant.
Ted, thanks.
We'll see you out there.
Rob, get the door, please.
Suzanne, this is my agent,
Rob Sonnenfeld.
He came by to make sure
that we're all A-OK.
Nice to see you.
We came by to say hi and make sure
everything's up to snuff.
Yeah, everything's great.
And we'll need a drug screen.
Excuse me?
lt's not for us.
We're not worried about you at all.
The damn insurance company
won't cover you without a screen.
l see.
We're behind you a hundred percent.
lt's just...
...a formality.
Yeah, l understand totally.
So do you want blood or urine?
l think urine would be fine.
Do you have a cup or something
that l can put it in?
Don't worry about that.
We'll have the nurse come by
and pick that up later.
lt's great to have this little chat.
We're gonna leave you.
Do what you have to do.
We'll see you outside, okay?
Okay, great. Go, go, go.
Have fun.
Thanks.
-Who do these belong to?
-They're Frank's.
-Frankie, l got your shirt.
-Watch your back!
Good morning.
Hi there. You're just the cop
l'm looking for.
We're ready for a lineup.
Are we gonna get a rehearsal
by any chance?
You got this film confused
with a big-budget film.
The lower the budget, the fewer
the rehearsals, the worse the food.
Hello, darling! Great day for it.
You look glorious. Big kiss.
Cactus.
Stick your arms
through the holes please.
-Good morning.
-Hi. Suzanne.
Robert Munch.
Quiet, please! We're gonna
do a block for camera.
There's a lot of dialogue,
so we need total cooperation.
Also, keep in mind there are
live snakes in this shot...
...so we need you to be very careful.
Come in.
Your mom's here.
How was your day, dear?
They made me do a drug test.
l knew it.
l knew you shouldn't do this picture.
Yeah, because it's a bad film, not
because they'd make me do a drug test.
l don't analyse the way you do.
lt just felt wrong to me.
l had a dream that it wasn't right.
You don't believe my dreams,
even the one about your kidney stone.
-l'd really like a Percodan.
-l had a dream the other night.
-l had a dream that l was drowning.
-Two Percodan. Make that three.
-A sequined gown dragging me down.
-What does that mean?
l don't want to alarm you,
but l do want to prepare you.
l didn't tell you this before
because of the drug clinic thing.
Remember my hysterectomy?
-The one last year?
-Right. Well, they found tumours.
-Really?
-Fibroid tumours.
But isn't that normal?
Usually. Usually it's normal.
But in our family
all the women die young.
Grandma's still alive.
Barely, and don't contradict me.
l might not be around for much longer.
l don't want to alarm you.
l want to prepare you for my death.
lt is so important that you understand
how precious your life is to me.
How did we end up talking about
your death from my drug test?
l don't understand. Could we not talk?
l don't feel very well.
You should have Dr. Feldman look
at you. Maybe you have tumours.
Mine was big as a grapefruit.
l'm gonna kill myself.
Don't say that, even in jest, Suzanne.
You were in a drug clinic.
People might take it the wrong way.
Looks as though
there's a party going on here.
l invited a few friends over
to celebrate your coming home.
Oh, no, Mom. l have to get up early.
l don't want to see them.
All right, if you want,
l'll tell them all to go home.
Surprise!
My little girl is home.
There are people here
l haven't seen since high school...
...nor would l want to.
Louis Karasik!
For chrissake, where did
she come up with Louis Karasik?
Last time l saw him, he threw up
scrambled eggs out of his nose...
...on the way to the library.
Let me look at you, before your fat
old grandmother goes home to bed!
Give me a hug, you fat old grandma.
You sure do stink pretty.
This is my friend Aretha.
-Hi and bye. We're hitting the road.
-Not yet.
Your mother started drinking wine.
She'll rattle off
at the mouth all night.
l'm hightailing it out of here.
Now that you're better,
why don't you get her to stop?
l know. Ornery as a mule,
just like Owen.
-l heard that!
-Well, you are bullheaded, honey.
Don't you want more cashews, Grandpa?
-Did l have some already?
-He's worse every day.
Who gets worse? l heard that.
Get off my back. l want to go home.
-Yeah, well, we're going.
-Not with you!
l want to go home.
Are we going soon?
Soon, sir. Very, very soon.
-You know what my daddy did?
-What?
-What are we talking about?
-l told you.
l heard that!
Get off my back, woman!
Yap, yap, yap!
That's all you do,
all the livelong day.
And the farmer hauled
Another load away
The other day he punched me when
l tried to put clean pajamas on him.
l'm going to skedaddle, baby doll.
You ought to eat more, young lady.
You're no bigger than a pound of soap
after a hard day's wash.
Good night, sugar.
Gotta let them dogs out.
Howdy's got worms.
l have nothing to say.
The same cannot be said
for the rest of your family.
l love them, though. To me, she was
always this lovable, loud mountain.
Your mother wants you inside
to cut the cake.
Cake?
Sing something, Suzanne.
Wonderful idea!
-Come on, sweetheart.
-l can't, Mama.
Sing one of your old numbers
from my act.
l don't want to. Really.
One number for your old mother.
Come on.
You know that....
You give your hand to me
That Ray Charles tune.
-And then you say hello
-Keep going.
And / can hardly speak
Can hardly sing.
My heart is beating so
And anyone can tell
That's it.
You think you know me well
Sweet song.
Well, you don't know me
No, you don't know the one
Who dreams of you at night
And longs to kiss your lips
And longs to hold you tight
To you /'m just a friend
And that's all that /'ve ever been
But you don't know me
l don't know the bridge.
Afraid and shy
/ let my chance go by
A chance that
You might have loved me too
You give your hand to me
And then you say goodbye
/ want to walk away
All / can do is cry
No one will ever know
The one who loves you so
No, you don't know me
That was so lovely, dear.
l don't know why you don't
sing any longer.
-l get so nervous.
-But you shouldn't.
You have such a terrific voice.
Such a terrific talent.
Now, Doris sing something.
Come on, Doris.
l couldn't. No, this is
my daughter's night. Really.
Come on.
-Do you think l should, really?
-Yes.
All right.
You sang for me, l'll sing for you.
'' l'm Still Here'' in D flat.
Good times and bum times
/'ve seen them all
And my dear, /'m still here
Darn right you are!
Plush velvet sometimes
Sometimes just pretzels and beer
But /'m here
Ten years of braces, voice and tap
Touring in places off the map
Getting auditions on Zanuck's lap
Never fear
My mother drew up the contract
So /'m here
/'ve done commercials
And club dates and talk shows
Gee, that was fun and a half
When you've done commercials
And club dates and talk shows
Anything else is a laugh
Black sable one day
The next day it goes into hock
But /'m here
Top billing Monday
Tuesday you're touring in stock
But /'m here
First you're another true-blue tramp
Then someone's mother
Then you're camp
Then you career from career to career
/'m feeling transcendental
Am / here?
/'ve gotten through,
''Hey, lady, aren't you who's its?
Gee, what a looker you were. ''
Or better yet,
''Sorry, / thought you were who's its.
Whatever happened to her?''
Good times and bum times
/'ve seen them all
And my dear, / am still here
Smooth sailing sometimes
Sometimes a kick in the rear
But /'m here
/'ve run the gamut, A to Z
Three cheers
And damn it, c'est la vie
/ got through all of last year
And /'m here
Lord knows, at least / was there
Look who's here
/'m still...
...here
Cut!
-Hello, darling.
-Hey, Simon.
We've got some adjustments,
you've got 1 5 minutes.
What's happening?
Did they make you do a drug test too?
No, no. lt's nothing, really.
The producers saw the rushes
last night.
They had some rather
interesting notes.
-Well, what?
-Now, don't take it the wrong way.
l saw them this morning.
They were fine, you were fine. Really.
lt was my first day.
l couldn't agree with you more.
lt was your first day.
They basically felt that you...
...could have fun with it.
You know, just have
more fun with it, that's all.
Fancy meeting you here.
Neil Bleene, associate producer.
l understand
my enjoyment levels are down.
No, we felt the performance was fine.
But you're holding something back.
Holding something back?
l've been in the theatre.
l'm actually a theatre director.
Sometimes certain line-readings apply.
Like in comedy, it is a rule.
lnflections go up at the end.
That's a comedy rule?
Well, not so much rule as guideline.
You were very good in Public Domain.
What did you do there?
Thanks. l rehearsed.
l guess l don't take
criticism very well.
But l mean, l've had one day
of work on this...
...and two conversations about
what's missing in my performance.
We're talking about
two minutes of film.
Two minutes out of 90.
ls it correctable?
Oh, come on.
lt's not as though you farted
during all your dialogue...
...and we sat in rushes saying,
''What's that noise over her lines?''
l'm so relieved.
That analogy's bathed me in relief.
Well, Neil, thank you very much for
the acting tips and the pep talk.
My pleasure.
-l'm feeling much more relaxed now.
-Good.
Can't we put her in a girdle?
Not with that dress. Maybe control-top
pantyhose, but it may not be enough.
All right, all right.
Anything. Just do something.
We have to get her into pants, not
shorts. The tops of her legs are....
Bulbous. She has cellulite.
l wish we could get her
to stop eating so much.
l guess having given up drugs,
she has to do something.
You think we can get her
to start smoking?
What are we going to do
about the bed scene?
Cheat the angle, l presume.
Her breasts are rather
out of shape, aren't they?
lf you have her on her back,
as the script indicates...
...her tits will move off
into her armpits.
How very unpleasant.
Well, perhaps you should
buy a camisole.
l had no idea she was so
out of shape when l hired her.
But we wouldn't have got her
if she was in her prime.
lf you'll forgive me, with her
reputation she's lucky to have a job.
She pretty much destroyed her career.
This is a break for her.
You're right.
lt's sad, though, isn't it? She was
so good in A Night Full of Shoes.
l hope it's not
too much trouble for you.
l'm almost sorry
we didn't get Valerie Rogers.
Valerie has a terrific body.
Oh, well. See you.
George Lazan, executive producer
of Kitchen Sink...
...and now, L.A. Beat.
How are you?
Fine.
-Suzanne.
-Vale. l know.
Have l caught you at a bad time?
l saw the rushes.
And frankly, you're holding back.
-What seems to be the problem?
-The problem--
The problem is that hundreds
of people have talked with me...
...about my low enjoyment levels
and my....
lt bothered me. l'd prefer
to receive direction solely from you.
Really? Hundreds?
l'll have a word with them.
l mean, we're talking
about one day of work.
A day in which l was tied
to a cactus and assaulted by snakes.
As if l were a child!
They could call my mother to come in
and stand by and make sure l'm relaxed!
That's her! That's the character!
That's the quality l've been
looking for! Now, what you're doing.
But Simon, this is not relaxed!
This is incredibly upset!
-lf this is the quality--
-People, this'll be picture!
Just be yourself and you'll be fine.
lt sounds trite, but it's true.
Just trust me.
l'll speak with the producer.
l promise what happened today won't
be repeated. Try to calm down, okay?
Quiet on the set!
-Roll sound!
-Speed.
Roll camera.
Marker.
Roll plate.
Action.
Help. Help me.
Help me!
lt's me!
-Jack.
-Oh, sure! Jack.
-How've you been?
-Great. You?
Great. Okay.
God, l've just had
this long, weird day so....
How long has it been
since we've seen each other?
Oh, too long. Way too long.
Good to see you now.
You too. You going to the reunion?
-What reunion?
-High school.
-You went to Beverly High!
-Where'd you think l knew you from?
l didn't mean it like a question,
''You went to Beverly?''
l meant it in a nostalgic way.
When's the reunion?
End of the month.
You remember Mr. Craverly?
The biology teacher.
lt's terrible what happened to him.
What happened to him?
-Oh, l thought you knew.
-No.
He went to this party
and met this girl.
And she seemed tired, sick maybe.
He took her to a restaurant. Maybe
some food would make her feel better.
Next thing you know,
she goes home with him.
-You haven't heard this?
-She goes with him and then what?
He thinks it's a wonderful evening...
...and then she takes
a handful of pills and overdoses.
-Then he drives her to the hospital.
-The next morning.
And he didn't leave his name.
Mr. Craverly, l presume.
At your service.
l don't have a service.
l have a machine.
l'm glad to see you're all right.
Well, l suppose l should thank you.
l could apologize for not leaving
my name at the hospital.
Under the circumstances,
it was probably secondary.
What's polite during an overdose
with a complete stranger?
l'm not a complete stranger.
More like a relative one. Like family.
l don't know what happened that night.
l can only guess.
No, l don't even want to do that.
l want you to know l'm not like that.
l don't know what l am like,
but l don't make a habit of--
What if l told you nothing happened?
Nothing what?
Nothing happened. We just talked.
Then you took my Daradil
and fell asleep.
Why? Am l so completely
unappealing to you?
Quite the contrary. lt's just that
you were a little the worse...
...or better for substances,
and l have rules about that.
Didn't Jimmy Stewart say that
to somebody in a movie?
Well, if he did,
then he darn sure should have!
l didn't sleep with you?
Sleep?
Yeah.
Kiss?
-What? Here, right now?
-No. Then. That night.
Well, does this ring a bell?
That rings something. l'm not sure
if it's the memory bell or--
How about this?
That reminds me of something
l should've done before.
Reminds me of something l'd like
to do later so l can look back on it.
l'm nostalgic already.
Did anybody ever tell you
that you smell like Catalina?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
just this morning.
Did anybody ever tell you
that you smell like the future?
'' But l break just like a little girl.''
Oh, hello.
May l help you?
l'm here for Suzanne. Jack Falkner.
Jack. Well, l'm Suzanne's mother.
ls she expecting you?
l believe so.
We're driving to my ranch.
Come in.
-Thank you.
-l'll just call her.
l hope you don't think l was rude.
You know how protective
mothers can be.
-You said you had a ranch?
-Yes, ma'am, in Malibu.
Way out in Malibu.
How nice for you.
Have you known Suzanne long?
We've known each other about a month.
Seems like longer, though.
l know what you mean. l'm her mother,
and it seems like longer.
She's a very interesting woman,
don't you think?
-Oh, yes.
-Authentic.
So you said you've known her
about a month?
Good morning, dear.
This is my husband, Sid Roth.
This is Suzanne's little friend Jim.
Jack. Good to meet you, Mr. Roth.
You certainly don't seem like
your average rancher to me.
Well, you don't seem like
your average mother.
lf all ranchers looked like you,
there wouldn't be many crops.
That depends on
what you're raising, ma'am.
Certainly not doubts!
Oh, hello, dear. l was just coming
to get you. Your friend's here.
Could l just talk to you
for a second?
My daughter wants to talk to me.
What you watching, Mr. Roth?
l'd like to have people of my own...
...without them having
to like you so much.
Why can't we share people?
Why must you take over every situation
and completely overshadow me?
l am not overshadowing you.
l don't care if he likes me or not.
-Your friend with the bedroom eyes.
-Right.
And the living room nose and
the kitchen forehead and den ears.
Wait, l can't.
Stop, please.
-l can't do this.
-Can't do what?
What do you mean ''what''?
Re-upholster your furniture. This.
l don't have casual affairs.
Ever?
No.
There was a moment when l thought
l might have had one with you--
l don't want to have a casual affair.
ls this a proposal?
Do you joke about everything?
When things get too serious or stray
too far from what l can talk about.
Have we strayed too far?
Officially, yeah.
Look, l just got out of a drug clinic.
l'm uncomfortable with...
...whatever this is. Feelings, okay?
So you have feelings for me?
-Don't do this.
-l want to know, because l do for you.
What?
Have feelings.
How many? More than two?
-l won't do this if you make fun of me.
-Promise?
l'm not going to make fun of you.
l am making fun of you.
Sorry.
l'm sorry. l'll stop.
What are you trying to say?
l think l love you.
-When will you know for sure?
-This is hard enough.
You can't be serious.
You just met me.
l'm as surprised as you are.
l thought l'd lost the ability.
With you, l....
l thought l was immune to movie stars.
But l've wanted you from
the first time l saw you on-screen.
And that never happens to me.
You're the realest person
l've ever met in the abstract.
You had a shot in Public Domain where
you looked at the camera, into me...
...and l loved you.
l can't explain it.
You're doing pretty well.
But you're my fantasy, and l want
to make you real.
Let me love you.
You're serious?
l don't know what to say.
-l shouldn't have told you.
-lt's good you told me. lt's very...
...brave.
Brave?
Right, because it's a long shot.
You could never love me back.
No, no, no. Well, who knows?
l mean....
You certainly are
infatuation material.
l love you.
You're crazy.
Stay with me.
Take a risk.
l'm worth the risk, you'll see.
l don't want to see anyone
or smell anyone but you.
l don't know when you're kidding.
l'm serious.
-Okay.
-You'll never be sorry.
You sound like a rug salesman.
My rug salesman.
Do you have any idea
what time it is, dear?
l suppose it never occurred to you that
you scared me by staying out so late.
l was about to call
all the emergency rooms.
l'm sorry, Mama.
l didn't call because l thought
you might be asleep.
l came home because l didn't want
to worry you.
You did worry me.
Look at me. l'm a wreck.
l'm sorry.
What if you'd been out taking drugs
or something?
l'm supposed to be taking care of you.
You're my responsibility.
You're my daughter.
What was l supposed to think
when you didn't come home?
You mind if l have a drink?
Do you mind if l drop acid?
Dear, l drink socially.
l took acid socially.
l hardly think my drinking can be
compared with your drug-taking.
Even if it could be...
...your involvement with drugs
has vindicated me.
l hardly think you're in a position
to judge me.
l hope you weren't
sleeping with someone.
-l wasn't sleeping with--
-lf you were, l hope you used condoms.
l didn't raise you to act this way.
l hope it's your morals in question,
not your judgment.
l'm middle-aged.
How many 1 20-year-old
women do you know?
You just got out of a drug clinic.
You don't know what's best for you.
Oh, and l suppose you do?
Suzanne, how did we become
so estranged?
l've tried to be a good mother to you.
Only to be met by this fresh
and superior attitude of yours.
You've felt you were my intellectual
superior since you were 1 4 years old.
Rightfully so.
You were always more verbal than me.
l.
Whatever.
Why did you turn away from me?
l just want you to like me.
l want to be your friend.
Could we have this conversation
in the morning? l'm very tired.
Every time l try to get close to you,
you push me away.
How'd you like to have Joan Crawford
for a mother? Or Lana Turner?
These are the options?
-You or Lana or Joan?
-When l had my breakdown...
...l would've killed myself
if not for you.
lt's just like that, that you say--
l don't know what to do with that.
l came from nothing
and l made something out of my life.
You come from somewhere and you're
trying to make nothing out of yours.
You should just get over what happened
to you in your adolescence.
lt is time to move on.
Cut!
-Jack Falkner?
-Yeah, why?
He produced that Cambodian movie?
l guess. Why? You know him?
Ask Evelyn Ames about him.
Evelyn Ames that's playing
the prostitute?
Can l have your gun, please?
Thank you.
He says, ''What am l gonna
do without you?''
So l say, '' l don't know.
Juices, l guess.
Lots and lots of juices.''
Hi.
Could l talk to you just for a second?
Sure.
Come on, honey. lt can't be that bad.
Oh, no. lt's just--
lt's about this guy.
lt usually is.
Bobby said you might know him.
l guess l might. Who?
Jack Falkner.
You know him.
Yeah, you might say that.
You've slept with him.
Well, l don't know how much
of a rest l got.
Why?
What's the matter?
-Has he got--?
-Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, God, l hope not.
God, you scared me for a second.
l thought you were from a celebrity
AlDS notification board.
Could l ask you a personal question?
Asking who l sleep with isn't
personal anymore?
What do you want to know, if l smoke?
When did you see him last?
l don't know. A couple days ago.
Saturday. Saturday afternoon.
Saturday afternoon.
Yeah, why?
l was with him Saturday night.
That's two girls in one day.
That's just the ones we know about.
lmagine what you could pick up
if you got a satellite dish.
How can you laugh? lt's disgusting!
Especially in this day and age.
You look like somebody who can take
care of herself. Buy some condoms.
Don't feel bad.
He probably really likes you.
He didn't give you his big
Walt Whitman speech, did he?
The one about genius?
-l don't think so.
-That's a good sign.
That's his standard pickup line.
That and the big Cambodian speech.
And the thing about
smelling like Catalina.
That l've heard.
That's not bad. One out of three.
You're obviously getting some new
stuff, which means he must like you.
So he goes out with lots of people.
Yeah, sure. That's his big thing:
Women.
So if you can just enjoy
yourself with him...
...like he's enjoying himself
with you....
That's what l do.
l'm in it for the ''endolphin'' rush.
Endorphin.
Whatever.
Good morning, L.A. /t's burnt toast
and coffee time, 7.:30 a.m.
Jack?
-Morning.
-Hey, babe!
Oh, excuse me, officer.
Would you like to see my l.D.?
l've seen it.
Well, just hold that thought.
Hold it between your knees.
-Or would you join me?
-No, l'm on duty.
Be right out.
l saw someone you know last night.
Oh, yeah? Who?
Evelyn. Evelyn Ames.
Oh, yeah.
-Where'd you see her?
-On the set. She's in this movie.
How's it going?
Great, now that my relaxation levels
have stabilized.
-l don't know how you put up with them.
-Neither do l.
-l would've quit.
-You can't quit.
lf you quit, no one will hire
you again. l like working, so....
l like Evelyn.
-Yeah, l do too.
-Yeah, she told me.
She told you?
She told me you fucked her Saturday.
Saturday afternoon.
-Jesus, here we go.
-No, here you go.
Straight from her Saturday
afternoon to me that night!
-You have exclusive rights?
-What about moderation and discretion?
As far as discretion goes, what were
you and Evelyn doing, comparing notes?
No. She just told me
she fucked you on Saturday.
She marches up to you and blows her
wad? Or did you nose it out of her?
She said she was in it for the
endorphins. Sorry, the ''endolphins.''
You said you loved me.
l meant it at the time.
What is it, a viral love?
A 24-hour thing?
Apparently Evelyn smells like
Catalina too. Must be going around.
l just got out of a drug clinic
and you manipulate me?
-Give me a break, we just met!
-That's what l said to you!
We should stop this. lt's ridiculous.
l do not like this side of you.
l'm not a box with sides.
This is it! One side fits all!
You are so competitive!
-You're not?
-No, l'm not.
You're just a reaction to me?
You got this far by
not being competitive?
That's not competitive.
That's ambition and talent.
lf you do say so yourself!
This is a jealous tantrum!
l am not jealous!
l am humiliated! How could you fuck
us both on the same day?
What bothers you? That it was
the same day or that it was Evelyn?
lt's not that you fuck around a lot.
lt's that you lie about it.
Could've told the truth, fucked
them all, had the cigarette with me.
That is such bullshit!
Women say, '' lt's not the fact that
you left. lt's the way you did it.''
'' lt's not that you fuck around,
but you lie.''
You are all so full of shit!
lt is the fact that l fuck around...
...and it is the fact
that l will leave!
l have to stop this with you.
-Are we breaking up?
-We can't. We were never together.
-You're acting like a wife.
-Better than acting like a whore!
You can't judge me.
You were in a drug clinic.
Where you belong, Mr. Pothead.
Mr. Vodka, Mr. Bedroom Eyes.
You're a virgin? You weren't
hard to convince the first night.
l thought we didn't do anything.
l lied.
You were more fun
when you were loaded!
And Public Domain
was a piece of shit!
Relax, they're blanks. Asshole.
Hi, Ma.
l was just looking for some aspirin.
Did you find it?
Yep.
Good.
Why are you still wearing
your costume?
l was in a hurry.
l have some news.
What?
You dreamt l lost some weight?
Endorsed a line of clothing?
Don't be fresh, dear.
Don't you have looping this morning?
Shit!
How do you expect to get anywhere in
this business if you don't show up?
Dear?
l have something...
...inevitable to tell you.
l don't want you to be angry
with me for having predicted it.
What?
Your beloved business manager,
Marty Weiner...
...the man you stayed with,
the one l begged you to leave....
-Mom?
-Yes, darling?
The news?
l know.
l don't want to say. l know how upset
you'll be. l know how upset l was.
Marty Weiner has disappeared.
Disappeared?
The police called to say he is
nowhere to be found...
...and neither is his clients' money.
Meaning what, that l have no money?
-l don't know.
-Can't they find him? Can't l sue him?
l contacted your stepfather's lawyer,
Samuel Stone.
He's terrific. He's on it.
Oh, that's perfect. Just perfect.
Thank God l got sober so l'm hyper-
conscious for these humiliations!
Shit.
Dear, it's no good
feeling sorry for yourself.
You're gonna have to overcome
these difficulties.
You might as well do it
with some style.
You could easily make an enormous
amount of money if you'd only sing.
You have a God-given talent
and you just throw it away.
You could be much bigger than Madonna.
She hasn't got half your voice.
You'd have to stop smoking. You could
make an album. l'd produce it.
l'm getting out of the business.
lf l don't, l'll never have any kind
of a chance at having a normal life.
Let's take this one thing at a time.
First, everyone is always getting out
of the business.
And B: You are just like me.
Some days l wake up--
Will you please stop telling me
how to run my life...
...for a couple of minutes?
lsn't it enough that you were right?
You feel sorry for yourself for having
a monster of a mother like me.
Everything about you says,
''See what you did?''
l never said ''monster.''
You don't say it, but you feel it.
Somehow you lay the entire blame
for your drug-taking on me.
l do not. l do not, Mother.
l took the drugs, nobody made me.
Go ahead and say it.
You think l'm an alcoholic.
Okay.
l think you're an alcoholic.
Maybe l was an alcoholic
when you were a teenager...
...but l had a breakdown when my
marriage failed and l lost my money.
That's when l started taking drugs.
l got over it. Now l just
drink like an lrish person.
You drink to relax.
You just enjoy your wine.
l know, you've told me.
You don't want me to be a singer.
You're the singer.
You're the performer.
l can't possibly compete with you.
What if somebody won?
You want me to do well...
...just not better than you.
You are jealous because l can drink
and you can't take drugs any longer.
-l can handle it and you can't.
-Handle it? How do you handle it?
My drinking does not
interfere with my work.
l wish my mother had been as concerned
about me when l was a little girl!
Will you tell me what awful thing
l did to you when you were a child?
-You want to know?
-Tell me!
Fine. From the time l was 9
you gave me sleeping pills!
lt was over-the-counter medication.
-You couldn't sleep!
-You don't give kids sleeping pills.
They were not sleeping pills!
lt was store-bought and it was
perfectly safe!
And don't blame me
for your drug-taking!
l do not blame my mother
for my misfortunes or for my drinking.
You don't admit you drink!
How can you blame her
for something you don't even do!
Remember my 1 7th birthday party
when you lifted your skirt up...
-...in front of--
-l did not lift my skirt!
lt twirled up!
You only remember the bad stuff.
What about the big band l got to play?
Do you remember that? No!
You only remember that my skirt
accidentally twirled up!
And you weren't wearing underwear.
Well....
Dear, l am sorry if you think
l hurt you.
Everything l did,
l did out of love for you.
l might've done wrong sometimes.
How can you do everything right?
Can we--? Let's just stop.
l made some mistakes, but l'm human.
-Where are you going?
-To cut an album.
l'm gonna go have
some fibroid tumours removed.
l'm going to fucking loop.
l'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
-l thought l was late.
-No.
We didn't expect you for half an hour.
Oh, well, so, is it okay now?
Yeah, it's okay now.
Victor, Miss Vale is here.
Would you put up her reels now, please?
Wasn't that simple?
Oh, excuse me. Suzanne, this is
our editor, Phil Hartley...
...and sound editor, Elliot Morse.
Ready, Lowell.
Thank you. Shall we begin?
Could l have some coke--
--a-cola? Please.
-Could you get Suzanne a Coke, please?
-Sure.
You're better in the film
than you deserve to be.
Good. l mean, thank you.
l'm sorry l was such a nightmare.
You seem better now.
Really? No, l don't.
-Better because you're sober--
-Worse because l'm sober.
Yes, but worse in a good way.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
We have more spirit
and resources than you.
All it'll cost us is money.
There isn't enough mommy in the world
to further your cause.
Shit.
That's as good as it got all day.
We never got a full take after that.
l know. l'm sorry.
Don't be sorry, just fix it.
What?
Okay, let's try one.
Could l get a level from you, please?
There isn't enough money in the world
to further your cause.
Bring it down a little.
Can you try again, please?
-Good.
-Okay, let's do it.
Can l do another?
l have to do it one more time.
Let's look at that.
Perfect.
Will you guys take--?
Take five minutes, will you, please?
Thank you.
What could possibly be the matter?
You've gone back and corrected
the past, at least in your work.
What could be a better metaphor?
lt couldn't be something l said.
Nothing you say to me is as horrible
as what l say to myself.
And at least it's outside my head
where l can deal with it.
You've had it too easy
and you don't know it.
No, no. l do know it.
You're not gonna get
a lot of sympathy.
People would give their right arm
to lead the kind of life you lead.
l know, but the trouble is,
l can't feel my life.
l can't feel it. l see it all
around me and l know...
...that so much of it is good.
But l just take it the wrong way.
lt's like this thing...
...with my mother. l know she does
all this stuff because she loves me...
...but l just can't believe it.
And other stuff.
l don't know about your mother.
Maybe she'll stop mothering you
when you grow up.
-You don't know my mother.
-l don't.
l know you can make
a mother out of anybody.
Look, your mother did it to you,
and her mother did it to her...
...and back all the way to Eve.
At some point, you stop it and say:
'' Fuck it. l start with me.''
Did you just make that up?
l was working on it before you came.
lf you were half an hour later...
...it would have been better.
lt's pretty good as it is.
lt sounds like movie dialogue.
That's me. l don't want life to
imitate art, l want life to be art.
Look.
Look at that.
See what you can do?
You weren't even conscious then,
for chrissake.
lmagine what you could do now.
Maybe l should just...
...go back to the clinic?
Growing up isn't like in a movie...
...where you have a realization
and life changes.
ln life, you have a realization and
your life changes a month or so later.
So l just have to wait a month?
lt depends on the realization.
Some of them you only wait
a couple weeks.
Look...
...you're better here coping
than in a clinic giving up.
You're gonna be out here
eventually coping anyway.
So why don't you start now?
Anyway...
...you can't go to the hospital.
l've got a job for you.
You wouldn't be ashamed
to work with me again?
lt doesn't start for a few months,
so you have time for realizations.
Grow up. Leave your mother.
Thank you, God.
What happened?
Lady plowed into a tree.
Where's the lady? ls she all right?
-Who are you?
-l'm her daughter.
She hit her head.
She's at Canyon Medical Centre.
Look, l'm afraid we had to book her
for driving under the influence.
Thank you.
May l help you?
Miss Vale. Your mother's getting
patched up. l'll take you to her.
l'm afraid the press has been alerted
to your mother's presence here...
-...and her arrest.
-Oh, great.
Doctor, this is Miss Mann's daughter.
Your mom's fine. lt's a slight
contusion. A superficial wound.
-Can l see her?
-Yeah. Sure, sure.
She's more frightened than anything.
There she is, my other monster.
l can't seem to keep you two out
of the hospital lately.
She's fine.
She just bumped her head is all.
She was worried about you.
She got into her car and backed
up a tree.
Why am l in this family?
l got a wino daughter
and a doped-up granddaughter.
Oh, sure. '' Cry all you want. You'll
pee less,'' as my grandma used to say.
l swear. l don't know where
you get it from. But you!
You're just spoiled.
You've thrown everything away.
l told you not to bring her
up that way. Would you listen?
Don't run to me now.
l got my hands full with Grandpa.
Oh, shut up, Grandma.
-l beg your pardon?
-l should think you would.
lf you'd washed her mouth out
with soap when she was little--
l'm simply suggesting that we all
try to enjoy each other...
...without having to assign blame.
Listen to Miss Snooty Britches,
''assign blame.''
Come on!
-What're you doing?
-Moving you to the waiting room.
No need to shove! l'm going!
You need a good pop on the butt
like l used to give your mother!
Yap, yap, yap, yap.
lf l thought l made you feel
like that, l'd kill myself.
Don't say that, even in jest.
Particularly in a hospital,
people might take it wrong.
l suppose she means well.
She sounds like the voice in your head
that tells you you can't do anything.
lt's true, isn't it?
Where'd you go to?
Looping. But l shouldn't have
left like that. l'm sorry.
You don't really think l don't
want you to do well?
No, Ma.
And you were right about that guy.
l'm right about your doing
that music video too.
Just wait and see. That's where
your big success will be.
lt's blood.
Blood on my wig, on my clothes.
All my makeup's come off.
Do l have any eyebrows left?
Some, l think.
They're not all rubbed off.
-l hate not having eyebrows.
-l know.
Since the studio shaved them,
they never grew back.
Come on, let's put
some makeup on you now.
Makeup?
Are you less mad at me?
l've always been
less mad at you, Mama.
Remember when l was little, you'd
write notes to the school saying:
'' Please excuse Suzanne
from morning classes.
She has insomnia
and needs to get some sleep.''
When you were sick,
l'd sing you that little song.
Little drops of water
Little grains of sand
Make the mighty ocean
And the pleasant land
You know, dear?
l think l'm....
l think l'm sort of...
...jealous of you.
And that is because, well...
...it being your turn and all.
l think l find it tough to face...
...that mine is almost up.
lt's real important to enjoy
your turn.
And it would help me a lot
if l knew...
...that one of us enjoyed our youth.
Let me see my mirror.
Oh, dear.
Look at this.
l don't mind getting old.
l never thought l'd live this long.
What l do mind is looking old.
My eyebrow pencil, okay?
Here.
You know, it's in my will...
...that they don't bury me
without eyebrows.
l do not go in the ground
without them.
l know.
Should l have liposuction?
Like under here?
There's press out there, Mama.
l figured. The Enquirer.
The Star. Variety.
'' Doris Mann in drunken brawl
with tree.''
'' Doris Mann...
...still distraught over divorce
from Tony Vale 25 years ago...
...attempts suicide with lethal oak.''
How do l look?
Not bad for an old-timer, huh?
l'll say.
Hand me a coat.
'' Never let them see you ache.''
That's what Mr. Mayer used to say.
Or was it ''ass''?
'' Never let them see your ass.''
Anyway, you know what my mother
said to me yesterday?
She said that l put on airs.
That l use big words like
''gesture'' and ''devastate.''
l don't think they're so big, do you?
What am l supposed to do, sound like
a hick just to make her happy?
And the farmer hauled
Another load away
Well, compared to the end of the world.
Let's go get them, baby.
Seems like it takes a crisis
to bring us together lately.
Like war buddies.
Sid speaks!
Don't laugh, dear.
The man is also a dynamo in bed.
Still waters, you know.
My scarf. Where's my--?
Oh, l'm wearing it.
-We should get a family rate here.
-At least.
She seems to be feeling a lot better.
We're designed more for public
than for private.
Did you ever get my flowers?
-You're the guy!
-l pumped your stomach.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, l'm really--
Well, thanks for the flowers
and everything.
How you doing with the drugs?
l want to do them all the time.
That's not unusual.
lt sometimes never goes away.
How you talk.
But have you done any?
Almost.
Sometimes l want to so bad l have
to put my head down till it passes.
l just go to an AA meeting.
ln fact...
...l should.
Would you like to go to a movie
with me sometime?
Okay. We could go see
Valley of the Dolls.
We can say fate brought us together.
Fate and too many painkillers.
Always my favourite combination.
Thanks.
But it can't be a ''date'' date.
-Why not?
-Because....
Because l'm not...
...ready.
Oh, okay.
l understand that.
l'll wait.
What are your plans for the future?
To go on drinking.
We're gonna try one.
Please don't go over your marks.
Let's go to number one, please.
Let's clang the bell, please.
-Can we watch from here?
-No, they're working here.
l want you to see it.
l'll see it.
Marker.
Pull back them dark...
...and dusty drapes
Let in some light
Here, bellboy, come and get my trunk
'Cause /'m leavin' here tonight
Well, /'ve packed my bags
And /'ve paid my bill
And /'m turnin' in my key
And if those sad souls...
... down in the lobby...
...ask for me
Just tell 'em
/'m checking out...
... of this Heartbreak Hotel
/ ain't gonna live on
Lonely Street no more
No more.
/'ve found a new love
And a new place to dwell
Where teardrops
Ain't soaking the floor
So take down my suitcase
And hand me my hat
/'m going...
... from sleazy to swell
Give that desk clerk a dime
And you can just tell him
That /'m checkin' out...
... of this Heartbreak Hotel
Well, you can give that sad bellhop
My bebop blues guitar
'Cause /'m only gonna sing
Them sweet songs from now on
And you can tell that ol' bartender
He might as well close down the bar
'Cause chugaluggin' Sally's
Packed and gone
Through that grey windowpane
/t always looked like rain
But there's sunshine...
... outside, / can tell
Open up that door
/'m leavin' and / won't
Be back no more
/'m checkin' out...
... of this Heartbreak Hotel
Checkin' out...
... of this Heartbreak...
...Hotel
Cut! Print!
End mark!
/'m checkin' out...
... of this Heartbreak Hotel
/ ain't gonna live on
Lonely Street no more
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org