Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I hate surprises.
Yeah?
Yes.
You didn't mind when
I surprised you with my promotion.
That wasn't a surprise, that was earned
by my genius husband.
You see, I tought you really
like me for my body.
I do like to feel your body.
What are we doing here?
Surprise.
I don't understand, what is it?
It's a house.
Yes, yes, I can see that, thank you.
Also known as a home, sanctuary, dwelling.
Yeah.
Or if you like,
you could just call it ours.
Ours?
Uh-huh.
Where were we get the money, I mean,
how do we get into something like this?
Oh, well..
Maybe with the.. key.
Oh my god, oh my god,
are you kidding?
It's a classic.
1920's, good frame,
3 bedroom..
And the old owners even left us
a brand new swing set out back.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you too.
Let's go home.
Mommy!
Uh?
When's daddy coming home?
What, baby?
Uh... Today, baby.
It was just an overnight trip.
Why can't he take us?
Because it was work and we couldn't go..
But how about a "Good morning, Mommy".
Nice to see you.
Good morning, Mommy.
Mom, you gotta get dressed.
Sweety, we got plenty of time.
We're gonna be late for school.
Oh, no, we're not gonna be late for school..
Bridgette, are you okay with this spelling words?
Yes, Mom.
Hey, hey, hey,
don't forget your lunchs.
Come on, Megan.
I am.
This isn't dirty.
Hey, girl! What's going on?
I can't believe it's Thursday already.
Tell me about it, I have no idea
where this we planned.
God, I wish you were here..
I'm having the hardest time trying
to pick up my dress for tonight.
What about you guys?
You have any big plans for the weekend?
What, besides jetting off to Acupulco?
No.
Yeah, right.
Okay, I gotta go.
I gotta figure out what
I'm doing with my life right now.
Oh, yeah? What's his name?
His name, well, the name is
really bad, it's Harry..
But you never know, he could be the one.
You have one new message.
First new message.
Linda, listen,
I need to tell you something..
I meant what I said in front
of that girls the other night and..
I just...
I just want you to know that.
And..
Please remember it.
Oh, damn it, someone's calling..
Hold on.
Is that you?
End of messages.
If you leave a message,
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Hey, it's me, uh, I got your message,
I don't know when you left it, but um..
Just, uh, call me when you get mine, okay?
Bye.
Mrs. Hanson?
Yes.
Linda Hanson?
Uh-huh.
I'm Sheriff Reilly.
Yes.
I'm, uh, sorry to tell you this.
Your husband, Jim..
Yeah.
Was in a car accident.
He died on the scene.
When?
Yesterday.
No! No, it's impossible because I just, uh..
I just heard his voice on
the answering machine, so..
Well, I'm sorry, Ma'am.
We, uh, we couldn't get to you any sooner..
The other driver was in a truck..
Semi-- Pretty certain it was instantaneous..
He was on the highway, mile mark for 220.
Ma'am? Mrs. Hanson? Ma'am?
Ma'am, is there anything that I can do?
Can I call someone for you?
Let me leave you my card, okay?
If you have any questions, you just call me.
What's wrong, Mommy?
Mommy?
What's wrong?
It's about daddy.
Yeah?
Yeah.
He's had a very bad accident.
What kind of accident?
When is he coming home?
Is he okay?
No baby, he's not.
Well, I'm impressed.
You guys got this far all by yourself?
Yeah.
It's really amazing.
Hey, it's Annie, leave a message after beep,
and I promise I'll get right back to you.
Hey Annie, it's me..
Could you please call me as soon
as you get this message? Thank you.
Wow, you girls are doing so great.
Daddy's better our puzzle.
He was going to help us.
I think I finally got them to sleep.
Oh, I should say good night.
No, don't do that, they just fell asleep, leave it.
I was thinking about, um,
everything we need to get done.
Tomorrow we should probably start
looking into funeral arrangements.
And then, um, you know, just see
where you are in terms of insurance.
I'm not ready for that, Ma.
Nobody is ready for any of this, dear.
But you'll be surprise at how
strong you're gonna be..
You know, when I lost your dad..
I can't stop thinking about our serving platter.
What serving platter?
You know, the big one on the top shove.
The one that his folks gave us.
I can't reach that.
Jim, Jim does that for me.
Nobody expect you could get everything
done in the first few days, dear.
I-- I'm pretty tired.
I'm gonna go lie down in the dent.
I'll get some sheets out of the closet.
I'll be right up here if you need me, dear.
Mom?
Jim.
What's wrong?
I don't know.. I just-- I just had..
This is really strange just to..
What? What is it?
Ok, I guess it's nothing,
it's nothing, it's nothing..
Mom, we're late.
Three times and we'll get detention.
You know how's a good way to start the day?
How about, "Good morning, Mommy!"
Good morning.
All right, I gotta get going,
it's a Monday morning meeting.
Hugs for everybody.
All right, I gotta get going.
I need to-- train this new assistant manager.
Packed their lunches, ready to go.
Are you ok to-- take them to school?
Uh-hum.
Okay.
You girls have fun at school now.
Ok, bye, daddy.
Yes.
Hey, you guys don't forget your lunch--
Come on, Megan, get out of the car!
I'm coming!
You have no messages.
Shit!
That was quite a stop there.
Yeah, I was just, uh, I was totally..
Yes, I just-- I got com-
Um, I just-
I was totally distracted.
Let's just take it a little easy out there, huh?
Sure.
We don't want anyone
getting hurt now, do we?
I'm trying to figure out,
should I call him, I mean..
I really feel like I wanna
call him but don't it sound like..
I think that's breaking the rule.
You think it's better, if I just wait?
What?
Did we talked yesterday?
Yeah, we talk everyday.
No, I mean, um..
Did I leave you a message?
I don't think so, why?
Wait a minute, hang on,
I'm the one with the crisis, okay?
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah.
Everything's cool with you and Jim?
Yeah, everything is exactly the same.
So, how was everybody's day?
Mine was okay.
Kinda boring.
Yeah, kinda boring.
Boring, huh?
Jim?
Lithium.
Here she is.
Hi, honey.
Did you get some rest?
What's going on?
Hey, how are you feeling, but..
Why don't you go upstairs
and let's get some clothes.
Are you going to go upstairs and get dressed?
Where are the girls?
The girls are fine, dear.
The girls are fine, honey.
Don't worry about the girls.
This isn't right.
What is it?
No, everything's fine, you need to go
upstairs and get more sleep?
No! No, I don't need any more sleep,
and I don't need to wake up either.
Everything is going to be fine.
No mother, everything is not fine.
Something is really, really wrong.
Ok, all right.
He's not dead.
Hi, baby!
Hey! Hi!
Sorry I wasn't awake
when you guys got up.
Grandma said we had to let you sleep.
No, baby. You can always wake me up.
It's just a dream.
Swing me.
Yeah.
I think she's sad.
Oh, my god! Oh, my god, baby!
Baby, what happen to your face?
Baby, talk to me, how did you get this cut?
Who did this to you?
Did what?
The cuts! The cuts on your face!
There is no cuts, Mommy.
What are you talking about?
She's perfect,
like a beautiful princess.
Oh, god, come here, just hold on to me,
It's going to be ok, it's going to be ok.
Everything's going to be all right,
everything's going to be all right.
Mommy?
Yeah?
I wonder what it like when daddy died?
I don't know, baby.
I wasn't there.
So, how did you know he died then?
You all right?
What if this is a mistake?
What do you mean, "a mistake"?
People just don't day one day and
they're okay the next day, that's all.
It's not a mistake.
Oh, Ok, Mum, did you see inside the cascade?
No, I didn't see,
but it doesn't..
Okay, Mum, something is seriously
fucked up with the situation.
Linda, we need to go in the church now.
Come on, dear.
No, you need to take the kids inside.
Why don't you come inside with us..
Just take the kids inside!
Go ahead, go ahead with the kids.
Linda? Linda?
Hello, Mrs. Hanson.
Ow, I just want you to know
that everything's on schedule.
I need you to open the cascade.
No, no, no.
I don't think that would be a very good idea.
Open up the cascade, god damn it!
Open it up, open it up!
Mrs. Hanson!
I beg you to let this go.
Don't do this to me.
Mrs. Hanson.
What kind of problem?
Jim left this world,
a beloved person.
His friends spoke about his kindness..
His laugh, his graciousness, his helpfulness and
consideration to everyone around him
But his greatest devotion
was to his family.
His girls as he like to refer to them.
His lovely wife, Linda..
The precious daughters, Megan and Bridgette...
Mom?
What?
Who's that?
Who?
Her, that woman.
I don't know, dear.
Linda?
It's ok, It's ok.
Wait! No, please wait, wait!
I'm sorry.
Stop.
How do you know my husband?
I just thought that after we talked.
We talked?
Yeah, yesterday.
Yesterday?
You don't remember?
No!
I've never met you before in my life!
I'll just gonna go, Ok.
Please talk to me!
You have all my sympathies,
and your girls too.
Who are you?
Please, don't..
Dr. Norman Roth.
Dr. Norman Roth!
Mommy?
Hey, why don't you girls go downstairs
and visit with Grandma and Aunt Annie.
No!
I'm sure it'll be fun.
What are you looking for, Mommy?
I'm in need of someone to talk to, baby.
Why don't you talk to us?
Baby, I love talking to you, but this is--
this is grown up talking..
Mommy needs some help, okay?
Come on, baby, please go downstairs.
Thank you, baby. Thank you for being so good.
You've reach the offices of Dr. Norman Roth..
We are currently closed.
Our office hours are: Monday to Friday 9 am to 5.30 pm.
Do you guys want some tea or coffee or anything,
can I get you something?
Maybe we all just think about
getting the girls to sleep, huh?
Oh, yes.
Been a long couple of days.
Hum... Yes, it does.
Allright, girls.
Come on with Auntie Annie, we're gonna go upstairs
and we'll get your jamas on, okay?
Can I read you a story?
Yeah?
Come in.
Good evening, Mrs. Quinn.
Hi there, Annie.
Hello Linda.
Hello.
I'm Dr. Roth, remember?
No, I don't, I--
Annie?
Okay, girls, let's go upstairs.
Mom, what's going on?
Honey, please don't be angry,
please don't be angry with us.
Wait a second, Annie!
Annie, what are you doing?
Linda, your family is worried about you,
you family cares about you.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Annie? Annie?
What else could we do?
What?
Just tell us what happened to Bridgette's face!
Mom, I don't know what happened to Bridgette..
You see, that's what I mean!
I would never do anything to hurt my child!
Get away from me!
Mommy is sorry!
Mommy is very sorry!
Sir, sir, sir!
Obviously she's never been corrected before..
Her husband was in a fatal
car crash on Wednesday.
I told her about it on Thursday.
Wou, wou, wou, wou,
hold on.
Wednesday?
That's strange, she showed up
in my office on Tuesday.
Claiming he was already dead or..
He's going to be..
She said he was going to die, before the accident?
Yeah.
You sure it was an accident?
Hello, Linda.
Please don't do this,
I just wanna go home to my girls.
Please don't do this.
Please, Sir.
Just let me go home to my girls.
We'll have time to talk about that tomorrow.
Everything's going to be just fine.
Jim?
What?
You're ok?
Come on, Linda. You're going to get yourself soaked.
Just give me a minute,
just one moment.
I can hear your heart beating
and it feel so good.
Hey, hey, hey,
hold on.
Everything's going to be fine.
Come on.
You promise?
I promise.
What is it, honey?
Tell me what's going on.
I don't really know how to explain it.
I gotta get going, I gotta go to work.
Just give me a minute, just one more minute.
Girls?
Good morning, Mommy.
Morning.
Oh.. Oh, you are so beautiful,
did you know?
Beautiful, you are both beautiful.
I need for you to be very,
very careful today, okay?
No playing with scissors,
I don't want you to running around.
Ma'am, you're holding up the line.
Sit quite, promise me.
Ma'am!
Just give me a second.
Just promise me, you promise?
I promise.
Baby, you are going to promise me too, okay?
All right.
Ok, here you go, you guys be good.
Ma'am, come on, please.
Mrs. Stevenson?
Steven...
Can I help you?
I'm Linda Hanson.
Hello, Linda. I'm Dr. Roth.
Do you know me?
Should I?
I wake up, and his dead,
I wake up, and his alive.
Different things around me
all the time that I can't explain..
Things that I've done.
People talking to me.
People who know me, but I have never met.
People like me?
Yes.
Seems a little complicated.
Tell me about it.
What about the Lithium bottle?
I don't know, it's, it's,
I don't know, I misplaced it somewhere.
Look! I can't explain it,
but I tought if somebody was trying to..
Trying to, drug you?
Uhum.
Why and who?
I don't know, you tell me.
I didn't prescribe it.
But your name was on the bottle.
Why do you think I came here?
To get some help.
Obviously, you're dealing
with some inconsistencies.
I wake up every morning to find
my husband has died again..
I think that goes just
a little beyond inconsistent.
How do you feel..
During the times of his dead?
What?
I mean, what kind of
emotions run trough you?
Is it sorrow, resentment, relief?
What are you saying?
That's a pretty common day dream
to imagine people being death.
I'm not day-dreaming, okay?
I wake up and he is dead.
Except for today.
Do you have any history of
mental illness in your family?
No.
What about yourself,
any episodes of psychosis? Memory lost?
Judgment lapses?
I don't want him dead!
It was a car accident.
Well, it's not a crime imagining it.
I'm not imagining it.
He's dead!
Well, it is a little odd..
But the prescription was far that lift you..
Why?
Because, that's probably the
best thing for you right now.
It'll help you cope.
Do you think you can make
it in to see me here tomorrow?
Hey, look who's here!
Hey, Bob. Is Jim here?
Yeah, how come you don't
come by to anymore?
Hi.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
What's going on?
I know I've been acting strange,
but something wrong..
There's something very wrong.
What is it? The girls?
No, no, no, they're fine,
at least, for now.
Can we just go somewhere?
Just us, let's just take the girls.. Just go..
I can't go anywhere,
I have to work.
Please, I really need you, can we just.
I have to go to the sales meeting.
Excuse me. Jim, we're waiting for you.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm Claire Francis,
you must be Jim's wife.
Yeah, Linda.
I've seen your pictures,
it's nice to meet you.
Claire is our new assistant manager.
Your husband has been really
helpful for the last few weeks.
Guys, we're starting.
Excuse me.
We can talk about this later.
Girls?
Hurry, the laundry is outside, grab it!
Hurry!
I'll meet you guys outside, okay?
Bridgette, no, Bridgette!
Bridgette, no!
Baby, I'm right here,
I'm right here.
Megan, go get me some towels, please.
Mommy?
I got you.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, baby.
She's still bleeding, Mommy.
Somebody, somebody, please!
I'm Dr. Norman, can you tell me what happened?
Yes, she went through the glass door.
Any allergies that should we know about?
Cordim, cordim.
Okay, just put her in 14 please.
Ma'am, I'm going to need you to wait out here.
No, ma'am, we'll take care of her..
Everything is going to be fine.
It's going to be okay, baby.
Is she okay?
Yeah, they just took her in.
You all right?
Yes.
She was running out to get the laundry,
and she was, she just went through the glass window.
What are you doing, Mommy?
We are going to forget about Mary's for a while.
Do you feel any better?
Does she going to have that
ugly scars forever?
I don't want any talk about scars.
I don't care what anyone tells you, okay?
Do you understand?
Because you are beautiful.
Like a princess?
Yeah, like a princess.
My two princesses.
I tought you're gonna put up stickers?
I did.
I don't know, maybe,
maybe I thought I did.
Christ, Linda.
What? Are you blaming me for this now?
I've asked your mother to
come and stay while I'm gone.
What? Why?
Just to help, you know?
I don't need any help.
Help take care of the kids.
Look, you can take a break.
You know,
some time for yourself.
For what? Time for myself for what?
So I could stop acting like a crazy person?
What are you talking about, I never said..
You are not separating me from my kids.
I'm a good Mom.
Ok. Uhm.
Thursday. I discover that Jim died.
Monday. Jim alive.
Funeral's on.. Saturday!
What else..
Lithium, it's on Saturday.
Except for today.
Meet Dr. Roth on Tuesday.
Saturday... Dr. Roth.
Bridgette's cut happened on..
Bridgette! Bridgette!
Mommy?
Tuesday
.. still open in Wednesday.. Wednesday..
You have one new message.
When?
Yesterday.
Oh, God.
Jim dies on Wednesday.
What are you doing?
Jim, don't go on this trip, please.
I have to, I've waited all the
year for this interview.
Besides, it could be good for us,
you know.
Take a break from each other.
Well, it might be a bigger break
than need broken for.
What if something happens to you?
Something could happen to me
on my way home from work.
Should I stop working?
You want me to beg?
I will beg, please, just don't go,
you have a children and you have a family.
Why are you saying that?
You think I've forgotten that?
No, I haven't..
Because I haven't!
I realised that,
I didn't say that you forgot..
All right, good.
Just listen to me.
Just do me one favor..
If tomorrow is Wednesday,
just please, wake me up before you leave?
If tomorrow is Wednesday?
Just... I know it sounds crazy.
Just, please, wake me up, okay?
Promise me!
I promise.
Good.
Okay.
Oh, that guest bed is just awful.
Mom.
That's why you stayed over..
You forget I was here?
No, no, no, I remember,
I remember now..
Friday, friday, friday morning..
Friday morning!
This is Sunday and there's friday,
I don't remember. Shit! Shit!
Are you all right?
Shit.
She appears, Claire Francis..
Miss Claire, Miss Claire.
We talked?
We had yesterday,
you don't remember?
Mom, I have to go.
What?
You need to be with the girls,
you had the shock of your life yesterday.
Tell me about it.
Is there something we should
be talking about?
Something involving my husband?
I've told you.
I think you just did.
He was going to cheat on me.
What?
Wait a minute, how did you know,
how did you find out?
I talked to her,
she told me everything.
When?
Today.
Oh, I'm sorry,
are you still in shock?
No.
The whole thing is bad, the accident,
the other woman, it's a mess..
I don't know if it's so bad.
Maybe it's supposed to happen.
What do you mean?
Even though he didn't do anything yet..
The damage that it would
have cost us, the girls..
Maybe it was enough what he was going to..
Are you listening to
what you are saying?
We were roommates, Annie.
We were roommates,
two girls...
And my roommate was a liar.
Well, as far as you mortgage, and your
daughter's education should all be taken care of..
You know, Linda.
I have to tell you,
the timing of all this.
'Timing'?
What do you mean, 'timing'?
Jim stopped and he see me on
Wednesday morning, right before..
Wednesday?
Yes.
And he seemed very anxious,
like he wasn't quite sure of things..
And he kept talking about you,
and the girls, and he said that..
No matter what happen,
he wanted to make sure you're all okay..
And then he tripled his death benefit.
I mean, it's on no problem.
The police reports all confirm
that it was an accident, so..
I'll just get this clear to the main office.
And, um, I should have a check for you very soon.
Nice view, huh?
Yes, very.
You have a family?
I have two daughters, but, um..
It's no big deal,
happens to a lot of people.
They drive by here, just like you did,
to see the houses by this beautiful lake..
Suddenly said to themselves:
What a great place to start over.
I moved here after my divorce.
Really?
Yeah, it's great.
It's like a whole new life.
Hello, I'm Dorothy Quinn.
I know.
Got it.
Hi, honey.
Hi, Mom.
One for you.
Cool!
Thank you, Mommy.
You're welcome.
You know how much
I love you, right?
Linda?
Yeah.
I don't want to upset you.
What is it, Mom?
I know this is very difficult, but...
I really do think we need to drive
out to the funeral home, dear.
I'll go with you.
Oh, it's done.
What?
I already made all the arrangements.
Oh.
When are you thinking
of having this..
The funeral is tomorrow, till Saturday.
Saturday?
Saturday.
That soon?
Yes, that soon.
You okay, Hon?
Hey, Mom.
Uhum?
If I let Jim die..
Is that the same thing as killing him?
Honey, Jim's already dead.
Good night, dear.
Hot Sunday.
All day long.
Hey, you want to go take
the girls out for a while?
You know, you guys should
spend some time together.
You can have some fun.
Yes, okay.
That's a good idea.
You girls want daddy to make you
some pancakes for breakfast?
Yeah!
Hello, Father.
Linda..
It's been a long time.
I'm scared, Father.
1632, a Dutch trading company
move off the coast of Carolina..
A hysterical woman claimed..
To have walked through the aftermath
of a terrible hurricane that haven't happen yet.
So, what happened?
They hung her for being a witch.
Two days later, the entire town was
wiped out by a force of hurricane.
It's awful.
Let's get ahead to the 20th century.
Boston, 1918.
At the height of the influence of epidermic.
A father told a friend he's been to the future..
He seen a grave of a two small children.
Oh, my God.
The autopsy showed that the
children were never infected.
He shot himself a week later.
Who are these people,
why did it happened?
You see..
History's full of unexplained phenomena..
Nobody knows why.
Some people tought, they suffered from
what the ancients called..
"Blasphomare Absence Fudas"
The dangers of the fatales.
The fatales?
Even spritiual.
People who've lost their belief..
They are like empty vessels.
They are more susceptible of having their life
taken over by a force whose bigger than themselves.
It's almost like a curse.
Or a miracle.
Yeah, but I don't believe in miracles.
Everyday, we're alive can be a miracle.
I doesn't feel that right, not for me.
Father..
Something bad is going to happen.
I need your help, I need your direction..
I need faith.
Faith, it's just believing something behind yourself..
Something you can't feel, or smell, or touch..
Like hope.. Or love..
I believe I've let that all go.
Maybe you should try and get it back again, huh?
But if it's too late?
It's never too late to realise
what's important in your life..
To fight for it.
I don't know what to fight for.
He was on the highway, mile mark for 220.
Mrs. Hanson?
Ma'am?
Who are these people?
Why did it happened?
History's full of unexplained phenomena.
Bridgette, no, Bridgette!
Nobody knows why.
Open it up!
Open it up! No!
Obviously, you're dealing
with some inconsistencies.
Dangers of the fatales.
I'm Claire Francis...
Your husband has been really
helpful for the last few days.
How do you feel during
the times of his dead?
We don't want anyone
getting hurt, do we?
If I let Jim die..
It's never too late..
Is that the same thing as killing him?
Inconsistencies.
.. the same thing as killing him.
You guys have a good time?
Yeah, yeah, we got a great time.
Good.
Let me help you with that.
Smell good.
Oh, good girls.
Nite.
Good night.
Hey, why don't you girls go give your
dad another hug and say thanks.
Okay, okay.
What's this all about?
Momma said to give you extra hugs.
Extra hugs?
Extra hugs and extra kisses.
Now off to bed,
go brush your teeth.
Hey, girls. Why don't you tell
daddy how much you love him.
Love you, daddy!
Me too!
Well, thank you, ladies.
Aren't you going to tell them?
Tell them what?
That you love them.
You do love them, don't you?
Of course I do.
Then tell them.
You girls know how
much I love you, right?
Huh? Right?
I love you more than anything
in the whole wide world.
Mom too.
More than anything?
I do love your Momma..
I love her very much.
Linda!
What are you doing out here?
Honey, let's go back inside.
How did we get here, Jim?
I miss you.
I miss us.
It's still an us, it's just different now,
that's all.
Why? Why is it different?
I don't know why!
What did you expect this to be like?
Just the way we used to be.
Linda, look at us. We're married, we got
a house, a mortgage, two kids.
Why do we have to talk about this now?
Why can't we just go inside?
Because we're running out of time!
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You wanna tell me something?
I had a dream you're going to die.
That was only a dream.
Everything's going to be fine.
Hello.
Annie, Annie what day is it today?
It's, um, it's Wednesday.
What's the matter?
Girls? Girls? Jim? Jim?!
Jim?
Oh, shit.
I took the girls to school,
I'll be back tomorrow.
Hi, this is Jim Hanson,
I can't get your call right now, but..
if you leave a message,
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Thanks for calling.
I should be able to take care
of this right away, no problem.
Thanks, Doug.
I just got to the room.
It's really nice.
I can't wait for you to get here.
Jim? Something wrong?
Yeah..
Sorry, I can't.. I can't do this..
Do what? The interview?
Us.
Jim...
Jim?
Pick up, pick up, Jim, pick up.
Hi, you've reached the Hanson residence..
You know what to do!
Listen, Linda..
I need to tell you something.
I meant what I said in front of
the girls the other night..
I just.. I want you to know that..
And.. Please remember it.
Damn it, someone's calling, hold on.
Is that you?
Linda?
Jim!
I love you, honey.
I need to tell you something.
It's all right, I know about her,
I know about Claire.
You do?
Yeah.
I have to explain it, but..
Honey, honey, honey, listen..
I thought that's what I wanted,
but I don't..
I want to make things better,
you know, between us..
Whatever it takes.
I see you, I see you,
I'm coming up right behind you.
You are?
I'm pulling over.
Thank you, thank you.
I can see you, honey.
Oh, no.
Jim, do you love me?
Do you trust me?
Of course I do.
Then turn around now.
What? I don't understand..
Turn it around!
Jim!
Are you okay? Jim?
Jim?
Baby, are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Baby, can you hear me?
Sorry, I dropped the phone.
I love you, let's go home.
Okay, hold on.
Jim! Jim! Get out of the car!
Jim! Get out of the car!
Jim!
Get out of the car!
Jim! Jim! Get out of the car!
Mommy, they're here!
Oh, no, maybe I must've have fallen asleep.
The moving truck is here.
I know, I heard.
You're healing so nicely.
Why don't you guys go downstairs,
I'll be there in a second, okay?
Okay.
Faith is just believing something
behind yourself.. like hope, or love.
It's never too late to realise
what's important in your life..
To fight for it.
I don't know what to fight for.
Everyday we're alive, can be a miracle.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org