Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Are you alone?.
- Yeah.
- Don't fuck with me, man.
- I swear to God, don't fuck with me.
- I'm not, man. I'm being straight.
Nobody knows I'm here,
nobody knows you're here.
You recording this?.
Do you want me to?.
You got a recorder?.
No.
Then I don't want you to record it.
Okay.
All right, look, you could just...
You just talk, all right?.
Tell me anything you wanna say,
I won't interrupt you. Say whatever.
So you can get my story, right?.
So you can fuck me.
- Turn my name to shit, is that it?.
- Hey, Sandy. You called me.
I'm not a priest, I'm a writer.
I came down here to freeze my ass off
sitting in this fucking car. I did my part.
I gotta get this out of me.
- I gotta get this out.
- What?.
We're all dirty.
We sold our shields off,
highest bidder, murder for hire.
Stole drugs off dead men, planted shit...
...beat suspects.
We robbed and...
We condemned four of our own to die.
- What are you talking about?.
- Washington Heights.
We sent them into a slaughter.
- Who?. Who, Sandy?. Who sent those men?.
- I fucking told you, no names!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can't undo it now.
There's no atoning.
I'm gonna burn, man.
I'm gonna fucking burn.
No, no, no. No, this is-
We can work this out, okay?.
- No, no, no.
- Look, I'm gonna call my city desk.
All right?. I'm gonna call my editor.
All right?.
To save space for your story, okay?.
Your story.
Okay?.
Becoming a cop...
...the respect that earned us...
...the pledge we took...
...to uphold something honest...
Being in the blue, wearing that shield...
...the pride that I felt...
...the fucking glory...
We let it all go out from under us.
I was a good man once.
Who is it?.
It's Kenny.
What does he want?.
I just got up.
How the fuck should I know?.
Jesus Christ.
We're about to get fucked.
He's dead. Jimmy, he's fucking dead.
Sandy fucking killed himself.
Shh. Come on.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...it is with sorrow
and a deep sense of regret...
...that I appear before you today.
At 10:30 p. m. last night...
...Officer Ruben Santiago of the
31 st Precinct in Washington Heights...
...took his own life.
Officer Santiago...
...along with the four officers slain
in Washington Heights...
...had formed an illicit criminal cabal.
Working in collusion
and under the aegis of the N.Y.P D...
...these officers undertook all manner
of criminal misdeed.
Investigators from Internal Affairs
have isolated the involvement...
Where the hell have you been?.
... of this rogue unit...
- ... to the deceased men.
- Yeah, we need to talk.
- No other officer in 31 st Precinct...
- Yeah, okay. Tonight.
- ... has been found culpable of...
- You be there.
...or in any way linked
to this criminal conspiracy.
Francis.
What the hell is going on here?.
- I can't talk, Pop, I gotta go.
- What the hell is going on here, Francis?.
How involved are you?.
Look at me.
Did you know what they were doing?.
I knew enough.
Dad, come on, man. All those years,
you never got jammed up?.
- It never came down on top of you?.
- No.
Because I kept my head up.
All I took was a check cut by the city.
That's all I took.
I didn't take any money.
I didn't take a fucking cent.
Then what?. What did you do?.
- I gotta go. I'm sorry.
- Francis, sit down. Let's talk.
- I'm here to help you, Franny.
- I can't do this now, Pop. I gotta go.
I gotta do this my way, all right?.
I'm sorry.
Happy New Year!
Happy fucking New Year!
Taxi!
Thanks.
Fuck!
Move, I'll break it off.
Who are you?.
Bragon, Carlos Bragon.
I'm a reporter, for chrissake!
- You know me, Tierney.
- Shut up, shut up!
You know me, Tierney. You know me.
Yeah, I know you, you fucking hack.
What the fuck are you doing following me?.
What do you want?.
I'm writing a story.
I got two versions,
I wanna run them by you.
First one goes like this:
Hero detective captures cop killer.
Kills him in self-defense.
Yeah, what else?.
The other one is key witness
in a cop-corruption case...
...dies mysteriously in the presence
of cops from the 31 st Precinct.
- Which one sounds better?.
- Whatever sells more papers, right?.
Yeah, I know cops from the 31
were there before you, Ray.
That's your brother's house, isn't it?.
Sources are telling me that Angel Tezo
was tortured and was executed.
He had half his teeth shoved down
to his belly, splinters in his throat.
- You carry a stick?.
- Keep pushing me, you're gonna find out.
I'm trying to help you. Be smart.
I can be writing a story
about Ray Tierney.
But I should be writing a story
about the 31.
You were there. Here's your opportunity
to set it straight right now.
I don't like my odds with you.
Last cop you talked to
blew his brains out in your car.
Last time I saw you, you were
feeding bullshit to the grand jury.
I was only sitting there
because of your hard-on to crucify cops.
I do. Because they were protecting
their own and burying the truth.
Don't talk to me about the truth. You got
no idea what it takes to do what we do.
- You weren't there.
- You wanna know what I know?.
I know you took a bullet in the face
during the raid.
I know Kareem Aldovise, a 19-year-old
kid, went off that roof and died.
Everybody knows that.
Yeah, and I know a witness
saw him surrender before they did it.
He had no priors, he had no gun.
You wanna bullshit the grand jury, fine.
Don't do it to me.
Well, in case you didn't hear, they cleared
us two years ago, okay?. Case closed.
So don't get in my face because you're
skeeved about losing your Pulitzer.
But you know what?.
I don't really think about it that much.
Wake up, all right?. Come on.
Jimmy!
Help.
Help me, Jimmy.
Hey, boss.
Where is he?.
Have you lost your fucking mind?.
Mayor goes on TV, moans the loss, gives us
a clean bill of health. What's the problem?.
I asked you point-blank, "Were you
involved in this?. " What did you say?.
I said what you wanted to hear.
- I wanted the fucking truth.
- What truth?.
Truth about the money we were getting?.
The dirty cops you preside over?.
You knew. All you cared about
was your promotion.
- I knew what was fucking going on?.
- Yeah.
I gave you room to get the job done.
If you took a little here...
...I wasn't looking.
But you crossed the line.
What, you think because you didn't
take an envelope, it absolves you?.
Silk hat, same pig.
Crimes down, collars up.
It's what you wanted.
End justifies the means, buddy boy.
Let me tell you something, Jimmy.
You think you can set Ray up for this?.
You are dead fucking wrong.
We took you in.
You were a fucking brother to us.
My sister's your wife, your family's my
family, and you jam us up like this?.
I jam you?. I saved you.
It's a lay-up, Fran.
Oh, yeah?. How's that, Jimmy?.
Run that by me.
- Ray sticks to the story, he's a hero.
- That's not gonna happen.
- You're gonna make this right, or I swear-
- Or what?.
What the fuck are you gonna do, Franny?.
You gonna burn down your own house?.
Blow up everything you worked for?.
All Ray's gotta do is walk into IAB...
...say what needs to be said,
end of fucking story.
- We go home, we go to sleep at night.
- You think this ends that simply?.
We all go to sleep at night. Let me tell you,
what we've done does not get forgiven.
Here we go with the
Sister Mary Margarets.
Someone says you're dirty, who cares?.
They say you're fucking corrupt.
Fuck them.
Do they know how these animals live?.
We tour the sewers, Franny!
I will not apologize for doing what I do.
I earn 65 grand a year.
Some fuck like Tezo wipes his ass
with that shit in a week.
We're in this together, Franny.
- What the fuck is that?.
- It's your cut. I've been keeping it for you.
Take the fucking money, Franny.
You were my brother, Jimmy.
Franny. Take-
Fuck.
Yeah, Tierney.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. IAB?.
Well, no, no,
but I thought I'd have some time.
Detective, let me start
by saying we're aware...
...of your outstanding service record...
...and we wanna thank you
for your role in solving this case.
We 're gonna make this as brief as possible,
gonna get you out of here.
We need a statement detailing your
participation in the incident on record.
Now, you declined to give a
statement at the scene of the shooting.
- Is that correct?
- That's right.
Mr. Tezo was tried and sentenced
in a bathroom in the Bronx.
But you're prepared to give us one now?
Far removed from a jury.
- Far removed from a judge.
- I'm gonna do my best.
Far removed from our basic rights
endowed on all men by our Constitution.
This march will commence at noon.
Can you explain how your investigation
led to the apprehension of Tezo?
- and end up on the steps
of the 31 st Precinct.
Angel Tezo was identified by
witnesses at the scene of the shooting.
I sought information
regarding his whereabouts...
...from a former confidential informant.
He directed me to the location in question
in Morrisania...
...and I followed that lead.
The reverend reiterated
that this planned march is about peace...
...and is not intended as a condemnation
of the entire N. Y.P.D.
His target: the 31st Precinct...
...and the officers involved in the
Angel Tezo killing.
The investigation is continuing.
- Now, did you pursue this lead alone?.
- No.
I called the task force.
I spoke to my colleague, Detective Miller.
I told him where I was going.
I requested backup, and he initiated that.
But you arrived on the location alone.
I arrived before the rest of the team, yes.
Okay.
Now, could you describe for us what
transpired at the location in question...
...leading up to you having to
discharge your weapon?.
Detective?.
This isn't gonna go how you want it to.
Excuse me?.
I know what you guys want me to say...
...but it's not gonna happen.
No one's looking for you to say anything
except your version of what happened.
- Really?.
- All we need is a full accounting...
...of what happened,
then we can go home.
Yeah, I know what you need.
But I can't give it to you,
because I didn't shoot him.
Are you aware that ballistics
has confirmed that the perp was killed...
...by three bullets fired from your gun
at close range?
I am.
But you maintain
that you didn't shoot him?
I do.
Could you elaborate on that?
No, I would not care to.
What are you saying, detective?
From here on out, nothing.
I respectfully refuse
to answer any further questions.
Are you denying that you
were involved in the Angel Tezo killing?
I respectfully refuse
to answer any more questions.
If you don't start answering,
this is gonna go bad.
We can do this all afternoon...
...but I have nothing more to say
in this matter.
This wasn't like Ray. He's not that guy.
He's a fucking good cop.
He's a good man.
He said something about Lonnie Mercer,
"Lonnie and I. "
I remember that they were close.
They were partners.
Lonnie Mercer, one of the officers
killed in the Washington Heights raid?
That's right.
What happened next?
I tried to revive Mr. Tezo.
I didn't know if he'd had a heart attack...
...or if he was still alive.
I tried to revive him.
I checked for a pulse,
I couldn't find a fucking pulse.
He looked pretty fucking dead.
So I did some fucking CPR.
After I tried to revive him,
I was still kneeling over the body.
That's when the shots went off.
Oh, fuck.
Who was shot?
- Mr. Tezo was shot?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he was shot. Yeah, he was shot.
Got what he fucking deserved.
Who shot Mr. Tezo?
I would've done the same thing myself.
Who shot Angel Tezo, Sergeant Egan?
Detective Tierney.
Detective Raymond Tierney?
Yes.
Listen, Frank...
...I know how this must feel,
and I wish I knew what to say.
But you should know that these officers
are all prepared to testify at a grand jury.
So what's critical now,
from here on out...
...is that we handle this thing quietly,
with as little incident as possible.
He's not capable of that.
I know my son. He's not capable of that.
Frank, we're gonna have to bring Ray in.
You okay?.
Hey.
I'm proud of you.
Call me when it's done.
They wanna take you in,
put "arrest pending " in the press tomorrow.
I'm sitting there on my ass,
watching this fucking testimony.
You believe that shit
that Jimmy's spinning?.
- You gonna tell me you believe that?.
- Of course not. That's not the point.
I told you to run everything through me
and that we would handle it.
And then you sit down
with the goddamn IAB...
...and don't give me a heads up?.
No fucking phone call?.
You don't talk to me, Ray.
I'm here. I'm telling you now, okay?.
Listen to me. Jimmy is a drug dealer, Pop.
He murdered that guy, and Fran is in it.
Pop, he's in up to his neck.
Now, I tried. I tried to talk to Fran,
and when I sat in there with those guys...
...I gave them nothing.
I said as little as I could say.
But if Jimmy's gonna box me in, I gotta tell
them what I know. I got no fucking choice.
The fuck you got no choice.
You could've taken that lay-up
that they were handing you.
- Oh, no. No, Pop.
- And saved us a fucking mess.
Come on. What good would it have done?.
Jimmy's a scumbag. Jesus.
We'll take care of him.
But we got a hole that needs
to get plugged up...
...before it takes down
half the department.
It's too late, Pop.
We protect our own, Ray.
That is all I know. We protect our own.
You gotta show me some fucking loyalty.
No. Don't use that word with me. It doesn't
mean shit to me anymore, you know that?.
I done your loyalty. It cost me too much.
- What did it cost you?.
- It cost me everything!
It cost me the woman that I love.
Because she told me that we were wrong
on Mott Haven.
She told me. I didn't listen.
Look, you said you weren't sure about
what you saw. I heard it.
You heard what you wanted to hear.
Don't bullshit me.
It was a lie to protect a bad cop,
and you knew it, and I knew it.
And I got up there and said it
in front of the grand jury.
- I got it.
- I'm not gonna do this.
- Not for you.
- I'm responsible, huh?.
- This is my responsibility, this shit?.
- No. We did wrong. I wanna hear you say it.
Both of you, stop the yelling.
- Get out of here, Mo.
- No. Stop it.
- Get out of here.
- I am not leaving.
- This is not for you.
- No, no.
- I am not leaving.
- I don't want you hearing this.
Hey, hey, hey. Dad, take it easy.
- Don't yell at her.
- Get upstairs.
This is too much.
Now, you listen to me,
and you listen good.
This is not just about the department.
That's not what we're talking about here.
This is family. This is our way of life.
Jimmy is married to your sister.
He's the father of her children,
for chrissake.
And your brother is in a bad hour here,
and the only way through this is you.
You're the only door.
Jimmy is gonna take back his story.
I'll see to that.
And you just follow the crumbs
like they're laid out for you.
Take a deep breath
and say what needs to be said.
Like you believe it with every bone of your
body, and then we move through this thing.
- And that's what you're gonna do.
- No.
No, he's not gonna do that, Pop.
- Franny, listen.
- Ray is not getting hung out for what I did.
What I did.
He'll get a slap on the wrist,
nothing more.
- You're not thinking clearly, Franny.
- Yeah, I am.
Listen to me, Pop. This shit ends now.
Tonight.
And if that means
I can't be a cop anymore...
...I'm okay with that.
What do you want me to do?.
We're gonna get Jimmy.
That's what we're gonna do.
Yeah. Okay.
Just gonna make a stop over here.
Real quick.
What are you doing?.
I gotta pick something up.
Picking up what?.
Whoa, whoa, what the fuck is that?.
- I gotta make a collection.
- A collection with a gun?. Jesus, come on.
Jimmy told us to lay low.
Stay under the radar.
- You know what?. Fuck Jimmy.
- Fuck Jimmy?. What are you talking about?.
- Jimmy's looking out for us.
- Jimmy ain't looking out for me!
He ain't paying my fucking rent! I got no
fucking money in my pocket. I'm broke!
- Jeez, you coming with me or not?.
- No, I'm not coming, Eddie.
- Do what you wanna do. Stay here.
- I will fucking stay here.
Yo, bro.
No, I'm not a fucking cop anymore.
Get the fuck out of here.
You gotta do this every time?.
Let's fucking go, Eddie. Let's go.
- Shit, Eddie!
- Get down. get down.
Eddie, fucking- Eddie.
I see how it is.
Out of the store. I'm a cop. Out of the
fucking store. Get the fuck out of the store!
Give me the fucking gun.
Give me the fucking gun now.
Get down! Get the fuck down!
Out now! Go.
- He got a gun, man.
- You! You!
- You!
Oh, shit.
Yo, that's that nigga right there.
- That's what I said.
- You sure?.
Yes, I'm sure.
No, I can't talk right now, Megan.
I know it, I'm with him.
No, we'll call you soon.
Okay.
He's at Irish Eyes.
You motherfucker, unlock that door!
You stupid, stupid idiot, Eddie.
You fucking...
How do I get out of here?.
Is there another way out of here?.
Tell me.
- Back door.
- Fucking show me. Show me!
Goddamn it. Go right or left?.
Left.
Oh, shit! Is there another fucking exit?.
No, fuck it. Don't talk.
MAN Callback, Central.
Stand by, units.
- Tierney.
- We got a 10-30 on Audubon.
- I know. It's coming over the radio.
- That ain't the problem, I got a riot.
Wait, man, slow down.
I can't understand you. What?.
Looks like it's two guys from
your command. Two SNEU guys.
Who?.
I ' m on my way.
It's Dugan and Carbone.
I'm gonna need units for crowd control.
You gotta go.
I'll get Jimmy.
Destroy that piece of shit!
I fucking told you not to do it.
Chief Tierney,
I'm Captain Lavier from Internal Affairs.
Have a warrant for your son's arrest.
We'd like him to come with us.
What makes you think he's here?.
Car's outside.
Got a message?. I'll tell him.
- How about if I come in myself and tell him?.
- No, you're not invited.
Now, get the hell off my porch
and take your boys with you.
Let's go.
You can tell your superiors I said so.
They got the fucking place surrounded.
Just get down here, Jimmy.
We'll meet back here.
What's going down in there?. Pepe okay?.
I hope Pepe killed 20
of you motherfuckers.
Let's go. Move back.
Do you believe this shit?.
- We got any communication established?.
- I requested Hostage Negotiation, sir.
- They give you an ETA?.
- Not yet, sir.
All right.
I want this perimeter pushed back.
Big Stevie, Ponch, you're my shooters.
I'm going in.
Boss.
These are my guys.
I'm going in.
Where is everybody?. Get over there!
Let's go, move it!
Fuck, man. Come on, hurry up.
They knocked my tooth out. Black and blue.
My whole family disrespected.
These motherfuckers!
Whoa. Whoa, man, easy.
Kenny, easy.
Let's not lose our heads here.
I'm gonna fucking kill him, boss.
Kenny, just keep it calm, all right?.
It's just me.
Get them motherfuckers out of here!
It's on.
I swear to Jesus Christ,
I will fucking kill him, Franny.
In about two minutes,
we got everybody showing up here.
You do not want that to happen. You do not
want me to lose control of this scene.
Do not fucking play me, Franny.
There's no play here, Kenny.
There's no fucking play.
You wanna talk to me or
you wanna talk to a stranger?.
Kenny.
Open the door.
Police. I want everyone
out of this bar right now.
You too, Mac.
You got anything you wanna say to me
about what you've done?.
You left me no choice, Ray.
Push to shove, it's me and mine.
It's Megan and the kids.
After that, it's every swinging dick
for himself.
You broke our fucking hearts, Jimmy.
Lot of hearts broken, Ray.
There's a lot of hearts broken.
So how do you think this ends?.
You gonna take me in?.
Take your gun out and put it on the bar.
Turn on me, Ray!
- I'm so fucking tired.
- Fuck you. Fuck you.
I'm gonna send in a crew! Open it up!
Let's go, let's go!
Back! Everybody step back.
You gotta push these guys back.
- Ray. Ray.
- Shut up, Jimmy.
- Move. Move.
- Ray.
That's him. That's that nigga Egan. Go.
- Get behind me.
- Take the cuffs off.
- Shut up. Get behind me.
- Yo, that's him!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Right there. Police
officer. Stay back. This man's under arrest.
Take the cuffs off, give me my gun.
Shut up.
We want Egan, not you.
Walk away, you live.
Fuck you! Stay back.
- I'm not kidding.
- You gonna kill everybody?.
Try me.
They're gonna tear us apart.
- This ain't your fight.
- That nigga's dead. Give me that stick.
You walk out with me right now.
Let's go.
Jimmy!
Let him be. Let him be.
- You motherfuckers!
- Back off!
Jimmy!
Back the fuck off!
Back off!
Back off! Nigga's mine.
This nigga's mine!
Get off of me, you motherfuckers!
You motherfuckers!
No! Don't you do it!
Don't you fucking do it!
Tell her I love her.
Don't you fucking do it! No! Jimmy!
No! No! Don't fucking do it!
Don't you do it!
Jimmy.
Detective Tierney. Your CO's my brother.
- You all right?.
- Yeah. I'm all right.
- You sure?.
- I'm all right.
You go find him, I got the brief.
Okay. Great job, boss.
Thanks.
Hi, chief. Couple of my suspended guys
were involved in this 30...
The fuck happened to you?.
What?.
Where's Jimmy?.
Let's go home.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org