Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I've seen him do it
a million times,
but I can't tell you
how he does it, Henry.
The right-handed part.
I can tell you what he does
with his left hand.
He's a genius with it.
He might put that hand
on your elbow. . . .
or your bicep,
like he's doing now.
Basic move.
he's interested in you.
He's honored to meet you.
But if he gets any higher,
if he gets on your shoulder. . .
. .it's not as intimate.
He'll share a laugh with you,
a light secret.
And if he doesn't know you,
but wants to share emotional . . .
he'll lock you in a two-hander.
You'll see when he shakes
hands with you,Henry.
Governor.
Governor Stanton,
this is Henry Buton.
I met your grandfather
when I was a boy.
I hitchhiked to Washington
to hear him speak.
He was a great man.
Thank you,sir.
He's glad you' re coming on board,
I can see.
I'm not coming on board.
I'm just meeting him.
No, no. Take it easy.
Why is he here? He's a southern
governor nobody knows.
You sound like a campaign
manager already.
-Howard, I'm not. . .
-I'm kidding.
If I said Stanton's here because
he cares about adult literacy. . .
You'd say I was full of it.
Yes.
Howard, Henry, this is
Marianne Walsh,
the librarian who runs
these classes.
Thank you, Governor walsh.
Govemor stanton, I'm sorry.
I'm a little nervous. I'm sorry.
If you'll with me.
I'll take you up to the library.
The walls are pretty bad,
but the library is much, um. . .
Better. . .
Yes,yes.
We' re very proud of the library.
When did you start
the reading program?
Three years ago.
We have very little money.
It's the only reading program
like it in Harlem I know of.
There may be others,
but I don't uh. . . .
You okay?
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
I'm Ruby. I'm a domestic.
I've been in this class 2 months.
Jack washington. I'm a handyman.
Hello, Jack.
Tawana Carter, Waitress.
Good to meet you.
Anthony Ramirez,
freelance carpenter.
I wanted to say welcome aboard.
What? I'm not on board. I just. . .
You' re kidding, right?
Yeah.
Tell the governor a bit about
yourself, Dewayne.
I'm a short order chef.
And until I come here,
I couldn't read a lick.
Dewayne's dyslexic.
They just kept passing me up.
Third grade, fourth grade.
I just sit in the back,
sticking to my own self.
It was like no one noteced.
and I went all the way through
and graduated elementary school .
They sent me to Ben Franklin
that's generar studies.
They could have sent me
to the Bronx Zoo.
No one ever said:
Dewayne, you can't read.
What will you do with your ass?
Excuse me.
Anyway, graduation come
and my mama come.
She took the day off
from the laundry where she worked.
So, we' re there. . . .
Dr. dalembretti calls out
the names on th diplomas. . .
and what each kid done.
Like "Sharonna Harris, honors."
Tyrone Kirby, Regents Diploma.
And then. . .
he come to my name.
he said, "Dewayne smith. . .
receive a certificate. . .
of attendance.
You could hear people buzzing.
A couple of folks laughed.
And I had to go up there
and get it.
I had to stand up there. . . .
just dying. . .
trying not to look at anyone.
trying not to look too stupid.
Mama's in front.
She has her hat on and her purse
in her lap. . . .
tears coming down from behind
her glasses. . .
Iike someone . .Iike someone died.
I want to thank you. . . .
for sharing that with us, Dawayne.
I want to thank you all
for having real courage.
My uncle charlie was. . .
a war hero, in World War ll.
He went to Jima,
where they raised the flag.
He took out four machine gun nests of Japanese
soldiers. . .who had pinned sown his buddies.
Did it with one grenade, his rifle,
bayonet, and bare hands.
Shit.
President Truman gave him
the Medal of Honor.
And when he came home,
there was a parade.
The town fathers came to
my parents house adn said:
Charlie, what are you going
to do now?
Charlie said he didn't know.
The mayor said,
Maybe you'd like a scholarship.
The banker said maybe Charlie
didn't want to go back to school .
Maybe he'd like a management
job with the bank.
and the owner said,
Don't be cooped up in a school .
Come manage my crew.
And you know what?
Charlie turned them all down.
What did he do?
Nothing.
He just laid on the couch
and smoked Luckies.
Couldn't git him off it.
Was he messed up in the head
from the war?
No.
It was just that he couldn't read.
He couldn't read and was too
embarrassed to tell anyone.
He had the courage to win the
Medal of Honor. . .
. .but didn't have the courage to
do what you' re doing here.
He didn't have the courage to get
the help he needed.
So, know that I appreciate what
you' re doing and I honor it.
When people say,
Why spend effort on adult literacy?
I say to them. . .
I say, Because. . .
It gives me a chance
to see courage.
I want to thank you.
I want to thank you for allowing me
to visit here today.
Let's get him out of here.
He likes it.
Governor Stanton,
thank you for coming today.
I will be damned.
You' re going to work for him.
No, I'm not.
I'm just going to meet him and talk.
About what?
Well , about going to work for him.
How can you quit on Adam Larkin
and get in bed with some cracker. . .
Who's done piss for blacks
in his state?
I could say the same about Larkin.
But he will . He has to wait.
He's a black congressman.
I don't like Larkin.
I don't know what Stanton wants,
but. . .
I do.
He wants to use the grandson of
a civil rights leader. . . .
a black man in politics
to get votes.
That's hilarious.
Yeah, put a black man on the team,
that'll roll in those votes.
That's why so many black men
run the country.
If politics upsets you,
work for the black Advocate.
We' re never like it.
Hand me that tie.
Get your own damn tie.
No,no tie, no suit.
Just leather jacket cool .
I'll be back in 2 hours.
Then we can discuss
the Black Advocate.
Don't be mad.
Okay, but only for 2 hours.
Wait up for me.
Oh, my God. My boy.
Henry Burton,
I am mighty honored.
I'm Arlen Sporken, the governor's
media consultant.
Nonfat caffeine?
Thank you,don't it.
I am delighted you' re on board.
-Honey, get me a sandwich.
-only if you pinch my cheek.
I'll get it. We' re going
to win this thing.
Absolutely.But the big question
is Ozio.
You think he has
the ones to run?
It's cojones. I don't know Ozio
well enough to judge his cojones.
They' re big, but they' re glass.
Hey, there, Henry.
Governor, it's nice to. . .
You remember Miss walsh.
-Sorry.
-You all right darling?
Thank you for this,
-The opportunity to discuss the. . .
-The program.
A great program,
don't you think. Henry?
Yes. It's an excellent program.
Now, tell the board what
we discussed.
Yes, I will .
I'll just see my way out.
Bye-bye.
She's on the board of
the teachers' union.
Ah, a teacher and a librarian.
Hi , darling.
Honey,
I'm sorry. We got stuck here.
But great news--we made real
progress with the teaches.
Tonight? Are you sure?
Oh, I'm so sorry, honey.
Did we have a meeting with the guy
from the portsmouth Democratic Committee
Goddamn it, Charlie.
Are you uncle Charlie,
the Medal of honor winner?
Well , I'm Uncle Charlie.
And whatever else he says.
If you'll stop popping my eardrum,
I'll leave now.
Don't Susan, don't go.
Susan, Just stay. . .
We better go. Where's the plane?
Teterboro.
All the way out there?
Okay, Let's go.
Arien, see you in D.C.
Daisy, go with Howard.
Henry. . .Mitch, Charlie, Let's go.
Go?
But I came to talk to you about-
We'll talk on the plane.
But I teach classes in the morning.
Call in sick. The keds won't mind.
Can I make a phone call?
When we get there.
Now, Let's talk. . .
Hi , honey.
This is Henry Burton.
My wife, Susan.
I met you 25 years ago
at your grandfater's.
You were running under
the sprinkler in wet underpants.
He was a great men.
Thank you.
Jack could also be
a great man. . . .
if he weren't such a thoughtless,
undisciplined shit.
Why is this a big deal?
Because first impressions count,
asshole.
This is New Hampshire.
These piople don't know you.
They don't even know your state.
They know Orlando Ozio, the governor
of a real state.
But they came to meet you and
you didn't show.
I talked to the head of their
Democratic party about fly-fishing. . .
for an hour and 45 minutes.
Do you realize how. . .
indescribably boring
fly-fishing is?
Do you realize I've now committed
to doing. . .
this, this thing with him?
I'm going fly-fishing
because of you, you asshole!
It's not funny. You can't do
this to me,Jack.
We've been at this a month and
you' re already fucking up.
The only shot we have here is
to be perfect.
Barely adequate won't swing it.
Jack, you can't blow off--
Primrose lane
Life's a holiday on Primrose Lane.
When I'm walking down Promise Lane
-With you
-You' re not funny.
I have to find a phone.
When we get to the apartment.
Honey, It was so great today.
the reading program.
You should have seen the piople.
And the teacher was inspirational .
Tell me how good was.
We can replicate a good curriculum.
You can't sell a program without
a good teacher.
Henry, was the teacher
that inspirational?
Well , she was. . . .
She was a pretty typical school
board bureaucrat, I thought.
We got it on a 6-month sublet.
Better than a hotel . Cheaper, too.
We can keep clothes and store stuff.
We have privacy.
I don't care about privacy.I'm here to
get know I can't do that in Private.
It's like the end of the campaign,
not the beginning.
Goddamn it, Charlie. No cable?
You can't run for President of
the United States without CNN!
Do you have any bags?
No, I didn't expect to come.
-You want something to eat?
-Yeah.
This is the worst damn place
I've ever seen!
Hey! Darling.
It's four A.M.
This is'nt how to introduce
yourself to the neighbors.
I'll make you coffee, Henry.
Well , I'm out of here
tomorrow morning.
I know we got to go cheap,
but not this cheap. Not loser cheap.
So, why did you quit Larkin?
Why?. . .
Why did you stop working for Larkin?
Careful , it's hot.
Thank you.
I just, Um. . . .
I know-you can't talk about
your old boss to your new one.
I don't have a new boss yet.
Larkin's very different from Jack.
Very cool .
Never blinks. A pro.
Wouldn't swallow tea without
testing it.
That's the real thing experience
teaches you.
How not to get bumed.
Do people ever learn that?
Not best people.
Adam taught me a lot. . . .
but it was all the same.
He never surprised me.
No one ever voted with us
because it was right.
They always asked for a lulu.
Lulu?
It's New York for artificial
sweetener.
Anyway, we'd win and then be
gutted. . . .
in the Senate. We'd accept
their version.
Then the White House would veto,
which was no surprise.
Then we'd celebrate our great
moral victory.
We'd forced a ceto.
So you dropped out.
So why are you here?
Tell me.
It's four in the morning.
Let's just tell the truth.
Okay, Well . . .
I wondered how it would be
to work with someone. . .
who actually cared about. . .
I mean. . .
It couldn't always have been
the way it is now.
It must have been different
in my grandfather's time.
You were there. You had Kennedy.
I didn't.
I've never heard a president say
"destiny" and "sacrifice"
without thinking, "bullshit."
Okay, maybe it was bullshit
with Kennedy, too. but. . .
but people believed it.
and I guess, that's what I want.
I want to believe it.
I want to be part of something
that's history.
I bet this is the longest answer
to a five word qusetion.
You've ever gotten.
No, it isn't.
The longest was the one I got to. . .
Do you do much fly-fishing?
It's a good answer, henry.
We are part of the history.
What else is there?
Hey, March.
Some guy about an automobile
insurance scam.
It's me. Don't hang up again.
-Fuck you.
-I'm in coffee shop in Hampshire.
I may not find another phone.
Listen.
Listen. I think guy could be
the real thing.
He's so incredible you could
work for him.
This son of a bitch actually
likes these people.
He's worth the risk.
Help me get him out of here.
We have a fund raiser in 20 minutes.
You bastard.
I waited for you all right.
I can explain about that.
I got you some stuff
at the drugstore.
I can't go to Mammoth Falls
without clothes.
Daisy can pack some things
and bring them to you.
Why I can't pack the things?
Because you' re going to Mississippi .
We have to set up campaign
headquarters before we go.
Thank you.
I thought you told us to hurry.
Susan. . .Mrs. Stanton, I'm not sure.
I mean, I don't know.
I've never helped run
a presidenteal campaign before.
Well , neither have we.
That's how history is made.
Henry-by the first-timers.
Stanton for President
Are you, uh. . .?
Is this. . .?
Where are the state party people?
They' re tied up with
the congressional races. We' re it.
All right.
Get the mailing lists of every donor
since the beginning of time.
I also need a complete database of
voting records on every candidate. . .
So we can set up a rapid response
operation.
How do we do that. Honey?
Don't you, uh. . . .
Don't any of you have
any special skills.
I speak Hebrew.
Great.
Voting Records
Now call up the Harris vote.
No,no!
Why can't I learn this?
This announcement is for
the candidate briefing on the 23rd.
Put it on five hundred leaflets.
And then what?
Hand them out.
Call only the Orthodox and
Conservative synagogues.
Speak only to the rabbis and
start off in Hebrew.
How's that?
Great. We need to file that with. . .
Excuse me.
Terry? Terry!
Just hold out the leaflets
for people. Don't stalk them.
How y'all doing?
We' re coming along.
We don't have much staff yet.
No, but what we have is choice.
Meet the most brilliant political
strategist in the party.
This is Richard Jemmons.
This is Henry Burton.
I sure admired your granddaddy.
Great.
-I'll pick you up for dinner.
-We can talk policy.
Nice meeting you.
Say hi to Winona for me.
Who?
He means Jennifer.
Every girl Richard falls for is
Winona Ryder to him.
Oh, that's uh. . .
. .psychotic.
Does that good or what?
It smells so good.
-We got it all set up. Where's
the governer? -He's down there.
He's got chicken.
Hey, Will , how's business?
Hey, Amalee, the Gov's here.
You got your mojo working tonight?
Ain't no end to it, gov.
Hey, Lo!
Gov's here.
How you doing?
Henry burton. Poeased to meet you.
How are you, honey?
I had to tell jackie you were
too busy working to baby-sit
and he was not happy.
How are you, honey?
Not so good since my mama died.
I miss her like a pain.
You got to let that happen.
Your mama deserves it.
Your pain will heal ,
but give your mama her due.
We got to miss our mamas.
Nobody loves us like them.
Your mama still with you, Henry?
NO. she's in Beverly Hills
with her second husband.
You' re a lucky man.
Thank you.
And the next time I see my mama,
she's blind.
A year later, she's got
one leg from diabetes.
She could have done anything.
Been anything.
God bless the mamas.
My mama worked her whole life.
My mama raised seven chikdren.
If he doesn't,
we focus on New Hampshire.//He does, we focus on the South.
He may wait until New Hampshire.
Shouldn't we wait for
the Govemor for this?
He's in a mama-thon.
That'll go in all night.
My mama worked her whole life
for her family. . .
and never did anything
for herself!
and now they' re cutting her up!
Cutting pieces out of her!
Why is that happening to her?
I looked over jordan and
what did I see
Coming for to carry me home.
You know what Richard's favorite
song is?
It is the most American goddamn song
I can think of.
A southern governor wrote it.
Know what I'm thinking ofz?
You are my sunshine.
My only sunshine.
You make me happy
when skies are gray.
-I didn't know a governor wrote it.
-You'll never know. . .
Please don't take my sunshine away.
The other night,
dear as I lay sleeping.
I held you in my arms.
When I awoke, dear.
I was mistaken.
and I hung my head and cried.
You are my sunshine.
My only sunshine.
You make me happy when skies
are gray.
You'll never know,
dear How much I love you. . .
I have a list of all grassroots
organizations in New hampshire.
Great. Put it on my desk.
theae rabbis are putty
in my hands.
Fantastic.
I started out with 200,
I have one left. Know how I did it?
Look it.
I'm speechless.
I think my grandfather would
endorse the Governor.
Jesse. even if you ran.
Okay. You, too, my friend. Okay.
Where the fuck are my clothes?
Relax.
Daisy got sidetracked
to Washington.
Does this guy have a chance
in hell?
I haven't canvassed hell lately.
But if we worked for guys who had
a chance, we wouldn't have Richard.
Shit. He's bird-dogging.
Why don't you go over to
my hotel room with me?
You' re crushing my originals.
Sorry.
You don't know
what you' re missing.
Wait. Don't embarrass him.
I got cable. Want to walk
the snake?
What, you don't believe me?
Baby, I got a python in here.
Gee, I've never seen one
that old before.
Come on, bud. Park the Mustang
back in the garage.
Fuck you!
You redneck son of a bitch!
Ever hear of Anita hill?
You' re lucky she's cool .
I wouldn't have done it
if she wasn't.
And you know when a muffin is cool .
When to show her your cock.
Where'd you go to school?
Hotchkiss. You' re a tight-ass
prepie elitist from Hotchkiss.
Bullshit!
Bullshit it's bullshit!
You called me a redneck,
which I'm proud to say I am.
You are a honky.
You just look black,
and it's your best part.
Lets you
intimidate the palefaces. . . .
and work that voodoo sexual shit
on white girls.
I'm blacker than you are.
I got slave in me, I can feel it.
You are crazy.
-Henry?
-What?
You got a visitor.
It's not a visitor. It's me.
Where the fuck is my suit case?
I got it.
You can't let a lady carry
a suitcase.
Herny I'm glad you got a wardrobe
because we' re haveing dinner. . .
with a very important person.
Who?
Govemor Ozio's son.
What the fuck does Ozio's son want?
It could be that Ozio's
looking for someone to endorse.
Jesus.
That'd be something.
You think?
This must be handled just right.
Just right.
Mind eating pig with your hands?
Is there any other way?
Not in the South.
Jack, the govemor's been
watching you.
He was hoping when you next pass /our way, You stop in.
Get to know us.
Absoultely, Jimmy,
You got the book.
When can we meet with. . .jimmy'd dad,governor Ozio?
Do you mind us talking business?
No, no. How else will I learn?
Next tuesday we' re in Albany,
on our way to New Hampshire.
How's Tuesday?
Let's look.
Tuesday. Let me just scroll down here.
Tuesday's pretty full ,
but I can slot you in somewhere.
We land at four,
then do a drop-by
at the Teachers Union party. . . .
before their dinner at the Sheraton.
I'd skip that, but they'd notice.
I'm the only candidate invited
to the party.
I know.The govemor tumed,
It down because he's speaking
at the dinner.
Good. You'll both be
at the Sheraton.
You can meet after the party
and before the dinner.
Perfect.
I'll see him there.
Excellent.
Fuck all , Henry.
You don't know fuck about
briefing me!
You make me look like an amateur.
Like a barefoot dipshit,
third-rate, southern fried. . . .
piece of shit alderman!
You didn't know Ozio was speaking
at the dinner. . .
to keep me from shooting
my mouth off!
Hello, Richard.
If you'd like to make a call-
Shit! What kind of operation do
we got here?
How'd we get scheduled for a drop
when he's the main speaker?
Get me Howard!
You threw the phone out
the window.
Stop the car.
Don't kill us, Just stop it.
I think it landed in the brush.
It landed in the trees. I saw it.
I look like shit going to that
cocktail party.
I'm Ozio's warm-up,
and he knows it.
But we didn't know it.
I told you, it landed in the trees.
Jimmy probably told his dad
he's nothing to worry about.
He would have even if
Henry hadn't screwed up.
Here's the phone.
It landed in the trees.
It was in the brush.
Well , you wouldn't have found it
if I hadn't thrown it out.
Hi .
Sorry, he's not here.
Henry Burton. Can I take a message?
Oh, God. I see.
How reliable is Daisy?
Hundred percent.
Then we just got bad news.
An interview in Manhattan magzine,
Ozio blasts you.
His state's last in everything.
He knows shit about education.
You were ritht about the meeting.
This is bad.
Hit back, Jack.
Not too hard
or you lose the liberals.
You'll lost them anyway.
Richard?
Give him a poke. We'll look
better when he drops out
When who drops out?
OZio's 24 points ahead of our.
Exactly. If he's willing to
acknowledge us. . . .
then he's the strpidest
fucking ltalian since nero. . .
or he's not going to race.
He'll sit and snipe.
Desn't matter. I won't do it.
Jack?
Susan, I'm not going negative.
Any jackass can bum down a bam.
-It's self-defense.
-I'm not doing it!
Shane!
Come back!
Come back, Shane.
Run for president.
How you doing,Henry?
Uh, fine.
There was a bender
on the interstate.
I'm on my way to meet the family,
so cancel Howard.
Yeah, okay.
And, um, Govemor, look. . .
about the Teachers Union dinner. . . .
I know how much I lay on you.
I know how hard you work for me,
and I'm honored by it.
I'm honored.
But I should have thought-
Forget it.
Now, get out of
that office and rest.
Open a bottle of Chablis.
What are you doing this weekend,
Henry?
Setting up a list of meetings-
Do you think it's possible to
get yourself laid?
Sir?
I'm serious.
I don't want you too horny to
think straight when we need. . .
What are you doing Tanksgiving?
-What?
-Your mama's in Beverly Hills. . .
so if you' re free. . .comespend it
with Susan, Jackie and me.
It's not like being
with your mama. . . .
but we' re family, too.
Thank you. Yes, I'd like that.
Good, good.
and, the reason
I won't take on Ozio. . .
is so I don't give that bastard
the power to make me the bastard.
All right? See you, Henry.
Right.
Dear Lord, thank you. We' re about to receive.
Okay, son. Here we go.
Happy Thanksgiving, everybody.
Who are all these people?
Most are from shelter.
-You' re kidding.
-They come every year. A good news.
The bad news is, he also invites
his friends.
Piople he's been collecting so he can
take them aboard when he sails.
Some of them really suck.
Henry? Daisy?
she had the same problem.
Right.
Meet lucille Kaufman, an old friend
of mine from New York.
Hello!
I marched with your grandfather.
Hi ! Lucille.
Lucille and I went to law school .
You' re Jack's coordinator?
Do something about his clothes.
And the campaign posters.
And Arlen Sporken, too.
I'm swamped, or I'd join
the campaign full-time.
Henry, I want you to meet my son,
Jackie.
Hi ! jack.
This is our family doctor,
Dr. Beauregard.
Henry!
You and jack must find a way to
educate them Yankees.
Maybe if they both wear capes.
This is Randy Culligan.
I gave Randy his first job
as a law clerk.
Folks, may I have your attention?
Folks, y'all know me.
I'm Jackie stanton's mama.
How about if we sing a chorus of. . .
You Are My Aunshine.
. . .in honor of the great governors
of the South?
You are my sunshine.
My only sunshine.
You make me happy when skies
are gray.
Hi !
You' re kidding. You' re kidding.
Hey! hey! Wait, wait.
Ozio just dropped out.
That's fantastic! Yes!
Gentlemen,
welcome to the first debate of the
Democratic Presidential Primary.
Remember to keep your responses
to one minute.
God, I'm so nervous, I'm sick.
Health care.
What I want to say about
health care is. . .
. .While it's vital that
every American be covered. . .
It's also vital that we conserve
as well as expend.
We' re peoviding a safety net
for folks on welfare. . .
Oh, shit.
How?
Oh, man. . . .
What did you see?
Nothing No one.
You' re missing one of
the assholes of our time.
I can't help feeling sad as
I listen to Senator Martin.
I remember a time when being
a Democrat. . .
. . .meant more than just giving
welfare recipients a safety net.
It meant giving them a ladder. . . .
. . .giving them a way to climb back
to an equal height.
If we don't control spending. . .
and shore up the economy of
this country, it will go under.
-This is a new economic era.
-Who' re we shoring the economy up?
Your bond-holding fat cats?
No, not just bond holders.
Ordinary men and women
will benefit, too
My God. Lie.
Why is he doing this?
Because he just has to get on
the good side of Lawrence Harris.
A lower deficit means.
working families will have lower
mortgage rates.
Okay, not bad, but shut up.
Now Govemor Nilson's idea
has merit.
We must provide jobs for those
who need work.
Jack, excuse me.
What, if anything, are you against?
I'm against doing nothing
while people are suffering.
I'm against dismissing any idea hat
might help because it isn't my idea.
Senator, you've met these people.
Are you saying we'd nothing to help
unless we come up with it?
Nailed him!
He's toast!
-What I meant was. .
-Kicking ass and taking names!
How was it?
You took it. It was yours.
Govemor-March Cunningham,
the Black Advocate.
Were you ever arrested
during the vietnam war?
No.
You weren't arrested in Chicago?
No. I was accidentally detained,
then released.
The record was expunged.
How were you released?
The realized it was a mistake.
It was a long time ago.
Check your records.
Come on. We'll be late.
You guys go ahead. I'll meet you.
What are you doing here?
Why is the Black advocate
interested in Stanton?
They' re not. I am.
I'm finding out who he is
because a friend works for him.
MECH, don't do this.
Aren't you interested, too?
Know why he was released?
He called. .a senator
to get him out of jail . . .
ask Daley to expunge his record.
So?
He was already so manipulative
in the 60s
that he got in be with Daley. . .
who busted the protestors
at the Convention.
I don't care.
Stanton was never a radical .
He's a politician.
He couldn't get elected with
a record, so he had it expunged.
You want to work for that?
A man wants to get elected?
No, I want to work for a man
who fights for right.
and watch a Republican get elected.
Do you know the diffeerence?
I know the difference between
a man who believes what I do. . .
and lies about it to get elected. . .
and one who doesn't give a fuck.
I'll take the liar.
How did he do this to you?
Do what? what are you. . . .?
Why are you making him
into the devil?
Get to know him.
Spend a few day with us.
I miss you. We could be together.
I think you'd fuck me
to get good press for Stanton.
We' re in trouble.
What does she have?
Why is the Black Advocate
covering Stanton?
They' re not. It's. . .she's. . .
It's personal .
Don't matter. We' re fucked.
If some little shitty paper. . . .
Like the Black Advocate can
dig this up. . .
They'll all come after us.
I mean, did you see any
other president there tonight?
We' re it.
We' re the fucking ball game.
Now every flea that ever nipped
This ass will want a piece of us.
It'll be the war thing,
the drug thing,
the woman ting. That's the killer.
You talk to him about that.
Me? No. You' re the strategy guy.
But you' re the boy man.
We could talk to Susan.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Mrs. Stanton, we need to know
who Jack's plugging
so we can have spin control .
Then let's just quit.
If we won't act, let's work
for someone,
We' re not too chicken-shit
to protect.
Okay, set up a meeting.
Him or her?
shit, her!
Goddamn, this is going
to be rough.
I have to be in Concord
in an hour to meet Jack.
What's the crisis.
It's campaign business.
It's private
-Oh, please.
-Susan is my good friend.
What's the crisis.
You' re in the wooks,
taking a shit. . . .
and a wild boar comes
charging at you.
Do you pull your britches up
and run?
Or do you try to pull
your britches up
and grab the doves you
just shot. . . .
and then try to run,
all at the same time?
Or do you just forget
about the doves. . . .
pull your britches up and run,
cause you got no time to aim
and button your fly?
And if you miss. . . .
you don't want to die with
your dick hanging out.
See what I'm saying?
I think I speak for everyone
when I say no.
Well , I mean. . . .
what if you' re not prepared
for the boar. . .
get caught with your britches
down and lose the doves?
What Richard is saying is. . .
if you get caught in the forest-
Forget the shit
in the woods metaphor.
What are you talking about?
Okay.
Say this boar is part of-
I don't believe this.
Who do the boars represent?
The Republicans?
The press.
The press?
Yes.Don't they?
Yeah, the press.
Now, you' re dealing with
these boars. . . .
and suddenly they say thing
like "marijuana" . . .
"Chicago" Maybe a woman comes
forward-
That's not going to happen.
Absolutely not.
I don't think so, either.
But. . . .
I just wnat to figure this out.
If is did happen. . . .
he won't get trapped like Hart,
cause we know the rules.
If some bimbo comes forward,
-we just say, "Bullshit."
-Bullshit is right.
What do you suggest we do?
How do we deal with it?
Be prepared, so when a story hits,
we can fight back with the truth.
What can they make?
That's the point, Lucille.
That's the whole fucking point.
We need to hire an operative
to do research.
Investigate our lives.
Investigate everything
anyone could make into an allegation.
But we don't play that game.
We play the people's game.
We say "the republicans and media
want to talk about trash."
We talk about your future.
We don't shoot doves in this
campaign. We protect them.
What do you mean?
Don't the doves represent
the people?
No.
Then who are the doves?
Forget the doves. Henry,
you agree with this?
Yes.
We'll do it. I'll tell Jack.
I want Libby Holden.
If we' re hiring someone
to dind the dirt. . . .
we must have someone who knows us,
who we trust.
Is she out of the hospital
Yes.
And she's okay?
Who is she?
She was Jack's chief of staff.
She had a breakdown.
She suddenly became incoherent
during a press conference.
-She's been in and out of sanatarums
for years. -She's ok now.
You and Henry can fly back
and brief her.
well , that's good
that she's stable.
Because you' re putting
the campaign in her hands.
Yes. I know.
That's good.
then are we the doves?
Lucille, don't kell the doves!
I think we' re the ones taking
the shit in the woods.
Henry.
I'm just thrilled, thrilled
Y'all came back.
I have a million messages for you.
He looks like a band leader.
I'm getting rid of it.
Henry, how you going?
On behalf of jack Stanton,
thanks for your support.
Call them assistants,
not secretaries.
Jennifer, look who's back.
Henry.
Shalom.
You' re working on Friday,
wearing a yarmulke?
Actually, I'm dressed for work.
Hi , Henry.
I'm here.
who's going to talk to me?
Miss Holden.
Henry burton.
I'm Terry Hicks.
Jennifer.
Hi , Lib.
Hi , shit-for-brains.
You learned to
watch your mouth yet?
I will not let you fuck up
this campsign, too!
That was 20 years agw.
Yes, I was thinner then.
I had a waist.
Peter Goldsmith.
Ella Louise Harriman.
Where is this happening?
The fucking meeting.
I'll need a safe house.
I know the one. Little,
nice rose garden.
Call becky Raymond,673-4982
Tell her it's for the Governor.
She'll understand.
Now, staff.
I want her. The one who looks
like Winona Ryder.
Gorgeous. Is she smart?
Oh, she's smart.
I want her right away. Start.
A Black Advocate reporter dug up
the Governor's Chicago arrest.
We can't stop that.
Why bother?
It's not that important.
But we' re concerned there
may be other things.
Like Cashmere Mcleod.
Who?
You don't know shit, do you?
Susan's hairdresser?
and Jack's porkpie.
What?
Oh, for Christ's sake,
act your age.
Jack Stanton fucks around,
and has enemies.
But what can Susan's hairdresser
do to us?
Sell her story to the Flash
for $150,000. . .
.minus the 10% she's giving
to the slime sucking. . .
. .shitty night school attorney
who's agenting the deal .
You know this?
No, I imagined it
in the booby hatch!
It's bullshit.
In your dreams, sweetheart.
She can't hurt us.
She's selling a story.
She has no proof.
It's the tip of the iceberg.
Jackie's done some pretty
stupid things.
He's poked his pecker
in some sorry trash bins.
stop them before they stop us.
Crush 'em and sweep 'em up.
From now on, you can call me
the Dustbuster.
You know, honey child-
I'm stronger than dirt.
I believe you.
We could offer her $200,000
not to print it.
Then kill her to make sure?The important
thing is he did nothing wrong.
-He should act pissed off.
-But not too pissed off.
More like it's too bad, but we
don't take it seriously.
It's not as frightening as things that happen
to real people, like losing a job.
Where's the light?
I'm looking.
Shit happens, but we' re calm
in a shit storm.
Or maybe,
we expected this kind of crap.
Right.
The usual media trash bash.
But why did he do it?
Did he think Cashmere would be
so honored she'd never tell?
Maybe it isn't true.
Would it matter?
It'd be better if it wasn't.
Why Hitler was faithful
to Eva Braun.
Does that make him better?
Or Jefferson or Roosevelt
or Kennedy.
or any of the guys
who fucked around?
But we can't say that
in interviews.
No, of course not.
Today, a potentially explosive
development. . .
for Governor Jack Stanton is his quest for
the Democratic presidential nomination.
A dresser has alleged an affair
with the married candidate.
The story, unconfirmed,
appeared today in the Flash.
Stanton's made statement regarding
the woman, Cashmere Mcleod. . . .
but the accusation directly
follows the disclosure. . .
that Governor Stanton was arrested
in 1968 in Chicago.
Fucking Eyewitness news.
Ted Koppel wants someone
for his show.
-60 Minutes.too. -Do we have to take this?
They' re treating this like real .
We can't ignore it.
They could write off Chicago
it was 30 years ago.
Or Cashmere-she was paid
for her story.
But the two, right on top
of each other?
People will say Do we want a
radical who messes with hairdressers?
He did not fuck Cashmere Mcleod.
If you can't handle that fact,
leave now.
Okay,
Let's think this through.
Who has thoughts about
"60 Minutes"?
I think do it.
You agree to these interviews.
Show them we've nothing to hide.
And soon, because
this will cut into the money.
We should act like
we expected this. . .
Doughnuts.
Henry. Sit down, have some coffee.
You going to get
some sleep tonight?
Absolutely.
Don't you worry. I was just
talking to Danny, here.
Danny Scanlon.
this is my friend, Henry Burton.
Can I get you something?
Apple fritter?
No, thanks.
Danny works here every night,
12-hour shifr,
$5.25 an hour.
Like I was telling the Governor,
I don't mind.
I'd mind if I couldn't work.
Apple fritter?
Not for me.
What was the best college game
you saw all year?
Utah State versus San Diego State.
That was a great game. I saw it.
Great ground game.
You need a good ground game.
Apple fritter?
No, I just said-
I'll have one, Dan. But just one.
I'll make some fresh coffee.
If you want some, you call me.
Thank you, Danny.
You look tired, Governor.
Maybe it's time to go home.
They'll kill me with trash.
Don't let them.
It's my own damn fault.
I didn't keep it together.
We can still win this thing.
We' re going to win it.
And these problems are nothing
compared to what folks go throgh.
Losing their jobs,
losing their homes.
Keep that in mind.
Keep the folks in your mind.
It's about them, isn't?
It's about them.
It's about history.
That's truer for Susan than
for me.
It's always been about them.
Like this fella, Danny Scanlon.
He's worked every day since
he was 14.
Couldn't get insurance,
couldn't get his leg fixed.
Doesn't complain.
Doesn't do any one any harm.
Aching to do good.
God, if you let a man like
that go down. . . .
you don't deserve to take up
space on the planet.
We won't let him go down.
Bummer. Bummer.
What? Libby?
She's go tapes?
Who has tapes?
Cashmere, the hair slut,
you moron.
She's playing them tomorrow.
I have no time for ineptitude!
Now tell Jack and Susan
the cunt has tapes
and get back to Mammoth Falls.
Honey, I have to run.
I will . Hold on.
The new member of the swimming
team wants to talk to you.
Hey, Jackie boy. That's great.
You made it.
That's great. We' re proud of you.
No, that's just a bunch of
campaign garbage.
Govemor, this can't wait.
We'll call you tonight.
I love you. Bye.
What is it?
Libby says Cashmere Mcleod's tapes
of you and her talking. . .
On the phone and. . . .
she's going to play them tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
How bad?
I don't know.
Did you tell her--
Henry, excuse us.
It's cold here, Sam.
But these are friendly people.
Reminds me of home.
I like here hair that way.
It softens her face.
Yes. It could be longer, though.
If you spent a day with us. . .
. .you'd see what folks care
about is the future.
He's gotten fat.
He jogs, so how much does he eat?
And what does he eat?
What's he govemor of?
Let me see. . .It's not Georgia. . .
. .not Florida. . .
Sam, I'm not going to dignify
that trash.
At a time when the American people
have a lot to be concemed about. . .
I saw a picture of the hairdresser.
Not bad.
I don't think this is fair.
People suffer and struggle and
go through all sorts of things.
What matters is, we' re still here.
If you want to draw a lesson from
that about Jack's character. . . .
. .here it. He will stick.
He will work through tough times.
He will bust his butt for
the Americann people.
Bust his butt. The mouth on her.
He should take her in hand.
Yeah, right.
She's honest. They had problems.
Maybe that's when he screwed
the hairdresser.
You watching?
It's going off now.
And we' re out. Thanks everyone.
It's over.
How'd it play?
Wasn't she fantastic?
Yeah, great. But they'd like to
see her hair a little longer.
Hey, Henry!
Nice to see you!
Are you fine?
How long are you in town?
-Not long.
-No time to talk.
We got to get to Sailor's and
watch Cashmere with an expert.
You take care of youself, dear.
I'll be home for dinner.
We'll take my truck.
So you met jack and Susan
working for McGovem?
Right!
What were they like?
Glorious.
Golden. Golden.
Did they have any aspirition. . .
Please, mister, please
Don't play B17.
It was our song. It was her song.
Sing with me, Henry!
Please, mister, please
If you know what I mean
play that song again
Sailorman!
Good to see you, Libby.
How was the boody hatch?
A better class of drungs
than the old days.
Where's the beer?
Welcome to the world of
electronics.
Brewski .
Here she comes.
Recording.
I know just what she looked like
in high school .
I'm Sherman Presley,
Miss Mcleod's attomey.
I want to make one thing clear.
We'll take no questions
until the tapes are played.
This will not be an inquisition.
Yeah, right. We git the inquistion.
The tapes were recorded
on Miss Mcleod's phone machine.
This portion was recorded just
before Thanksgiving.
Governor Jack Stanton. . . .
seduced me. . .
and I have tapes to prove it.
I'm on my way to meet the family.
but you said you loved me.
You said no one could do
the things I did to you.
I could come up there.
God, what a whiny bitch.
Remenber we met in Taxas.
I get hot just thinking about it.
What you doing this weekend?
Nothing, now that you' re leaving.
Open a bottle of chablis.
Do you think it's possible
to get laid?
I'd say it's entirely possiblie,
if you postpone that trip.
I'm too homy to think straight.
As you can see these tapes were
recorded on Miss Mcleod's phone machine.
I'll record the rest of it.
Let's go to work.
I'll kill him, How could he
be so dumb?
There are some abrupt cutouts.
I'm on my way to meet the family.
An abrupt cutout right there.
What are you doing the weekend?
That's picked in mid-sentence,
or it could be.
Open a bottle of Chablis.
Do you think it's at all possible
to get laid?
That breakup in the middle could
be static or they used it to cover.
Wait a second.
Wait a damn second.
Play that again.
Do you think it's at all
possible to get laid?
Again.
Why!
Just again, damn it.
Do you think it's at all
possible to get laid?
Yourself.
Henry, are you carcking up?
Two of us dwould be one too many.
Un-fucking-believable!
He said, Do you think it's at all
possible to get youself laid?
He said he didn't want me to be
too horny to think straight.
It was just before thanksgiving.
Play it again from the top.
Just his lines.
Shit!
I'm on my way to meet the family.
There was an accident, a bender,
on the in interstate.
That's the family he was
going to meet. Next.
What you doing this weekend?
An abrupt cutout, right?
He said, What are you doing
this weekedn, Henry?
He called me Henry.
I remember the whole call ,
it meant so much to me.
Christ, we got her!
You got her. We don't.
How do we prove it?
Oh, no,no, No.Libby,they-
They can't get away with this.
This cannot be a world that
lets them get away with it.
Imagine a black boy saying that.
What a privileged life you've had.
But never mind about the world.
I won't let them get away with it.
I'll track down Ted Koppel and
Larry King.
Can you nail their cellular
conversations?
I have to rent a van. Sure.
Do it. We'll pick the best one.
Let's go, Henry.
We have to change the world now.
You aasshole!
Yes, it was off a cellular phone.
But don't pull that outraged
puppy shit.
You haven't become an innocent
just because the tape is phony.
I wish we'd castrated you
when we had the chance.
Libby, You' re on a cell phone.
Oh, shit!
Yes, I'm goddamn sure
I know who did it.
Yes, I'll get it done.
Okay, Bye.
You know who did it?
Yes. Oh, yes, indeedy.
A triumphant day, Huh, Randy?
Perhaps your best ever.
Is that Cashmere on the line?
No.
Then say good-bye
to Sherman Preslsy.
It's not Sherman Presley,
whoever he is.
You've branched out.
Electronics now.
What do you mean?
You've been recording your friend
Jack's private conversations.
why would I do that?
I'm a big Stanton supporter.
I always have been.
I've been here 20 seconds and
you've exhausted my patience.
I want a signed confession.
Libby, put that away before
you get yourself in trouble!
Randy, you human turd. . . .
. .you admit you ambushed
Jack Stanton, or you die.
You' re crazy!
Certi-fucking-fiably.
At last, a fact.
You'll go to jail , too
I know nothing about this.
He's shocked. he had no idea.
Now, are you going to write
this out?
I don't know what you mean!
Enough.
You know what? I'm going to
blow your nuts off.
Yes, I am a lesbian. I do not
mythologize the male organ.
Now, you tiny scumbag,
I know you did it.
You' re on retainer to the Flash.
And you, you stupid shit. . .
. .the crap Jack actually
did wasn't enough-
you had to embellish it.
Mister, You' re about to
become missus.
Libby, don't.
You have a choice to make.
And quickly.
Just how Crazy is libby?
and you have to do it now. One. . . .
two. . . .
This is going to be fun.
Okay, Okay, Okay!
Very good. Very wise.
Now. I want you to be eloquent
in this letter.
Guilt-ridden about
your jealousy and greed.
You couldn't live with yourself
if you deprived America of
this great man.
Tonight, an aide of
Governer Jack Stanton
is joining us to play a tape.
I haven't heard the tape,
but my producer has.
We'd like to thank her for
letting us go on with such notice.
Here we go.
I can be there in 14 minutes.
I could come up there.
No, I can't wait,
I have to have it now.
I get hot just thinking about it
Look at King. Look at his face.
That sounded like me.
It was you,
asking the head waiter
at Cafe Des Artistes. . . .
. .to seat you right away
because you hadn't eaten all day
but how. .
We recorded it off
your cell phone.
I'd like to read a letter
from the man who did this
to Governor Stanton.
To whom it May Concerm:
I am an employee of the Flash.
I took innocent statements of Governor
Stanton's off his cellular phone. . .
edited them and paid
Cashmere Mecleod
to pretend she was talking to him.
I did this for my own gain
and advancement
I confess it now because
I cannot live with the fear. . .
that I may deprive the American
people of a great man.
Signed, Randy culligan,
Attorney-at-law.
Now I think the media owes
Governor Stanton an apology. . .
for spreading
this unsubstantiated garbage.
Very good, girl .
It should be harder than
this to smear an innocent man
We'll be right back
with your phone calls.
How did you get my cellular?
Henry, well done.
I want to thank you all for
sticking with us through all this.
We haven't much time,
but with you help. . . .
and the grace of God,
we'll get done what needs
to be done.
It's would be easy to get laughs. . .
by doing some cheap
blow-dry jokes. . .
so I'll get started.
It all started innocently
for Govemor Stanton.
He walked in one day and
asked for a little trim.
And some longer bangs.
They just don't care about
the fine points.
NO, it would ruin the punch line.
Does anyone survive onw of
these feeding frenzies?
If they've been around
a while,Maybe.
But this the first thing
people hear about Stanton,
-so he's history.
-Fucking idiot!
Damn it.
O'er the land. . .of the free
And the home. . . of the brave.
Thank you, Phil .
as head of the Portsmouth
Democratic Party
It is my loeasure to introduce. . .
. .one of the South's most
progreessive govemors. . .
. .and the husband of one of
the best fly-fishers I've met.
Please welcome
Governor Jack stanton.
Thank you for that kind
introduction, Tommy.
And thank you for the fish.
He gave me a big, slab-sided,
white-bellied fella.
Looked a lot like me.
Put it on the grill ,
gave it some heat.
kind of like I'm getting now.
Thank you for coming tonight.
I know you work hard and have
little time to rest.
Some of us got more time than
we'd like.
Right, I understand.
Since this factory closed,
how many of you have found work?
Raise your hands.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org