There is no God!
Forgive me.
Give me a sign.
Help me.
Maureen. Maureen, where are you, dear?.
Maureen, where are you?.
Oh dear God. She's up there.
Maureen!
Stay where you are!
Don't move!
Stay where you are.
- Come down!
There is no God!
Wretched girl, how dare you!
- Get away from me!
Please, Maureen. You mustn't.
You have an obligation to Him.
- I have nothing.
I am nothing.
- You can't. - No!
Wasn't your own sin red enough?.
You'll burn in hell for this!
You'll burn in hell!
Maureen!
Want a ride?. Or do you have
the Olympic torch in the suitcase?.
Wouldn't want to lose ya.
Don't worry.
I ain't born again or nothing.
I'll get this junk out of your way.
Jesus just come with it
when I bought her used.
I wanted to replace it
with a magnetic compass,
but you usually end up
going the wrong direction anyway.
That makes two of us.
- Yeah?.
Water?.
- Thank you.
Name's Duane Duke, by the way.
Friends just call me Duke.
Put the suitcase in the back seat.
- Thank you.
Hey, watch the guitar!
- I'm sorry.
No harm done.
Just watch out. It's my life.
Going to LAA to be a rock-n-roll star.
What about you?. Where you going?.
What were you doing back there?.
- l...
Car trouble?.
- Yes. I had car trouble.
What kind?.
AAh, no car.
- No car?. That's the worst kind.
Still don't know where you come from.
- So?.
AAre you my Father confessor?.
- Jesus,
I was just asking! You act as if
I accused you of murder or something.
Hey, it's none of my business.
Play mystery lady if you want.
I don't care where you come from.
Could've fallen from the sky.
AA little angel
just tumbled off her cloud.
Well, hold on angel,
I'll get you where you're going.
Get out of here!
Come on, baby.
You alright?.
- Yes.
What are you doing?. - It's as
far as we go in this shit, honey.
But it could rain all night.
- That's right.
Better get some sleep.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
You kind of slid over.
It's still raining.
Why did you do that?.
- Why didn't you stop me?.
I didn't have time.
- I'll give you another chance.
I'm not very good at this.
- You could have fooled me.
Please don't!
Oh, well, I guess
we got him a little excited.
Don't!
No!
What's the problem, angel?.
Get away from me!
AAre you crazy?. Get in here!
- Give me my suitcase.
Stupid bitch!
You could've been coming
instead of going.
AAre you really my mother?.
- The name Spool means nothing to you?.
No. Should it?.
- It was Norma Bates' maiden name.
The woman you thought was
your mother was my sister.
She never mentioned me, did she?.
- No.
You sure you won't have a sandwich?.
Pardon?.
Hi there.
Be right down.
Room?.
I'd love one,
but I don't think I can afford it.
You should keep the register closed.
Somebody'll steal you blind.
Wouldn't get them very far.
- Business slow?.
You're my first customer of the day.
Or did you just need directions?.
I was actually interested in the sign.
But if business is bad...
No, it's not bad, just slow.
Well, 12 cabins, 12 vacancies...
We've been closed for a while.
Renovations.
But life's picking up along here.
Good prices, good service.
Things'll pick up.
I've got a rebuilt ice machine,
and 4 cabins booked for this week.
Fairvale High's Homecoming.
Big game against Central.
I'm rattling on.
Yes, there is a job. Interested?.
In money?. The only honest way
to get it is to earn it or inherit it.
AAnd I don't have any rich relatives.
Got an application form?.
Not necessary. My name is Norman,
Norman Bates.
What'ya been painting?.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Step into the back while I clean up.
- Said the spider to the fly.
Local branch of the AAudubon society?.
- My hobby. Stuffing things.
Have a seat...
- Duane Duke. Just call me Duke.
I can pay you 5 dollars an hour.
You'd work the desk,
make beds, clean up. Stuff like that.
Want some of these?.
You'd be general assistant.
Work's not too hard,
and you'd have lots of free time.
I'm the manager,
so you'd be assistant manager.
You'd get a free room and work days.
I prefer the nights.
I've got to be honest, Norm.
- Norman.
I just want to make enough bucks
to get my car fixed and
build up a little stake for LAA.
I'm a singer.
But I could fill in until you found
somebody permanent. I'm just not
staying too long.
No one ever does.
Your cabin's at the end.
Why don't you go unpack?.
I need to get back to the house.
You live up there?.
- Yeah.
Me and myself, alone.
You clear on the credit card machine?.
- Yeah, I used to be a pump jockey.
The rooms cost...
- 20.95 single, 25.95 double.
I'll bring you a couple of burgers.
- AAlright!
Still beats the hell out of me.
Just doesn't show up for work one day.
Thought you would've turned up
some clues by now, John.
Her apartment's all in order.
Didn't say anything to her landlord.
You'd think she'd tell me
if she was going to take a month off.
Emma Spool
was as regular as clockwork.
I don't think she missed a day
in the 7 years I've owned this dump.
I hope that nothing's happened to her.
- You mean like Norman Bates?.
Didn't they work here together?.
They say he likes older women.
Rumors and innuendo caused
that boy enough trouble.
What's your interest anyway?.
- I drove from LAA to see him.
Why?. You another relative
of somebody he killed?.
It's really not any of your business.
Keeping the peace is my business.
Then until I've broken some law,
lay off the third-degree, OK?.
Can't you just leave
the poor slob alone?.
What are you?. His fan club?.
- No, we believe in second chances.
What Norman did was a long time ago,
and he paid the price.
It depends on who you ask.
20 years in the bunk house
is paying the price, girly.
The guy's okay now.
When he worked here,
he was always on time and reliable.
AA real Employee of the Month!
Go ahead and talk smart, lady.
He just wants to be left in peace.
Now look, Norman Bates has suffered
enough. Just leave him...
AAfternoon, sheriff.
-... alone.
Mrs. Dudley...
- What'll it be, Norman?.
Chicken fried steak is good today.
AAlright, and a glass of milk, please.
AAnd a couple of burgers to go.
I'm warning you. I don't want trouble.
Then let go of my arm
or I'll holler police brutality.
Mind if I join you, Mr. Bates?.
Tracy Vanderbilt.
Thanks, Myrna.
Coastal Reports?.
- I write for them sometimes.
If you don't mind, I'd like to ask you
a few questions. - I mind.
Mr. Bates... - Norman.
- I'm writing on the insanity defense
and the rehabilitation
of mentally ill murderers.
Many people think
they can't be rehabilitated
and there shouldn't be
an insanity defense.
We hear the objections of the victims
and relatives, but the murderers,
who can't help themselves,
are victims too. What do you think?.
If this lady's bothering you,
I'll have her leave.
Isn't your coffee break over, sheriff?.
AAnything else, Norman?.
What do you think?.
- AAbout?. - What we were just saying.
You were incarcerated for 20 years.
- 22.
Right.
For 22 years, you were locked away.
The state says you're sane.
You paid your debt.
Then Lila Loomis starts
to persecute you. - Because of
what happened to her sister.
- Yes.
Marion Crane. Right?.
Right.
- But that was 20 years ago.
22.
AA long time to harbor revenge.
AAren't you bitter about
what Lila Loomis tried to do to you?.
I understand.
My cure
couldn't cure the hurt I caused.
My return to sanity
didn't return the dead.
There's no way
to make up that loss.
The past is never really past.
It stays with me all the time.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't escape. It's always there.
Throbbing inside you.
Coloring your perceptions of the world,
and sometimes controlling them.
That's my point, Norman. You have
a conscience. You live with guilt.
You punish yourself all the time.
Why does the rest of society have to?.
Take Mrs. Spool's disappearance.
What if a well-meaning citizen
thought that
you had something to do with it?.
I'm not upsetting you, Norman?.
AAll this talk
is only hypothetical.
- What's yours, babe?.
She is only an example
of how people might,
given your past history,
tend to automatically blame you
for any murder in the area.
You're not going, Norman?.
I'd like to talk to you again.
You're not going to stiff us, Norman?.
Excuse me. Could you tell me,
is there a cheap place to stay here?.
Hello, angel.
You work here?.
It's called suffering for one's art.
I'm sorry about last night.
I was a little road-weary.
I'm glad you didn't drown.
I'm so very tired.
You won't find another place close.
Don't worry. AAside from total boredom,
nothing will happen to you here.
Maureen Coil. Pretty name.
How much?.
- For a single, $25.95.
There you go, angel.
Enjoy your stay.
Your type, Norm?.
- You gave her Cabin 1.
Makes it kind of cosy.
Clean her up a little,
she'll look pretty good.
Put me closer to the window.
- Someone will see you, Mother.
AAre you ashamed of me?.
You know why, Mother. They've
even written about you in the paper.
Stop your whining, boy.
AAll this fuss over nothing.
Not nothing. I saw her.
Even the initials on the suitcase.
M.C., Marion Crane.
AAnother of your cheap,
erotic delusions.
You killed her.
The slut deserved it. But she's dead.
AAnd the dead don't come back.
You came back.
- I never went away.
Don't you know that by now?.
You can't get rid of me.
I'll always be with you, Norman.
AAlways.
Stand up straight and
wipe your snotty little nose.
If the disgusting little whore upsets
you so much, just get rid of her.
No!
Then maybe I will.
You have an obligation, Maureen.
Maureen, don't!
There is no God.
Please Maureen, you mustn't.
Get away. You'll burn in hell.
You have an obligation.
I have nothing.
I am nothing.
What'll it be?.
- Give me a beer.
Hi.
I'm Duane.
- No kidding?.
AAny objections
to a guy buying you a drink?.
I got a drink.
- So have another.
You got a limit?.
- Only to my patience.
You don't have to call me Duane.
- No, I don't. - Friends call me Duke.
I had a dog named Duke once.
- Really?.
Scratch my belly, my leg'll shake.
- I hated the mutt.
Keep the matches, lady. You need 'em.
You're as warm as a cry for help.
Just a minute. Duke. AAh, Duane.
Whatever. I'm easy.
- I've noticed.
You staying there?.
- Working there.
Even better.
Let's sit down. I'll buy.
Help.
Help me!
Miserere mei, Deus.
Forgive me.
I figured Bates was a geek.
But a full-fledged loony tune?.
You think he offed this Spool broad?.
- Well, he acted pretty weird.
But then he's pretty a weird guy.
- No shit.
So you'll pay me for...
- AAnything I can use. - How about:
AA girl checked in this afternoon.
Nice looker, too. When Norman saw her,
he kind of freaked.
Strolling down memory lane.
AAre you leaving so soon?.
- I'm afraid so.
Don't you want to work this off
in trade?. I'll credit your account.
You shouldn't rely so much
on that face and those pearly whites,
because come-ons like that
could get them punched out.
Forgive me.
You're alright.
You're in St. Matthew's Hospital.
I'm Father Brian.
I'm the resident psychiatrist.
Maureen,
do you know who saved you?.
Mary.
I'm sure she had a hand in it.
But there was someone else.
You ought to be real proud, Norman.
- Yes, it was very heroic.
How do you happen to be here?.
- Just my dumb luck.
I saw the ambulance leaving the motel
and wanted to see what was up.
Must've been disappointing for you.
- How did Norman find out?.
Towels. - Towels.
- Yes, he took her some fresh towels.
Now I do know my job, Ms. Vanderbilt.
- Mr. Bates, she wants to see you.
I wouldn't pick out a silverware
pattern just yet, sheriff.
You found me, Mr. Bates.
Norman.
My name's Maureen.
I just wanted to thank you
for what you did.
I can't have that going on
in my motel. It gives it a bad name.
Please don't take it the wrong way,
Marion. I'm sorry, I mean, Maureen.
I'm sorry.
- I did leave the bathroom a mess.
I've seen it worse.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to be such a bother.
Oh, you're no bother.
No bother at all.
People should look out
for each other, don't you think?.
Sometimes we get lost.
But if there'd only been someone
to help us understand,
then maybe we wouldn't do
some of the sad, awful things we do.
You're very kind.
You should rest.
Do you have somewhere to go
when you get out?.
If you want, you can stay
at the motel until you're better.
FOC, of course. Free of charge.
AAs long as you like. It's never full.
It would give you
a chance to sort things out.
Why are you so kind to me?.
You remind me of someone I knew once.
You don't know me.
AAfter the way you found me,
you must think I'm mad.
- No, no.
We all go a little mad, sometimes.
But sometimes...
the despair is just so overwhelming,
that all you want is for it to stop.
I'd like to stay at your motel
for a few days, if you don't mind.
I'm glad you're safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you for looking out for me.
Sure.
You were down there, Mother.
Weren't you?.
I'm glad she didn't die. I'm glad.
She will.
Don't you touch her. Never!
Be quiet or someone will hear us.
- Let them.
Let them hear.
- They sure like the TV up loud.
I'm sorry.
AAre you okay?.
- Yeah.
I usually keep this locked
when no one's here.
Mommy's little helper. Very sweet.
You always watch TV so loud?.
Oh, the TV, yeah.
Who are you?.
AA friend of Duke's?.
- We're getting to know each other.
Why don't you come and
join our party?.
Oh, no. No, thanks.
Too bad. Thanks for looking after me.
See you around, maybe.
Oh my God.
Maybe!
Hey,
watch the guitar.
Oh God, don't tell me you're of those
who farts, rolls over and sleeps.
I picked you up in a bar.
What, you want to get married?.
You shithead!
I got to get up for work soon.
Just go home.
How?.
You brought me out here.
Here's the cab fare.
Phone book's on the table.
You make it all sound so cheap.
- It is, but it beats a vibrator.
Yeah?.
AAt least a vibrator gets me off.
Use the payphone, bitch.
- Ouch. Let go!
Give me my clothes. Bastard!
You fucking idiot!
Oh shit.
No! Help!
We're unable to complete
your call as dialed.
Please hang up and dial again.
Mother! Oh God, Mother!
Blood, blood!
Up early, huh?.
When I was young, my parents
always made all my decisions.
Becoming a nun was my idea.
But as my final vows grew closer,
it became so frightening.
I began to dwell upon things
that I would never know.
What things?.
Hungers for the flesh, Father.
It's perfectly normal.
Sister Catherine said
it was bad, and...
if my faith were strong enough,
that I wouldn't have evil thoughts.
Why didn't you just leave the
novitiate rather than be tormented?.
But the Church teaches us
to endure suffering.
It also teaches us
that suicide is a sin.
I knew it was wrong, Father.
I was afraid...
to face the consequences of my sins.
Maureen, it seems that only you
have given up on yourself, not God.
Why else would he have twice saved you
from your own desperateness?.
The other night,
as I lay there,
I saw the Virgin standing above me.
AA halo of white light was about her,
and she held a shiny, silver crucifix.
Her arms were outstretched
as if she were beckoning me.
Oh Father, what did she want of me?.
What about this?. - Maybe she got
change for the phone or cigarettes.
It might help if you knew her name.
- Forgot to ask.
It usually comes after "Hi, I'm Duane,
but you can call me Duke."
I'm more interested in those voices
you heard up at the house.
Maybe voices.
It could have been a TV or a radio.
Quite a crowd!
- Yeah, homecoming weekend.
They're celebrating the big victory.
The game's not until tonight.
Where are you going?. - You said
he's at the hospital picking her up.
Yeah. But what if he comes back?.
You don't know a thing.
Fairvale or Central?. Come on!
Where are you from?. - Fairvale.
Too bad. Hope you don't mind losing.
Ms. Vanderbilt!
AAfter you check in, come down to 4.
There's a party. We gonna beat you.
Ms. Vanderbilt, are you looking
for something?. - Just you.
Hoping we can finish our little chat.
- Your chats end up sounding
more like interrogations.
- AAnother time?. - No.
AAnd please, don't come back.
Oh, Norman. How sweet of you.
You had them cleaned.
- They were a little wrinkled and wet.
AAnd a little out of style, too.
Oh, no. Conservative clothes
never go out of style.
I especially like that one.
You'd look swell in that tonight.
I think Mrs. Spool said she had
a son once. But he never visited her.
AAnd she never went anywhere.
- Never went out, huh?.
Just work. AA real homebody.
I've got a backed-up toilet in 6...
- Mind if I stay and snoop a bit?.
Why should l?. The cops have already
paraded through here and everything.
You can rent it for all I care.
Spoolie's rent was two weeks past due.
How much for just a couple of hours?.
- Thanks...
It's a pleasure to see a woman here
without blue hair and varicose veins.
Yeah.
- Just close the door when you leave.
Sure thing.
Bates Motel.
Hello?.
I'm going now. I won't be out late.
Mother?.
She's a nice girl.
I've never drunk this much before.
- Me neither.
My mother never allowed liquor
at home. - What can we toast to now?.
To happiness.
Would you like to dance?.
- Oh, no. No. I couldn't.
It's very easy.
My mother taught me. Come on.
I feel woozy.
- lt'll make you light on your feet.
Norman, I feel silly.
- Nothing wrong in that.
Just follow me.
I go forward, you go back.
Slow, slow, quick, quick...
See?. You just learned
your basic back step.
Slow, slow, quick, quick...
Oh well, they say
the wet-look is coming back.
How's the party going, Duke?.
- It's cool, Norm.
You mind hanging on for a while?.
- It's your overtime.
What's wrong?.
I must've had too much to drink.
I just thought
I saw a woman in your house.
It's okay, Duke. You can go now.
Whatever you say, boss.
Sorry, I can't offer you anything
to drink. - That's okay.
Except water.
- That's fine.
They're pretty loud.
I had a very special time tonight.
- Me too.
Thank you.
I should go.
Because of her?.
- Who?.
That lady you say I remind you of.
Did she mean a lot to you?.
We weren't...
It wasn't...
Iike it is with you.
How is it with me?.
What's wrong?.
I'm sorry, Maureen.
I can't do this.
It wouldn't be right.
Not just now.
It wouldn't be right?.
Let's just lie here...
and hold each other.
Sorry to wake you, honey, but
you fell asleep with the door open.
With all these horny bastards
running around here, it's not a good
idea. Just wanted to let you know.
Thank you.
- I'll close it on my way out.
You dirty, dirty boy!
But I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything, Mother.
She's a nice girl.
- She's a whore.
We didn't do anything.
- You let her come between us.
It isn't right. It isn't natural.
It's perfectly natural
for a son to love his mother.
Would you leave me alone, Mother!
Will you leave me alone!
Norman,
are you in there?. AAre you awake?.
It's me, Maureen.
- Bring me the knife, Norman.
Norman!
AAre you up there?.
- Bring it to me.
Did you hear me?. What are you doing?.
Can't you do it?.
Please answer me. It's Maureen.
What do you want?.
- What happened to you?.
AAre you alright?.
- Yes.
No... I'm feeling a little sick.
Let me come up.
- No. Get away!
I had a little too much to drink.
That's all. I just need to rest.
AAlright, Norman.
Please, Maureen,
go back to your room.
Lock your door.
Please!
- AAlright.
Stop! Stop!
You haven't changed in 15 years.
You're still disgusting.
Ruthie, all cheerleaders
boff the linemen.
I wasn't a cheerleader.
I was a majorette.
You can twirl on...
What?.
- You can twirl on my...
You can twirl on my baton.
Hey, cutie.
Hello?.
You have a john?.
Men!
Hey, where'd you come from?.
Geez, you scared the piss out of me.
Do you mind, sister?.
This is occupado.
Duke?.
Hey, innkeeper, I need change!
- Charlie, I got it.
Get away from me.
Looks like someone's getting lucky!
What's happening?.
Come on, Leo.
Don't go up there.
- Why?. Something's wrong with Norman?.
It's time somebody told you.
Good morning, Norman. It's a bit hot
to be sleeping so late, isn't it?.
We had a lot of revelers last night.
- I know.
One didn't come home.
Name is Patsy Boyle.
She came with a group of locals
to party after the game.
When they all left around 3,
nobody noticed that she wasn't there.
Someone's missing and you come to me.
- There have been other accusations.
From that reporter! She knows nothing.
That's what we're going to find out.
Now it's too hot to argue.
That rain made everything more muggy.
- Nothing back there. - Of course not.
Please get out of my house.
- Sorry, Norman.
We have the warrant.
It's in everybody's best interest.
Who's?. There's nothing here.
I didn't do anything.
Then there's nothing to worry about.
Norman, come back!
Get him, Leo. Doggone you!
Norman,
what the hell's the matter with you?.
Mother?.
I'm sorry, Norman.
AAll seems a little unnecessary now.
- That's okay.
Still no reason to get so...
so riled up.
We'll leave you alone now. AAgain,
I'm sorry. - That's not enough.
You just can't let it lie!
I've had enough
of this Nancy Drew horseshit.
I'm letting it lie and so are you.
Until I have evidence to the contrary,
both ladies are missing persons.
AAren't you going to question him?.
Why not drag the swamp?.
He dumped the last bodies there.
Don't tell me my job,
Ms. Vanderbilt.
Somebody has to.
You're not going to let him go?.
- Despite all your glib insinuations,
I don't have one iota of proof.
- He didn't do it.
Norman was with me
until 6 o'clock this morning.
Whatever happened to that girl,
he didn't have anything to do with it.
- Well, Miss,
had you told us sooner, you would
have saved us a lot of trouble.
No one asked me.
- Come on, Leo.
Bad time to beat the street, Norman.
You'd better follow
the sheriff's example.
I'm taking a passenger. Ready?.
She told you about me, didn't she?.
- Yes.
Where are you going?.
Father Brian said I could come stay
with him if I needed to.
Please let me go.
Mother!
Mother, where are you?.
I love the silver
that shines in your hair.
AAnd the brow that's all furled
and wrinkled with care.
I kissed the dear fingers,
so toilworn for me.
Oh God bless you and keep you,
dear Mother...
Bates.
It doesn't scan, does it, Norman?.
But...
a lot of shit around here doesn't.
What are you doing with my mother?.
Don't you mean...
Mummy?.
You did a nice job on her, Norman.
Fresh as the day she was croaked.
Why?.
Just looking out for you.
AAnd yourself.
- I have ambitions, dreams.
But dreams don't come cheap nowadays.
I could have turned
Mom over to the cops,
but all I would have gotten
was a pat on the back.
That reporter
would've shelled out a few bucks,
and gotten the lion's share
of the credit, a five-figure salary,
and a big news job.
Fine for her dreams,
but what about mine?. No.
I figure Mama's greatest value to me
is in her value to you.
I don't have that kind of money.
- Don't gripe to me.
With that big piece of real estate
and this thriving business,
you could just sell an acre.
Please, Duke.
I want my mother back.
Take her. You know what I want.
AAnd you know what I'll do
if I don't get it.
I know.
I'm going to kill you,
you little freak.
You think I'm stupid, Duke?.
Even if I gave you money,
you'd still tell on Mother.
No one must know what she did.
She can't help it.
She can't help the things she does.
She's just an old lady.
AA sick, old lady.
Watch the guitar!
You shouldn't sneak up
on a guy like that, Duke. Duke?.
I didn't mean it.
You made me do this!
Your tainted blood in me!
Don't laugh at me, Mother.
Don't laugh at me.
I didn't even know she had any kids.
- Wasn't it on her job application?.
She was already here
when I bought the place 7 years ago.
Best waitress I ever had.
- She worked for the previous owner?.
Harvey Leech. - Where's he now?.
- He used to be in a nursing home.
Outside town.
- Probably dead now.
Spool?.
- Emma Spool.
She worked in your diner.
- Diner?.
Yeah, I had a diner once.
- Mrs. Spool used to work for you.
I had a woman named Spool
who used to work for me. AA waitress.
She come from that place.
- Place?.
That place for nuts. AAs-s-asylum.
Mrs Spool was in an asylum?.
AAsylum, that's it, asylum.
You know, she killed somebody.
Who?.
- Somebody. Husband?.
I don't recall. Good waitress, Spool.
AAre you sure, Maureen?.
- Oh yes.
Norman understands me.
He understands forgiveness.
I failed so many people, Father.
I won't fail him.
That's why Mary came to me
the night he saved my life.
It was a sign.
AAnd the woman in the window.
That must've been Mary too.
I'll be back, Mother.
Miserere mei, Deus...
I thought if she saw these copies
she might change her story.
Can I see her?.
I'm afraid not.
Norman!
Norman?. It's me.
I've come back.
I never should've gone away.
Whatever happened to you in your past,
I know you're good. You took a life,
but you also saved a life.
My life.
Let it be your life.
Oh, Norman!
What happened to you?.
- I slipped in the mud.
I slipped too.
I know I've hurt you.
Can you forgive me?.
- Norman!
Maureen?. Maureen?.
Mother!
Maureen?.
Get that whore out of my house!
Throw her down in the mud,
filth, where she belongs.
I'll get you for this, Mother.
I'll get you for this.
You haven't got the guts, boy.
You dumb, stupid,
naive girl.
Why can't you leave my poor son,
my Norman, alone?.
What set you off again, Norman?.
You killed Mrs. Spool, didn't you?.
Did she tell you
that she was your mother?.
She was crazy, Norman,
but she wasn't your mother.
Neither are you!
She was your aunt,
and in love with your father.
But your mother stole him
away from her. Emma Spool...
killed your father in a jealous rage
and kidnapped you as a baby.
She killed your father
because she thought you were hers.
The child
she should've had with him.
She was crazy.
They locked her away.
- It's lies, it's all lies.
She's a lying whore.
- Norman, where are you?.
She's a slut.
Don't let her talk about me like that.
Norman, please listen to me!
Norman, Mrs. Bates! Whoever you are.
It doesn't matter to me.
Get her, boy.
Get her, just like the others!
Get her!
- No! No!
Don't! Don't! Please! Norman!
No!
Norman, can't you do anything right?.
How dare you treat your mother
in such ways.
So, I don't have the guts, huh?.
I was for you, Norman.
Believed in you.
You made a fool of me.
Look what you did to yourself!
Why, Norman, why?.
Good God, son,
you'll never get out again.
They're going to lock you up forever.
But I'll be free.
I'll finally be free.