Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
-Yeah
-What’s that
Yeah
-Yeah
-Funky, funky
-How ‘bout a big hand now
-Wait-Wait a minute
Groovy, groovy, jazzy, funky
pounce, pounce dance
As we dip in the melodic sea the rhythm
keeps flowing and drips to M.C.
Sweet, sugar pop
sugar pop, roxy pop
You don’t stop
‘til the sweet beat drops
I’m showin’ proof as I stick
and move, every poem’s recited on top of the groove
Smooth my floatin’ like a
butterfly, notes that are floatin’ sung like a lullaby
Brace yourself as the beat hits ya
dip trip, flip fantasia
[ Radio ]
-Yeah
-What’s that
-Biddy-diddy bop
-Yeah
Biddy-diddy bop
Funky, funky
funky, funky
-Would you like another muffin?
-No, that’s, uh, fine.
[ Clears Throat ]
Just take one, please.
I’ll give you another. They
check in, but they don’t check-out. Billy Rago wrote that.
The guy was practically a god in New York.
Worked for all the heavy shops...
before we got him out here,
and I’m telling you, we had to beg.
It’s got to be the traffic.
He’s always on time.
Have another muffin.
I’ll see what I can do.
-[ Man On Radio ] W-E-Z,
Detroit. The Big Wheeze.!
-[ Phone Rings ]
-Yeah?
-Where are you?
Where am I?
Take a look out the window.
I’m parked in the middle of Jefferson.
-I’ve been here for 20 minutes.
-What?
It’s construction everywhere.
They’re laying down cones.
Hey.! You had to pick today?
These guys are on a 1 0:30 back
to Chicago. They’re not
the sitting-around types.
I’m 500 yards away.
Can’t you stall ‘em? Give ‘em a muffin.
I’ve been stalling. We talked
about the Bulls three times.
They didn’t like the muffins.
-Just put me on the speaker.
-What? No way.
-I’ll pitch in on the phone.
Let me talk to these clowns.
-Okay.
Uh, we’re gonna try
a little modern science here.
We do it all the time.
-Bill, you still with us?
-Uh, yeah. Can they hear me?
Bill, I want you to meet Noah Bradley
and Peter Brosnan of Key Brands.
-Morning.
-Noah. Pete. Good to see ya.
Yeah, Bill, listen,
we really do have a plane to catch.
Hey, guys, I mean, can’t you wait
ten minutes? It’s not
the last flight out of town.
Look, you guys see the panels
on the board there?
-Jack, flip up the first panel.
-Bill, I think--
Just flip up the first panel!
Jesus, a lab monkey could do that!
-Okay, now.
-Let me take you to the panels.
When you think of food wrap,
you think of America, baseball, Mom...
apple pie, the old west.
-Speaking of which, you should
be looking at a sheriff.
-[ Together] Yeah.
Yeah, well he’s sittin’ there and
he’s got his feet up on the desk, see.
Now, behind him, his jail cell
is covered with Key Brands food wrap.
Right? Now, we got
all this food inside tryin’ to escape.
We got an actor dressed up as a melon.
One is a wedge of cheese.
Another one is uh, um,
is a, uh, um, um--
-Another one is, uh--
-A sandwich.
Okay. A sandwich. Right.
And the sheriff smiles
into the camera and he says--
Blow it out your butt, tubby!
That’s right, wide load. I’m talkin’
to you, fatso. You guys aren’t fat?
Anyway, so the sheriff’s lookin’
right into the camera and he says...
Partners, there’s only one way--
[ Static ]
"Key Brand--’"[ Static Continues ]
"... Name that means qual--’"
-[ Static ] You get a sheriff like...
-I think we’re having
a little phone trouble.
-the guy from Gunsmoke.
-Bill, you’ve gone into cell hell.
[ Woman ]
Hi, I’m Joy.
If you want to be dominated, press one.
If you want to discipline me, press two.
-No, that’s not Bill.
We’ve got some crossover here.
-[ Man ] How many kilos?
Stop it!
Moms will love it. Dads’ll love it.
Kids are gonna have shiny badges, boots.
Look, I may lose you in the elevator,
but I’ll see you in a couple of seconds.
-[ Elevator Bell Rings ]
-You got me? Hello?
-One, two, three, four--okay.
-Good morning. Shorris-Grey Advertising.
Whoo! Traffic was a--
-[ Panting ] Where are they?
-[ Groans ]
I’ll pack up your office.
I kept the boxes we moved in
with. It’ll save a few bucks.
-[Jack ] Let me talk to him.
-[ Man ] Tell him to print up
some resumes.
-Oh, come on, Paul.
-Come on, what? The guy’s
been runnin’on fumes.
His work’s slipping. He’s hostile
to clients. I couldn’t believe it.!
A six-million-dollar account
and what do you got?
-You got two guys staring
at a speaker phone!
-What was I supposed to do?
You were supposed to be
working with professionals.
-I’ve never seen a stunt
like that in my life.
-Paul, look.
The man’s had a few personal setbacks
the last couple years.
[ Beeps ]
[ Man ] Yes, this is Evan from
You-Love-To-Rent Furniture.
You love to rent, but apparently,
you don’t love to pay.
Our truck will be there at 9::00 a.m.
Thank you. [ Machine Beeps ]
Bill, it’s Jack. Listen,
I’m making a few calls...
but I got to tell ya, you burned
a few bridges out there, pal.
Now, I’m gonna try and line up
some freelance stuff next month.
Just stay in touch, okay?
Bye.
[ Machine Beeps ]
Mr. Rago, my name’s Akeem.
I deliver your Free Press.
You still owe me $ 1 1.50.
[ Machine Beeps ]
Hi, Daddy. It’s me, Emily.
Daddy, I know you’re probably
still at work, but, uh, listen.
I hate to ask you this, but Mom said
she’s broke until next month...
and since you just got that big, new
Key Brands account, I had to ask you.
So, here it goes. There’s an eclipse
coming up in Mexico, and it’s a big deal.
My whole astronomy club
is going. If we get the ticket
early enough, it’ll be cheap.
This is really important to me.
I really, really want to go.
There it is. Thanks, Daddy.
[ Machine Beeps ]
[ People Singing ]
-Hey, buddy, you got two bits?
-No.
[ Harmonizing ]
I’m flat broke but I don’t care
[ Man ]
I got better things to do than--
[ Female Clerk ]
How many times I gotta tell you?
-You can’t collect unemployment
if you don’t look for a job.
-[ Grunts ]
[ Male Clerk ]
If you bring that in, we’ll help you.
-Thank you.
-Next!
[ Exhales, Sighs ]
-You were in advertising, I see. Hmm!
-Yeah.
Princeton?
-Guess that was before
it went co-ed. [ Laughs ]
My, my, schools like that, you think
they’d teach you how to read.
-Wrong line.
-What?
New claims are the two windows
at the end. You get that
stamped, you come back to me.
What are you, crazy?
I’ve been here since 9:00.
So have I. Next!
-[ Female Clerk ] Number 1 25.
-[ Woman ] Okay.
-You’ll hear from us. Next!
-Thanks.
You think there’s a chance
I could get unemployment
before I get social security?
Have you previously collected benefits?
No. I’ve always had a job.
Can you operate any industrial machinery,
farm equipment?
Yeah. That was a required course
in college. Theory of Plowing.
I have all day, Bill.
Now, why don’t you tell me what
you’d be willing to do?
If you give me a check,
I’d be willing to cash it.
Come here.
Now, this is your first time here, right?
A man your age. It can’t be easy.
You’re humiliated.
You’re frustrated.
I see it on
a hundred people’s faces everyday.
And whether you believe it or not,
I feel for each and every one of’ em.
Now...
you can either help me help you,
or you can be an asshole...
in which case
I’m gonna make you stand there
until you die and turn to dust.
So...
let’s begin again.
Have you previously collected benefits?
No.
What would you be willing to do?
Milk cows.
Uh... shear sheep.
-Pluck chickens.
-All right, Bill.
A couple of weeks
you’ll hear from us. Next.!
[ Bill ] Smack it.! Run.!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.!
-Aw! Oh!
-Bang, bang, bang.
He can’t run. Two million dollars a year,
he runs like Bill Clinton.
The eclipse, Dad. Mexico.
Come on, Emily.
You don’t wanna go down there.
It’s a hundred degrees.
You get held up at the airport.
-You probably won’t get off the toilet
long enough to see it, anyway.
-Dad!
[ Bill Groans ]
Astronomy? Jesus, when are you
gonna grow up?
-I am growin’ up.
You know it’s what I wanna do.
-Damn!
There’s the path to big bucks.
Starin’ out into space. Look!
I discovered Venus. Pay me.
Astrology, maybe you could make
a few dollars doin’ people’s
horoscopes or somethin’.
Why do you always have to be
such a jerk about all this for?
-Frozen malts.
-You want a frozen malt?
-No.
-Gimme two. Gimme two.
Em. Wait a minute. Em, come on.
I’m sure you’ll find a very nice eclipse
to see around here someday.
-Yeah, in the year 2047!
-You want your pennant?
No, I just want you
to believe in me.
[ People Singing ]
-Hi, guys, how ya doin’? Okay.
-Okay.
You feel like you wanna drown
-Next!
-Hi, Beverly.
-Bill. Good to see you.
-How are the kids?
-Great. Everything’s great.
-Good.
-How’s your daughter?
-She hates my guts.
Surprise, surprise.
You know, it’s strange.
I don’t like you either.
Yet somehow I’m gonna miss you.
We found you a job.
There you go.
What do you think?
-I can’t do this.
-Sure you can.
No, no, no, no. I--Beverly.
You got the wrong file.
When have I ever been a teacher?
Look, you got a master’s degree.
That means you can teach.
No, it doesn’t. No, it only means
hypothetically that I could.
Come on, Bill.
Now, it’s a good job. Six weeks.
A decent salary.
And you get to live there.
Bev-Beverly,
I-I’ll get my head blown off.
Do you know how many kids
carry guns to school these days?
Hmph! In this case, all of’ em.
[ Chuckles ] I guess you didn’t get
to the "where’" part.
Must be the army
that’s turning me on
that’s making me strong
Yes, sir.
Sir. Halt.
-May I help you?
-Yeah.
I need directions
to the Army Education Center.
A.E.C.? That’s building 231 0.
Park your vehicle in the green zone,
step inside, get a pass.
I’m runnin’ a little late.
Can’t I drive somewhere?
Yes, sir. You can drive
to the green zone and get a pass.
Look, I’m not even in the army.
I just have to meet--
Park in the green zone,
step inside, get a pass!
Right.
Green zone, inside, pass.
You’d probably get along good
with my ex-wife.
I’m just a soldier, Sergeant
marching for you
[ Drill Sergeant ]  I will not quit
until P.T. is through
-I will not quit
-Excuse me.
Excuse me. I’m lookin’ for
the Army Education Center.
Captain Tom Murdoch.
Captain Murdoch’s not at the A.E.C.
Captain Murdoch’s at the A.R.C.
A.R.C., A.E.C.
You lookin’ for Captain Murdoch?
The A.E.C. is building 231 0.
-You want building 4475.
-447--
Look, here’s what you do. You go right
here. Take another right at the P.X.
Go half a click ‘til you see
the D.P.T.M. Center.
-Then take a left.
-P.M., P.X.
If you hit the R.F.P.C.,
you’ve gone too far.
[ Sighs ]
D.P.T.M.
R.F.P.C.
Can I buy a vowel?
[ Ringing ]
Captain Murdoch’s office.
May I help you? Oh, hi again, sir.
-Can you hold?
-Okay, Sergeant, these are ready to go.
-Uh, sir.
-Bill Rago.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Well, actually, I needed
to catch up on world events.
-That Gulf War thing
worked out for us, huh?
-Sure did.
I’m Tom Murdoch. Welcome to Fort McClane.
Would you come with me, please?
-Give us a couple of minutes.
-Sir, the extra housing units.
I’m workin’ on it.
They keep shutting down forts
on us and we’ve picked up
troops from every goddamn one.
I got 1 5 buses coming in
at 21 00. Fifteen!
-Bummer.
-I’ve got that key somewhere.
Uh, uh... here it is.
Would you come with me, please, Bill?
-You mean, go?
-Yeah, after you.
-Ever been in the army?
-No.
Good. I’ll show you around
and explain your job to you.
-The sergeant sent us a list of names.
-Next.
No go, they said.
These are the ones who can’t hack it.
-None of’ em wanted the boot.
They all volunteered.
-Ouch!
-[ Groans ]
-Come on, Bill. It don’t hurt
much. They all go through it.
Where was I? That’s when
Colonel James stepped in.
He put out a call to find the kids that
could best be served by this program.
-[ Panting ]
-Keep breathing.
-This is sick.
-Bill?
-You all right? What are they
gonna catch in Michigan?
Bill? Stay with me, okay?
The point is, their Drill Sergeants
out there in the field...
didn’t have the time
to explain everything a
dozen times over to these guys.
As far as I’m concerned, they
shouldn’t have to. But that’s
strictly between you and me.
-Okay.
-Hoo-ah, Drill Sergeant!
-I can’t hear you!
[ Capt. Murdoch ] So the squeakers
we’re talkin’ about are in your file.
-Why don’t you just send
the squeakers home?
-That’s a darn good question.
Ask the colonel. He keeps insisting if
we can help ‘em do push-ups...
we can give ‘em a hand
in the brain department.
That’s where you come in, Wild Bill.
You’re it for these guys.
-The last chance saloon.
Sergeant Save-it.
-Is it much further?
-What’s this?
-Oh, isn’t that a thing of beauty?
That’s our victory tower.
Biggest one in the country.
We give ‘em physical confidence.
Doesn’t do much good
if they got sawdust for brains.
What we need you to do is to
get ‘em to think a little better
on their feet. That’s all.
-[ Screaming ]
-Oops.
Must be one of yours, Bill.
[ Laughing ]
Let me get this straight.
-The colonel selected these
eight kids for his program?
-Right.
-And you want me to teach
these guys how to comprehend?
-Yes, sir.
-Hard stroke left!
-[ Recruits Shouting ] Kill! Kill!
Are they saying kill?
-You betcha.
-[ Recruits ] Kill! Kill!
[ Bill ] Victory what?
Victory Starts Here.
That’s Fort McClane’s motto.
Novel.
Here it is, Bill.
Home sweet home.
-[ Recruits Singing ]
-They never stop singing.
What about my car and all my stuff?
Don’t worry about a thing, Bill.
It’s all taken care of.
Would you like to do the honors?
Yeah. [ Sighs ]
I’ve died and gone
to Gomer Pyle’s house.
[ Murdoch ] He’s a marine, Bill.
What did I tell ya?
-[ Door Closes ]
-Bill.
Your bedroom with a closet
and a latrine are right over here.
-[ Bill ] Mmm, elegant.
-Come on. Lots to see.
And you were worried about your stuff.
All-purpose table.
And... you share this lovely kitchen
with the people next door.
-What?
-It’s a Scandinavian thing.
Simplicity of design. Economy.
-Uh, the Swedes I think.
-You ever wonder why so many
of’ em blow their brains out?
[ Chuckles ]
I’m gonna use that one.
I’ll let you get washed up, Bill.
You got 40 minutes ‘til your first class.
Cheer up, will you?
You’re serving your country now.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Exhales ] I’m honored.
I won an advertising award.
What am I doin’ here?
[ Sighs ]
-Maybe I could hock it.
-[ Banging ]
[ Recruits Chanting ]
Hi. [ Chuckles ]
I’m Bill Rago.
Uh, welcome to...
the first class
in basic comprehension.
[ Exhales ]
I’ve never taught before...
and you’ve never thought before,
[ Chuckles ] so good luck to all of us.
[ Sighs ]
Oh.
[ Mumbles ] What am I gonna do?
-[ Man ] Left.! Left, right.
-[ Recruits ] Warriors.!
-Left! Left! Left, right!
-Warriors!
-Left.! Left.! Left, right.!
-One, two, Warriors.!
Left! Left!
Left, column right, march!
Left, right, left.
Left! Left!
Squad, halt!
-[ Marching Stops ]
-Left, face!
Sir!
First squad reporting
for instructions, sir! Sound off!.
Sir, Private Myers, 1 02 4, sir!
Sir, Private Benitez, 7 061 , sir!
-Sir, Private Haywood, 389--
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[ Chuckles ] Lighten up. Uh, you guys
don’t have to do this.
This is just a class. We’re not
invading Angola here. [ Chuckles ]
Uh--
-Um--
-Sir, permission to speak, sir.
-Yeah, sure, speak.
-Sir, what should we call you, sir?
Bill.
[ Clears Throat ]
Uh, si-sir! I think the private
means your rank, sir!
Well, I don’t have one.
I’m a civilian.
-Oh, man.
-What?
You got to be kidding me. They let
a civilian in here. I don’t believe this.
To teach double-D’s? Who do you think
they gonna get, Colin Powell?
-[ Squad Leader ] Squad, sit.
-I ain’t no double-D, homeboy.
You speak for your damn self.
Wait, hold up. You in here
by accident? You somebody
special? I don’t think so.
-Sit your dumb double-D ass
down, Haywood.
-Screw you.
-Asswipe.
-Screw you!
-[ All Chattering At Once ]
-You wanna sit down or you
want me to sit you down?
Haywood!
-Stop it.!
-Whoa, whoa.
-Guys, guys.
-Haywood, sit down. Yo, yo.
-Sit down. Sit down.
-That’s Shaolin, see?
-Why don’t you do something?
-What do you want me to do?
Haywood, sit down.
Hey! Hello? Hello!
-[ All Chattering At Once ]
-[ Whistling ]
What the hell’s goin’ on here?
-That dumb-ass hillbilly
talkin’ that bullshit.
-Look at your dumb ass.
Haywood, please!
-Look, you don’t wanna be here
and I don’t wanna be here.
-You got that right.
So let’s just make
the best of this, okay?
God! Squeakers.
And what’s a double-D?
The whole fort calls us double-D’s.
-Yeah, dumb as dogs hit.
-[ Both Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Howling ]
All right, I’m supposed
to take attendance now.
So, uh, help me out, all right?
[ Whispers ]
I’ll help you out.
-Benitez, Donald.
-Yup, yup.
That’s me. Present.
New York City, New York.
-[ Scoffs ] Who would a guessed?
-You’re killin’ me, Haywood.
-[ Haywood ] I just might.
-Haywood.
Here we go. Tommy Lee.
Present, sir. Tommy Lee Haywood.
Willacoochee, Georgia.
Is that as small as it sounds?
-No, sir.
-Sooey.!
Small? This boy grew up in a cave.
His mother come downstairs every morning.
[ Stomping ] Tommy Lee.
Time for breakfast. Run on out there
and scrape up a squirrel.
We’re gonna have us
a "roadkill omelette".
Aaah, back at ya.
[ Bill ] Hobbs, Roosevelt.
-Uh, it says here you’re from Detroit?
-Mm-hmm.
-What part?
-The part you drive through doin’ 85.
-Been there.
-Mm-hmm.
-Is anybody else from Detroit?
-Hoo-ah.
-Yeah.
Miranda Myers, it says Cleveland here.
Yeah, I lived there too. I lived
in Pittsburgh, St. Louis, Miami, L.A.
-Seattle.
-Any particular reason?
My mother liked to drive.
-Sound like she liked that
back seat kinda right too.
-Excuse me.
-[ Bill ] All right, all right.
-[ Groans ] Yo!
-Now, you deserved that.
-True.
-She hit harder than you, Haywood.
-[ Haywood ] Very funny.
Leroy Jackson.
Yes, sir. Um, but that’s
Jackson Leroy, sir.
Oh, sorry. It says here
you play football.
-Yes, sir. Well, I--I did for a while.
-All-state.
-Yeah. Um--yeah.
-This boy was all-planet.
I seen him one time pick off
a pass and go 90 yards through
the other team like, bang.!
Left ‘em all on the field.
Dead. This boy got skill.!
Gimme some love, kid.
Two times. Go ahead,
sit on down, Heisman boy.
You should a won the Heisman.
-What?
-Uh--
Brian Davis, Junior, sir.
Grand Forks, North Dakota.
-Hey, Bill. Ask him about his daddy.
-Yeah.
Shut up, Benitez!
-My daddy was the bravest
and neatest soldier...
-[ Bill ] Hey.!
-in the whole wide world.
-Everybody shut up! God!
Um, Melvin, Mel.
Charlotte, North Carolina.
Melvin Melvin?
-[ Snoring Lightly ]
-Is he up?
Mel. He does this
sometimes, Bill. Mel.
Hey, Bill, he was at the B.R.M.
yesterday in the hole
with his rifle, just like this.
-[ Snores ]
-And you’re--
Me? Montgomery, Jamaal,
from Detroit, Michigan.
Jamaal, you mind letting
these people speak for themselves?
How he gonna speak?
That boy droolin’ down his chest.
None of the others are.
You got a wise comment for everybody.
Bill, what’s the matter?
I’m tryin’ to help you. I’m
your assistant. What’s what?
-Yeah, well you’re succeeding
in bein’ an asshole.
-Aw, thank you!
Hey, he can’t do that.
You can’t do that. You can’t
do that. You cannot do that.
-It says in the rule book--
-Thank you.
Shut up! No soldier shall
be singled out for abusive
mistreatment of any kind!
-That’s regulation.
Leroy, I want a new teacher.
-Shut up.
-Shut up?
[ Bill ] All right, all right.
[ Sighs ] So much for attendance.
So, Mr. Rago,
what are you gonna teach us?
That’s a good question.
Anybody got any ideas?
How ‘bout teachin’
somebody to get a job?
Uh--
All right. We’ll begin
with language skills.
Everybody will read something.
What?
Not for nothin’, I mean,
I don’t see any books.
Maybe you do, but I don’t.
-You know what I’m sayin’.
-All right.
Then we’ll all write something.
Would you hand these out for me?
-[ Benitez ] Hoo-ah.!
-Here you go. Thanks.
Um... start now and have these ready
for the next class.
Uh, write about... why you’re here.
-This is where they told us to come.
-No.
I mean the magical twist of fate
that prompted you to gravitate...
toward this institute of imbeciles.
What?
Write why you joined the army.
Why I joined the army.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Montgomery ] I joined to be
with you, Billy boy.
Do you want us to,
like, write that at the top, sir?
W-Why I joined the army?
[ Sighs ]
-[ Bugle Playing Reveille ]
-[ Groans ]
[ Troops Shouting ]
-[ Bangs Table ]
-[ Groaning ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
What the heck’s goin’ on here?
What the heck is goin’ on
at 4:30 in the morning?
[ Shouting Continues ]
I hate this place!
A bunch of banshees.!
What? You have to do this here?
On my lawn? Can’t you take it
six blocks down the road?
What are you doin’ here?
Aw, that’s it. I can’t stand
this job. I’m outta here.
Platoon, attention!
More P.T., Drill Sergeant!
More P.T.! We like it! We love it!
We want more of it! Make it hurt,
Drill Sergeant! Make it hurt! Hooo!
[ Bill ] Find me something.
I’ll do it for free. If they
like it, they can pay me.
I’ll work nights. Nobody
sleeps around here anyway.
No, no, no, you’re not listening to me,
Jack. You’re not listening.
Screw my pride! I’ll take anything.
I’ll write papers for your children.
Do you hear this?
[ Shouting Continues ]
It’s the sound of hell.
Seven... eight...
nine... ten...
eleven.
[ Troops Shouting ]
Go, Navy!
[ Grunts ]
[ Chattering ]
Eat your beans, Haywood.
That’s good brain food.
-[ Chuckles ] Oh, why bother?
-Don’t, no, no.
Pay him no mind, Tommy Lee.
-You took it all. Now eat it all!
-Eat, eat, eat, eat.
You got more than me.
I could kick his ass.
I could definitely kick his ass.
Double-D’s. Dumb as dogshit.
-[ Girls Laughing ]
-Dumb, huh?
Well, let me tell you somethin’.
I’d rather be a double-D...
than a swinger
from the ugly tree, you fat pig.
[ Girls ] Oooh!
[ Laughing ]
You’re bad.
Nice goin’, Myers.
-Swingin’ from the ugly tree? Damn.
-[ Laughs ]
[ Drill Sergeant ] Anything left
on your plate, we’ll do extra push-ups.!
You know, Mel, cling peaches
were my daddy’s favorite.
Gimme a break, will ya, Junior?
My daddy this.
My daddy that. How many freakin’ times
do we have to hear about your daddy?
Eat! Eat! Eat!
Eat! Eat!
We eat now, we taste it later!
-Where did all this
freakin’ food come from?
-Eat! Eat it!
-[ Chattering ]
-All right, who wants to start?
Nobody?
[ Snorts ] I thought this was
the volunteer army.
You tryin’ to diss us? You can’t do that.
Leroy, tell him he can’t do that.
-Shut up, asshole.
-Naw, man, he’s dissin’ you.
Why you startin’ with me, inbred Jed?
Sit over there and shut up.
Montgomery, you finished? Is that
the end of the intelligent repartee?
All right. Why don’t we begin
with Haywood?
How come I got to go first?
Because you’re from
Wallahoochee, Georgia.
-[ Montgomery ] Get up there, boy.
-Willacoochee, Bill.
Willacoochee.
[ Exhales ]
There’s these woods
behind our trailer park.
This old guy lives
in the woods there...
and everybody in town
swore he was crazy.
-""He showed me how to hunt...
-[ Yawning ]
how to be real quiet
and how to listen.
He said he had seen everything
in the world there was to see.
And that’s why he never wanted
to leave those woods.
Me and my daddy got laid off
at the paper mill.
""Whilst I spent about five
months watchin’ TV with my brothers...
I kept thinkin’
of what the old man said.
Finally, I decided that I did
want to see more of the world...
than what was behind that trailer park,
so I joined up.
I liked living with my Aunt Mavis
in Chicago the best.
But last summer, my mother Ruthie
came back, and we drove to Atlanta.
She said we don’t have to stay long,
but then she met a man and take off.
""I waited around for a while
for her to come back...
but everybody keeps sayin’
just go on home.
I don’t know where that is.
""So I take the bus to Cleveland
and spend two days staring at
the poster behind the driver...
that said, Be All You Can Be.’
""So I think about that for a week...
and then I think...
I gotta be somewhere, so here I am.
[ Montgomery ]
""In my crib...
there ain’t never been a time
when we eat, or sleep, or nothin’.
You know, everybody just runs
around crazy. Half the time
I don’t even know who they are.
[ Scoffs ]
I must be the only person
in the world to join the army...
so he’d know exactly what time
he was eatin’ lunch.
I wanted to learn a new trade.
-Sergeant Cass.
-Afternoon, sir.
-[ Bill ] Brian Davis, Junior.
-Sir, yes, sir.
[ Clears Throat ]
Why I joined the army...
by Private Brian Davis, Junior.
I wanted to be in the army
for as long as I can remember.
""I never really knew my dad ‘cause he
died in Vietnam when I was a baby.
His name was Brian too.
My whole life my mama
showed me pictures of him...
and read me his letters
and told me how he was a hero.
-Bullshit, man. He wasn’t no hero.
-He was so!
-How you gonna prove that?
You got no proof.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-[ Davis ] I don’t need proof.
-Get it through your thick skull.
Your daddy was no hero.
-[ Myers ] Shut up.!
-Read my lips. He’s selling you a dream.
-Would you knock it off
and let him finish?
-[ Davis ] My mom told me.!
-[ Benitez ] Your mommy made it up.
-[ Haywood ] Cut it out.!
Go ahead.
She told me about how he was a hero.
He died for his country.
I think that if my daddy
was alive today...
he’d want me
to be in the army too...
[ Crying ]
so I could learn to be brave.
I’m sorry.
That’s okay. It’s all right.
Take it easy.
[ Clears Throat ] So, um--
I guess the real reason
I, I joined the army...
was to get a better education
so I could get a better job.
And that’s why. ‘"
When I was a kid, I used to
love summers ‘cause there was no school.
[ Montgomery Laughs ]
"I had to baby-sit my kid sister,
but I didn’t mind too much.
I mean, we’d fight a lot but, you know,
mostly we just used to kid around.
She wanted to be a dancer.
She was pretty good too.
One day a couple
of summers ago, I sent her up
to the store to buy some milk.
Now, the bullet was meant for the dude
comin’ out of the store...
but it killed her just
the same. She was only 1 3.
""I still miss her a lot, but I always
miss her more in the summer.
After that I decided that being part of
a gang didn’t seem like such a good idea.
So I joined this gang.
That good enough, Mr. Rago?
Yeah.
-[ Man ] How you doin’, sir?
-Let’s have a coin check.
[ Bill ] Can I have a Dewars, please,
with seven aspirin back?
-Seven aspirin? You okay?
-Catch you later.
Yeah. Oh, Jesus.
I mean, some of the stories these kids
have. I can’t--I can’t believe it.
It’s really somethin’, huh?
Everybody’s got a story.
You wanna hear my story, Bill?
[ People Chattering ]
Not now, Tom. Some other time.
Well, you know what I think?
What’s that, Tom?
I think the whole educational
system is in deep trouble.
You see, after their families
let ‘em down, they go to
what’s left of their schools.
The teachers are underpaid.
They’re scared, so they stop teaching.
But that doesn’t stop ‘em from
handing out high school diplomas
like they were toilet paper.
So that means we gotta take ‘em.
Country better shape up soon, though.
We’re going to hell in
a handcart. But that’s strictly
between you and me, right?
Yeah. [ Knocking Bar]
Could I have my aspirin, please?
[ Drill Sergeant ]
Swing up and stand on--No.!
-Stand on the log! You ready to quit?
You ready to quit?
-No!
-No, Drill Sergeant!
-Get the hell back up there!
This is not that complicated.
Forty-one, Drill Sergeant.
No, Private, it’s not 41 .
You’re reading the wrong
numbers. Read the red numbers.
-One, two, three--
-[ Groans ]
-You’ve got to be kiddin’ me.
-No, Drill Sergeant.
Three weeks, motor mouth.
Three weeks, you have yet
to show me a real push-up.
-I expect to get this one pretty good.
-They’ve all got to be good!
Two fingers. That’s what it’s supposed
to be, two fingers.
-Understand that, Private Myers?
-Yes, Drill Sergeant.
[ Drill Sergeant ] Keep movin’, Benitez.
All the way to the end. Don’t stop.!
Come on, get back to the line! Go back
to the start of the line! Hurry up!
You’re gonna make it, Benitez.
All right, time’s up.
Who wants to talk about
what they read?
-Benitez, come on up here.
-All right.
[ Chuckles ]
-What are you readin’? Okay.
-Archie comic.
I mean, what’s up with Jughead?
Archie’s got Betty.
And you got Reggie with Veronica.
I mean, what’s up with Jughead?
He got nobody.
That’s no excuse ‘cause he’s ugly.
In my neighborhood,
it didn’t matter how ugly
you were, you always had a girl.
I don’t know what’s the matter
with this guy. Another thing,
you guys maybe could help me.
-Mr. Rago, hold on a sec.
Uh, here it is.
-[ Groans ]
Come on, Archie, let’s go
to the malt shoppe. “What
the hell’s a malt shop-ee”?
-[ Montgomery ] Benitez.
-What’s a malt shop-ee? You guys know?
Bring your stupid ass over here.
-What’s the matter with you?
-What do you mean?
-What are you doin’
readin’ a comic book?
-He said bring anything.
-I bought a comic book.
I like comic books.
-Knock it off.
-You’re here for education,
not to read comic books.
-You’re embarrassing me, boy.
-That’s stupid.
-You could a got something else
at the P.X.
-Yeah, like Batman
or Superman or Spider-Man.
-Come on, shut up!
-[ Benitez ] They scare me.
-[ Sighs ]
-[ Montgomery Laughs ]
-Bunch of hyenas.
-What’s the book you got, Mr. Rago?
-This?
-Yeah.
-This is called Hamlet.
Hamlet. Yo, that’s about
a little-bitty pig, right?
No, it ain’t about
a little-bitty pig!
What’s it about, Billy boy?
It’s about... sex...
murder, incest...
-insanity.
-Ohhh.
-Shoot. Beats the hell out
of this garbage I’m readin’.
-Guns.
Sure does. Pretty much beats the heck
out of any book ever written.
-All right, Leroy.
-Yeah?
-What are you readin’?
-Uh, Sports Illustrated. The
Faces in the Crowd section.
Why don’t you tell us more about
your book? Sounds more interesting.
Yeah, who wrote it?
Well, it was written
by William Shakespeare.
You ever hear of Shakespeare?
-I heard of him. That guy’s in
Central Park every summer.
-Dude must’ve got mugged a lot.
He’s been dead
for almost 400 years.
-See that? They killed him.
They killed him. New Yorkers.
-Yeah, yeah.
He wrote plays.
Plays. You know, like TV.
Without the box.
Mmm.
They didn’t have any TVs
back then or movies.
Or that many books even.
So everybody went to the theater.
Everybody.
Kings, queens, right down
to the working stiffs.
-Why don’t you read us some of that?
-Word.
Skip to the page with some incest so we
can make Haywood feel at home. Sooey!
No, you guys don’t want
to hear about Hamlet.
What? What? What?
I guess we’re not smart enough.
-No, no, no, no. It’s just very,
I don’t know, it’s--
-[ Montgomery ] Here we go.
-What? It’s just what?
-It’s complicated.
So? We’re here. We’re listenin’.
[ Clears Throat ]
Sit down.
Okay, okay.
All right, here’s the deal. Um--
Hamlet is, uh...
uh, he’s a prince.
All right. And, uh...
-and he’s away at college.
-[ Montgomery ] Rich kid.
Right? And he, he gets word
that his father died.
-Oh, no, Davis, please,
don’t start cryin’.
-Leave me alone, Benitez!
-Forget about it.
-Benitez, shut up, all right?
-Chill.
-Go ahead.
All right, so he comes home
from college for the funeral.
And when he gets back,
everything’s fishy.
All right?
You ever hear of the term,
something is rotten
in the state of Denmark?
Naw, but in apartment 3-C,
my building, Miss Leary...
every Thursday, she always cooks
the corned beef and cabbage.
-Mm-hmm.
-Something sure smells rotten
in the state of New York.
All right.
That’s the same kind of thing.
-That was dumb. That was really dumb.
-Leave him alone, man.
He gets back, and he’s in mourning...
and less than a month goes by
and his mother gets remarried.
-Damn.
-To his uncle.
-[ Everybody Gasps ]
-That’s the incest part.
Okay? So, now, Hamlet spends
the rest of the play trying to decide...
whether he’s got the guts
to go after his uncle the king...
and avenge his father’s death,
or if he wants to just...
go with the flow and do what his mother
is tellin’ him to do.
-Naw.
-Don’t go out like that.
So, where I am in the play,
[ Clears Throat ]
He’s with his mother and the king
and she’s trying to cheer him up.
And she says...
Good Hamlet,
cast thy nighted color off...
and let thine eye
look like a friend on Denmark.
Do not forever with thy veiled lids
seek for thy noble father...
-in the dust.
-[ Montgomery ] What?
-Hey, you wanna lay that
down one more time?
-Please.
Well, it’s--it’s really easy.
You just gotta listen, all right?
Cast thy nighted color off.
Well, what color do we wear at a funeral?
-Black.
-Black!
-A nighted color.
-She’s tellin’ him not to wear
black, to stop mourning.
-[ Bill ] Right?
-[ Hobbs ] Right.
It says, Let thine eye look like
a friend on Denmark.
Which means she’s sayin’
don’t glare at me as though you hate me.
Why should he? His father’s
body’s not cold yet and she’s
given the punnani to UncleJoe.
Something like that.
Only it’s Uncle Claudius.
-What the hell is a punnani?
-[ Montgomery ] Cave boy
never heard of punnani.
Hey, Mr. Bill, when my daddy split
on my mama, he moved in...
with her sister,
who is, of course, my auntie.
And I got a baby cousin
who’s also my baby sister.
That’s sort of the same thing.
Mel speaks.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Applause, Whistling ]
-Glad to have you, Mel.
-I got a question.
-Yes?
-Now, if look like a friend
means don’t hate me...
why don’t she say don’t hate me?
-Because it’s poetry.
-But it don’t even rhyme, yo?
Yeah, but it’s like, you know, uh--
It’s language. It’s trying to put things
together that evoke...
a certain--
It sounds better.
What do you mean?
I mean, it doesn’t sound like
anything to me. I don’t get it.
Yeah. Come on, Teach, teach us.
It’s--all right.
It’s a simile.
-A what?
-A simile. All right, here.
-[ Benitez ] A simile.
-Yeah.
[ Montgomery ] That’s a little
yellow face with a smile on it.
Um--
-[ Melvin ] Si-mi-le.
-Simile.
It’s, uh...
when you take two things...
that, um... don’t seem alike...
but in a way, they are.
-Huh?
-[ Leroy ] Hmm?
All right. All right, we’re lookin’
for a simile. Haywood.
Um...you’re, uh--
You’re workin’ in the mill and, uh...
you come home
or you’re on your way home.
You go to a bar, you stop
for a brew. Down at the end
of the bar is a beautiful woman.
And she winks at you.
All right?
You go to her like--fill in the blank.
-[ Mumbling ] I don’t know.
-Like a rooster with an itch!
[ Class Chuckles ]
Like a rooster with an itch.
Way to go, Davis.
You gotta love those barnyard similes.
All right, that was simile.
Now, here’s somethin’ else. A metaphor.
-All men are--
-Dogs.
Dogs! Okay, you got it?
Simile: like dogs.
Well, here’s metaphor.
We just plain are... dogs.
Okay? All right.
Now, this is a good one here.
-All right, let’s see.
-[ Writing On Chalkboard ]
-Oxymoron.
-[ Montgomery ] Hold up.
Hold up, hold up. You can’t do that.
That is a diss. I ain’t no oxmoron.
No, no, no, no.
Not oxmoron, schmuck. Oxymoron.
It’s when you take two words
that are totally the opposite
and you jam ‘em together.
All right? Like, uh...
military intelligence.
Dark victory.
Thunderous silence.
Hmm?
Girly-man.
-[ Class Chuckling ]
-He talkin’ about you, Benitez.
-[ Benitez ] You’re killin’ me.
-Okay. So, let’s end
the class with, uh...
an oxymoron from Shakespeare himself,
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
If you say so.
-Take it easy, Billy boy. Two times.
-[ Leroy ] Fall in outside.
-Thanks, Mr. Bill. See you tomorrow.
-Hoo-ah.
Thanks, Mr. Rago. That was neat.
-Take care, Bill.
-Take it easy, Rocko.
I’m teachin’ Shakespeare.
[ Chuckles ]
That is, uh,
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
All right.
Readin’ Hamlet to the double-D’s.
Come on!
-I’ve been waitin’ for this!
-[ Troops Shouting ]
-Beat him down! Let’s go!
-Kick his ass!
Come on!
[ Grunts ]
[ Helicopter Passing Overhead ]
-Hey! Hey!
-Huh?
You must be Bill.
-Yeah, that’s me.
-Yeah.
-You don’t seem to mind them calling
you that. Okay if I do the same, Bill?
-No problem.
Bill, I’d appreciate it if you’d employ
a bit more discipline in your classroom.
Would that be too much to ask?
I mean, this isn’t Harvard yard.
This is a military--
-Whoa, whoa, Lou, take it easy.
-Who the fuck is Lou?
What’s your problem? I’m just
walkin’ here. You got a bug up your ass?
You know what I think, Bill?
I think your whole class thing
is a bunch of bullshit.
-I think you’re wastin’ my time.
-Your time?
-That’s right.
-It’s their class. I don’t see
you in the class, so lighten up.
Their time is my time, Bill.
Now, I have exactly 54 days
to teach these young kids...
what it takes to save lives
in combat, in combat, Bill!
Now, I don’t think
they’re gonna learn that...
writing a bunch of touchy-feely little
papers for the English teacher. No.
They’re gonna learn that out here
with me! I’m gonna be certain of that.
Now, that’s my mission, Bill.
And I can handle it ‘cause it’s my job.
Yeah, well, you do your job
and I’ll do mine.
You know what the difference here,
Bill, is? I care about what I do.
[ Troops Continue Shouting ]
Do him, Haywood.
-[ Class Chattering ]
-Lady and gentlemen, it’s show time!
[ Montgomery ]
Oh, show time at the Apollo.
-What’s this?
-This is Hamlet.
I figured that since we have
to do something, we might as
well do something that I love...
and that you showed
a little bit of interest in, so... here.
-Put your desks in a circle
facing each other.
-[ Chattering ]
You mean you want us
to read this stuff?
Yeah, Benitez, even you could do it.
-Plus, it cost me nine bucks
to run those things off.
-Billy boy, it says here...
""Show me the steep and thorny
way to heaven...
uh, whiles--Willis, like...
the puffed and reckless “libertinay”.
-Libertine!
-Libertine. Hey, yo.
-You gonna come translate this for us?
-Why? It’s in English.
-Uh-uh.
-Now... Roosevelt Hobbs...
-you be Hamlet.
-All right.
Benitez, you’re gonna be
Hamlet’s best friend, Horatio.
-That’s cool, bro.
-Okay, Miranda Myers, you will be...
-Hamlet’s girlfriend, the fair Ophelia.
-She ain’t exactly fair.
-Quiet. Melvin!
-[ Hobbs ] Mighty fair to me.
Melvin! Mel.
Melvin, when you wake up,
you will be Polonius, Ophelia’s father.
-Leroy. You’ll be
Ophelia’s brother, Laertes.
-Right.
-Montgomery, you’re the ghost.
-The who?
-The ghost.
-[ Haywood Chuckles ]
You the ghost in the hood.
[ Mimicking Haywood ]
You the ghost in the hood. Goo-ooh.
-[ Blabbering ]
-[ Sighs ]
Haywood...
-you’re the king.
-Thank you, Bill.
-Damn, I should have been the king.
-Davis.
You will be Queen Gertrude,
Hamlet’s mother.
-[ Class Laughing ]
-Sir, isn’t that a woman’s part?
-Alas, Private Davis, we have
but one woman in our class.
-One.
But, sir, I’d really prefer
another part.
Relax, Davis.
You’ll be reassured to know...
that in Shakespeare’s day,
all the parts were played by men.
-What?
-Yeah. That’s right.
-Romeo and Juliet were a couple of guys?
-Correctamundo.
Bill, you know as well as I do
a guy playing a girl is plain filthy!
Especially if it’s gonna be my wife.
-That’s your woman.
-[ Haywood ] Shut up, Leroy.!
Oh, they say Jove laughs.
Oh, gentle Romeo.
""If thou dost love,
pronounce it faithfully.
Or if thou thinkest
I am too quickly won, I’ll frown.
And be perverse.
And say thee nay.
So thou wilt woo.
In truth, fair Montague,
I am too fond, and therefore...
thou mayst think my behavior light.
But trust me, gentle man.
I’ll prove more true than those
that have more cunning to be strange.
Hmm.
I should have been more strange.
I should have been more strange,
I must confess.
But that thou overheardst,
ere I was ware, my true love passion.
Therefore, pardon me, and not impute
this yielding to light love.
Which the dark night
hath so discovered.
You know, that shade of blue
really brings out your eyes.
-[ Laughing ] See?
-[ Class Laughing ]
-Hoo-ah.
-No problem. All right.
[ Troops Yelling ]
Let’s go, ladies. Come on.
-That’s it, Baby Huey. Come on.!
-Move it!
Do not saw the air
too much with your aim thus.
[ Troops Yelling ]
[ Shouting ]
No, no, no, no.
Gimme that.
-You step in and then step in
with the right foot.
-All right, Drill Sergeant.
So, what Hamlet’s father,
the ghost, is tellin’ him...
that because he was killed...
poisoned in his sleep
in the afternoon...
with his sins still on his soul...
that he can’t get a pass
straight to heaven.
He’s stuck in purgatory.
All right, soldiers. Close your eyes
and break the seal of the mask.
-Do it!
-Keep your mouth closed...
-and do not inhale the gas
under any circumstances.
-Drill Sergeant.
Too easy, Drill Sergeant!
[ Coughs, Gagging ]
[ Grunting ]
All right, good, Melvin. See how good
it is when you stay awake?
Hamlet’s confronted his mother,
and she knows deep down in her soul...
she’s gonna have these stains
forever on her soul.
That’s deep, man.
Stains on her soul.
-Way deep. Right?
-Mm-hmm.
[ Troops Shouting ]
Queen Gertrude.
[ Drill Sergeant ] Yeah. Yeah.
Too easy, Hobbs, eh?
Neither... a borrower...
nor a lender bef---before--"
No. For loan oft...
"Ioses both... itself and friend.
"And borrowing...
"dulls the edge of husbandry.
This above all, to...
thine own self be true.
Melvin. All right, Melvin.
Stop. You can say the rest
when you come out of the coma.
Sit down. Look, look.
You gotta, you gotta say it...
to a beat, you know?
-Does anybody play the drums?
-[ Together] Hoo-ah.
-Both of ya?
-Mmm.
Whack this out on the desk.
Bop, bada, bop, bada, bop-bop-bop-bop.
Da, dada, dat,
dada, dat-dat-dat-dat.
Da, dada, dat, dada, dat-dat-dat-dat.
Come on, Haywood, get with it.
Give him time.
He’s a white boy.
Da, dada, dat,
dada, dat-dat-dat-dat.
You see, you say the lines
to the beat. And you--you hear it?
Um, do I hear ‘em
bangin’ on the desk?
No, this, fool! Bop, bada, bop,
bada, bop-bop-bop-bop.
This above-- Get up.
This above all,
to thine own self be true. Say it.
to thine own self be true.
[ Everybody ] This above all,
This above all,
to thine own self be true.
-This above all,
-Come on, Mel.!
to thine own self be true.
-This above all,
-Go, Mel, go!
This above all,
to thine own self be true.
-You got it!
-This above all,
to thine own self be true.
-Way to go, Mel! Gimme five! Mel Melvin!
-[ Class Cheering ]
Yee-haw!
One two three four
one, ho, three four
-Tiny bubbles
-In my wine
-Makes me happy
-Makes me feel fine
[ Haywood ]
Don’t you tell my heart
-My achy-breaky heart
-[ Groans ] That’s cruel.
-Whoo!
-[ Hobbs ] Damn, Haywood.!
Oh, if you tell my heart
My achy-breaky heart
I just don’t think
he’ll understand
-[ Hobbs ] Davis is thinking
about his daddy again.
-I’ll cheer him up.
Hey, Davis, you should a seen me in there.
[ Imitating De Niro ]
Never got me down, Ray. Ya hear me?
-Never got me down, Ray.
-Who’s that?
Jake LaMotta.
-Who?
-You never seen the movie Raging Bull?
-No, I missed that.
-You crazy?
[ As De Niro ] Hey, Larry! Who’s
an animal, Larry, huh?
Your mother’s an animal! I’m gonna eat
your dog for breakfast, Larry!
-Ya hear me, Larry?
-You’re an animal.
What? I’m an animal?
What are you, crazy?
Huh? I’m not an animal!
-I’m not an animal!
-Stop!
-Please stop. Stop.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-All right, I got mail call!
-[ Men Shouting, Whooping ]
All right. We got Abney.
-We got Anderson.
-Right here.
-Judd.
-Ho!
Bonner. Whoa!
-Byrd.
-Look out!
-Montgomery.
-Oh, man.!
Montgomery. Montgomery.
Montgomery.
Ahh! Hey, give me that.
-Albrecht.
-See that, baby?
-Get out.
-We got Melvin.
-Melvin! Melvin!
-Melvin.!
Anybody home? [ Laughing ]
Ho! We got Ben.
We got Bartol.
-And we got Scott!
-Right here.!
-That’s it, fellas.
-[ Men ] Aw.!
Sorry, man.
Davis ain’t gettin’ no letter, Junior?
Look, I got one.
-From who?
-From my brother.
I ain’t got a letter yet.
You gotta read that to me.
-Has anybody seen my green socks?
-We all got green socks.!
Let’s see what he has to say.
How ya doin’. How ya’ doin’.
How ya doin’.
Let’s see, uh--
Oh, listen. Dad put new
holleys on the Camaro...
so he could race it up at the speedway.
It was runnin’ like greased owl shit.
Hey, that’s a simile, Mel.
That is a simile, ain’t it?
Damn right.
Let’s see. Then Toby drove it last week
and threw a rod...
and Dad got mad and threw him
down the stairs.
This ain’t my real dad.
This is my step dad.
Things are sure different...
now that you’re in the marines.
-Marines?
-Well, he’s 1 2.
He gets ‘em mixed up, ya know.
Dad don’t have you
around anymore...
so I guess he’s startin’ in
on his real kids.
Mel, what kind of Camaro has he got?
A Z-28?
Mel. You okay, Mel?
Mel?
[ Sighs ] I ain’t never
gonna hit my kids.
Oh, don’t start
sleepin’ again, Mel.
You know it ain’t
gonna solve nothin’.
[ Sighs ]
-Mama, mama, don’t you cry
-Little boy ain’t gonna die
-Your little boy ain’t gonna die
-Oh! Aw, jeez!
-What’s the matter? Heart attack?
-It’s the food, I’m tellin’ you.
-Oh, Jesus!
Junior, where you goin’?
-I gotta go back.!
-We’re gonna be late! Junior!
Oh, no! Oh, no, no!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
-What?
-Wait, wait, wait!
-Jesus.
-What’s your freakin’ problem, Davis?
-My bag! My daddy’s bracelet!
-His what?
-It’s a Montagnard bracelet.
He got it in Vietnam.
-He wore a bracelet?
Lots of soldiers wore ‘em over there.
I left it in my shirt pocket.
Good, now it’ll be clean.
Come on. Let’s go.
Come on, man!
What if it gets lost?
Please, you gotta help me, man.
It’s all I got.
We gotta get this
to the quartermaster’s laundry on time.
[ Imitating Al Pacino ] I don’t care.
Look for the bracelet, okay?
-All right. What’s his name?
-His name is Brian Davis, Jr.
-Come on, man. This is stupid.
-[ As Pacino ] Shut up, you!
I kill you, you cockroach!
Shut up!
Now look. I gotta touch
the dirty clothes, man? You kiddin’ me.
Please, please.
Yes! Yes!
Here it is.
Oh, man, thank you. Thank you!
[ Cass ]
Prepare to uncover.!
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five...
four, three, two, one!
Freeze! I said freeze!
What was that again?
What time is it?
Drill Sergeant!
Breakfast is at 0600, Drill Sergeant!
Zero six hundred.
That’s correct.
Which by my reckoning
has come and gone, has it not?
-Drill Sergeant.! Yes, Drill Sergeant.!
-Hi, Miranda.
[ Cass ] I don’t know. Maybe it’s me.
I just can’t seem to hear ya.
I don’t hear that--
Benitez! Davis!
Front and center.!
You wouldn’t happen
to have the time, would you, Private?
Sorry, Drill Sergeant.
Slight problem with the laundry.
Does this building look
like a Denny’s to you, New York? Huh?
Show me where it says
breakfast served anytime.
Get on down there and push ten.
Drill Sergeant, it was my fault!
Who was I talkin’ to?
Was I talkin’ to you?
Drill Sergeant, I asked him to help me
find my daddy’s bracelet.
-My daddy! My daddy!
-My daddy sent it--
Your daddy ain’t here, son,
and your daddy can’t help you.
I don’t know if anybody
can help you, high-speed.
Lou. Lou, go easy on the kid.
What?
He’s five minutes late.
I mean, talk about anal. You must’ve
been toilet-trained at gunpoint.
[ Stifles Chuckle ]
Come over here.
-What?
-Come over here. Right here!
-Take it easy.
-Don’t ever interrupt me when
I’m talkin’ to my soldiers.
-He was five minutes late.
-You understand me?
Man, you been on my bad side since
the day I laid eyes on you.
You better comprehend this.
You better get this down...
-’cause I have had it with
your smug college-boy attitude.
-Yeah?
You listen to me: stay away from me.
And don’t you ever, ever impugn
my authority in front of my soldiers.
-Now, you got that, man?
-Yeah, I got that.
-You got it?
That’s point-blank and period.
-Yeah, I got it.
[ Muttering ]
For the rest of the week,
you’ll show up here nine minutes early.
-You will report here--
-Davis.
Just show up to my class nine minutes
late is all, ya see? No problemo.
-Oh, that’s it! That is it!
-What?
-Drill Sergeant!
Drill Sergeant! Calm down.
-What?
Who do you think you are?
You gonna tell me what to do?
-You’re nothin’. You’re nothin’.
-I’m nothin’?
Did you hear what he said?
I’m nothin’.!
-Come on. Come on. Right here.
-Just let me--
[ Knocking ] Sir?
So they finally sent you
to the principal’s office.
Yeah.
Man could’ve killed you, Mr. Rago.
He would’ve been court-martialed,
but he could’ve killed you.
-He started it.
-I don’t know what happened,
and I don’t care.
All I care about is this program...
and I will not let you, Sgt. Cass
or anybody curtail its chances, okay?
Okay.
You never served in the military,
did you, Mr. Rago?
No, my military experience
is limited to the day...
that I walked for hours in the rain
from Arlington Cemetery...
to the White House carrying
the name of a soldier...
who died needlessly in Vietnam.
Do you remember the soldier’s name?
No.
Do me a favor, Bill.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org