[Hollow Log Horn]
[Radio] Thundershowers are expected
in the Crocodile Falls area,
and some of the
surrounding gullies.
- Cody!
- Yeah, Mom ?
What about
your breakfast ?
- I've got some sandwiches in my pack.
- Be home for supper!
No worries, Mom.
[Hollow Log Horn]
[ Bird Calls ]
I know !
I'm coming.
Hustle up, Nelson.
Faloo is sounding
the call!
Come on,
little wombats!
[Hollow Log Horn]
- Who's caught this time ?
- Her name is Marahute,
- the great golden eagle.
- Where is she ?
She's caught, high on a cliff
in a poacher's trap.
- You're the only one who can reach her.
- I'll get her loose.
Right-o, hop on !
No time to lose.
She's up on top of that ridge.
Be careful, little friend.
Marahute !
[ Screeches ]
Calm down, calm down.
I'm not gonna
hurt you.
That's a girl.
Stay still.
It's okay.
- Screech !
- I'm gonna help you !
Easy, easy !
[ Screeches ]
You're free !
No !
[ Screeches ]
Higher !
Whoa !
Ha-ha !
[ Screeches ]
Squawk !
Ha-ha-ha !
Whoa !
[ Screeches ]
Wow !
[Scratching]
You're a mom !
They're very warm.
Are they gonna hatch soon ?
Where's the daddy eagle ?
Oh, my dad's gone, too.
[ Screeches Softly]
[Screeches]
[ Airplane Sounds ]
Squawk !
[Bells]
Mmmph !
Hey, little fella,
what happened to you ?
No, no !
It's a trap !
I'll get you loose.
[Beep, Beep]
[ Beep, Beep ]
Ah, heh-heh!
Got one!
Are you all right ?
- I think so.
- Okey-dokey !
Hey, come back !
Mmmph!
Ugh... Mmmph!
Here you go.
Grab on !
That's great !
Just a little more.
There, I got it !
[Rumbling]
Uh-oh!
[ Bird Cries ]
Yike !
[DoorSlams]
- Grrrr !
- Ahhh !
Well,Joanna,
what'd we get today ?
A dingo ?
A fat old razorback,
or a nice big... boy ?
Grrrr!
Joanna, you been
digging holes again ?
Dumb lizard's always
trying to bury squirrels.
Uh-uh, it's a trap,
and poaching's against the law.
Trap ? Where'd you get
an idea like that ?
You've been in that
hole for too long.
Well, come on,
grab a hold.
We'll get you out of
this little lizard hole,
and you can just
run along home.
This is a poacher's trap,
and you're a poacher!
Aaah !
Let go !
Hey, get off me !
I'm gonna kill her.
I'm gonna kill
that dumb, slimy,
egg-sucking salamander !
Get off !
[Click]
[ Gulp ]
Grrrr.
Hmmm.
Good girl,Joanna.
Where'd you get this
pretty feather, boy ?
It was a present.
That's real nice.
Who gave it to you ?
It's a secret.
That's no secret, boy.
You see, I already
got the father.
Heh-heh.
Now you just tell me where Mama
and those little eggs are.
No !
Joanna, sic him !
Grrrr!
You're coming
with me, boy.
My mom will call
the rangers !
No, not the rangers !
What'll I do ?
Don't let your ma
call the rangers, please !
Ha-ha-ha !
My poor baby boy...
got eaten by
the crocodiles.
Boo-hoo-hoo.
Let's go, boy!
[ Engine Starts ]
Help ! Help !
[Thunder]
Help, help, help ! Send for help !
McLeach took a boy !
Send for help !
[ Morse Code Beeps ]
[ Beep, Beep ]
[ Whistle ]
[Telephone Ring]
[ Wind Blowing ]
[ Beep, Beep ]
A code red !
Attention alI Rescue Aid
Society delegates !
Please report immediately
to the main assembly hall.
This is an
emergency meeting.
This is a code red
Order, order !
I know it's late--
really, pajamas !
Hello, Frank.
How are you ?
And Esmerelda,
there you are !
Quiet, please.
Everyone pay attention.
There has been
a kidnapping in Australia !
A young boy
needs our help.
This is a mission
requiring our very finest,
and I know we are all thinking
of the same two mice.
[Gasp]
What's this ? Gone ?
We must find Bernard
and Miss Bianca at once !
Mmm, pea soup !
Pea soup !
To my dear Bernard...
and our wonderful
partnership.
Uh, yeah, wonderful.
Wonderful.
You've been very
quiet this evening.
Is there something
on your mind ?
Well, um,
actually, I--
I was wondering.
Yes, darling ?
Miss Bianca,
would you--
Would you--
Would you excuse me
for a minute ?
Mademoiselle Bianca,
l have important news.
Yes, Francois,
what is it ?
You and Bernard have
been asked to accept...
a dangerous mission
to Australia.
The poor boy.
This is dreadful.
Where is Bernard ?
I must tell him.
Allow me, madam.
I will tell him immediately.
Miss Bianca,
will you marry me ?
Monsieur Bernard--
Please marry me.
Not now, Francois !
No, no, no,
you don't under--
O, sacre bleu !
- Did you talk to Francois ?
- Yes, but--
I know exactly what
you're going to say.
- Francois told me.
- How did he know ?
It doesn't matter.
I think it's a marvelous idea.
You do ? I mean,
you really want to ?
It's not a matter of wanting,
it's a matter of duty.
Duty ? I never
thought of it--
Well, all right.
How does next April sound ?
Heavens no !
We must act tonight !
Tonight ? B-But, wait !
Bianca, this is so sudden.
Don't you at least need
a gown or something ?
Just a pair of khaki shorts
and some hiking boots.
Hiking boots ?
Ah, there you are !
Come along,
come along.
Delegates, we have an
important announcement.
Bernard and I
have decided...
to accept the mission
to Australia.
- Australia ?
- Good show !
You must fly out
immediately.
It's a bit nippy outside,
but that won't stop us, will it ?
Miss Bianca,
I'm not sure...
it's a good idea to fly
this soon after eating !
Darling, you'llbe
just fine.
But aren't you supposed
to wait 45 minutes ?
Oh,just knock
on the door...
and see if
Orville is there.
Nobody's home.
Let's go.
Bernard,
this is no time
to play in the snow.
I wasn't playing.
It was an avalanche.
Look, Bernard !
"Under new management.
See Wilbur. "
## [ Rock Music ]
Come on, darling !
Let's get a move out.
#l know that you
would say he's gone#
#Black slacks
Mostly in the head#
# I'm the cat's pajamas #
#Always running 'round
with crazy little mamas #
Yoo-hoo,
Mr. Wilbur.
- Get down there, son !
- Hello !
Pick it, boy,
pick it !
Yeah !
Whoo, here we go !
Let's walk !
Look out !
Bernard, do something.
He can't hear us.
Big time!
- #The girls all look when I go by#
-[MusicStops]
Hey, who killed
the music ?
That's better.
Excuse us for interrupting.
We're from
the rescue aid society.
I am Miss Bianca.
The Miss Bianca ?
I don't believe it.
My brother Orville
told me all about you.
Oh, boy,
this is an honor !
May I just say
"enchante senorita" to you ?
Ahem !
- We need a flight.
- You've come to the right place.
Welcome to...
Getit ?
'A fair fare. "
It's a play on--
Never mind.
I've got tons of exotic
destinations, far away places...
custom designed for
"a romantic weekend get away,"
as well as the finest
in-flight accommodations.
Speaking of which,
what can I get you ?
How about a nice
mango Maui cooler ?
No, thank you.
A coconut guava nectar ?
It's carbonated, very nice.
I've got little umbrellas
for each one of them.
We must leave
immediately !
- Nothing at all ? Cream soda ?
- Wilbur!
We need a flight
to Australia !
The land down under ?
That's a fabulous idea !
So when can I
pencil you in ?
After spring thaw ?
Mid-June would be very nice.
We must leave tonight!
Tonight ?
You're kidding me, right ?
Have you looked outside ?
It's suicide out there !
Oh, no, your jolly little
holiday will have to wait.
What a bunch
of jokers !
But you don't understand. A boy
needs our help. He's in trouble !
Boy ? You mean,
little kid kind of boy ?
- He was kidnapped !
- Oh, that's awful.
Locking up a little kid.
Kids should be free,
free to run wild through
the house on Saturday mornings,
free to have
cookies and milk...
and get those little
white moustaches.
Nobody's gonna take a kid's
freedom away while I'm around !
Does that mean
you'll take us ?
Storm or no storm,
Albatross Airlines
at your service !
Passengers are requested to
please fasten their seatbelts.
We'll be departing following our
standard preflight maintenance.
Thank you.
Loosen up, get the blood
flowing up to the head.
And a couple ofthese.
Ow !
Okay, one's enough.
There we go.
That feels better !
Oh, baby !
Tie your kangaroos down,
sports fans !
Here we come !
Let's go for it !
Whoa, hey !
I didn't adjust
for the wind.
I just had to duck
down a little lower,
go under the wind.
Here we go !
Whoa, hoo-hoo !
Oh, this is cold !
Hey. Slippery. Ice !
We got ice !
Whoa, hang on now!
Ow, hoo-hoo !
Here we go !
Aaah !
Cowabunga !
- [ Honk]
- [ Crash ]
Captain, is this a non stop
flight to Australia ?
Not exactly, no.
I could definitely say no.
We're gonna make connections
with a bigger bird.
Non stop ?
What do I look like,
Charles Lindbergh ?
Let me out ofhere !
You can't do this !
Help, help, help !
Breaker, breaker,
little mate.
I forgot
to tell you,
around here,
you need to be quiet!
Or the rangers
might hear you.
Now sit down and relax.
Enjoy the view.
Nothing but
abandoned opal mines...
as far as
the eye can see.
And dead ahead
is home sweet home.
#Home, home on the range#
# Where critters
are tied up in chains#
#I cut through their sides
and I rip off their hides#
#And the next day
I do it again#
Everybody!
#Home, home on therange##
Cody ! Cody !
Cody !
[P.A. System] Flight 12
is now approaching Sydney Airport.
Make sure your seatbelts
are fastened and tables secured,
and enjoy your stay
in Australia.
[ Snoring ]
- Are we there yet ?
- Yes.
Perhaps we should
wake up Wilbur.
All right,
I'll get him up.
- Wilbur.
- [ Snoring ]
Wilbur !
Just 5 more
minutes, Ma.
Aaah !
5 more minutes.
- Areyou awake ?
- Get up ! We're there !
- Okay, I'm up.
- Watch out !
[ Back Cracks ]
I must have been
sleeping on a bolt.
Oh, boy!
Throw another shrimp
on the barbie,
- 'cause here I come !
- Here we go again.
Cannonball !
Whee !
Gang way !
Coming through !
Mice on board.
Clear the way !
Move over, madam.
There you go.
Coming through, sir.
Thank you.
Next stop,
Mugwomp Flats !
Did we lose anyone
back there ?
[ Bernard ] Miss Bianca,
from now on...
can't we just
take the train ?
Well, Sparky,
you've had this coming
for a long time,
and now you're
gonna get it.
Ha !
Hmmm, wise fly.
[Wilbur] Mugwomp Tower!
This is Albatross 1-3
requesting permission to land.
Over.
Albatross ? Let's see.
Finch, wren, scrubbird,
lorikeet, freckledduck,
galah, kookaburra, parrot,
cockatoo, albatr--
Albatross ?
It's a jumbo !
Negative 1 -3.
Turn back !
Our runway isn't long enough
for a bird your size.
- I can land this ona dime!
-[Bernard] Wilbur--
[Wilbur] You can't let these
radar jockeys push you around!
Leave it to me,
all right ?
I say again, mate,
our runway is too short.
- And I say again, mate, I'm coming in !
- Crazy yank.
Sparky, we've gotta
extend the runway !
- We'll never make it !
- Here we go !
Oof! Aaah !
Passengers,
please remain seated...
until the aircraft comes
to a complete stop.
Thankyou.
Whoa !
Quick, Sparky.
We need to make a drag line !
Whoa !
Ouch !
Don't try and tell me
the runway's too short.
Hold this for me,
will ya, pal ?
[Buzz]
That bloke ought to
have his wings clipped.
Your captain thanks you
for flying Albatross Airlines.
Crazy Yanks.
They think they can
do any fool thing--
Oh, no.
Welcome to Australia.
My name's Jake.
If I can make your
stay more pleasant,
- don't hesitate to ask.
- Oh, how kind.
Allow me to get
that bag for you.
Ahem, I've got a lot
of luggage here.
Let me give
you ahand.
All part of the
friendly service--
- [ Back Cracks ]
- Big-time hurt !
Are you all right ?
Don't worry,
I'll handle this.
Sparky, watch the tower.
I gotta get him to the hospital.
Can't go down, can't go up.
Take the bags !
Heave-ho!
[Wilbur] What are you doing ?
- Heave-ho !
- What's going on ?
Wait a minute.
Just stop everything !
Wilbur, don't worry. We'll come back
the moment we find the boy.
Wait a minute !
Heave-ho !
I'm feeling much better now,
ready to hit the beaches.
I'm even
ready to mambo.
# Dun-dun-dun #
Doctor, will he
be all right ?
Now, now, my dear,
keep a stiff upper lip.
They come in with a whimper
and leave with a grin.
Off with you now.
Leave everything to me.
Shoo-shoo.
Off you go.
Hop to it, ladies.
We've got a bent bird.
- Will it hurt, doc ?
- Bustle !
Dear boy, you won't feel a thing.
Launch the back brace !
Hey, wait!
Ahhh !
I've been skewered !
I've already missed tea,
Mr. Albatross.
Don't force me to take
drastic measures.
- You must relax !
- Relax ? I have never
been more relaxed !
If I were any more relaxed,
I'd be dead !
I'm not convinced.
60 milligrams !
60 milligrams.
Hey, what ?
Are you guys crazy ?
You can't do that to me.
I'm an American
citizen, buddy !
- Better double it !
- Double ?
- Double, coming up.
- No!
Prepare him
for medication.
I'm dreaming !
Wilbur, wake up !
3 degrees right!
- 3 degrees.
- Down 2 degrees.
- Don't go down 2 degrees !
- Ready !
- I'm not ready !
Aim !
- Please don't do this to me !
- Fire !
[ Boom ]
Oh, whoa!
Aaah, ooh!
We just gotta figure out
how to get there.
So, you and your husband
on a little outback excursion ?
We're not married.
We're here on a
top secret mission.
Very hush-hush.
Gonna rescue that kid ?
That's right !
How did you know ?
You'll find it's tough to
keep secrets in the outback.
So, which way
you taking ?
Suicide trail through Nightmare Canyon
or Satan's Ridge ?
Suicide trail ?
Good choice. More snakes
but less quicksand.
Once you cross Bloodworm Creek,
you're scot-free.
That is, until
Dead Dingo Pass.
Wait a minute.
I don't see any of
that stuff on the map.
A map's no good
in the outback.
What you need is...
someone who knows
the territory.
Oh, Mr.Jake,
will you guide us ?
At your service !
Take my arm. It's gonna
be a treacherous hike.
I remember the time
it was just me...
and 400 of these
big, giant possums.
He doesn't even know
how to fold a map.
This is how we get around
the outback, Miss B.
The only way to travel,
hey, Berno ?
Yeah, it's just a little
b-b-bumpy back here.
Cinch up your seat belts, mate.
We're coming in for a landing.
Hold it. Hold it.
Not yet !
Caw-caw !
Well, boy,
Iet's see ifwe can refresh
that rusty old memory ofyours.
Is she on
Satan's Ridge...
or Nightmare Canyon ?
What do you think, Joanna ?
Grrrr, ahhh.
Yeah, that's it.
Right smack dab...
in the middle
of CrocFalls !
- Am I getting warm ?
- I don't remember !
Don't you realize a bird
that size is worth a fortune ?
I'll split the money 50-50.
You can't get a better offer than that.
You won't have any money
after the rangers get you.
Grrahh !
Grrr... aaah !
[Bernard]
Jake's been gone... ow!
Been gone
along time.
Maybe I should go... oh !
Maybe I should
go look for him.
Don't worry about Jake.
He can handle himself.
Yeah, I noticed.
I am sure he'll
be back in no time.
You know,
now that we're alone,
there's...
there's something that
I've been wanting to ask you.
Yes, what is it ?
Well, it's like this.
Miss Bianca,
I-l would be
most honored...
if you--
Look out !
Aaah !
No mice for you,
Twister,
not today !
Miss Bianca !
I've been looking
all over for you.
Now look, we've got
a long way to go,
and you're gonna
take us there !
And you're not gonna
give us any trouble !
Right ?
They're perfectly harmless...
once you look 'em in the eye
and let 'em know who's boss.
Ain't that right ?
Now, git !
It's all right, Bernard.
Jake has everything
under control.
Yeah, I noticed.
You know,
Miss Bianca,
I used to be quite
a dingo wrestler.
This one time
it was just me...
and 300 ferocious
mouse-eating dingos.
They had me surrounded.
The sight of
their teeth...
was like a great
wall of ivory.
Oh...
[Clanking]
[GateSlams]
I'll give you a night down here
to think it over.
But tomorrow,
no more Mr. Nice Guy !
[ Squeal ]
Joanna, you thickheaded
chunk offishbait!
I'll never tell you
where she is !
Never ! Never !
Yeah, we'll never tell !
You'll have to
drag it out of us !
- Hey, where did you come from ?
- Um, the desert ?
Well, well,
Fancy that. Looks like McLeach
has begun trapping his own kind.
There's no hope
for any of us now.
No hope ?
But there must
be a way out.
- There's a way out, all right.
- There is ?
Absolutely !
You'll go as a wallet,
you'll go as a belt,
and our dear Frank...
- I don't want to hear it !
- Frank will go as...
#Waltzing Matilda
ta-ta-la billabong #
- A purse.
- Oh, no !
A lovely ladies' purse.
I don't want
to go as a purse!
Please, please,
don't let him do it.
Don't worry,
we're gonna get out.
- We are ?
- Yeah.
If we put our heads together,
we'll think of something.
- Yeah, something, something.
- Frank, what's wrong ?
- Here he goes again.
- Take it easy.
You don't want
to hurt yourself again.
Yeah, I got it !
All we gotta do
is get the keys !
Oh, is that all ?
Well, then, we'd better
start packing our bags.
Wait !
He's right !
If we could get these
long pieces of wood--
Wood ! Yeah, wood, wood.
Good ! Good !
- Maybe we could--
- Caw-caw !
That's right.
Just a little more. There !
Come on, everybody,
get more stuff!
The kid's right.
What are we waiting for ?
That'sit!
You've got it!
We need something
to tie it together.
[ Rattle ]
Hey!
What do you got ?
Shoelaces, oh.
Almost.
A little further.
[Frank] Yeah... no!
- Let's try again.
- Yeah !
[Cody] Easy does it.
- No... yeah !
- Somebody shut him up !
[Frank] You got it!
Ssss.
Heh-heh.
Hmmm !
Yeah, I got it !
I'll just take my tail
and pick the lock, like this !
Frank, give it a rest.
You'll thank me
when you're free.
I just insert
my tail like this,
I turn it like this,
a quarter turn to the left,
then I push it
a little bit further.
It's all
in the timing.
Pull a little bit back,
push a bit forward.
Show him who's
boss, Berno !
Ah, ah-choo !
Aww, I feel like
I got my head in a vice.
Oh !
#Ta-dee-da-da #
- Are we ready, nurse ?
- Ready, doctor.
All right, ladies,
snap to it !
- [ Snap ]
- Ooh, that smarts !
Oh, let me see here.
#La-la-dee-dee#
Forceps !
Oh, no.
What now ?
Spinal streculator.
That's gonna hurt !
Artery router.
Mother !
This is rusted tight.
I wouldn't dream of using it.
Bring me the epidermal
tissue disrupter !
The epidermal what ?
- Oh, no!
- [ Engine ]
Aaah !
[Alarm]
Mr. Albatross, we haven't
operated yet !
You gotta
catch me first, doc !
Mr. Albatross, please!
Cowabunga !
Mr. Albatross, we must return you
to the operating room !
You'll never
take me alive !
Please don't do this !
Your spine needs...
tender loving care !
Aaah !
Oh, oh !
Ahhh... my back !
Ooh.
It works !
I'm cured !
My back !
I'm coming,
you little mice !
This is the finest fleet
on two webbed feet !
Oh, boy !
I gotta go on a diet
when I get home.
Here we go !
[Knock, Knock]
[ Knock]
[Radio] ln other news,
authorities have called off
the search for the missing boy.
His backpack was found
near Crocodile Falls,
and local rangers believe he was
a victim of crocodile attack.
Authorities warn residents
to use extreme caution--
Think you're pretty
smart, don't ya ?
Who out smarted who, huh ?
I still gotta
get that boy...
to talking, huh ?
I'm hungry.
Can't think on an empty stomach.
Gotta have protein.
Gotta have eggs !
Everyone's got his price.
I'll offer him
whatever he wants,
and then not
give it to him.
- Did you take one of my eggs ?
- Uh-uh.
Open your mouth.
Ahhh.
These are not
Joanna eggs !
Boy's got
the eagle,
I want the eagle,
the boy won't
give me the eagle.
If I could just find
the boy's weak spot,
I could get him to tell me
where the eagle is.
But the boy's only got
one weak spot,
and that
is the eagle.
Maybe if I stuck him
in a giant anthill,
it would loosen
his tongue,
- and then I got him !
- Eeek !
Got your hand caught
in the cookiejar, didn't you ?
Who do you think
you're messing with,
you dumb animal ?
My mental facilities are twice
what yours are, you pea brain !
I give you platypus eggs,
I give you snake eggs,
I'll even give
you eagle eggs !
But I want you
tost ayaway from my--
The eagle's eggs.
That's it !
That's the boy's
weak spot!
A little farther,
take it back
a little bit,
then you turn it
once more around.
Then take it back,
and then you...
Aaah, waa-haa !
I give up !
I'll never get this.
We're doomed!
Doomed.
Look, Krebbs !
- Frank's out !
- Frank, Frank, you're free !
I'm free ?
I'm free !
-Joanna will hear !
- Free, free !
Double or nothing,
he's caught in 5 minutes.
Calm down,
little mate !
Look at me !
I'm free !
- Get the keys.
- I should get the keys !
I'm stuck !
- Shhh, quiet !
- Quiet, ya fool !
Take it easy.
I'll get you loose.
- There you go.
- Ooh !
Now, go get the keys !
The keys !
Yeah !
I can't reach them.
Get something
to stand on !
- Yeah, stand on !
- This ought to be rich.
Yeah, yeah !
Stand on !
- Frank !
- Huh ?
- Climb on the box !
- The box, of course !
- Aaah !
- Quiet !
These darn things
are heavy !
Heh-heh.
Oops. Aaah !
The keys, Frank !
Give us the keys !
Over here !
[ Crash ]
Yee-haa!
Ride 'em, Frank!
Yahoo !
Howdy, howdy !
Aaah !
Waaa !
Let me in !
Aaah !
No, no, no !
No, no !
No-o-o-o !
Ah, ah, ah.
Huh, missed !
Ooo-ooo !
Surprise !
If I didn't know better, I'd
think you don't like it here.
Let me go !
Let go !
What are you doing
out of your cage ?
That's better.
Come on, boy.
Say good-bye
to your little friends.
It's the last
you'll ever see of them.
There is no time to waste.
We must try to get in.
Here, Miss Bianca,
start digging.
Has anyone considered
trying "Open Sesame" ?
[Clank]
Hey, it worked !
[McLeach]
Get out of here !
Look, Bernard,
it's the boy !
And McLeach.
It's all over, boy.
Your bird's dead.
Someone shother, shother
right out of the sky!
Bang !
No !
What do you mean ?
You calling me a liar ?
I heard it on the radio.
She could have been mine !
Now you better get out of here
before I change my mind!
Go on, git !
- Why is he letting him go ?
- It's gotta be a trick.
Too bad about
those eggs,
eh, Joanna ?
They'll never survive
without their mother.
Oh, well,
survival of the
fittest, I guess.
Bingo !
Heh-heh-heh !
- Bird ?
- Eggs ?
Shhh, listen.
[ Engine ]
Heh-heh-heh.
I didn't make it all the way
through 3rd grade for nothing.
[Jake ] I don't know
where he's going,
but we can't
let him get away !
Hurry up,
you two !
Quickly, Bernard, now !
Oh, no!
Get between
the treads !
Whoa !
Bernard, Bianca !
Here, catch !
Got it !
Miss Bianca,
you can do it !
Oh, whew!
Boy, this is some
head wind, huh ?
Say, you lovely ladies
wouldn't have seen...
2 little mice running around
down there, would you ?
Where are you going ?
Hey, I mean it !
I'm looking for 2 little mice !
Is it something I said ?
He's gone down
the cliff.
Come on.
We gotta warn him.
Cody ?
Huh ?
Who are you ?
There is no time
to explain.
You're in
great danger.
-[Screeching]
- Marahute ? It can't be !
Cody, wait !
She's alive !
Cody, please.
You must listen.
McLeach is
on the cliff !
Marahute !
No ! Turn back.
Stay away.
It's a trap !
[ Screeching ]
I got her !
Did you see that ?
Perfect shot.
Perfect shot !
She's mine.
Ha-ha-ha.
All mine !
No !
Hold tight, you two.
We're going for a ride.
Bianca ?
Bernard ?
That meddlin' brat !
I'm gonna get rid
of him for good.
Help !
I'm slipping !
Cody, don't move.
[ Screeches ]
Heh-heh-heh.
There she is, Joanna.
Just look at her.
Look at the size ofher !
The rarest bird
in the world.
That bird's
gonna make me rich.
Filthy rich !
I got what I want.
Now, what does
Joanna want ?
Does she want to make
sure that bird stays rare ?
Yeah-yeah !
How 'bout great big
triple-a jumbo eagle eggs ?
Huh ? You want 'em ?
You want 'em ?
Go get 'em !
No ! Please !
[ Gulp ]
Whatever's the matter,
Joanna ?
Ooo, ooo.
Get moving !
Ahh.
[ Gulp ]
Grr.
Ahhh.
Huh ?
Grr.
Yike !
Joanna, you hurry up
and eat those eggs...
and get your
tail up here !
Move it!
Yeah ! Ha-ha.
# Dum, dum, dee-dum #
Okay, you guys.
She fell for it.
- Looks like the coast is clear.
-[Wings Flapping]
[Wilbur] Girls, I'm here !
Ha-ha-ha. Where are you,
you little chickies, you ?
Wilbur ?
- Wilbur !
- Aaah !
Don't ever do that
to me again !
Oh, boy ! I lost a lot
off eat hers on that one.
Wilbur,
am I glad to see you.
- Give me a hand
with these eggs, will you ?
-Sure.
Wait a minute.
What the heck are you doing up here ?
The kidnapper took the boy
and Jake and Miss Bianca.
Miss Bianca ?
Miss Bianca's in trouble ?
Whoa !
That's terrible.
We got to do something.
Bernard, I'm disappointed in you,
hiding underanest while
Miss Bianca needs our help.
- I gotta talk to you, mister.
- Wilbur.
You should start searching
the desert for her.
And I'll
scan the coastline !
- Wilbur ?
- That's what I'll do.
- Wilbur !
- Huh ? What ?
Listen, there are some chicks
here that need your help.
Really ?
Ohhhh, no.
Wait a minute.
Hold it.
I know what you're thinking
and you're wrong.
Don't look at me like that.
You're getting "no" from me.
You understand ? I will not
ever sit on those eggs.
Ah, nuts !
Gotta learn to
be more assertive.
No is no is no !
Hey !
Quit moving in there.
Well, Joanna, it
looks like lady luck...
has finally decided
to smile on us.
Everything's going
our way.
[Cody] You can't do this.
You'll getin big trouble.
I'll tell the rangers
where you are !
I almost forgot.
We got a loose end
to tie up,
haven't we, girl ?
Now, now, Cody.
We mustn't lose hope.
Bernard is still
out there.
That's right. If anyone can get us
out of this scrape, it's ol' Berno.
- Nice bluff, Miss B.
- I wasn't bluffing.
You don't know Bernard
like I do.
He'll never give up.
Oh, my gosh !
[ Snoring ]
[ Snorting ]
[Snoring]
Ah, ahem, ahem.
Excuse me.
Grrr.
Now, look !
I've got a long way to go.
You're gonna take me
and not give me any trouble.
Right ?
Good !
Now, git !
Are you ready, boy ?
It's time you learned
how to fish for crocks.
They like it when you
use live bait.
And you're as
live as they come.
# Oh, you get a line #
#And I'll get a pole, matey#
#You get a line
and I'll get a pole, friend #
# Oh, you get a line
and I'll get a pole #
# We'll go fishing
in the crocodile hole#
#Buddy palo'mine#
That's right, babies !
Supper time !
[Screeches]
It don't look good,
Miss B.
- I can't see anyway out of this one.
- Bernard, please hurry.
# Pal o' mine ##
Now, this is
my idea of fun !
Nothing personal, boy.
But I wouldn't want
to disappoint the rangers.
They was looking
so hard for you.
And now they're gonna
find you !
What the blaze
is going on here ?
[Snorting]
Joanna ?
Did you know there was
a razorback in my truck ?
Did ya ?
There was a razorback
in my truck !
Quit playing around
and do your job,
you 4-legged python !
Hey, what happened
to them keys ?
Must be around here
somewhere.
They couldn't just
get up and walk away.
Something weird's
going on around here.
I smell a big
fat rat !
Grrr !
- Look ! It's Bernard.
- I don't believe it. Way to go, mate !
Miss Bianca, Jake, catch !
Grrr!
Whoa !
Well, there's more than
one way to skin a cat.
Heh-heh-heh.
Yeow !
[Gunshot]
Blast it !
Oh, my gosh ! I hope
I know what I'm doing.
Sniff, sniff.
Grrr, grrr !
Heh-heh. Yeah.
Hey, get off of me !
Joanna, what are you--
What ? Oh, oh.
Aaaah !
Joanna !
Joanna,
you stupid lizard !
Get off of me,
you idiot.
Get off of me !
No ! No !
Bernard, the boy !
[ Gasp ]
Help !
No, no.
Get back.
Get, get away.
Get away !
I whooped ya !
I whooped you all.
You'll think twice...
before messing with
Percival C. McLeach !
Aaah, aaah, aaah!
Noooo !
Don't give up, Cody !
There !
Hop on, Miss B.
Help ! Help !
[ Screeches ]
Squawk !
It's okay.
Come on.
Thanks,
little mate.
Oh, Bernard,
you are magnificent.
You're absolutely
the hero of the day.
Miss Bianca, before
anything else happens,
- will you marry me ?
- Bernard !
Of course I will !
Well done, mate.
Come on, Marahute.
Let's all go home.
[Wilbur] Help !
Anybody !
Bernard !
Bianca !
Where are you ?
Okay, that's it.
I'm outta here.
This is ridiculous. You
can't leave me here alone.
I'm gone.
I am gone !
-[Cracking] Cheep, cheep.
- Oh, no. Stay in those eggs.
That's a direct order.
Ah. Hey...
You're kind of a
cute little feller.
- Coochie, coochie.
-[SnappingBeaks]
Yeow ! Whoa !
[ Groaning ]