Hey!
Come back here.
I hate that when you do that!
I was bored to death.
Well, I was having fun.
Well, good for you.
- Get in!
- No, I'm grabbing a cab.
Get in!
Stop it!
Leave me alone, Eddie.
Don't ever try that again...
or else!
Or else what?
Mr Yoshida says,
"We regret we can go no further. "
"This is our final proposal. "
"Your company will benefit greatly
from this new relationship. "
"Now you must decide the fate of MicroCon. "
We should close at this price.
Let's see if we can hold out
till Congress votes.
We can't pull backjust now.
Deal's too far gone.
- They'll suspect if we stall.
Listen, I'm the last guy
who wants to screw this up.
Deal's too good,
but we have to have some strategy.
That's what I'm saying.
They're going to stall.
Hey, guys.
- How's it going?
- Good.
If there's anything you don't understand...
Oh, no. We're uh...
- We're fine.
- Great. That's good to hear.
You're gonna be part of a great team.
Once these guys draw
a line in the sand, that's pretty much it.
You want that research and development
money, don't you?
Nakamoto Group can do a lot for you.
- Yeah, right.
- Great.
That guy is an asshole.
The deal will put vital elements of our
military weaponry under Japanese control.
Come on, Senator Morton.
That's really a scare tactic.
During the Gulf War, the Japanese suggested
they could deny us that weaponry. In fact...
- You're oversimplifying a complex issue.
- No...
He's trying to say America is looking for
a new enemy now the Cold War is over.
Talk about simplifying!
You're doing the simplifying, Senator.
Hold on.
Let's let... Eleanor, let the Senator in, please.
I came here to Los Angeles because...
Before we hear that, I couldn't detect
exactly how you're going to vote.
- You know, they warned me about you.
- Well, they should!
They should!
- How are you going to vote?
- Against the sale of MicroCon.
Thank you for saying that flat out.
Let me ask you guys on this side.
You sometimes make it sound as if
Japan's prosperity is bad for America.
Is that what you mean?
The real issue is that this technology
is paid for by American taxpayers...
This discussion is degenerating
into the kind of argument we don't need.
This is already a very tense situation.
There will soon be a vote
in Congress and we will decide
whether the MicroCon sale goes through.
I don't get you, Eddie.
So what?
Oh, ladies, one thing.
Do remember that the custom here
is bow when you're bowed to.
Oh, wow!
They really rolled out the red carpet.
- What floor are we going to?
- 45th.
- After you, Greg.
- Thank you, Rick.
Bow when you're bowed to.
- Oh, wow! Look at this. Everybody's here.
- This is amazing!
There's Barry Hirsch. The Mayor.
- We're in the fast lane now.
- Oh, we sure are.
- Look, here's Yoshida-san and the boys.
- Get ready to bow.
Wife.
- Taiko drums!
- Huh?
Taiko drums. Long ago
they were used to drive away evil spirits.
Come here.
No, here.
Yes.
Yes...
Yes... More...
Ah, yes...
Yo, what's up?
Web. Tom Graham. You're on the chart
tonight, Special Services liaison.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Better get over here.
The new Nakamoto building. 1100 Figueroa.
- I can't believe they're pulling this shit.
- What stuff?
Demanding to see
the fuckin' Special Services liaison.
They say the police can't proceed
until you get here.
And what time
was that phone call from Lieutenant Graham?
What time?
Yes. What time was it?
9.00pm.
February 9th.
Four nights ago?
Was that a yes, Lieutenant Smith?
Yeah. It's a yeah.
Lieutenant Smith,
we appreciate your cooperation.
You waived your right
to be represented here by an attorney.
So... Lieutenant Graham called for
the Special Services liaison.
He said he had a homicide.
Yeah, a homicide. Apparent 601.
Caucasian female, I'd say 25.
Lying flat on her back on the boardroom table
like a piece of sushi.
Quite a sight. Better get down here.
Hello. I'm a police officer.
Can I be of assistance?
May I see your passport?
- What's up?
- This is Watch Commander Hoffman.
Yes, sir.
You're on your way to Nakamoto Towers.
I want you to pick someone up.
- Certainly, sir.
- A guy named Connor.
- Connor?
- Yeah, John Connor.
But I thought... he was long gone.
No, he's very much alive.
They put in a request for him.
- They? Who's they?
- You go. I'll phone him.
- He lives by Little Tokyo. 428 Rose Street.
- Yes, sir.
428 Rose Street.
Connor?
And you did not know
Captain Connor prior to this night?
No, I did not.
- I'd only heard about him.
- What had you heard?
I heard that he had long ago
put himself on indefinite leave.
That he had lived in Japan.
Some people thought they got to him.
Some people said that...
Said what?
The man couldn't be trusted.
You're late.
Yeah, sorry.
- The directions were...
- No.
Be on time.
Shoes.
Is it normal procedure now for the Japanese
to demand a liaison officer?
No. It's usually an assignment.
What time were you called?
Lieutenant Graham called at nine.
Hoffman called in the car.
You were called twice?
Yeah.
I wish I'd known that sooner.
Have you negotiated with the Japanese?
Negotiated?
Mm. Perhaps I can suggest the strategy.
Well, this is hardly a negotiation.
Oh? What is it, then?
What is it?
It's a homicide.
When we arrive,
you take charge of the negotiations.
Don't introduce me or refer to me.
Don't even look in my direction.
Keep yourjacket buttoned at all times.
If they bow, you bow back.
Believe it or not, I have done this before.
You know, I do know these things.
Do keep your hands at your sides.
The Japanese find
big arm movements threatening.
Keep your voice calm and even.
You'll probably find them irritating tonight.
But whatever happens,
don't lose your temper.
I don't lose my temper.
That's good to know.
When you start to get into trouble...
I won't get into trouble.
When you start to get into trouble,
I will say, "Perhaps I can be of assistance?"
From then on, I do the talking.
You stand behind me.
And don't appear distracted.
We may come from a fragmented,
MTV, rap-video culture, but they do not.
Every aspect of your appearance
and behaviour will reflect on you,
the Department, and me as your sempai.
My sempai?
That wouldn't be massa, would it?
No. The sempai is the senior man
who guides the junior man, the kohai.
In Japan, the sempai-kohai relationship
is presumed to exist
when the younger man and the older man
work together.
Hopefully, they will presume that of us.
So what does it mean
that I was called twice?
It means they're ahead of us.
For all they know,
I could have been five minutes away.
They know who was on call tonight,
how long it would take you to get here.
They know all about you.
- All about me?
- Mm.
- It took you long enough.
- Tom.
What the fuck's he doing here?
Fred Hoffman told me to bring him.
The guy is trouble. Watch out.
The Department put him on leave
because he's too close to Japan.
- He's not a team player.
- Where is everybody?
They made us put our cars around back.
They keep saying
nothing must disrupt the grand opening.
Finding that blonde piece of sushi
drove them nuts.
Don't want their guests or the press to know.
Step aside, pal.
- You come down already.
- Yeah?
Well, now I go back up.
Maybe come down, go up 10 times more. OK?
We're still the fuckin' police
in our own country.
Built this building in six months.
Prefab units from Japan, slapped 'em
together here. Not one American worker.
City gave 'em an eight-year break
on property taxes.
Shit! We're giving this country away.
Nobody forced us to do it.
Jesus!
If an elevator's gonna talk, it should
speak in American. What did it say?
We're arriving at the 45th floor.
No, no. Wait a second.
The Japanese provide jobs here,
but US companies are moving jobs offshore.
Ground floor, please.
- They must...
- Going up, Senator.
- No, no. I wish to go down.
- Get the next one, Senator.
Come on.
No, no, no. You don't understand!
Senator Morton.
Real nice to find him partying here,
considering he's on the committee
which sets all import regulations.
Geronimo!
Coming through!
I have your liaison for you.
Is this your home phone, Detective?
Yes. Right there at the bottom.
Detective, let's dispense with the formalities.
We'd like to cooperate,
but you can't start without a warrant.
- Bullshit. We don't need one.
- We can get one in 15 minutes.
- But we do have a reported homicide here.
- More likely a drug overdose.
We can't know that until we investigate.
Obviously.
But I'm concerned about the attempt
to link this death to our reception downstairs.
I don't know, sir.
Looks like she's wearing a party dress.
She is, I agree.
Lieutenant, you have to appreciate
the position of the Nakamoto Corporation.
- Sir, I...
- This is an important evening for us.
A very public evening.
We don't want it marred by the death
of a woman of no importance.
- Of no importance?
- You have some nerve!
- I can't imagine how she came to be in here.
Your Lieutenant Graham intends
to interrogate everybody,
the Mayor, the Senators, and Congressmen.
Graham said that?
Oh, Christ! What is this?
Do you mind turning around?
- Who is he?
- Mr Tanaka works for Nakamoto Security.
- Get him outta here!
- We have authorised him to be here.
I'm authorising him out!
He's contaminating the area. And get his film!
- We must undertake our own private inquiry.
- I'll get you a warrant and a restraining order!
Do that! Be my guest!
Excuse me.
Perhaps uh... I can be of assistance.
Ishihara-san, I'm sure none of your guests
are involved in this unfortunate incident.
They are free to go as they wish.
I am grateful for your assistance.
But before they leave, give me
the names of those gentlemen, please.
I'm sorry.
The names of those gentlemen.
May I ask why?
- Ritchie! Mugshots! All of them!
- You cannot do this!
No! You are to blame here!
You will assist my detectives!
And I want to know who discovered the body!
And don't you fuck with me!
But of course... Captain.
Yeah, don't fuck with us.
Mount up, boys. Let's get it done
before she starts to smell.
- Isn't it bad form to lose your temper?
- It is. But I had to, to assist Ishihara.
Assist Ishihara?
Now why would you wanna do that?
He wasn't the most important man
in the room.
- Oh, he wasn't?
- No. It was the older man.
His juyaku, his superior.
But I wanted to get the investigation going
so I played the out-of-control gaijin.
So Ishihara wouldn't lose face.
So now, Ishihara owes me a favour.
Deep, isn't it?
Heavy.
The executive fuck chamber.
Oh, man, I like this! I like this!
That's nice. That's nice.
These guys sure know how to do business.
Hold that.
Her nostrils look like
a margarita glass rim.
- Think she OD'd on coke?
- I don't think so.
We'll get lab values on all fluids.
Some seminal fluid down here.
External genitals are pretty raw.
It looks like forced intercourse,
but I'm not sure she was murdered.
Not sure she was murdered?
Come on, you gotta be kidding me.
The make-up on the neck
covers signs of prior throat injuries.
That suggests a pattern
of repeated cervical trauma.
Could be a case of sexual asphyxia.
She's a gasper.
Which is what?
Individuals sexually aroused by
the hypoxia of near-strangulation.
They ask their partners to strangle them
or suffocate them during sex.
It's easy to make a mistake and go too far.
This looks like death from inhibition to me.
- Instantaneous physiological death.
- Meaning what?
The person just... dies.
Happens with neck or chest injuries.
Had a kid got hit with a baseball.
Fell down dead in the schoolyard.
Yeah. Maybe she got hit with a baseball.
Odds are she was strangled.
But since having sex isn't a felony,
it wouldn't be murder.
Anyway, file in the back of your mind
that maybe she just popped off.
Cheryl Lynn Austin. Age 23.
This says she has a Westwood address,
but she hasn't changed
her Kentucky licence yet.
Japanese cigarettes and credit cards.
Nice tight roll of $100 bills.
Miss Austin's well taken care of.
These little guys eat shit in Tokyo.
Crammed into subways,
working for big companies.
They come here and they're rich and free.
They all want to fuck a Rose Bowl queen.
And then kill the Rose Bowl queen
on the Nakamoto boardroom table?
Call the police and create a scandal?
Is that your theory?
- My theory?
- Mm.
My theory is that these guys
are known perversion freaks.
I got a nose for these things.
I'm sure.
Hey, Spider-san.
Tell your pal they got a contest.
Whoever kisses the most asses
wins a Toyota.
Hey, Graham! Want some sushi?
Nah. If I get a craving for mercury,
I'll eat a thermometer.
In Japan, criminals expect to be caught.
Convictions run about 90%.
Here, it's closer to 17%.
They think we're stupid.
They think we're corrupt.
And they're not often wrong.
What the hell are you doing?
Good evening, officers. Can I help you?
Yes, you can. Where are you located?
- Lobby level. Across from the elevators.
- Thank you.
How long have you been on duty tonight?
About half an hour.
Mr Tanaka was here when I got here.
Mr Tanaka? Who's Mr Tanaka?
He's the head of security.
Mr Phillips, the 46th floor, the cameras?
I know in Japan
they like to observe their workers
to help them improve their efficiency.
I saw at least four up there. Why so many?
You didn't hear this from me.
I guarantee we didn't hear it from you.
Maybe they put in a couple of new cameras
to observe those negotiations.
What negotiations were those?
The ones that go on up there during the day
with a company called MicroCon.
MicroCon. The computer chip company?
There's a vote coming up
in Congress on that deal.
Put up the 46th floor.
Can the camera get in closer?
- You have to use the gizmo.
- The gizmo? Show me.
You, uh, use the gizmo... to zoom in.
This is all next-generation. There is
nothing like this in this country... yet.
You record by disk?
Record? What do you mean, record?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The disks are all back there.
It's all there on next-generation laser disk.
I'd like to see tonight's disk for the 46th floor.
You'd have to talk with my supervisor.
You got a warrant?
These disks record for 12 hours.
Why does the one on the 46th floor
only show two hours?
Excuse me?
The original disk isn't even here,
anyway, is it?
Because it's been replaced.
I wouldn't know about that.
That's Mr Tanaka's department.
Someone at this very moment is watching us.
Under the circumstances,
you've been more than helpful.
I'd like to tell you officers something.
This is a good job.
Around here, if something doesn't work,
I got a problem,
I tell somebody, they fix it!
It's not like when I was working
at GM out there in Van Nuys.
- This is different here.
- You're part of a team.
What, a team? What are they doing for you?
They spotting for you?
Sending you in plays, huh?
Maybe they got instant replay...
Hey, brother, come on!
These people have been good to me.
Kohai, I'm gonna call in a favour.
Stay here with Mr Phillips.
Come on, kohai.
Lieutenant Smith.
Don't fuck with these guys.
Hey, the honeys are out tonight.
Oh, here's a nice one. Let's use the gizmo.
Oh, yeah, she's nice.
Not so nice.
She's my ex-wife.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Don't be. She's a lawyer.
It must be nice to fuck a lawyer
instead of always being fucked by one.
I've seen your friend
around here quite a bit.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Real friendly with Mr Yoshida there.
And who's Mr Yoshida?
Mr Yoshida's the man!
Let's listen in.
I know nothing of this.
Any recordings we have
are yours to examine.
I will look into it immediately.
What does that mean?
Massa wants me to get the car.
Senator Morton, you said
if the sale of MicroCon is approved,
they will control the market
and use the technology
to compete against our own companies.
You know that there is a time and a place
for business,
and tonight I just want to say
that our hosts threw one heck of a gala.
But, Senator, you've said,
"Look what happened to our TV industry. "
- Is there such a thing as off-duty?
- Let's wrap it up.
Hey, you! Quit loafing!
Get the Senator's car! We're waiting.
No! You get the Senator's car.
Wrong guy. Wrong fuckin' century.
Penguin-lookin' motherfucker!
Let me smack this asshole.
Captain Connor!
Remember me? Bob Richmond.
Myers, Lawson and Richmond.
I understand my Nakamoto guys
got a little frazzled tonight.
If I can be of any help to you,
I'm available.
That's comforting.
Asshole!
I knew him when he was a government
trade negotiator dealing with the Japanese.
Now he's working for them.
Like I said... asshole.
Help you?
Cheryl Lynn Austin.
- She not in.
- Yeah, I know.
Keys.
Room two.
The doorman's Yakuza.
I noticed his tattoo. I didn't know
there were so many Yakuza in America.
This isn't America.
This is that shadow world.
They have bars, clubs and... bettaku.
Bettaku. Love residence
where mistresses are kept.
- This is one, huh?
- Correct.
Here we are.
What time did it start raining tonight?
After nine.
Someone was here after nine.
Correct.
Look at this.
She's with Eddie.
You know him?
Mm. Eddie Sakamura.
What's this?
Girlfriend was into some different shit.
Look.
What is with this guy? There's a lot
of pictures of her with your friend Sakamutu.
- Sakamura.
- Whatever.
Somebody's taken photos from here recently.
Oh... I thought I heard Eddie's voice.
Say...
- Why is everybody in Cheryl's room tonight?
- Everybody?
Well, you and...
Aren't you just a little bit off limits here?
And who are you?
Me?
Well, I'm Julia.
I'm just a little neighbour girl
who lives down the hall.
Are you Cheryl's back-door man?
And what if I am?
Well...
If you are,
I heard of you.
You better watch out
cos Eddie, he's the real jealous type.
They don't call him Crazy Eddie for nothing.
Really? Well, I'm kinda tough.
Mm, well,
tough as you may be,
Eddie finds out,
then you're gonna be crying.
Um, say,
is Cheryl all right?
No, she isn't.
Lieutenant Web Smith. LAPD.
I knew he was gonna do something to her.
I heard him screaming at Cheryl.
Shouting things like, "I'll kill you",
before he took her to that party tonight.
Many thanks, miss.
Someone from my office will contact you.
I knew he was gonna do something to her.
Kohai.
You know, Web...
Eddie's father is a big industrialist
over there at Daimatsu.
He has a... a friend he sees.
Jeanette.
Right up here on the second floor.
You know how Eddie met Cheryl?
Well,
she was working in that Toyota plant
back there in Kentucky.
Then one day,
who should show up
in that small, little town...
but Eddie.
Web...
She was about to give up the murderer,
and you just walk away.
Maybe I've been bought off by the Japanese.
Sempai, apple pie, whatever I have
to call you... we have a murder here.
I want to solve it,
not listen to true confessions.
You know what's true?
When something looks too good
to be true, then it's not true.
Everything she said about Eddie
might have been true.
The real question is
why was she saying it?
OK! Why was she saying it?
I'm not sure.
Because she thought
Eddie killed the girl!
This Julia accidentally walked in...
Nothing is happening accidentally.
She's a messenger.
- Oh, you think someone sent her?
- Mm.
OK. Who?
The bad guys.
And I suppose they sent her in
to find out what we know.
Or to tell us what they wanted us to know.
Or maybe to slow us down.
She certainly slowed you down.
Bullshit!
Bullshit?
Never underestimate your opponent.
Never take what he offers you.
You want to solve this crime?
- Yes.
- Well, so do I.
Now let's move.
Come on, Eddie!
Darling, those days are gone from your life.
I could dance like that. I'm an old
song-and-dance man from way back.
Oh, yeah? Wanna teach me some steps?
- It's by invitation only, gentlemen.
- Mr Sakamura.
- Mr Sakamura is not here.
- That's him. The bad tap-dancer.
Mr Sakamura is not available.
Mr Sakamura is a good friend of mine.
I'm sure he's available for me.
Gentlemen, you're trespassing.
Now, unless you have a search warrant,
you'll have to leave.
You should know I'm a black belt.
- But of course you are, dear.
- Need help, Perry?
So is Jeff.
OK, fellas. You're leaving.
That's assault.
I don't wanna hurt you.
They say if you must resort
to violence, you've already lost.
What do you think, Jeff?
I think I'll go get Mr Sakamura.
- Ah, Captain Connor!
- Eddie.
My father will be happy to hear
you're still up to your same old tricks.
We're here to talk, Eddie.
So talk. It's a free country.
It's about the murder at Nakamoto tonight.
Well, let's talk outside.
Yeah. I heard about that. Some poor girl.
You know her, Eddie.
Cheryl Austin.
Oh, yeah, Cheryl. Mm. That girl.
Too bad.
I hear she was a real hentai onna.
You knew her better than that.
You're putting her up at the Imperial Arms.
Oh, that Cheryl. Oh, I know her real well.
- She was all over me, Connor-san.
- You're irresistible.
That's true, but...
Connor-san, she had a big problem.
She was a sick girl. She liked pain.
Put a plastic bag over her head,
always saying, "Squeeze harder. "
Squeeze the neck? You like that, do you?
Me? No!
I'm a straight meat-and-potatoes man.
Don't let 'em see you like this. Get up!
- Did you see her tonight?
- Tonight? Me?
Maybe for two minutes at the party.
Just to say hello.
Mr Sakamura,
I think you'd better come with us.
Yeah, I saw her tonight.
I brought her to the party.
But I have nothing to do with it.
Look, I can prove it to you.
Just let me call you later.
I will bring you something.
- I think that's a bad idea.
- Captain.
Nakamoto is keiretsu.
My father is Daimatsu keiretsu.
If his son is arrested here,
there will be repercussions.
Business is war. I know you understand.
Do you have your passport?
Yeah, sure.
Give him your card.
And you call him, Eddie.
Connor-san!
- I sure hope you know what you're doing.
- Me, too.
He's guilty as hell.
Well, my dairokkan says he's not.
I hope your intuition is right.
Look, sempai,
my dairokkan tells me your dairokkan
wasn't why you let Eddie go.
In Japan, his father saved my life.
And Eddie reminded you of that?
He would never remind me.
It's my responsibility to remember.
So what is all this bullshit
about his father's keiretsu?
Bullshit? There's a keiretsu war going on.
A Japanese corporation never stands alone.
A keiretsu is a united front
of hundreds of powerful companies,
all acting in partnership to win.
To win what?
Whatever's there.
You ever hear "business is war"?
The war is never over.
Maybe you heard
"All's fair in love and war"?
No.
- So where does that leave us?
- Us?
We're in the war zone.
So, based on the lab results,
the guy who fucked her was Japanese.
Semen analysis is blood type AB.
Diego factor positive.
Negative for ethanol dehydrogenase.
Asian pattern.
Male pubic hair also Asian in origin.
Evidence points to a Japanese perpetrator.
It's a Jap perp all right.
What the hell's this?
Looks like your guy confessed.
No. It's just Sumimasen.
If they're caught doing something wrong, to
get leniency, they must perform an apology.
- You mean it's an act?
- Not exactly.
He's genuinely scared
you'll create a scandal.
Yoshida-san insisted that he find
the missing disk and deliver it to us.
Yeah, good luck.
That disk is probably
in a Tokyo landfill by now.
What the hell's this?
Daytime. 46th floor.
Negotiations for MicroCon.
Semiconductors.
Hey, can we skip the cartoons?
Hold on. We're just starting.
Richmond-san. Busy, busy.
Hey, let's go. Get to it!
Night-time. Same place.
Looks different then.
Jesus! It's her.
Hello.
Come on in.
He looks Japanese.
Maybe he's Polish.
He's checking to see
if she's carrying a gun.
Someone's using the gizmo.
Gizmo. He's sure using it on her.
There go the hands to the neck.
Just the way she likes it.
Hey, Mr Nice Guy. Turn around.
Oh, no! Don't tell me
he's gonna walk out in the dark.
No! Step into...
There! Back it up!
There.
That's right, I knew it all along.
- I was right about this.
- Eddie.
You know this fucker?
Eddie Sakamura.
We had him tonight.
- What do you mean, you had him?
- We had him. We let him go.
- I kept his passport.
- His fuckin' passport? Jesus!
Get his ass, not his passport!
What are you waiting for? You want banzai
carved on her ass with a samurai sword?
Let's go get this Eddie Sock-It-To-Me.
I'm gonna break your arms, my friend.
I'm gonna love breaking them.
Come on, Web!
The old guy sucker punched me.
If I see him again, he's dead meat.
Oh, forget it.
Good evening, Jeff. Mr Sakamura in?
Easy, big fella.
Just like old times, Web.
Do you miss it? A night out with the boys?
- Sure beats all that diplomacy shit.
- I thought no violence.
Last thing we want.
The guy's a murderer, Spider-san.
LAPD takes no chances.
Yeah, but we do take prisoners. Right?
Why did Connor let this guy walk?
I can't say.
What is he about?
He's always careful not to offend their...
What is it we're not supposed to offend?
Fuck 'em, they break the law.
If that brands me as a reactionary...
- We're in position. Stand by.
- Moving in.
Is reactionary a dirty word?
Like racist, or something like that?
All this talk of race.
Whatever happened to good and evil?
A guy did it, you catch him.
Plundering our natural resources.
Fuckin' guys are into everything!
What time you got, Web?
2.10.
Make a note.
At 2.11, suspect was apprehended.
Eddie Sakamura calling. It's urgent.
I must speak about missing disk.
Police! Get down!
Stay where you are! Get down!
Don't move! Get down!
- You guys, out the back!
- You son of a bitch!
What the hell? Get off of me!
There he goes!
Ow, shit!
What the hell is wrong with you? Get off!
You're nuts! Get off of me!
Get that son of a bitch!
- I'm a police officer!
- You're a piece of shit!
8- Adam-65.
Am in pursuit of 187 suspect,
eastbound, Sunset.
All units, stand by.
8- Adam-65 in pursuit eastbound...
8- Adam-65, what is your location?
Stay back, I want him alive.
Holy shit!
Damn! Damn, damn, damn!
Coroner's officials have taken possession
of the charred remains
identified as Mr Edward Sakamura.
The crash took place after...
We tried to take him, but he ran, Chief.
Burnt beyond recognition. The guy's a cinder.
You got proof that Sakamura
committed the murder?
- Absolutely. Got it all recorded. Right?
- Absolutely.
You did everything by the book?
By the book. Absolutely, Chief.
Absolutely.
But everything was not
absolutely by the book.
Absolutely not.
And when did you discover this?
Yeah.
- Lieutenant Smith?
- Yeah.
This is division dispatcher.
Uncleared messages.
- All right, go ahead.
- 5.27 am, Captain Connor.
Oh, Connor.
He said to give you a wake-up call at seven
and to meet him at the golf club at 9.15am.
All right, all right. Anything else?
Let's see... Nope.
What about last night?
You got all your messages last night.
No, I didn't call in last night.
Yeah, you did.
Let's see... yep.
2.33. Your clearance number was given
and messages were transmitted.
Look, I forgot.
Can you give those messages to me again?
All right, just a sec.
What were you doing last night?!
- Sort of helping my career.
- Is that good?
Yeah. It's always good.
Cos you gotta look out
for yourself in life.
Grandma says you gotta look out
for other people.
Yeah. Well, you gotta do that, too.
That's why everybody's so busy all the time.
So, is that what business is?
Business?
No, business... Business is...
Business is... is...
I can't explain it to you right now.
Is that why Mommy says
you've no head for business?
- Lieutenant Smith? Here we go.
- Yeah.
Daddy? Why does Mommy call you a loser?
Out!
Ken Shubik, please call. Message reads,
"The Weasel's checking up on you. "
- The Weasel?
- Yeah.
Then 2.10 this morning,
Mr Eddie Sakamura...
- Eddie Sakamura?
- Correct.
2.10am. Message reads,
"Urgent. Must speak about missing disk. "
Nice shot!
Hey! I gotta talk to you!
We gotta have a conversation.
Shit!
Yoshida-san. I'm embarrassed
by this crude interruption.
You must play your stroke again.
No penalty.
- Ken Shubik.
- Hey, Ken! Web Smith.
- Did you get my message?
- Yeah, about the Weasel.
Last night, I'm working late at the paper...
I see the Weasel arrive, dressed in his tux.
He goes right to the library.
I could tell the ambitious turd
had the scent of blood.
He's still here.
I ask the librarian what he's checking out.
She says, "A cop named Web Smith. "
- What?
- Yep. The guy's a scumbag for hire.
He used to do jobs
for the studios and realtors.
The little turd just got
a new Mercedes 500SL.
Pretty good on a reporter's salary.
Wonder who he's working for now?
You get on the wrong side
of somebody last night?
- Maybe.
- Somebody's got the Weasel tracking you.
Something about
a charge brought against you.
- A charge brought against me?
- You and a Lieutenant Tom Graham.
At the hearing I was cleared. It was bullshit!
Maybe so, but I thought you'd better know.
Smells like something heavy coming down.
What happened to the disk? We left it
with you when we went to get Eddie.
And you got Eddie.
Oh, yes. It was all over the paper.
There was no mention of the murdered girl
on the boardroom table, right?
You had the disk.
It is against the rules to take evidence.
The rules?
Whose rules?
The rules!
The chief says we fucked up...
The Japanese have a saying.
"Fix the problem, not the blame. "
Find out what's fucked up and fix it.
Nobody gets blamed.
We're always after who fucked up.
Their way's better.
Their way is better?
You wake me up to tell me that?
Wake you up? That'll be the day.
Keep it, sport.
Next time, try a parking meter.
- Captain Connor?
- Yes.
A gift from Mr Hanada.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Most welcome. Most welcome.
You must have really
took those guys this morning.
No. I lost.
Lost? Guys didn't look all that good.
They're not.
It's difficult to lose
without making it too obvious.
- That way they don't lose face.
- Saving face.
Sounds more to me
like you were kissing ass.
Not exactly.
I've done services for those men in the past.
And we've shared information.
They said that Eddie's death
will have repercussions.
Yeah, right!
I'm sorry. The guy was a fugitive.
He killed the girl.
- I doubt it.
- You doubt it?
Well, I saw it on the disk.
Did you?
It's the only space available to us.
We analyse commercials and network news
to see how the public's being tricked.
Problem is, most students want to learn
the tricks so they can use them to get ahead.
OK, everybody!
Class is over.
Ice-skating rink upstairs.
The ice melts down here.
Speaking of ice, Captain, she's been at it
since you gave her the disk at 3am.
Jingo Asakuma...
meet Lieutenant Web Smith.
You're late.
What have we got?
Something there.
In the edge colours.
Look at shadow lines.
They added some shadows.
Look at the light source.
We can see her face, but we can't see his.
- Perfectjob, though.
- And what else?
The reflection.
- Of Eddie.
- It's fishy.
Wait a minute. What's going on here?
Here we are.
Let's look at the colour shift in the pixels.
Yeah. Let's look at those pixels.
Pixels have been doctored.
See the blue edge?
- This disk's a copy.
- A copy? Wait a minute.
You're saying somebody put Eddie's face
there and it's not his reflection?
Come on, that's bullshit!
Bullshit? Where have you been, Lieutenant?
You don't think video can be altered?
I want you to watch what I've been recording
on that camera.
This is quick and crude, but imagine
the effect with more sophisticated equipment.
Watch this.
You're saying somebody put Eddie's face
there and it's not his reflection?
Come on, that's bullshit!
- They'd need photos of this man.
- They have photos of Eddie.
From the dead girl's apartment.
Off the mirror.
- Do you believe in ghosts, Lieutenant Smith?
- What do you mean, do I believe in ghosts?
In Japan, when I was growing up,
we believed in many ghosts.
I want you to watch this.
Tell me what you see.
See it?
- See what?
- Yeah.
Play it again... but slowly.
The way to see it is to move slightly faster.
It's a ghost!
- Look at that! It's a ghost!
- A third person.
- It's been systematically erased.
- Erased?
Just like airbrushing someone out of a still,
only much harder.
It pisses me off, though.
They expect us to be sloppy Americans.
They think we will not be thorough,
not be intelligent.
In Japan, I guess they'd have done it right.
Right. The ghost would have stayed hidden.
To do this, they would need
high-res video stills,
close-ups of the table, anything in the area.
They'd have to duplicate
the ghost's walk.