Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hey, I got you something.
Oh, what is it?
It's something
I think you don't have.
A history
of reliable boyfriends?
No, it's--
Well, it's only, you know...
- Open it later on.
- OK.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- No.
Oh.
- Everyone, could I have
your attention?
- Oh, my God.
Hey. Everyone,
your attention, please.
Everyone, hi.
Thank you for coming.
- Really good to see you all.
- Thank you.
As you all know,
we're here to celebrate...
the birthday
of one Elizabeth Olivia O'Dell.
Happy birthday.
As many of you know, uh,
my passion in life is running.
In fact,
in a couple of days...
I'll be completing another
marathon, thank you very much.
Uh, now, success in running
requires a lot...
of the same things
as success in love--
passion, determination...
and something I've needed
a lot of with Libby, stamina.
That's just inappropriate,
isn't it?
The long-winded point
I'm trying to make...
is that both love and running
require heart...
and Libby has...
truly, has more heart...
than any other person
I've ever known.
So happy birthday, sweetie.
Thank you all.
Oh, trainers!
I'm sorry. Can l, uh,
just see this for a second?
Now, what, um...
As most of you know...
I usually run my races alone,
but I thought...
I was wondering
if you would consider...
becoming my partner?
Oh, my.
Libby, will you marry me?
No, no, no, no.
OK. Yes.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
So beautiful.
Just beautiful.
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
Crazy.
What'd I miss?
So...
You bloody...poison.
All right. You can stick it
up your ass...
you big American prick.
# Our love has changed #
- I don't mind they've decided.
- # It's not the same #
# And the only way to say it #
# Is say it #
# It's better #
# I can't concede #
# This way I feel #
# For all the time
we spend together #
# Forever just gets better #
# See, what I'm trying
to say is #
# You make things better #
# And no matter
what the day is #
# With you here, it's better #
# I'll stand by you #
# If you stand by me #
# I think it's time
that I reveal it #
# 'Cause I believe it #
# It's better #
# See, what I'm tryin'
to say is #
# You make things better #
Dennis!
So what do you think
we should do, Dennis?
Jake got really upset when
I tried to explain it to him.
So, I just wonder whether maybe
you could talk to him today?
You know, just--
If he heard it from you...
that you're always gonna be
his daddy, you know?
I take it the diet's off.
Dennis, are you even listening?
Dennis!
What? You want--
You want me to tell Jake...
what a--what a--
what a perfect guy Whit is...
and it's all gonna be
really perfect...
in his new perfect life?
No.
Not necessarily in those words.
I cannot believe
you're gonna marry this guy.
He pulled your engagement ring
out of a shoe.
Please, Dennis,
you're the only one...
who can help Jake
feel OK about this.
Listen, if you wanna marry Whit,
that's fine, OK?
You're a big girl, and you can
make your own mistakes, OK?
But don't come down here
while I'm eating...
my full English breakfast
with extra breakfast...
and expect me to make things
easier for you, OK?
Can I please get
some ketchup here?!
I'm not gonna run.
What?!
I said I'm not running.
What do you mean,
you're not running?
I mean, I'm not running. I'm
not running a stupid marathon.
Why? Because Libby's
getting married again?
What did you think?
She-- She's not gonna find
anybody better than you?
Well, let me be the first
to tell you.
You know, you're
not a tough act to follow.
Oh, what?
You think I don't know that?
I don't care any more!
- What about me?
- What about you?
I've got money on this!
A lot of money!
That is not my problem!
Quit it!
I'm not the quitter.
- Let me go!
- Ow, my ear!
- Let go!
- Ow!
Oh, OK! Oh, all right!
Oh, enough!
Just-- Just stop for a minute!
# Every day,
I love you less and less #
# I've got to get this feeling
off my chest #
# The doctor says
all I need's pills and rest #
# Since every day,
I love you less and less #
# Unless, unless #
- # I know, I feel it #
- Are you gonna run?
# In my bones #
- No!
# I'm sick, I'm tired #
# Of staying in control #
- # Oh, yes, I feel
I race upon a wheel #
- Oh, God!
- OK, OK, OK, OK.
- You'll run?
# Oh, yes, I'm stressed #
# I'm sorry I digressed #
# lmpressed,
you're dressed to SOS #
# Oh-oh #
- My balls!
- # And my parents love me #
# Oh-oh #
- # And my girlfriend loves me #
- That's it! Run away!
That's what you always do!
Run away!
# Every day,
I love you less and less #
Hey, what the--
- Hello, Dennis.
- What are you doing?
Gordon called.
He tells me
you're not running the marathon.
- Yeah, but--
- But, what?
Are you running or not?
- No, but--
- So there you go.
- Wait--
- Sorry, Dennis.
A bet's a bet. You're out.
Mr Ghoshdashtidar?
Mr Ghoshdashtidar!
- Who the hell are you?
- Oh, please, look.
- I thought you were
a good man, Dennis.
- Yeah...
A little screwed up here
in the head, OK.
But Maya was right about you.
You are no good.
- Look--
- Always running away...
never running
in the right direction.
Yeah, but, oh--
I bought you
new running shoes, Dennis.
The man said
they were the best you can buy.
- Yes, but--
- "But, but, but!"
Always "but"!
Always excuses with you!
Always some reason
why it's not your fault!
I have news for you,
Dennis Doyle from downstairs.
It's all your fault!
- Hi.
You-- You havin' a yard sale?
No. Where's Libby?
Uh, she's pickin' up Jake.
I suppose, uh,
congratulations are in order.
Oh, yeah. Well, thank you.
Best man won.
Well, I wasn't really aware
it was a contest.
Dennis! Dennis!
Is Jake with you?
No, why? I--
Well, is he here, Whit?
- I thought you were
picking him up.
- Jake!
- Libby?
Libby, what is--
- What did you say to him?!
- l-- What are you--
I didn't say anything.
What do you mean?
Well, he was at Emily's
and something happened.
He just ran out.
- What?
- He has run away, OK?
Jake ran away!
Jake!
Gordon!
- Yes?
- Jake's run away.
- What?
- He's run away!
All right.
Well, wait a minute.
Just calm down.
Think for a second.
Where would he go?
Hiya, snot-face.
Yeah, he's fine.
We'll be back in about
a half an hour, I guess.
OK.
Is she mad at me?
No, no.
She's just glad you're OK.
Do you wanna tell me
what happened?
Emily doesn't wanna be
my girlfriend any more.
Why not?
'Cause there's this other boy,
Robert...
and he's got a ponytail...
and she likes him now.
What, she likes him
because he's got a ponytail?
Uh-huh.
Jake 'n Bake...
as you get older,
you're gonna realize...
there are a lot of things
that you don't like, OK?
Things much worse than this.
And when those things happen,
you can't just run away.
Why not?
Because it doesn't solve
the problem.
You know,
when you start running...
the problem's still there.
You've got to stick at it,
and then figure out a way...
to solve the problem, even if
it's really, really hard.
Is that what you do, Dad?
Dad?
Dennis!
Gordon!
- Found him?
- Yes.
Good. You can't stay here.
Gordon!
What?!
I'm running.
Well, come on up then.
Wow, these are great.
Where'd you get 'em?
- Whit's place.
- Thanks.
See, the trick is...
you got to load up on carbs
the night before the race.
I read it in Cosmo.
How are the legs? Not too tight?
No. No, they're fine.
Have you got everyhing
you need?
You know, your shoes,
your shorts, penis t-shirt?
- Yes.
- Oh.
I'm not really in the mood.
- It's for your nipples.
- What?
You run a 26-mile race,
a lot of friction...
is generated from your shirt
to your nipples.
And the last thing you want
during a marathon...
is nipple chafing.
- Cosmo?
- Yeah.
I'm not puttin' that
on my nipples, OK?
And I'm not gonna eat this.
Let's just go to sleep.
Well, at least,
let me make your bed for you.
Anything else?
Have you got a pillow?
- No.
- Well, then I guess I'm fine.
Hey, what time
do you have to be up tomorrow?
Well, we should set the alarm
for about seven o'clock.
- I don't have an alarm clock.
- Why not?
I never need to be anywhere.
The race starts at 9.00, OK?
So we should leave here
no later than 8.00, OK?
OK.
Night.
Love you.
A very good morning to you.
It's a beautiful day
here in London...
for the first
annual Nike River Run.
We've had a very warm welcome
from the crowd...
and we've got perfect conditions
for this race, Denise.
We certainly have.
26.2 miles
along the River Thames...
10,000 runners
from all over the globe...
and an amazing way
for many of these folks...
to raise money for so many
worthwhile charities.
And as we can see,
race officials...
are already busy
at the starting line...
with the start
less than an hour away.
- Taxi!
- # Keep on runnin' #
Taxi!
- # Keep on hidin' #
- Taxi!
Wait!
- Wait!
- # One fine day #
# I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
- It's a wonderful course.
- # Oh, yeah #
- They'll wind
around the Thames...
- # I'm gonna be your man #
They'll cross over five bridges,
including Osney Bridge...
Albert Bridge,
and the Millennium Bridge.
OK, OK. So go at your
own pace today, all right?
- Slow and steady.
- OK. Slow and steady.
Yeah, they're challenging
the leaders we have here.
One from Japan,
Hiyusha Shinuzu...
and, of course, up there also,
is Sumi Yamata.
Watch it!
- ldiot!
- # Keep on runnin' #
- # Runnin' from #
- The other way! Go back!
- # My heart #
- No, we're not goin' back!
Amongst the names
we should keep an eye on...
are the men from Kenya.
Always so strong, Wilson Deetay
and Collington Degwa...
they always can be found
at front of the pack.
This is as far
as I can get, mate.
But I need to get to the start
of the race.
Well, it's just over the bridge.
That's fifteen quid, mate.
Have you got any money?
Sir, we have
a slight liquidity problem.
That is a shame.
Uh, no. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Look, look. This is a 19...
...40 Rolex 520 Perpetual
Oyster with a bubble back.
That's not too shabby.
Gordon,
you can't possibly give him--
Hey, it's an investment.
Gordon, thank you.
I'll see you later then.
# Keep on runnin' #
Hey, good luck!
Now, typically,
the day would have started...
at the crack of dawn
for most of these runners.
They had a balanced breakfast...
precise physical
and mental preparation.
On a day like today,
to leave anything to chance...
you'd either have
to be extremely naive...
or a complete idiot.
# Everyone is talkin' about me #
Over here. To me, to me.
That's it. Be careful.
That's an antique.
- Did it start? Did it start?
- Not yet.
- Turn it on.
- Here we go.
What do we love
about these days...
is the sheer
mix of competitors.
They come
in all shapes and sizes...
from the elite over there
to the--how should we put it--
not so elite.
That's Dennis!
Look at that stretch.
Look at that.
Double or nothing?
Yeah, right.
Just a few minutes to go now.
The warm-ups should be complete.
It's time, if you have one,
for that pre-race ritual.
Well, well, well.
You made it, huh?
Yeah.
Just wanna wish you luck
out there.
You, too. How are your nipples?
Great.
- More toast.
- Only a few moments...
to go now,
and the officials are--
Who do you want to win,
Daddy or Whit?
- Who do you wanna win?
- Daddy, of course.
- If you're one
of the fun runners...
- What about you?
- it's just about
completing the course.
- Eat your toast.
And what a great turnout
we've got here today.
Why am I always the tortoise?
A bet's a bet.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
- Pardon me.
- All right.
Well, Dennis, I gotta admit...
I didn't think
you'd make it this far.
I mean, uh...
you don't exactly have
the best, uh, track record...
now, do you?
Yeah, well that was then,
and this is now.
No, Dennis.
This is now.
All right.
Don't feel you have to keep up
with me.
Well, don't feel
you have to keep up with me.
Oh, yeah, that's the spirit.
And they're off, Chris.
Yet another great marathon...
getting under way
here in London.
And having these great runners
go 26.2 miles...
of crowded London streets...
That was great, what you did
with Jake yesterday, by the way.
Thanks.
I know Libby
really appreciated it, too.
Oh, I'm glad.
In fact,
she was so appreciative...
we had a nice little jump
on the bed.
- What?
- Have a good race.
Isn't it enough?
What?
You got the girl, all right?
Isn't it enough?
I just think it's high time
you realize...
that it's over, sir.
Otherwise, it's gonna be
very tough for you...
- when we move to Chicago.
- What?
You better
slow down there, chief.
You got a long way to go.
- Yeah, well, so have you.
- Oh, yeah!
Yes, I like it.
Run, fat boy, run!
I can lose weight...
but you'll always be
an asshole.
Now, once again,
it's still being dominated...
- by the Kenyans, Denise.
- Look at that.
The runners are making their way
along the embankment.
What a beautiful view of the...
So, here we are
among the leaders of the moment.
The pace is relatively relaxed
for the opening miles.
Maybe a little too relaxed,
Chris.
It looks like we've got
a couple of amateurs...
coming up from the back.
Mom!
It looks like these two boys...
are running a race
of their own here today.
In fact,
they're causing quite a stir...
among the serious runners.
Not something
you'd really expect...
at this stage in the race.
Oh. Sorry, sir.
There's a man down.
Sorry.
All eyes right now
are on these two runners.
No, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
- We hope to bring you
that information quickly.
- Slow down.
But he looks good, doesn't he?
- Oh, yeah.
...setting a new world record.
What are you trying to prove?
She doesn't
love you any more, man.
I'm not doing this for Libby.
Yeah, right.
You're ridiculous, dude.
What's the matter, Whit,
can't keep up?
Oh!
Daddy!
Dennis! I mean, Whit!
It does look very serious.
We're getting
some more information--
Stay down! Stay down!
Where do you think you're going?
- I have to go help Dennis.
- Why?
Because I am
the assistant coach.
Yes!
He now leads
at the ten-mile mark.
And that looks really painful.
Looks like
this runner's race day...
will be ending
at a Leeds hospital.
Yeah, absolutely tragic--
Mom, do something!
- We certainly do.
Let's get back...
- Come on.
to the leaders
in the female race.
Shit.
Huh?
Gordon, I think I speak
for everyone here...
when I say, "Give me my money."
Five grand, please.
OK, here's the thing
about the money...
and, actually,
it's kind of funny.
Uh...I don't have it.
Would you excuse us a moment?
Hi. I'm looking
for a patient, Dennis Doyle.
Are you family?
- Yeah.
- Doyle?
Yes, Dennis Doyle.
Oh, I'm sorry,
we don't seem to have anyone...
registered by that name.
Are you sure?
He's a runner in the marathon.
Oh, the runner. Oh, yeah.
Well, he's just arrived.
- Libby?
- Whit?
How'd you know I was here?
What are you doing here?
Honey,
that psychopath tripped me.
He tripped me.
I think I have ligament damage.
Guys, can we-- Can we just--
Fellas, can we--
Look, I'm a patient, please.
Just one-- Find me!
Easy, easy! Ow!
Vince, look, when I said
I didn't have the money...
I meant
I didn't have the money here.
- I can pay.
- Oh, you're gonna pay.
No, wait. Look...Vincent.
Wait-- Wait-- What?
Wait. Wait a tick.
Not so bloody fast, mate.
Who the hell are you?
Thanks a lot, Mr G!
Your friend is a man of honour.
What, Vincent?
Yes, he said he's going to kick
shit out of you later instead.
I don't understand.
On the TV, they said
he was being brought here.
One second.
I could sue him.
You know that, right?
I could sue him
for everyhing he has...
but, you know, seriously,
what am I gonna do...
with some pizza boxes
and a Judas Priest t-shirt?
Honey,
I'm sure it was an accident.
Well, you weren't there, OK?
You didn't see it.
He was wild-eyed, all right?
He was frothing at the mouth
at one point.
It was like running a marathon
with Cujo, OK?
Jake, buddy,
can I control the bed, please?
No, but you can watch me
control it.
Libby? Where are you?
- The hospital.
- Are you with him?
No, he's not here.
Well, what do you mean
he's not there?
I mean, he's not here.
Well,
where the hell is he then?
All right.
It's still-- It's on.
The race is still on.
I can't believe
you let Gordon go, Vincent.
- Yeah, but he said
he was gonna pay us...
- Back to the story.
- right, Vincent?
- The first images
are coming in...
- from what looks
like a camera phone...
- Vincent?
- showing a lone,
mysterious runner.
Uh, he's looking very badly
injured, I must say...
and he's also causing
some major traffic--
- Cab.
- Yeah, it's a Rolex.
I'm not gonna sell it.
It's a family heirloom now.
What!
Wait! What are you doing?!
- Step on it!
- You can't
just take a man's cab!
All right!
Hello, there...
Dennis Doyle from downstairs!
Who the hell are you?
You beauty, come on!
And as the sun
sets over London...
we're still looking
into the identity...
of that mysterious runner.
Come on, Dennis,
you can do it! Come on!
The only concrete thing
we do know...
is that he's running
for erectile dysfunction.
Good news, Mr Bloom.
No rupture, no ligament damage.
Oh, that's great.
Jake, please?
In fact,
there's no real damage anywhere.
Are you sure, doctor?
Jake, please.
It's, uh, like, uh...
What is it you runners say?
You hit the wall.
No, no, that--
That's not possi--
God damn it, will you stop...
messin' around with the bed,
you little shit?!
God.
Good evening.
It's time for a sports update.
Top story, the Nike River Run.
We'll be chatting to the winner
a little bit later on...
but first, we've had thousands
of e-mails and calls...
about our mystery runner.
Well, I can tell you now,
our TV crew...
has just caught up with him.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Will you slow down, please?
You hungry?
You wanna get a bite?
Stop! Stop!
Everyone out. Get out.
- Come on!
- I'm goin'!
Hey!
Just go away!
- Somebody trip him.
- Go away!
Knock him over.
No, invalid. Off-side.
- Oh!
- Leave him alone! Get off him!
I want my money now!
Don't listen to them, Dennis!
You are a winner!
I want my money now!
Stop it! I'm wearing helmet!
Clear off!
"The loneliness
of the long-distance runner"...
a phrase epitomized by this man,
Dennis Doyle.
For the last eleven miles,
he's been running...
on what appears to be
a severely sprained ankle.
What a testament to the power
of the human spirit.
Mr Doyle, how do you feel?
How the fuck
do you think I feel?
What an inspiration.
We'll keep you updated
as this story progresses.
- Get out of the bloody way!
- Sorry.
- Well, what a remarkable day...
- Libby. Libby, I'm sorry...
- we've had at
the marathon on the Thames...
- all right? I lost it. I--
- with an event
dominated as ever...
- I wasn't thinking.
- by the crowds
and the fun runners...
- I'm sorry.
- Honey, can we just--
- but particularly by
- Jake, buddy...
- one man.
would you mind just giving us...
a little peace with the TV,
please?
- Thank you.
- Go on, Dennis!
The whole of London...
Honey, can we
just talk about this, please?
- Chin up!
- Keep it up, mate!
Do you know, Mr Doyle, sir?
Oh.
I'm the assistant coach.
Oh. Oh, really.
What's your name?
- Uh, Mr Ghoshdashtidar.
- Gosh--
- Ghosh...
- Gah--
OK, just call me John.
It was me who discovered
his potential.
I can't breathe.
My head's gonna explode.
He's not gonna make it.
I-- I have to stop.
- I have to stop this.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you can't.
What are you doing?
You can't stop.
You're nearly there.
What? How much further?
It-- It's a little, tiny--
Nine miles.
OK. OK.
Oh, no.
What?
He's hit it.
OK, baby,
let's get you to bed.
Jakey.
-...by the crowds
and the fun runners.
- Dennis.
- For those of you
just joining us...
- Dennis?
it looks like Dennis Doyle, a
clothing store security guard...
running for the last ten
and three quarter hours...
on basically one leg...
is refusing to rest
until this race is run.
Unbelievable!
You've never finished anything
in your entire life, Dennis.
All you're gonna
wanna do is give up.
I'm not the quitter!
That's exactly
what you're gonna do, Dennis.
Go on, run away!
Run away!
That's what you always do!
Dennis!
Dennis?
Oh, I don't believe this.
Yeah, boy, yes!
He's still going!
Go on, you beautiful man!
Apologies there,
ladies and gentlemen, uh...
but it's, uh, really rather hard
not to get caught up...
in the drama of it all.
Now let's take one more look
at how Dennis broke that ankle.
And here it is.
It appears
that the runner there...
next to Mr Doyle
is involved in some way.
In fact, if we look at it again
here...yes!
He deliberately trips him!
Bastard!
Apologies again, uh...
That didn't--
That's not what happened.
That is--
That-- That didn't happen.
I can't believe this.
I don't believe it, either.
I don't understand that.
What is that?
Honey. Honey...
That angle makes it look, but--
He tripped me.
He tripped me! Yes, he did!
- Go, Dennis!
- It's him! Dennis!
Go, Dennis!
I can't believe this.
Come on, honey.
Please, like I'm gonna do that.
What are you--
Are you kidding me?
Honey.
All right, look,
I'm just-- I'm not--
I'm not myself, OK?
I haven't been myself
for a long time.
Work has not been...
It's, uh...
It's just this city, you know?
It's just--
It's really hard here for me.
You know,
everyone's so polite here...
and it's like the food and the--
and the--and the ca--
I just don't-- I don't
know what happened to me.
I don't know what--
It's just this place.
It's this place, you know?
And if we-- I just know it's
gonna be better once we move.
- Move?
- To Chicago.
What?
Too soon?
Oh!
- Come on, Jake.
- Libby, wh--
Where you goin'?
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Dennis?
You can't be serious.
The guy left you
at the altar pregnant.
Nobody's perfect.
Libby.
Libby! L--
What a shithead.
Jake.
Hey. I know you feel bad.
I know you're
in incredible pain...
but you are so close
to me going on holiday.
Come on.
Dennis! Dennis! Dennis!
As we draw tantalizingly
close to the finish line...
here at St. Paul's Cathedral...
it's safe to say,
it's been a very long day...
for myself and my cameraman.
It's been a very long day
for you watching at home...
but for Dennis Doyle...
it's been the single longest day
of his life.
Come on, Dennis!
Good work, Dennis!
Hey! Move along!
That's it. You're there.
You're sixty feet.
Fifty-- Fifty-eight feet.
Call it fifty-six
and a half feet...
and you're there. Come on.
That's my man! My man!
Come on, come on!
Dennis, come on.
Stay down, you shamble of a man.
Don't get up.
Dennis!
Dennis, come on, get up.
Dennis, you're
at the finish line. Get up.
Dennis, this looks bad.
People are talking.
Get up.
Hello, Dennis?
- Dennis!
- Dad!
Dennis!
Dad!
Go on! You've got it! Go on!
Come on, Dennis! Yeah!
Yeah!
Dad!
That was a really stupid thing
you did out there today.
Don't go to Chicago.
Dad, you won!
He's done it!
He's actually done it!
This morning...
Dennis Doyle was a humble
shop worker from North London!
Tonight, he goes home a hero!
Oh, yay.
And look at that!
- God damn it.
- This extraordinary man...
collapses into the arms of--
I think it's backwards here--
the woman he loves!
And, look! He's got a son!
I didn't know he had a son!
Did you know he had a son?
- Hello, Dennis.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Jake, your dad's here!
How's it goin'?
- Pretty good.
- Good.
- You?
- Yeah.
Yeah, not bad.
You still running?
Every day, hopefully
in the right direction.
Yeah. So...
Um, Libby,
I was thinkin', um...
- Hi, Dad.
- Hey, you.
Uh, it doesn't matter,
actually.
I'll, um...
I'll sp-- I'll ca--
I'll speak to you later.
- OK.
- Say goodbye to your mom.
Bye, Mom.
Bye. I'll see you later.
Bye.
Libby, I was wondering,
would you like to go...
and have some dinner
with me next week?
You don't have to.
It's not, uh...
Yeah.
Uh...huh?
I mean, wow.
It'd be nice.
Yeah. Well, it would be.
I'll, um...
I'll give you a call.
OK.
Don't know why I did that.
It's just--
OK. Ready?
Yeah.
Hello!
Hello, Dennis!
Mr G.
- Hello, Jake.
- Hello.
I was just doing my spin class.
It's great fun, isn't it?
Oh, it's an amazing workout!
Dad comin' up behind
the young contender.
Come on! Jake!
Oh, he takes the ball from Jake!
He has the ball! He's clear!
Dad! Pass it!
Dad is clear!
Give it!
I'll give you one, too.
OK, let's go. Good game.
Jake to Mr G.
Yeah, thank you very much.
Take over, Mr G.
There you go, Mr G.
All right, I'm gonna--
Completely illegal move there.
Picks up the player,
runs with him.
Runs with him all the way.
Dad, that's illegal!
But that's not all.
Because the guy,
he can't barely walk, OK...
Iet alone run,
but he keeps going...
and twenty-five miles
on a shattered ankle.
And you know how he did that?
You know what he said
was the one thing...
that kept him going?
His trainer
never gave up on him.
He stayed with him
the whole way.
And that was you?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
It's a pretty amazing story,
actually.
I've got a bottle of champagne
opened here...
if you wanna hear it.
- Sure.
Well, come on up then.
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Never saw you,
I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# I never saw you #
# I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Now I know that,
now I understand #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Now I know that,
now I understand #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Aye, aye, aye #
# Everybody #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Never saw you,
I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# I never saw you,
I only heard of you #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# It's your life #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Now I know that,
now I understand #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Now I know that,
now I understand #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# La la la #
# Huggin' up
the big monkey man #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Keep on hidin' #
# One fine day,
I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah,
I'm gonna be your man #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day,
I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah,
I'm gonna be your man #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone keeps talkin'
about me #
# It makes me feel so sad #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone is laughin' at me #
# It makes me feel so bad #
# So keep on runnin' #
# Keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day,
I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah,
I'm gonna be your man #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone keeps talkin'
about me #
# It makes me feel so sad #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Everyone is laughin' at me #
# It makes me feel so bad #
# So keep on runnin' #
# Runnin' from my arms #
# One fine day,
I'm gonna be the one #
# To make you understand #
# Oh, yeah,
I'm gonna be your man #
# I'm gonna be your man #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org