Mr. MacDonald, by the time that runaway
reaches this bridge, it'll be doing 90.
The restriction
for that bridge is 50.
Get that runaway
on the spur in Jordan and derail her.
- Best idea, sir.
- I don't need you to tell me I'm right!
Derail that son of a bitch!
I don't care about engines!
- I don't want to lose the bridge!
- Hey, this system is designed...
so that I can get everyone
out of our way and onto the siding.
Meanwhile,
we'll think of something else.
Right now it's just four engines,
no people aboard...
and if I let you jerk off
with your system...
this wild animal's
gonna kill somebody!
You know what that'll cost
the company?
Derail her.
That's my order.
You say derail,
then we derail.
But these people are witnesses.
It's your decision, Eddy.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's my decision.
Central calling Jordan.
Signal maintainer 40.
This is an emergency.
Signal maintainer 40, acknowledge.
This is an emergency!
Central calling Jordan.
Signal maintainer 40, come in.
Where the hell are you?
- Central calling Jordan.
- Jordan.
- Signal maintainer 40 here.
- Central here.
There's an unmanned runaway
heading west on track one.
You're gonna have to line her
into the siding...
use the manual switch,
then get out of the way.
Superintendent MacDonald
wants to derail her.
- Yeah.
- You got that name? Mr. Eddy MacDonald.
I'll be goddamned.
Son of a bitch!
Hey, hear that?
Come on, Manny!
See? I told you, Manny!
I knew we had an engineer
on this sucker!
- All right, kid.
- I said blow, baby, blow!
Boy, this is gonna be something.
Signal maintainer 40 here.
Eh, Jordan.
- Central.
- Listen, did I hear you right...
that that runaway
is supposed to be unmanned?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Well, let me tell you something.
I think you're wrong.
The whistle.
The goddamn whistle's blowing!
Derailing is out!
Run, old man. Line her through!
Somebody's blowing
the goddamn whistle on that train...
and you would have killed them
just like that!
My God!
Okay, next hurdle.
Come on, big train.
I'll slap your big fat diesel ass.
Come on!
Do you like anchovies?
I don't remember having any.
If you had them,
you'd remember.
I tell you what.
- Get over here.
- What?
- I don't think he saw us.
- Okay. What do we do now?
Let him come.
When he gets two-thirds through
that door, we'll nail him.
We ain't gonna
kill him, are we?
Unless we have to.
We'll find out what's going on.
That makes sense.
Oh, man.
He's in trouble out there.
Let's go help him.
Ah, man.
What are you doing here?
I work on this train.
I'll tell you what
we're doing here.
We're on our way to Las Vegas
to see our close friend Wayne Newton.
Why? Are you collecting tickets...
sweetheart?
Hey, sweetheart...
how would you like
a really good fuck, huh?
Just try it!
Freeze on that bullshit.
What happened to you?
I was tired.
I was taking a nap.
I shouldn't have done it,
but I did it. So what?
My head got hit when we
slammed into that caboose.
I don't know what happened,
but there's no engineer on this train.
There's nobody on
this train but us!
She's lying.
We heard the whistle.
- I blew the whistle!
- You're trying to get us busted.
Listen! This runaway's gonna
run into something very fast.
I climbed back here, the last engine,
where it's safer. Get it?
I don't believe her bullshit.
You don't believe me?
Just look out the window.
See how fast we're going?
This train is out of control.
We can get killed!
Then we better
do something about it!
What about the hostler helper?
A woman.
Goddamn it! Does she know anything
about running a locomotive?
Shit.
The only person on
the whole train is a woman.
How lucky can I get?
- Now what?
- It's chief of security from Stonehaven.
- His name Ranken. He wants to see you.
- I don't have time for him!
- He says it's important.
- Know anything about the runaway?
- I don't think so.
- Tell him we'll see him later.
- How far to the bridge?
- Twenty-five minutes.
Shit.
- Seneca Station.
- Go ahead.
This is MacDonald at Central Control.
There's a runaway coming your way.
- It's going over 80.
- That's too fast for the bridge.
I know it's too fast.
Have your emergency crew together.
- Christ, can't you stop it?
- We're going to stop it.
Have them there just in case.
Asshole.
It won't do a thing.
- I tried it from the second engine.
- Why not?
I'm no expert. All I know is
when engines are hooked together...
everything operates
from the lead engine.
Stop the lead engine,
they all stop.
I don't believe this shit!
We get out of a maximum-security prison
and wind up on an unmanned train...
with this bitch and bad news.
- You guys bust out of Stonehaven?
- Yeah, so what?
- Man! Why'd you tell her that?
- You told her, clown.
What difference does it make?
She going to drop a dime on us?
I guess you guys
picked the wrong train.
How come you didn't go up
to the lead engine?
You can't cross from the second
to the first engine.
It's a streamliner.
It doesn't have a walkway.
I tried a door in front, but it must
have jammed during the collision.
Oh, man.
- What do we do now?
- Think they know about us?
They do now,
after we hit that caboose.
If they woke up,
there'll be all kinds of pigs...
all over this thing whenever
and wherever it stops.
- Ranken's all over this territory.
- Maybe he'll find us.
I ain't giving up.
No matter who has to die.
- I ain't giving them that pleasure.
- I don't want to die.
I ain't getting caught alive.
And you neither.
I don't know.
I don't know nothing right now.
I can't even think straight.
Just do what I tell you
and don't crap on yourself.
I let you tag along to be
a regular, not a piece of shit.
What you're doing ain't nothing.
We don't stand a chance
if we jump out there.
I can't jump here.
This is suicide.
You'll break every bone
in your body and then what?
- They've been broke before.
- I'm with you.
I'm with you till
the wheels come off.
You can't go.
- You can't leave me alone here.
- I don't care who jumps with me.
I know how to stop the train!
Why didn't you tell us that
to start with, goddamn it?
We probably can't stop it 100,
but we can slow it down.
You tell me how.
If we can disconnect the electric
cables between the engines...
the engines will shut down
one at a time.
It's not going to be easy.
They'll all be frozen solid
and we don't have the right tools.
It's a better chance
than jumping now.
You better know what
you're talking about.
Look, don't threaten me.
What's the matter with you?
Come on. Let's go.
That one.
The one next to the tow brake?
Yeah. Here.
Pull me up!
- You do it. You have two hands.
- Okay, hold onto me.
Use the wrench.
Hey, I did it!
I got it!
Get me up!
Come here! Look at this!
- Look at what?
- The runaway. It slowed down!
- It's at 80 and holding.
- It was 92 a couple minutes ago.
- I don't understand it.
- The girl. Somehow she slowed it.
It doesn't matter... eight, 180...
the bridge won't take it.
- How far to the bridge now?
- Five minutes.
- Let's go.
- Right.
We can use
the fire extinguisher.
I lost it!
She's coming!
E.T.A.'s in about three minutes!
Get me up!
Get her, man. Get her!
Grab my hand.
Look, Manny, look!
Get me Central Control. Quick!
- It's crazy.
- What?
There are three people
on the runaway.
Holy shit.
Where they come from?
How do I know?
We just saved three lives.
- Not for long.
- Dave, give me a fucking break.
I wish I could, but we got
five minutes to get the runaway...
off the main line, or else it's going
head-on with the Northeast Express.
No big deal.
We'll just head her into the 14.
Great idea. Why don't you
just send her to Elkins?
- So?
- No, that's the chemical plant.
- She'll never make the curve.
- She'll wipe out the whole plant.
There'll be toxic chemicals
from here to Kansas.
Better warn them.
You know, girl,
I ought to thank you.
It's one thing to jump,
wrap yourself around a tree or a pole.
But to wind up
spilt all over a ditch...
with a broken hip,
waiting for the bulls...
What a waste.
Yeah, man. You ain't kidding.
Look, we're almost there.
Come on, Manny.
- Let's rip this fucker!
- Is that the door?
- It's jammed. I couldn't open it.
- Don't worry, sweetheart.
We been breaking through doors
all our lives.
Come on, let me in there.
Let me help.
- Let me in there.
- I got it!
You can't do it with
that hand of yours.
Shit.
- Take the first west at McKessburg.
- Get onto the Bell Port siding.
Get the emergency crew ready
and evacuate the plant immediately.
Get them as far away
from the plant as possible.
You got 10 minutes if you're lucky.
Get off my back, woman!
Mr. Barstow, I have two very dangerous
prisoners on the loose.
I don't give a shit if your
whole prison's on the loose.
I got a killer train on my hands
with three people on board...
and I got no free tracks
left to play with.
Do me a favor and get lost or I'm going
to have ass kicked out of here!
On the double!
You keep an eye on her.
I'm going to take a leak.
Do that.
Hope you don't like it
and want to do something about it.
I didn't think you wanted to
back up that loud conversation.
Wipe that piss off your face...
and I don't want to hear
any more crap out of you.
If I don't get my convicts back,
the prison will be out of control.
You know what a riot in a maximum
security prison looks like?
Your brains are too small
to imagine it.
- Now, where's the train?
- Track one.
I'm gonna kick your teeth in,
you're playing with me.
You tell me real straight,
got it?
You tell me how to find
that train with a helicopter.
I'll show you.
I'll be goddamned
if I come all this way...
to get stopped
by some goddamned door!
- Shit!
- Don't give up now.
- We're gonna make it through this.
- How?
I don't know.
But I know that people
are clearing the tracks.
And I know they won't abandon us.
- How do you know that?
- I just feel it in my heart.
There are miracles.
You're stupid. You know how stupid
you sound? Miracle, my ass!
One must count on oneself,
nobody else.
You think I'm waiting around
for a miracle to happen?
I'm going out and around.
I'm going there.
That's where I'm going!
You can't make it.
I told you...
there's nothing to hold on to.
There's no walkways.
I told you, you can't make it!
I'll make it. If I have to
fly the five feet like a birdie.
I'll fly it.
I'll make it.
Manny, you can't do it.
Not with that arm of yours.
But I can do it.
I can whip this fucker.
So, give me a drink.
Let me go for it.
- All right.
- Hey, sucker!
Lighten up.
- You are so brave.
- Yeah, I know it.
Goggles.
I'm going. Here I go.
Partners? Yeah.
Fucking A.
You can make it!
Fuck, you got guts, kid!
You got real guts.
More guts than brains.
- What did you say?
- No brains!
- That's mean!
- That's the truth.
Come on, Buck.
Let's go, sucker.
Make it now! Jump for it!
- He's got to come back.
- Go for it!
- I can't watch this.
- Then sit down!
Don't give up on me!
Come on! Come on!
Go get the...
Don't quit!
Get out there!
He can't do it!
Don't you care about him?
- Does his life mean anything to you?
- Get out of here!
Get back, punk!
You want to be a tough guy?
You want to be a legend? Go back!
Let him in!
- What are you doing, Manny?
- Get the fuck up!
Show me you ain't got
shit for blood.
Give me a break.
Get out there!
Don't you talk to me!
I don't know who you are.
You want to be a tough guy?
Get the fuck out of here!
- Stop it!
- You want to kill me?
If I'd wanted to punch your ticket,
you'd be long gone.
I'm telling you,
you can do it!
I can't do it, Manny.
You don't know what you
could do or what you can't.
You're a coward! Why'd I break out
with this chickenshit?
Leave him alone!
- Get the fuck up! You hear me?
- Stop it!
- Get the fuck out here!
- Okay!
No! He's using you!
Don't go!
You're gonna do what
I tell you, aren't you?
- That's right! You're gonna do it!
- Do it yourself if you're so brave!
- I would if I had two hands.
- Bullshit!
You think you can sacrifice
someone else's life?
You're an animal!
No, worse. Human.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go! Get the hell out of here!
I'm not letting you go!
Don't you touch her!
I'll kill you, Manny!
You die, sucker!
Don't make me kill you.
I'll beat you to fucking death!
Come on, try me!
Kill him!
I thought you was my friend.
I thought we was partners.
Shit. You know...
you're worse than Ranken,
when the truth comes out.
At least he's up front
with his bullshit.
You was a hero.
You was a hero...
to all of us
back in that shithole.
Goddamn.
It's your mess, Frank. You should've
listened to me and derailed her.
So what do we do?
We shunt them onto the siding...
and in 15 minutes
they run out of track.
- Elkins Station!
- Elkins, go ahead.
- Gilchrist, this is MacDonald.
- Yes, MacDonald.
- Barstow here.
- Come on!
Listen carefully and act fast.
You have about one minute to line
the runaway under the old spur...
- the one we don't use anymore.
- You got it.
- All right, go.
- Good, good!
Good boy! We'll save
the chemical plant, huh?
We're still going to lose
those three people.
I still don't understand.
How did this happen? Why couldn't
we stop it with all this junk?
I mean, with all this
high technology?
Some things can't be explained.
Look!
Holy shit!
See that Ranken?
Did you see that?
Come on, Ranken!
You'll never take me back!
Try it!
You'll never get me alive!
What's the matter?
You got no fucking guts?
Come on!
You hear me?
You'll never stop this train!
I told you I'd break free!
Here I am, right in your face.
Come on down!
I won! I won!
Here I am!
I'm alive, sucker!
You hear me?
You'll never get me!
You'll never stop this train.
Never!
You understand?
I won!
What was that?
What happened?
They gave up on us.
They switched us onto
a dead-end track.
- What does that mean?
- We're going to crash.
Hold me.
I don't want to die alone.
We going to be all right.
We going to be fine.
We all die alone.
Come on, Ranken!
Here I am!
I'm out of my cage now!
I'm never going back.
You'll never stop me!
Never! I'm out. You hear me?
You can't get across, Manny.
I'm out of my cage.
You'll never stop me.
You're gonna learn, kid.
It's all up here.
I'll cross the stinking thing.
Watch me.
Waiting for you.
Is Jonah alive?
That's good.
He'll be glad.
Don't do it, Manny.
You'll burn for it. You know you will.
Push the button.
We're on a dead-end siding.
We're gonna crash
in five minutes.
Then we'll have a nice
five-minute ride together.
You think you're a hero, huh?
You're scum.
We're both scum, brother.
You're going to push that button
and stop this train!
We've only got a few minutes!
We got all the time
in the world.
- You'll die, bastard!
- You'll die with me.
Fuck you. You're as afraid
to die as anybody else.
And I never let you free.
You hear me?
I am free, Ranken.
You think you won!
I know how to die too!
Win, lose,
what's the difference?
What about that punk
and the girl?
No, it's just you and me.
Manny! Shut it down.
Shut it down!
That's all you got to do!
He knows what he wants to do.
He did it.