Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Once upon a time,
on the north shore of Long Island,
not far from New York,
there was a very,
very large mansion, almost a castle,
where there lived a family
by the name of Larrabee.
There were servants
inside the mansion
and servants outside the mansion.
Boatmen to tend the boats
and six crews of gardeners -
two for the solarium,
the rest for the grounds
and a tree surgeon on retainer.
There were specialists
for the indoor tennis courts
and the outdoor tennis courts,
the outdoor swimming pool
and the indoor swimming pool.
And over the garage there lived
a chauffeur by the name of Fairchild,
imported from England years ago,
together with a Rolls Royce...
and a daughter named Sabrina.
Among other things, the Larrabees
were noted for the parties they gave.
Few people any more give parties
the way they did.
It never rained on the night
of a Larrabee party.
The Larrabees
wouldn't have stood for it.
There was Maude Larrabee, who
inherited the Larrabee Corporation
when her husband died
on the 13th hole at Pebble Beach.
Sweetheart, go talk
to Cardinal Morgan, he looks bored.
Senator, have I got somebody
I want you to meet...
Maude was on the cover of Fortune.
There was Linus, the older son,
who graduated from Yale at 19
and took his mother and the company
for a ride on the fibre-optic highway
and turned a $100 million family
business into some serious money.
I don't feel like
buying any more networks.
There's never anything good on.
I said the offer expired
at ten o'clock. It's 10:08.
Linus was on the cover of Time.
But most of all...
there was David, the younger son,
who was in and out of many schools
and even more relationships.
He was handsome and charming
and funny and romantic.
It's so rare to meet
such a beautiful woman
with your sense of humour
and irony...
and poetry... and hair colour.
David did a Gap ad.
Sabrina.
Sabrina, come down.
She made him laugh.
- You have to finish packing.
- Am I witty?
I wonder if Paris is far away enough.
No, really, do you think I'm funny?
Hilarious,
you should host a talk show.
The full-time observation
of David Larrabee
is not a recognised profession.
Get out of that tree.
I'll be there in a minute.
Oh! It's just you, Sabrina.
Hello, David.
I thought I heard somebody.
No, it's nobody.
Sabrina?
You've spent more of your life
up that tree than you have on ground.
You know how lucky we are
that Mrs Larrabee has friends
who have a job for you,
so you can have
this European experience?
The time in Paris
will be so good for you.
If your mother were alive,
she'd be so happy.
- It's what she always wanted.
- What if he forgets all about me?
How can he forget someone
he doesn't know exists?
I didn't mean that, Sabrina.
I just meant...
There's much more to you than
this obsession. I hope you know that.
Thanks, Dad.
Good night.
I need more help out front.
Where are you going? It's early.
I've got to check on the Tokyo market
before it closes. Good night.
Linus, Andrea Colson told me
you just fired her son.
- He's an idiot.
- But she was my bridesmaid.
- She's one of my best friends.
- This is business, Mother.
I've got to drop something off
in David's room.
When he surfaces,
tell him I put his suspenders back.
You're not leaving now!
You'll miss my fireworks.
It's OK, Mother. I had a pony ride
and I got my face painted.
Good night.
David, David.
Come in.
- I came to say goodbye.
- What?
Don't come out.
If I look at you,
I may not get through this.
- OK.
- Please, don't say anything.
I'm leaving tomorrow for Paris...
and I'll be away a long time.
I don't expect you to think about me,
you haven't thought about me
while I was here.
I just want to say...
I think I know you better
than anybody else.
I mean, whatever they think or say,
I know the truth,
that you're a wonderful person.
Kind and generous and...
And for what it's worth, know that
someone far away is thinking of you.
If there's anything I can ever do...
Could you bring me one of those
Eiffel Tower paperweights?
My God!
Welcome to Vogue, Sabrina.
You speak no French, yes?
No.
I mean, yes, I don't. Sorry, please
could you repeat the question?
Alors, la, c'est le shopping. Vous
avez les shoes very, very important.
Tout ca, c'est hanging,
toujours folding.
Ca, c'est le jewellery, pressing
but the most important is
le Boutin, Manolo and Ombline.
You know, I speak very good English.
You put and close the place,
goes to shoot.
And all the days, most important,
le Boutin,
Manolos, Ombline.
Le Boutin?
- Ingrid, hurry up!
- I'm putting in my contacts.
Another one, another one. No.
Another one. Another one.
The nice one.
The fan!
Don't worry for Martine.
I tortured her, now she tortures you.
Succeed and you'll get
someone of your own to torture.
You've only been there for two weeks.
I doubt everybody in Paris
thinks you're an idiot.
Only because I haven't met them all.
Sabrina, you're being much too hard
on yourself. Give it a chance.
What matters is you're away
from here experiencing new things,
getting another view of the world,
finding new friends
and not constantly thinking
about you-know-who.
- Morning.
- Morning, Tom.
She's fine.
She hasn't adjusted completely...
- She's miserable.
- I told you not to send her.
Mr Tom, maybe it is not for me
to put my hands in this
but when I first come to this
country, I am alone, like Sabrina.
I just weigh more.
So, I ask to God, "Why I am here?"
I say, "Why, God?"
But there is no answer.
So, I stop crying.
It takes 11 years.
- Thank you, Rosa.
- Did she mention David?
Just that life without him was
an abyss of misery and despair.
Those were her words.
With your leg.
Yes, the same. Yes! Cool.
Have a drink with me.
What I do with the two first rolls
of film, I don't use them.
There's absolutely nothing.
They pose too much. It's fake...
- Fairchild.
- Good morning, sir.
Hey, Linus. Got a minute?
Are you aware you're an officer
of the Larrabee Corporation?
- Linus, I met someone.
- You recall our address?
- I'm not kidding.
- Your office is on the 48th floor.
- This is really somebody.
- So what's the problem?
I've invited her for dinner Friday
and I don't want you and Mother...
This girl is smart,
she's really smart.
That certainly
hasn't come up before.
- She's a real woman, she's not a...
- Transvestite?
She's not a bimbo.
She's a doctor. A paediatrician.
How did you meet her?
I was at this party and the
host's kid got sick with something
and I rushed him to Emergency
and she was the resident on duty
and we just hit it right off.
How did the sick kid make out?
Listen, when you guys meet her,
just try to make me look good.
I know I look good
but try to make me sound good.
Mention my accomplishments.
My qualities.
You can be creative.
Lie, OK? She says her folks know you.
- What's her name?
- Elizabeth Tyson.
- Tyson Electronics Tyson?
- Tyson I don't know.
Here's a toughie.
Which one works for a living?
- Wow, great hat, Mother.
- Good morning, Blue Eyes.
Bring her around,
we'll try and make you look good.
- You guys work Sundays now, huh?
- It's Wednesday, David.
Guess what. David's taking out
Patrick Tyson's daughter.
- Well, well, well...
- Yes, sir?
Mack, give me Harvey.
Harvey? I want you to start
buying up chunks of Tyson stock.
Not so much that
anybody would notice. That's it.
I hope she doesn't look like Patrick.
For once your father didn't lie.
- You are lovely!
- Thank you.
- I'm Maude.
- Pleasure.
- Linus.
- My father's talked about you.
- Are you really a doctor?
- No, he made that up.
She was just promoted
to Assistant Head of Paediatrics.
I told her the hospital can
count on us for a couple of million.
David!
Is he a world-class philanthropist
or what?
Just squeeze.
I like Louis. He's funny and sweet
and such a good photographer.
But someone is in the way.
Is it this David
you mentioned casually
40 or 50 times
when you first came?
He sounds perhaps like an illusion.
- It keeps me company.
- You think so?
Illusions are dangerous people.
They have no flaws.
I came here from Provence...
alone, uneducated.
For eight months -
no, more than that - a year,
I sat in a cafe, I drank coffee
and I wrote nonsense in a journal.
And then, somehow...
it was not nonsense.
I went for long walks
and I met myself in Paris.
You seem embarrassed
by loneliness, by being alone.
It's only a place to start.
Doctor Forest, dial 118, please.
Doctor Forest, please dial 118.
- I'm sorry about your party.
- It's OK.
- Are you hungry? I'm starving.
- Tell you what I'll do.
I'll draw you a hot bath
and whip us up a superb omelette.
Do you have eggs, cheese,
green pepper, tomato...
No green pepper, no tomato.
Well, then I'll just whip us up
a somewhat superb omelette.
David, you are the best.
You mean making a hot bath
and an omelette
are on par
with saving a 5-year-old kid's life?
Lt'll save my life.
God, you're easy on me.
OK, then why don't you marry me?
- OK, why don't I?
- Don't kid about stuff like that.
- You're sure you know what it is?
You hang together a lot,
sleep in the same room,
do each other's
hard-to-reach buttons...
- Then I accept.
- Really?
Why?
- Mr Larrabee?
- David, what a nice surprise.
He's at lunch. He doesn't like...
- Ron, Ron. I need to talk to you.
- I'm in a meeting.
- When was the last time I came here?
- You're right.
Ron, Ron.
I wondered why I was suddenly
being treated with respect.
Is something bothering you, David?
You've been pushing me
into this relationship
so you could merge with Tyson.
Pushing you? I could burn in hell
for the lies I told about you.
You begged me to make you look good.
You never mentioned
making an offer...
"Talk about my accomplishments,
my qualities. Be creative.
"Lie," you said.
I can't do this, Linus. I'm not ready
to make this kind of commitment.
Oh, she must have asked
for an actual wedding date.
I don't know what happened. She was
healing children, I was in a tuxedo.
I'm not able to take care of a wife.
Elizabeth is a doctor and
a millionaire. She won't be a burden.
You don't deserve her
but she appears to love you.
Doesn't that worry you a little bit?
I mean, about her mental health?
David...
- So this is all just a coincidence?
- It's an opportunity.
- Opportunity.
- What do you expect me to do?
Disqualify myself
from a billion-dollar merger
because of family connections?
What are you doing?
It was just a question!
Look at this thing. Not a scratch.
Is this a new way
of changing the subject?
No one has a flat-panel screen
this size except Tyson
and the thing's indestructible.
He has the hottest technology in town
and everyone on Wall Street knows it.
We've got so much competition
on this merger...
- You're talking about my life!
- I pay for your life.
My life makes your life possible.
- I resent that.
- So do I.
You went to law school,
you never took the bar.
You went to business school
but don't come near the office.
Studied languages you don't speak,
instruments you don't play.
You have girlfriends
you never see more than twice.
- Do you not see a pattern?
- Who are you to lecture me?
Your idea of a long-term relationship
is letting your date order dessert.
I don't have time for dessert.
I'm too busy with this company.
You're a grown man, David.
Finish something.
Elizabeth is the best thing
that ever happened to you
and you told me so yourself.
I would like to propose a toast
to my baby girl.
Dr Elizabeth Tyson, talented MD,
and to my future son-in-law,
David Larrabee, lucky SOB.
Just kidding, David. Just kidding.
No, we're all very lucky.
Not only is this the joining
of two gorgeous people
- but two gorgeous companies.
- Here, here.
I want to wish you all the luck
and happiness you deserve and...
"May your first child
be a masculine child."
It's from Serpico. Nacimiento,
tell Yoshi to bring the Portobello.
- You're quite a linguist.
- Yes.
I travelled a lot before I married
Patrick. I was a stewardess.
Now they call them flight attendants.
Really? I bet I could still get your
seat back in the upright position.
Whenever they try to be funny,
it comes out perverse or terrifying.
- I see.
- You'll get used to it.
...be sure to tell you that she misses
you and sends all of you her love.
But what does she say
about the engagement?
You didn't tell her?
I don't know how or what to say.
You say, "Darling Sabrina,
la vida es sueno.
"Your life is a dream and now it is
over." I know because we Spaniards...
My dearest Sabrina.
Although I am sure
this will come as a shock,
it is my belief that
what I am about to tell you
is all for the best.
I know how strongly
you have always felt about this
and so I have been
reluctant to write...
I am in Paris
but you are somewhere else.
I'm sorry, Louis.
I shouldn't have done this.
I would like to help...
but what you have to fix,
you won't fix it in bed.
You have to fix it here.
Dear Dad,
This is my last letter from Paris.
I may even be home
before you get it.
Don't worry about picking me up,
I'd like to surprise you.
Amazing. It's gone by so quickly.
Gertrude Stein said, "America is my
country and Paris is my home town."
I'll always feel that way
about Paris.
I want so much for you to know
what it's meant to me.
It's turned cold out
but I don't feel cold.
Across the street someone
is playing La Vie En Rose.
They do it for the tourists but I'm
always surprised at how it moves me.
It means seeing life through
rose-coloured glasses.
Only in Paris, where the light
is pink, could that song make sense
but I'll have it in my pocket
when I get home
and I'll take it with me
wherever I go from now on.
Love to you, Dad.
What are you doing?
Drove out with Maude.
I have to be here for her birthday
party. Might as well stay.
- What did you get her?
- Portable fax machine.
- You sentimental fool.
- It's easy for you.
She's so glad you set a date, you'll
never have to buy another present.
That's not what she says.
I got her a little Picasso.
I'm having it wrapped in town.
- What did that cost me?
- I don't know.
So, who's the new bidder on Tyson?
Unisat?
And a couple of other companies.
- Cash or stock options?
- I love it when you talk dirty.
Come back here! Excuse me.
- What's that?
- A dog.
- Why?
- It's Elizabeth's gift to Mother.
She feels guilty about missing the
party. She's stuck at some seminar.
I've got to pick up Maude's present.
I want you to know something, Linus.
- I'm glad about Elizabeth.
- You should be. She's terrific.
She's smart, independent,
pretty as hell.
- Why don't you marry her?
- Go on!
I'm kidding.
Hi.
How are you?
I'm great.
- How are you?
- Good.
I'm just surprised to see you here.
Well, you know me, don't you?
- Can I give you a lift?
- Are you on your way home?
- Yes.
- Well, that's convenient!
Sure you wouldn't mind?
You know, I can't remember
the name of your street.
- Desoris Lane.
- What? That's where I live.
- Small world.
- Big lane.
You don't recognise me, do you?
Yeah, of course I do.
You're my neighbour on Desoris Lane.
- And you're David.
- I sure am.
- One of the lesser Larrabees.
- In what way lesser?
Pretty much every way.
But please, no pity.
I could have sworn I knew
every pretty girl on the north shore.
I could have sworn you took in
more territory than that.
Ouch!
That was a while ago. I heard
that you're engaged to be married.
Yeah, I am. But we're both
very busy, busy people
and it's been very difficult
to set a date.
- Give me a clue, just one.
- No, this is too much fun.
- Please.
- There's your driveway.
I was just going to say that. Would
you like to come in for a drink?
What a good idea.
- Looks like you're having a party.
- Tomorrow night.
They used to have
lovely parties here.
- Then you've been to them?
- No...
but I saw the lights from a distance.
What's the occasion? It's too late
for an engagement party.
As a matter of fact, my fiancee
is in California this week.
It's a birthday party for my mother
but you probably know that.
Listen, the party is at nine o'clock.
Will you come?
Do you really want me to?
Very much...
if you'll tell me who you are.
Hello, Sabrina.
Hello, Linus.
Sabrina?
- Have a good time in Paris?
- Yes, thank you.
You look all grown up.
- Why does he keep saying that?
- I need to go find my father.
I'll get my bags later.
- Wait a minute...
- Thanks for the ride.
No.
- What are you talking about?
- No!
- I brought you a real Paris scarf.
- Has he seen you?
- Yes! No, who?
- Your father.
Oh, Sabrina!
For going out.
For staying in. For laughs.
Better than Christmas.
- Who took these?
- I did.
I hope this hangs out
before tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Mrs Larrabee's
birthday party.
Yes, I've been invited.
- By whom?
- By David.
Of course, he didn't know it was me
when he invited me.
- Now that he knows?
- I'm still invited, I guess.
Maybe I'll try steaming it.
Dad, please.
I promised myself years ago,
all those years, hundreds of times,
thousands of times,
and now I'm invited.
Excuse me.
- Hello.
- You're here.
Yes, I am. That's true.
You look beautiful.
So do you... look good.
Fabulous party, Maude.
I'm so sorry Elizabeth can't be here.
So am I. She gave me a dog.
I can't believe I'm here.
I went to a party once
in a villa in Provence.
I didn't know a single person,
Rothschild was there,
everyone was speaking in French,
I could hardly understand a word
but I felt more comfortable
than I do now.
Drink this as quickly as possible
and it won't seem so strange to you.
Better?
- Not yet.
- Trust me, it will be.
- Which Rothschild?
- Bubba.
Was that funny?
- Did Elizabeth pick out her dress?
- We're still doing the guest list.
- 600 so far, just on our side.
- It's not a wedding, it's a town.
Stop. It will be wonderful. Elegant
but simple. Lavish but tasteful.
Cheap but expensive.
Sabrina! Where have you been?
- Rosa!
- $23 a pound.
They'll be gone in five minutes.
Eat fast.
You are a princess.
For you.
- Who's that?
- Who?
That girl. The one with David.
Well, that's... that's just...
Oh, my God, that's Sabrina!
David's known her
since she was two years old.
She didn't have that dress
when she was two years old.
She's drinking champagne
and eating seafood
and her hair is washed and her lips
are red and her teeth are white.
- He made a song for her.
- I don't like it.
Well, Sabrina.
- When did you get back?
- Yesterday.
- Happy birthday, Mrs Larrabee.
- I didn't recognise you.
- It's the haircut.
- To say the least.
- Some surprise, isn't she, Mother?
- She certainly is, Son.
- Dance with me.
- Now?
While the music's playing.
It's harder when they stop. Come on.
- David?
- Yes?
You know, I've been to every party
you've ever had.
Right there, watching from that tree.
Like a bat.
And now, here we are,
dancing in front of God and everyone.
I should have paid
more attention to you.
- What was I thinking of?
- Yourself.
- It feels so good to hold you.
- Does it?
Do you know how beautiful you are?
No.
You're dazzling.
Dazzling?
Suddenly back in my life
and dazzling.
Am I back in your life?
I don't think you realise
what you've done to me.
- Then you'd better tell me.
- You're changing everything.
She's like a sister to him, Patrick.
I have a sister.
That's not how we dance.
It's Sabrina! Go look and see.
I can't believe this is happening.
You're absolutely transformed.
And you're exactly the same.
You were perfect, you still are.
- Sabrina?
- Yes?
Let's go someplace we can talk.
We are talking.
Someplace else. Please.
I haven't seen you in years.
I'm not sure I ever saw you.
Come with me... for a little while.
- We could just go...
- To the solarium?
- What?
- It has to be the solarium.
And you bring a bottle of champagne
and you put the glasses
in the back pockets of your jacket.
I don't think there are any
back pockets to my jacket.
You were paying attention.
And the orchestra will play
How Can I Remember?
Yes, I'll have them do that.
And then afterwards, I'll wake up.
Great. Thank you very much,
I appreciate it. See you later.
- You got a minute?
- No, I have an appointment...
Sure you do.
David, what are you doing?
Are you insane?
Right in front of your prominent
and paranoid future in-laws,
you are hustling
the chauffeur's daughter.
- We were dancing.
- Stop dancing!
You mean to say I can't have a drink
and a dance with an old friend?
Do I look stupid? I never thought
of myself as stupid but maybe I am.
- I didn't do anything.
- You were planning to.
- How do you know?
- You're kidding?
- David, you're like my own son.
- I am your own son.
Exactly. I endured 21 hours of hard
labour to bring you into the world.
The doctors begged me to take drugs
but I wouldn't hurt my child.
Well, I've changed my mind!
You screw up with Elizabeth
and I swear I'll kill you.
I don't know.
There's something about Sabrina.
I know this sounds crazy but I think
I'm falling in love with her.
- Oh, God!
- Listen, I didn't plan this.
I can't help it.
She's so... something. Sensational.
The last time you found someone
sensational, it cost us $1.5 million.
- This time it's different.
- How original.
What about Elizabeth?
You find the right girl...
Who's got the right parents,
who own the right company...
- You asked her to marry you.
- Actually, she asked me.
Mother, go and blow out your candles.
Can't we send somebody?
What do you think Sabrina wants?
She's lived her whole life
above that garage
with her nose against the glass or
in that tree watching us at parties.
Now, you invite her to one. You're
in your Rolex jacket or whatever.
She'll meet you in the solarium.
She knows you'll bring champagne.
- That has nothing to do with it.
- She knows what's coming.
The jet to Martha's Vineyard,
the cottage full of food,
house seats to some sold-out show,
drinks at the Carlyle.
After that, she'd fall for Noriega!
You don't know how she makes me feel.
I can't be engaged to somebody
when I feel like this.
- Sit down.
- I can't talk now...
Just sit down.
- What?
- I sat on the glasses.
- Don't move. Go get Dr Calloway.
- Who put glasses on the chair?
I'm bleeding. Can we talk later?
My God! Linus, stay with him.
Darling, don't worry.
Just elevate something.
Bad?
- Sabrina. She's waiting for me.
- I'll take care of her.
- Linus.
- Hello, Sabrina.
I have a message from David.
He won't be able to make it.
He sent me.
I'm sorry. You're upset, of course.
Yes. No.
I don't know.
I'm a little tired.
- Why didn't he come?
- He had a slight accident.
- He sat on a champagne flute.
- Is he OK?
- He's in the Emergency Room.
- Emergency Room?
It was a sharp flute.
That's a little joke.
Should I drive over to see him?
He'll be fine.
A couple of stitches.
You can see him tomorrow.
- What's this for?
- Part of the message from David.
They've sent you to deal with me,
haven't they?
- They?
- Like a lawyer in a movie.
He goes to the unsuitable waitress
or showgirl
or chauffeur's daughter
and says the family
is prepared to offer you $100,000
to stay away from their son.
"No," she says, "150,000."
- "No!"
- 200,000.
- No.
- A million.
No self-respecting lawyer
would offer less.
No self-respecting waitress...
- would take it.
- Good girl.
- I've loved him all my life.
- Have you?
I thought I was over it.
- Surprise, surprise.
- You don't object?
Object? To you? Look at you.
It's as though a lovely breeze
has swept through this house.
Even though the breeze
comes from the garage?
- It's the '90s, Sabrina.
- So they say.
They played that
the night before I left for Paris.
They often do play that.
He was dancing, right here,
with someone.
Yeah, he often does do that.
And tonight you wanted it to be you.
It's all in the family.
- I never thought of you as a dancer.
- Crazy about it.
They call me Bojangles at the office.
In all those years,
I never saw you do this -
meet a girl here with champagne.
- I never did it before.
- You never had to before.
Is it impossible to believe
that I want to dance with
the prettiest girl at the party?
Thank you.
Yes, it is impossible to believe.
Then you don't know me.
Oh, I almost forgot.
The rest of the message from David.
Thanks. I needed that.
- What am I doing? I...
- No, I apologise.
No, I should never...
You have my handprint on your face.
Maybe it's better if you pick up
your messages in person.
You'll see David tomorrow.
Good night.
Mack,
I'm staying out here for two days.
Cancel whatever I've got
and reschedule.
Have the plane stand by
from 9am tomorrow morning
and set up the Vineyard cottage.
I don't know.
Flowers, candles, singers...
Wonderful party.
Call David's secretary,
it's all she ever does.
Why not?
Well, hell, I'm up, you're up.
You weren't? Well, call her anyway.
Thank you for coming.
Good to see you. Good night.
Jesus. Dog...
Frank, I... What is it, an epidemic
of sleeping sickness? OK, listen.
David can't stand pain, so give him
a combination of morphine...
I don't... OK, not morphine
but something strong
and mixed with a sleeping tablet,
like Halcion.
They haven't proved that, Frank.
We have no idea. Maude thinks they
were left on the chair by some guest.
He is not going to sue
his own mother.
Well, he's not me!
- You're not going to work that way?
- Could you give us a moment?
Sure, Mr Larrabee.
Did Tyson say anything after I left?
He wondered where everybody had gone.
- Maybe I should talk to Sabrina.
- And say what?
"Sabrina, you're very lovely
"but David has a short attention
span. He's just jerking your chain."
Can I say that to a woman,
"jerking your chain"?
- When is Elizabeth back?
- Thursday. Should she come sooner?
I don't want him
breaking off the engagement.
This whole thing happened in 24
hours. I can make it unhappen in 48.
I like Sabrina, I always have,
but I won't kiss off
a billion dollars.
I don't care
what she did to her hair.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- I'll take you up to see David.
- Thank you.
David?
Can he hear me?
Sabrina!
Hi.
Did the dry cleaners have your car?
- How do you feel?
- I didn't get there.
Did I?
- Are you in a lot of pain?
- Am I in a lot of pain?
Look at your little hand.
- Guess what happened to me.
- I know, I know. I feel awful.
Me too.
How do you feel, Linus?
Falling a little behind here, David.
Do you want me to stay with you?
Listen, we got you a terrific nurse
and a two-day supply of red Jell-O.
He really should rest.
- Isn't Mr Linus going in?
- He has other work today.
Very good, Madam.
I'm sure he'll be
more responsive next time.
Don't worry. See you.
Thank you.
You know, I was wondering.
We have this summer cottage on
the Vineyard we never use any more.
I want to put it on the market. I was
going to have a few pictures taken.
The kind that make it
look bigger than it is.
I understand you have an interest
in photography.
I thought you could take them.
The trip would be no trouble.
Helicopter could pick us up here,
plane's at Republic.
Is that a lot to ask?
- Saves time fighting traffic.
- And all those toll booths.
- No, thanks.
- Something to drink, Miss Fairchild?
- Sabrina.
- What a beautiful name!
- Carol...
- Sorry. Can I get you something?
- Pellegrino.
- Same.
Mack, anything from Granger?
Anybody else at SEC?
Tell them I'll call them back
as soon as I can.
So, that really is a beautiful name.
How did you get it?
My father's reading. It's in a poem.
"Sabrina fair
Listen where thou art sitting
"Under the glassy, cool,
translucent wave
"In twisted braids of lilies knitting
"The loose train
of thy amber-dropping hair"
- That's so...
- Carol.
I'm sorry.
It's an incredible airplane.
It's beautiful.
I've never seen anything like it.
Well, yes...
- Don't you ever look out the window?
- When I have time.
What happened to the time
we saved taking the helicopter?
- I'm storing it up.
- No, you're not.
So, your little poem,
what does it mean?
It's about a water sprite
who saved a virgin
from a fate worse than death.
- And Sabrina's the virgin?
- Sabrina's the saviour.
- Is it always like this?
- I haven't been here in years.
How can you have a place like this
and never come here?
Gee, I don't know. I guess I...
I just never had anybody
to share it with.
I guess.
You could always hire somebody.
No, wait, not me. The house, please.
You're in the house, it humanises it.
I don't like having my picture taken.
I come out... looking depressed.
Are you depressed?
Maybe that's not exactly
the right word.
- What is the right word?
- I don't know.
Lonely, maybe.
- You think that's funny?
- No, I just expected something else.
No, I suppose you're right.
It is funny.
Linus Larrabee is lonely.
I'm sorry, I made you uncomfortable.
Let's get the outside.
- Do you want a view from the house?
- Sure.
- Which one?
- All of them.
More isn't always better,
sometimes it's just more.
- Pick one.
- I don't know anything about...
Just look.
Don't take a picture, just look.
Ocean, ocean, ocean, ocean,
quaint little fishing village,
ocean.
Lighthouse,
guy going into the lighthouse.
There's a job for you.
What must that be like?
What kind of a guy
takes a job keeping a lighthouse?
Every time I look through a camera
I'm surprised.
It's like finding yourself in the
middle of a story, like you just did.
What kind of a guy takes a job
keeping a lighthouse?
I think I've been taking pictures
all my life,
long before I ever had a camera.
Excuse me.
Call him back, Mother. Raise
the offer half a point. No more.
Here? Lousy.
So far I'm more affected than she is.
I damn near cried twice.
I'm running out of time.
I don't know what to try.
OK. Finished.
We'll have some lunch
and then you ought to get a look
at the island while you're here.
- You miss Paris?
- Not yet but I will.
- You liked it there?
- I loved it. You'd probably hate it.
- What? Why?
- It's all about pleasure.
They work hard, they just know
when to quit and enjoy themselves.
What a beautiful building!
Nobody builds with brick any more.
That's late 1800s.
In Paris they'd call that brand-new.
I hope they don't tear it down.
They won't.
I own it, that whole block.
I donated it to the village
as a halfway house.
You know, jails are full of guys
that never had a break.
Look at this guy picking cans.
They get backed to the wall,
commit some petty crime.
They're stuck, outsiders
for the rest of their lives.
It's not fair. The only chance
they'll ever have is a halfway house
that'll help them
get their feet under them.
Excuse me.
Could you take a picture of us?
Yeah.
It's that one.
Are you done?
I don't think I can eat any more.
It's too late
to give them their freedom.
You are not exactly
what people say you are.
Oh, yeah? What do they say I am?
You know...
No.
Well... that you're the world's only
living heart donor.
- Oh, that.
- And how does this one go?
"He thinks that morals
are paintings on walls
"and scruples are money in Russia."
- That's droll.
- Then there's my favourite...
No, no, I get the picture.
That's enough.
Do you remember the rainy afternoon
we spent together?
My father had...
had driven your mother and David
into town for a music lesson.
- How old was he?
- I don't know. 14, 15.
- That would be the oboe.
- The oboe?
It was a misunderstanding. He thought
he was going to take hobo lessons.
- It was a rainy afternoon, huh?
- Stormy.
I was afraid and I came into your
house and tried to turn on a lamp
but I got a shock and I thought
I had been struck by lightning.
And you stayed with me all afternoon,
until my father came home.
You didn't cry.
You were a brave kid.
No. I was more afraid of you than
being electrocuted. Everybody was.
Is that why you never married? You
probably don't believe in marriage.
Yes, I do.
That's why I never got married.
David, on the other hand,
believes in the tooth fairy.
- That's why I like him.
- I like him too.
I love him. I just don't know
what to do with him.
When he was a kid,
he loved coming into the office.
He'd sit behind my father's desk and
write memos and read the ticker tape.
One day he just stopped
and I can't figure out...
Are those the only things
people say about me?
It was a nice day.
You were a little
tough on me, I thought.
I guess you're used to
being treated very carefully.
- When will you have the pictures?
- Tomorrow.
- Could you drop them by the office?
- Sure.
Good night then, Sabrina fair.
Linus...
Yeah.
My father once asked David
why he stopped coming to the office
and David said, "What do they
need me for? Linus is there."
I do real work in the real word.
David watches from the north shore.
I know you work in the real world
and you're awfully good at it.
I'll bet you haven't made
a wrong move since you were three.
But that's work.
Where do you live, Linus?
It was a nice day. Thanks.
It's open.
- Hi.
- Where were you? In town?
On Martha's Vineyard.
Linus wanted me
to take some pictures.
Linus did?
I love so many things about you, Dad.
But you know what I love best of all?
That you became a chauffeur because
you wanted to have time to read.
All my life I've pictured you...
sitting in the front seat
of a long succession of cars
waiting for the Larrabees
and reading.
We had baked clams.
Linus baked them.
- I used to be so afraid of him.
- It was appropriate.
- What was he like as a child?
- Shorter.
I look out the window and I see
someone and it is a young woman.
So, I say, "What is a young woman
doing in the courtyard
"at this time of night?"
I am looking and looking
and I see Sabrina and she's talking!
Who is she talking to? A man. Not
her dad because he's not as tall...
- Linus. Sabrina went out with Linus.
- It was Mr Linus.
Sabrina went out with Linus?
That's weird.
- I thought he was gay.
- Mr Linus is not a gay.
- It's not "a gay". Just "gay".
- Linus Larrabee is gay?
- That makes me like him better.
- Linus Larrabee is a heterosexual.
- He's still sleeping.
- Is that normal?
When you're taking what he's taking
it is. He wakes up from time to time.
- Has he asked for anyone?
- Bert and Ernie.
Could you tell him Sabrina was here?
I could tell him the Pope was here
but I don't think it'd make a dent.
I'm going into the city but I'll be
back by seven. Could you tell him?
Quarterly reports
will be on-line at four.
International wants a teleconference
at 5:15. Harvey...
You know that old brick building
we own at the Vineyard?
Have you ever heard me be called
the world's only living heart donor?
Find out if there's any tax advantage
to donating that building
to the town.
- If there isn't?
- Then forget it.
Oh, and I want two tickets tonight
for whatever Broadway show
nobody can get tickets for.
And a table
at the Carlyle for drinks.
- For whom?
- Me.
- I know, I seldom go to the theatre.
- Seldom?
- OK, I'm not a theatre buff.
- Buff?
The most difficult tickets
will be for a Broadway musical.
OK.
That means the actors periodically
will dance about and burst into song.
Mack, forget about the tax advantage,
I want that building
donated to the town...
and I want it used
as a halfway house.
Sabrina Fairchild.
Come in.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Sit down.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- Thanks.
It's... big.
This is where I do that real work
in the real world instead of living.
- You remembered.
- It doesn't come up every day.
- Would you like some coffee?
- No, thanks.
- Some of these are very good.
- Don't sound so surprised.
I'm not.
This is an unusual view of the house.
Well...
You said you wanted it
to look bigger. Sorry.
No, you have...
You've got to admit it's beautiful.
I probably would, if you'd let me.
I found myself in Paris.
A friend said that.
- You were missing?
- Yes.
"I once was lost
and now I'm found..."
- You're making fun.
- It's my turn.
- You're very photogenic.
- It's because I'm handsome.
- No, that's not it.
- But not as handsome as David.
Nobody is as handsome as David.
Even David.
Don't tell him that
until he's fully recovered.
Are you sure
I can't get you anything?
Cafe au lait? Snails? French fries?
- Theatre tickets?
I thought I'd take my first step
towards all that French stuff.
The good life, knowing when to quit.
Maybe it's a bad idea.
No, it's a good idea.
It was my favourite food in France.
There was a little place in Pigalle,
I ate there at least twice a week.
Enjoy.
It's really so much better if you eat
with your hands. Do you mind?
No.
Not since I made that
contribution to the NYU burn unit.
It's good. Very good.
It's interesting.
I have to try it with soup sometime.
No one ever stops me...
I used to walk everywhere in Paris.
I used to walk from Montmartre
into the centre of the town.
Along the Seine,
there's a four-mile walk
from lle St Germain
to Pont d'Austerlitz.
It takes you past
all the bridges of Paris.
23 of them.
You find one you love and...
you go there every day
with your coffee and journal
and you listen to the river.
- What does it tell you?
- That's between you and the river.
It's funny,
listening to you talk makes me...
Makes me wonder if I shouldn't...
- What?
- I don't know.
Something's different.
I feel different.
At work, I don't...
I love the action
but sometimes I wonder.
Lately, especially,
I've been wondering...
what it would be like...
to spend some time in a place
that I love like that.
Not just a few days
but for a real change.
Actually, I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
- I just didn't know it until you...
- What exactly are you saying?
I'm not sure.
I do what my dad did. He...
He did what his dad did.
My whole life I've been...
I never chose.
The path gets deeper,
more familiar but...
You're not really
thinking about Paris?
No.
No, you're probably right.
How could I be?
Am I a lost cause, then?
I don't like to think of anyone
as a lost cause.
- What time is it?
- 9:45.
I told the nurse to tell David
I'd look in on him.
He's probably sleeping.
- We can go.
- No. You're right, I...
No, come on, let's walk a little.
Was there anything
you didn't like about Paris?
How expensive everything is.
I'd have to learn how to say,
"I'm just looking."
How do you say,
"This is what I want"?
"I'm looking at what I want"?
I don't remember.
I brought you some tea
and I brought you some flowers
to brighten up your room.
Have you been watching
Remains Of The Day again?
She can handle herself with him.
She's not a little girl any more.
It's just that she seems,
I don't know, displaced right now.
She doesn't belong in a mansion
or above the garage.
Most people live in-between.
Have your tea and try to sleep.
- Hi.
- David. How are you feeling?
Great. Just felt like getting
out of bed for a while.
- Mack says you went to the theatre?
- Just dinner.
Moroccan, on the floor.
Lots of cinnamon.
- What's the word from Calloway?
- I'm healing fast.
I just can't eat on the floor yet.
- It was good. Thanks.
- Are you heading back to the city?
No, it's getting late.
I think I'll sleep out here.
- Good night.
- Good night, Linus. Thanks.
So... you.
I've been thinking about you.
Have you? What were you thinking?
We never had that drink
in the solarium.
No, we never did. You sent Linus.
Should you be walking around?
- What's going to happen?
- I could scare us up some champagne.
A couple of dixie cups.
I'm through with glasses.
We could hobble down to the solarium
and pick right up...
- No, I meant after that.
- After?
Well, shucks. Whatever, I don't know.
- Don't you?
- Well, not exactly.
Is that so bad?
No.
We can talk about that later,
can't we?
Yes... but tomorrow.
I really think you should rest now.
OK.
Good night, David.
- Good morning. How was the theatre?
- Come in, Mack.
That bad, huh?
I want you to get me
two tickets to Paris,
one for me and one for
Sabrina Fairchild. That's it.
- What day are we flying?
- Tomorrow.
I almost forgot.
The Tysons are here waiting.
- Did we have an appointment?
- Not in my book. They showed up.
Is my mother in yet?
My nephew is the same.
I gave him a huge office but he's
never there. We use it for lunches.
These are the invitations.
We thought we'd use recycled paper.
- Why does it always look dirty?
- Oh, Maude.
Which do you like,
the taupe or the buff?
- What's the problem, Patrick?
- No problem from our point of view.
I feel like a... What's that word,
when a lot of guys are after you?
Whore.
I was thinking more a debutante.
Somebody else wants to be in bed
with Tyson Electronics.
You know Intermedia?
Lmpressive proposal.
Cash, stock... and they don't want
to tell me how to run the business.
- How flattering for you.
- How did you leave it with them?
I told him we're practically family,
you and I.
I couldn't possibly entertain
their offer at this time.
Good.
But Elizabeth came home last night.
She called David...
and we got the impression...
You. You got the impression.
I got the impression that
he wasn't very anxious to see her.
He's not himself, Patrick.
He's been injured.
He's on very heavy medication.
He wants to be perfect
before he sees her.
That's what I thought.
- Hello?
- Good morning.
Linus.
Would you mind another trip
into the city?
I'd like to discuss
some business...
- Business?
- Yeah.
I was wondering if we could
meet this afternoon?
I don't know,
there's something I ought to do.
It would mean a great deal to me.
That little leprechaun
was making a veiled threat.
There was no veil.
- Should we do something?
- It's under control.
I'm going to Paris tomorrow.
- What?
- It's a long story.
- I like long stories.
- You won't like this one.
Try me.
Things have been progressing
with Sabrina. We've bonded.
We've been confiding in each other.
Last night,
over a handful of chicken,
I told her I thought my life
was in need of radical changes.
I told her I was
thinking about getting away.
Moving to Paris.
She thought that was a great idea.
- And she believed you?
- I think she'll want to go with me.
How do you know?
The same way I knew fibre optics
would replace coaxial cable,
that Intel's chip
would change the industry,
that Cindy Crawford's House Of Style
would be a big hit.
I just know.
So here's the way it'll play out.
Sabrina will go to Paris with me.
A wiser David
will return to Elizabeth.
I'll come back from Paris to sign
the papers. The merger will close.
We'll make a very large sum of money
and you can buy a house in Tuscany.
I have a house in Tuscany.
- What happens to Sabrina?
- She grows up.
You're going to ditch her?
My goodness.
How did you think
this was going to happen?
Did you think there was
some nice way to do it?
I don't know what I thought.
I just don't want Sabrina to be...
What? Unhappy?
You've never seen
the face of somebody
the day after
we've taken over their business.
You're at the hairdresser
or celebrating.
I think I'm getting old.
I feel terrible.
Take a pill.
Watch it! I'm still your mother.
And you taught me everything I know.
I didn't teach you this.
Excuse me,
I have some calls to return.
Miss Fairchild.
He was expecting you earlier.
I'll tell him you're here.
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
Don't tell him I'm here.
But he pays me to tell him.
Sabrina Fairchild.
- I was beginning to worry.
- Why?
That's a favourite question of yours.
Didn't you want to come?
- I asked you first.
- I asked you second.
I've been...
I've been wandering around Manhattan
all afternoon.
It's something to do with maybe...
never seeing you again
and that's ridiculous
because we don't...
We don't have to...
Well, except by accident and...
How could that be a problem?
If two people...
I asked you first.
Well...
What you said, whatever it is...
makes what I was going to say...
obsolete, I think.
Obsolete?
Irrelevant.
OK, I like irrelevant.
Do you?
- Who cuts your hair?
- Tony.
Tony?
- Yeah. Should I go to your barber?
- No but...
Tony was my dad's barber. He's 94.
Maybe his hands
aren't as steady as they...
As they used to be.
It's just that it's all...
- So, what's irrelevant?
- I want you to come to Paris.
You mean go to Paris?
No, I want you
to come to Paris with me.
- You're really going?
- It's your fault.
You convinced me there were
some things missing in my life.
- Like what?
- Like a life.
- I didn't think you were listening.
- I was.
Will you come?
Don't say no. Will you?
- I just got back.
- So? Say yes, now.
- We'd leave tomorrow.
- Tomorrow? I have to talk to David.
Just come away.
He'll get the idea in a week or two.
You are formidable, aren't you?
- In business dealings...
- This isn't business.
Didn't you say
everything is business?
No, but it sounds like me.
What will you tell him?
I did knock.
Here are the tickets.
And the other things
are being taken care of.
And good night.
So it is.
You want dinner?
- No.
- I could order in.
No.
I don't understand what happened.
- I hardly know you.
- Yes, you do.
- I wasn't even interested.
- Gee, thanks.
I was interested in David.
He was so much what I wanted that I
had to escape and I did, to Paris
and I wrote in my stupid journal
and I cut my stupid hair
and I came back stupider than ever.
Oh, Linus!
I'm so happy.
You've made me so happy.
Linus... what...?
- I can't do this.
- What is it?
- You were right.
- About what?
About everything.
Everything that mattered.
It was all a lie.
Everything I said to you
from the moment I brought
the champagne into the solarium.
- I don't believe you.
- I was sent to deal with you.
I sent myself
and I did a hell of a job.
There was a marriage, there was
a merger. You got in the way.
The plan is to take you to Paris,
then leave,
to get you out of the way.
I think...
What other things
are being taken care of?
- What?
- She said "other things".
An apartment for you in Paris,
a bank account.
How much?
500,000 francs.
Your first offer was better.
You can have more.
I don't want more.
I don't want any.
You went to all that trouble
just for me?
- The helicopter and the jet and...
- It was no trouble.
Was I really so bad for David?
So wrong?
The chauffeur's daughter,
isn't that over?
That's not it.
- It's about a piece of plastic.
- Plastic?
Nothing personal.
May I?
Paris is always a good idea.
I was happy there.
You would have been too.
I'll drive you home.
I'm flying home.
"He shall have music
wherever he goes."
Hi.
- You're better?
- Oh, yeah, much better.
Stitches come out tomorrow.
How about you?
Where are you coming from?
Town.
Long evening.
I thought we were going to talk.
I was planning a big
stitch-removal celebration.
- I thought we'd go to...
- I was with Linus.
You know, of all the girls
I've known, and I've known some...
Is that a song?
You're the only girl
I danced with only once.
Twice.
What? How could I have forgotten?
Was there champagne?
I was eight and you were taking
dancing lessons.
I was homework.
I'm leaving town, David.
- I think I knew that.
- I won a ticket to Paris.
Lucky. One way?
Yes, come to think of it.
Travelling alone?
Yes.
You have a good trip.
- You're here.
- So are you.
I want you to call Seattle and Tokyo
and tell them to stop construction.
Then get the Rons and Tysons to an
emergency meeting on the merger here.
Then transfer my Paris ticket
to the name of David Larrabee.
- I need to see my mother...
- Linus.
I need to see my mother
as soon as she gets in.
Good morning, David.
Can I get you some coffee?
No? OK.
I've got a surprise for you.
Yeah? I got one for you too.
I watched you for years but I thought
there was a limit to how sick...
How could you, Linus? How could you
do what you did to me and to her?
How could you go that far?
What the hell makes you think
you have the right?
Habit.
Listen, David.
I tried something and it didn't work.
It worked but it didn't really work.
I want you to go to Paris today.
- With Sabrina.
- What?
This whole thing was a business
tactic but it got out of hand.
Somehow I lost my focus.
I screwed up everything...
but I know it can be fixed.
I manipulated her, I confused her...
but she's loved you all her life.
You're what she really wants.
You're what she's always wanted.
Go with her, it's not too late.
Things will work out.
She'll make you happy.
I don't want her
to have to leave here alone.
What about Patrick and the merger?
You'd blow a billion dollars
for this?
I see.
Get going. Go on.
You'll miss the plane.
Miss McCardle, I want to see you
in my office right away.
Where is it?
When your mother and I
first came here,
she cooked, I drove
and we had no expenses.
After a couple of years
we had $15,000.
I was driving
Mr Larrabee Snr at the time
and he never closed the window
between us.
He did a lot of business on the
daily commute and I paid attention.
When he bought, I bought.
When he sold, I sold.
Are you telling me
you have a million dollars?
No...
A little over two million.
Your mother and I were happy here.
We always dreamed of what it
would be like to do this for you.
$2 million might have
exceeded her expectations.
But then you've always exceeded mine.
I know what his instructions were
but I'm giving you new ones.
There's been a change, we...
Just get started
and I'll call you back.
Thanks for getting here so quickly.
I need to tell you a story...
and I need for you to tell me
how it's going to turn out.
All those years
you made all of that money
and you never told any of us
how to do it.
I'll tell you now, Joanna.
Marry me. Marry me for my money.
People do it every day.
I'm not amused, Thomas,
and I have a great sense of humour.
Then marry me for love.
Emergency what?
What's the emergency?
Darling, if I knew. I'm sure there's
a perfectly good answer to that.
- What the hell is going on?
- In a minute, Patrick.
What are we waiting for?
And what's with Siegfried and Roy?
Just a minute, Patrick.
OK.
We've known each other
for a long time.
We may have played hardball
on occasion but...
we have a healthy respect for
our individual business abilities.
We saw the potential of this merger
and nobody doubts it would have been
an enormously successful venture.
Would have been?
The purpose of this meeting
is to inform you that my brother...
Is late as usual. Sorry.
Sorry, everybody.
- What are you doing here?
- Elizabeth and I are going to elope.
- Where's Sabrina?
- Are we merging?
- Who's Sabrina?
- You didn't go with her?
Obviously not. Here I am, right?
She's probably having
her beverage service now.
- Who is Sabrina.
- The chauffeur's daughter.
- Don't call her that.
- She was after David for a while,
then she switched to Linus.
She decided he was the powerful one.
- He told you that?
- He told me everything.
And you didn't talk
to her before she left?
Sure. I said goodbye and
I think I wished her luck. Maybe not.
I told her I felt funny
accepting your hand-me-downs.
I told her you've always been very
generous to your women in the past
and I was sure she'd be more
than compensated for... whatever.
I told you. He loves her.
- Who?
- Sabrina.
- Is he packed?
- Yes.
- Is who packed?
- You are. Just one bag.
- You went to my apartment?
- I took her.
Going through your underwear was
like touching the shroud of Turin.
Sign this. It's your
authorisation for the merger
and this gives me the raise
I deserve for my new position.
A car is waiting for you downstairs,
a helicopter at East 60th.
The ticket has been changed to the
Concorde, it leaves in 39 minutes.
If you make it,
you might beat her there.
Go, Linus. Don't think.
- She must absolutely hate me.
- She'll get over it, we all do.
This is crazy. You expect me to just
drop everything and walk out of here?
- Running would be better.
- You're all nuts.
Linus, you know I love you.
No mother could be prouder...
but I think it's time
that you ran away from home.
But sign these first.
If you'll excuse me, it appears
I have a previous engagement.
The debt burden this merger
will accumulate makes it essential
to restructure a couple of divisions
that are generating cash drains.
I've done a review of last quarter's
performance of both companies.
David, when did you ever...
You always send me the financial
statements, assuming I can't read.
Go ahead, say it.
You don't deserve her.
I don't. I know that.
But I need her
and I don't need anything.
Time to run for it.
I just want to make her happy.
13 Rue des Beaux Arts.
Your attention, please.
Last call for Air France Concorde
supersonic flight to Paris,
now boarding at gate 34.
Air France
wishes you a pleasant flight.
- First time on the Concorde, sir?
- Yes.
- But not your first time in Paris?
- It's my first everything.
"Paris is always a good idea,"
you said.
You said I'd be happy here.
You couldn't have meant without you.
- How did you know where to find me?
- Your father.
I told him I need you.
I told him I'd make you happy.
I promised him.
I thought it was all a lie.
So did I.
But something happened.
It was a lie...
and then it was a dream.
I don't know how to believe you.
- How can I ever...
- Because you know me.
Better than anyone else.
I think you know I love you.
And you promised...
if there was anything
you could ever do...
Once upon a time,
on the north shore of Long Island,
not far from New York,
there was a very,
very large mansion, almost a castle.
I've been following in footsteps
all my life.
Save me, Sabrina fair.
You're the only one who can.
And on this very large estate,
there lived a small girl.
And life was pleasant there
and very, very simple.
But then one day, the girl grew up
and went beyond
the walls of the grounds
and found the world.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org