Dad...
Clear the ramp! 30 seconds!
God be with you!
Port side, stick.
Starboard side, stick.
Move fast and clear
those mortar holes.
l want to see plenty
of beach between men.
Five men is an opportunity.
One is a waste of ammo.
Keep the sand
out of your weapons.
Keep those actions clear.
l'll see you on the beach.
Open mortar holes!
Over the side!
Port and starboard, over...
Jesus.
Thank you...
l said, what the hell
do we do now, sir?
Captain Miller!
Sergeant Horvath!
Move your men off the beach!
Go!
OK, you guys!
Get on my ass! Follow me!
What's the rallying point?
Anywhere but here!
The sea wall!
Move up to the sea wall!
Sir, l'm staying!
Clear this beach!
Make way for the others!
This is all we got!
Every inch of this beach
has been pre-sighted!
You stay here, you're dead men!
Mama!
Stay down! Stay down!
What are you guys?
104th Medical Battalion, sir!
Here to set up field operations!
Get rid of that crap!
Grab yourselves some weapons.
Follow me.
l'm hit!
Briggs!
Get me out!
l'm hit low. God!
Medic!
Navy Beach Battalion, sir.
l gotta clear these obstacles
for the tanks.
All the armour's
foundering in the Channel.
Orders, sir.
You go somewhere else.
l'm clearing this one!
Come on, Briggs!
Medic!
Move! Move!
Move! Come on!
Move!
Shore party.
No armour has made it ashore.
We got no DD tanks.
Dog One is not open.
Who's in command here?
You are, sir!
- Sergeant Horvath!
- Sir!
You recognise where we are?
Right where we're supposed to
be, but no one else is!
Nobody's where
they're supposed to be.
Shore party.
First wave, ineffective.
We do not hold the beach. Say
again, we do not hold the beach.
Sir, we got the leftovers
from Fox Company,
Able Company
and George Company!
Plus we got some Navy Demo guys
and a Beachmaster!
Shore party.
Cat-F, Cat-F, C...
- Reiben here, sir!
- Anybody else?
Jackson, but that's about it.
Mellish here.
Caparzo!
DeForest's back with Wade.
He's hurt so bad he says
he sprung 100 leaks.
Wade says he's all used up.
Find somebody you can help.
He's battalion surgeon, sir!
Get his attention.
Wade!
Yo, doc!
Get him off the beach.
l got it!
We stopped the bleeding!
Fuck!
Just give us a fucking chance,
you son of a bitch!
Son of a fucking cocksucker!
Come on, Wade! lt's Mellish!
Wade!
We found Miller!
Let's move! Let's move!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
This is all?
This is all that's made it?
We got scattered
pretty bad, sir.
There's bound to be more.
Not enough. This is not enough.
Dog One exit...
On the right.
Or is it left? Shit!
No, Vierville is west of us.
This is Dog One.
They're killing us!
We don't have a fucking chance,
and that ain't fair!
Gather weapons and ammo!
Come on,
drag 'em in off the sand!
Hey, Reiben, Reiben, Reiben,
where's your BAR?
Bottom of the channel, sir.
Nearly drowned me.
Find a replacement.
Bangalores!
Bring up some bangalores!
Grenades, grenades!
Get 'em over here!
Bangalores up the line!
Heads up!
Bangers coming your way!
Come on, come on, come on!
Jackson here, sir!
Reiben back, sir!
One more. Give me one more.
Oh, my God, it hurts!
l'm gonna die!
Oh, my God! Oh, Jesus!
Oh, my God!
Keep it moving. Keep it moving.
Almost got it.
Jesus!
Lucky bastard.
Keep it moving. You got it?
God! God, help me!
You're not gonna die.
You're fine. Don't look at it.
Bangalores! Clear the shingle!
Fire in the hole!
We're in business! Defilade!
Other side of the hole!
That's it! Let's go!
lnspected. Morphine.
Routine.
Priority.
He's gone.
Son of a...
Get in there.
Fuck. l can't move.
Mellish, give me your bayonet.
Two MG-42s and two mortars.
Add 20, left 30.
There's a little defilade,
but it's the perfect position
if we get some armour.
We gotta open up this draw!
Get this draw open.
Reiben, Mellish,
let's get into the war!
Grab some cover and put
some fire on that crew.
Davis, DeBernardo, Young, Valk,
get ready.
Covering fire!
Go, go, go!
Goddamn firing squad.
lt's the only way
we can get everybody out.
Short, Payton, McDonald, Parkes!
You're next!
- Why not hand out blindfolds?
- All we'll do here is die.
Covering fire!
Go, go, go!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Go, Goddamit!
Jackson.
Sir.
See that impact crater?
Yes, sir.
That should give complete
defilade from that machine gun.
Wait for my command.
Go!
Captain, if your mother
saw that, she'd be very upset.
l thought you were my mother.
Be not thou far from me,
O Lord.
My God, l am sorry
for offending Thee.
l detest my sins for having
offended Thee, O Lord.
Listen to me, Lord.
All my strength...
haste Thee to help me.
Dog One exit! Right here!
We're in business!
Move! Move!
Reiben.
- Let's go, sarge. Go!
- Reiben.
Come on, Doyle!
Sarge.
Flame!
Doyle, do it!
Don't shoot! Let 'em burn!
''Comrade?'' You son of a bitch!
Lie down!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Cut it out!
Cut it out! Cease fire!
Sugar Cane. Sugar Charlie Three.
Say again, Dog One is open.
Send in the dozers.
l'm waiting
to tie in my flanks. Over.
What?
What? l'm sorry,
l can't understand you.
What'd he say? What'd he say?
''Look, l washed for supper.''
- Hey, Fish.
- Yeah?
Look at this.
A Hitler Youth knife.
Now it's a Shabbat challah
cutter, right?
Keep it moving!
That's quite a view.
Yes, it is.
Quite a view.
''Dear Mr Brian Boyd,
''no doubt you have
received information...''
''Dear Mrs Jensen...''
''..the death of your son.''
''..no words
can relieve the grief...''
''We have felt his loss
tremendously.''
''He was a fine soldier...''
''We were involved
''in one of the most important
operations of this war.''
''Al held us all together.
''He was always
first to volunteer...''
''..came to a clearing
''where 4,000 troops had passed.''
''Your husband served in a unit
''whose dangerous duty is
to place itself beyond...''
''..we all cherish
and hold so dear.
''The loss of Lee and others
like him is a distinct blow.''
''l understand your desire
''to learn about circumstances
leading to his death.''
Colonel, l've got something
you should know about.
These two men died in Normandy.
This one at Omaha beach.
Sean Ryan.
This man at Utah.
Peter Ryan.
This man was killed
last week in New Guinea.
Daniel...
Ryan.
The three are brothers, sir.
l've just learned
that this afternoon
their mother will get
all three telegrams.
That's not all.
There's a fourth brother.
He parachuted in the night
before the invasion.
He's somewhere in Normandy.
- ls he alive?
- We don't know.
Come with me.
'Goddamit.'
All four were in the 29th
Division, but we split them up
after the Sullivan brothers died
on the Juneau.
Any contact
with the fourth son, James?
No, sir. He was dropped about
15 miles inland near Neuville.
That's still deep
behind German lines.
There's no way to know
where the hell he was dropped.
First reports out of SHAEF said
the 101st is scattered to hell.
There's misdrops
all over Normandy.
Assuming Ryan survived
the jump, he could be anywhere.
ln fact, he's probably KlA.
And frankly, sir, we go sending
some sort of rescue mission,
flat-hatting through swarms
of German reinforcements
along our axis of advance,
they're gonna be KlA, too.
l have a letter here...
written a long time ago
to a Mrs Bixby in Boston.
So bear with me.
''Dear Madam,
''l have been shown in the files
of the War Department
''a statement of the Adjutant
General of Massachusetts
''that you are the mother
of five...
''sons who died gloriously
on the field of battle.
''l feel how weak and fruitless
must be any words of mine
''that would attempt
to beguile you from the grief
''of a loss so overwhelming.
''But l cannot refrain
from tendering to you
''the consolation
that may be found
''in the thanks of the republic
they died to save.
''l pray that
Our Heavenly Father
''may assuage the anguish
of your bereavement
''and leave only the cherished
memory of the loved lost...
''and the solemn pride
that must be yours
''to have laid so costly
a sacrifice
''upon the altar of freedom.
''Yours very sincerely
and respectfully...
''Abraham Lincoln.''
That boy is alive.
We are gonna send somebody
to find him...
and we are gonna get him
the hell out of there.
Yes, sir.
We expected 32 tanks,
27 didn't make it.
- Miller, Charlie Company.
- Go in, Captain.
lf we don't off-load
those Shermans by 0600,
we'll have an entire division
stuck at Carentan
with its pants
around its ankles.
Well, you let me know.
Have Charlie Company hold
Vierville until we get there.
Yes, sir. Runner!
Airborne was supposed
to win an open door for us.
They misdropped, scattered
everything into the wind.
What's your situation?
Yes, sir. Sector four is secure.
We took out towed 88s
here, here...and here.
They'd already gotten
four Shermans
and some deuce-and-a-halves.
These two minefields
are one big one.
We tried going through,
but it turned
into a high-density field...
little bit of everything.
Spreng mine 44s,
pot mines, A-200s...
the wooden bastards that the
mine detectors don't pick up.
This road here...
they placed Teller mine 43s,
l guess for our tanks...
from here
to the edge of the village.
So we marked 'em,
called the engineers.
Resistance?
We had higher
support expectations, sir.
There was an understrength
company without artillery.
Wehrmacht 346 lnfantry,
von Luck Kampfgruppe.
We ended up with 23 prisoners.
We turned them over to MPs.
What about our casualties?
Well...
the figures...
were 35 dead...
times two wounded.
They just...
didn't wanna give up those 88s.
lt was tough,
that's why you got it.
Yes, sir.
John...
l've got another one for you.
- Yes, sir.
- Straight from the top.
We're taking a squad to Neuville
on a public relations mission.
You leading a squad?
Some Private lost three brothers
and got a ticket home.
How come Neuville?
They think he's part
of all those airborne misdrops.
lt won't be easy finding one
particular soldier.
Like finding a needle
in a stack of needles.
What about the company?
We take our pick,
the rest get folded into Baker.
Jesus Christ.
They took away your company?
lt wasn't my company. lt was
the army's. So they told me.
Give me Reiben on BAR, Jackson,
Wade, Beasley and Caparzo.
Beasley's dead.
All right, Mellish, then.
We got anybody speaks French?
Not that l know of.
What about Talbot?
- This morning.
- Oh. All right.
l'll try to dig up
another interpreter.
Assemble
at battalion motor pool.
Yes, sir.
- What we doing?
- Listen up... What?
What we gonna do?
You're going home with a hunk
of cheese in your ass, Caparzo.
You like it in the ass.
Attention!
As you were.
l'm looking for Corporal Upham,
- Timothy E.
- l'm Upham, sir.
- You speak French and German?
- Yes, sir.
Accent?
A slight one in French.
My German's clean, sir.
You're reassigned to me.
Grab your gear.
We're going to Neuville.
When was this updated?
As of 0830, sir.
Uh, sir...
These two axes advance south...
Sir, there are Germans
in Neuville.
- Yes, Corporal.
- Sir, a LOT of Germans.
You have a problem
with that, Corporal?
No, l've never been in combat.
l make maps, translate...
l need someone who speaks
French and German.
My guys were killed.
But l haven't held a weapon
since training, sir.
- Did you fire the weapon?
- Yes, sir.
- Then get your gear.
Sir, may l...
May l bring my typewriter, sir?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
- That a souvenir?
- No, sir.
Take your time, Corporal.
Look on the bright side,
Corporal.
Yes, sir.
For one thing...
you don't need to carry those.
You'll need that.
Need this. Yes, sir.
Don't need that...
You want your head blown off?
Don't fuckin' touch me
with those little rat claws.
Get the fuck back in formation.
l was wondering
where you're from, that's...
Caparzo, is it?
Hey, drop dead, Corporal.
Got you.
And saluting the captain
makes him a target for Germans.
So don't do it, especially
when l'm next to him.
Corporal, what's
your book about?
- Watch your rifle.
- Sorry.
lt's supposed to be about
the bonds of brotherhood
that develop between
soldiers during war.
Brotherhood?
What do you know
about brotherhood?
Get a load of this guy, Fish.
Ask the captain where he's from.
Yeah, ask the captain.
He'll tell you everything
you wanna know.
You wanna explain
the math of this to me?
Why risk the lives of the
eight of us to save one guy?
20 degrees.
Anybody wanna answer?
Reiben, think about
the poor bastard's mother.
l got a mother, all right?
l mean, you got a mother.
Sarge has got a mother.
Shit, l bet even
the captain's got a mother.
Well, not the captain,
but the rest of us.
''Theirs not to reason why,
theirs but to do and die.''
What does that mean?
We're all supposed to die?
Upham's talking about
our duty as soldiers.
Yes, sir.
We have orders to follow.
That supersedes everything,
including your mothers.
Thank you, sir.
Even if you think
the mission's fubar, sir?
Especially if you think
the mission's fubar.
What's ''fubar''?
Oh, it's German. Yeah.
Never heard of that.
Sir...
l have an opinion
on this matter.
Well, by all means,
share it with the squad.
Well, from my way
of thinking, sir,
this entire mission is
a serious misallocation
of valuable military resources.
Yeah. Go on.
Well, it seems to me, sir,
that God made me
a fine instrument of warfare.
Reiben, pay attention.
This is the way to gripe!
Continue, Jackson.
What l mean, sir,
if you put me and this rifle
within one mile of Adolf Hitler
with a clear line
of sight, sir...
Pack your bags, fellas.
War's over. Amen.
Oh, that's brilliant,
bumpkin.
So, Captain, what about you?
You don't gripe at all?
l don't gripe to you,
Reiben. l'm a captain.
There's a chain of command.
Gripes go up, not down.
You gripe to me, l gripe
to my superiors and so on.
l don't gripe to you
or in front of you.
l'm sorry, sir, but, uh...
Let's say you weren't a captain.
What would you say then?
Well, in that case,
l'd say this is
an excellent mission, sir,
with an extremely valuable
objective, sir,
worthy of
my best efforts, sir.
Moreover...l feel
heartfelt sorrow
for the mother
of Private James Ryan
and will lay down my life
and the lives of my men,
especially you, Reiben,
to ease her suffering.
- He's good.
- l love him.
Right.
Thunder!
Flash!
Upham, over there.
Reiben, you four go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
You're a welcome sight.
Our relief showed up.
How many are you?
Just eight. We're not
your relief. Sorry.
What do you mean, sir?
We're here for a Private Ryan.
Who? Ryan? What for?
- ls he here?
- l don't know.
Maybe on the other side of town.
The Germans cut us in two.
- What's his name again?
- Ryan. James Ryan.
He dropped in with 101st.
- Goldman, get me a runner.
- Runner!
Come on.
Jonesy, make a hole there!
We got stopped by intense rifle
action from the eastward.
The Germans have been
reinforcing regiments all day.
lt's been quiet
for about 45 minutes.
Most of the German fire
is concentrated to the westward.
Who's on the loudspeaker?
That's Dagwood Düsseldorf,
our friendly neighbourhood
morale officer.
The Statue of Liberty is kaputt.
''The Statue of Liberty
is kaputt.''
That's disconcerting.
Take the second left...
Your father was circumcised
by my rabbi, you prick!
Private Ryan, James,
probably misdropped with 101 .
- Got that?
- Cover!
Go!
Those sadistic fuckin' animals!
Get down.
They know we're not in contact,
they'll get the runners.
Why keep shooting him?
Long as he lives,
he carries the message.
- We'd do the same.
- We wouldn't!
- Get ready to travel.
- Yes, sir.
Try again to let Captain Hamill
know we're coming.
What's the rest
of Neuville like?
Uh, next block's got
two-storey buildings both sides.
A lotta windows
and a square on the left.
- Show me.
- Sarge, hold right here.
Yes, sir.
Let's stay out of this enfilade
and use the buildings.
Try a left hook.
Two of yours, two of mine.
Hastings, Goldman, up front!
Reiben, Caparzo.
Fundamentals. Short runs.
High and low at the corners.
Be prepared for close contact.
Go. Upham,
stay with Sergeant Horvath.
Stay right here.
l'll wear him like underwear!
Stay with me.
Past the end
are the gates to the square.
Good.
Reiben,
where's the Captain from?
Figure that out,
you got yourself a prize.
300 bucks, l heard.
Company's got a pool.
Five bucks gets you in.
Easy.
lt's around this corner.
Defilade up to those gates.
Somebody must know
where he's from.
Been with him since Kasserine
Pass, and l don't know.
My ankles are killing me.
l'll need a wheelchair
before this is over.
Ow! That's it. Oh, my God.
Got ankles like an old woman.
Like an old...
Reiben.
So you don't even know
where he went to school?
Captain didn't go to school,
they assembled him
out of Gl body parts.
Pay attention to detail.
l know where he's from 'cause
l pay attention to detail.
Hey, Upham...
careful you don't step
in the bullshit.
Do it.
Thunder!
Thunder, or we will fire on you!
Upham, tell them
to show themselves.
Ask where the Germans are.
What's he saying?
The children.
Take the children.
No, we can't take the kids.
We can't take the kids! No!
They think
they'll be safe with us.
lt's not gonna be safe with us!
Are you nuts?!
Listen to the Captain!
They think
they'll be safe, sir.
Not gonna be safe anywhere.
Put that kid back!
Put that little girl back!
Caparzo,
give that kid back now!
Upham, how do you say
''lt's OK''?
She reminds me of my niece, sir.
Get the kid back up there!
Captain, we could take her
down the road to the next town.
We're not here
to do the decent thing!
We're here to follow
fuckin' orders!
Sarge, take this goddamn kid!
Cover! Cover!
Come on. No!
Goddamit!
Where'd that come from?
He was on the ground
before we heard.
That's where l'd be.
l didn't see it.
450 yards, Captain.
Maybe a shade under.
l wouldn't venture
out there, fellas!
This sniper's got talent!
Please don't cry. l'll take you
back to your parents.
Please don't cry. Come on.
Captain.
Hold on, Caparzo.
Help me up.
l can walk. l can walk.
Caparzo, stay still!
All right.
Two clicks, left wind.
Captain, can you see him
from there? How is he?
Wade, you stay put.
Where's he shot, Captain?
- Can you see him?
- Stay there!
Damn it, stay down!
What's up with you?
What if you get hit? Huh?
Fish, come over here.
Carpy, put your head down.
Put your head down.
O my God, l trust in Thee.
Let me not be ashamed.
Let not my enemies
triumph over me.
Copy it.
Copy it and send it for me.
You're gonna send it.
Put it down!
- lt's got blood!
- l see it.
lt's... lt's to my dad.
lt's got blood on it.
We got him.
Stay down.
How bad is it?
Chest, maybe lung shot.
Get that 30 up the street!
Detail!
Clear up!
Clear down!
That's why
we can't take children.
Sergeant Horvath,
do an ammo check.
Upham... canteens.
Fill 'em up.
- Sergeant Hill.
- Yes, sir.
Gather your men. We'll form up
at the north-west corner.
Mellish, check the tower.
Right now. Go!
Fuck Ryan.
- Thunder!
- Flash!
Come on in.
Hey, guys, we're looking
for Captain Hamill.
Somewhere across the square.
Across the square.
Go easy. Watch for snipers.
Take it easy. Sit down.
Jimmy T, find Captain Hamill,
bring him in here.
What? Up there?
How should l know?
Would you go look, please?
Thank you, you moron.
All right.
You guys just flake out
here for a while.
Let me get this goddamn
hitchhiker out of my boot.
Jesus!
Drop your weapons!
Drop 'em now!
Drop the fucking weapons!
l'll shoot you! l'll shoot!
Drop! Drop! Drop 'em!
Now! Put 'em down!
Clear up!
Shit.
Shit!
Clear up!
Clear down!
Enough to make you old.
Let's hope so.
Fred Hamill, Pathfinders 101st.
John Miller, 2nd Rangers.
Thank you.
We're looking for
Private James Ryan.
He's part of your outfit.
Any chance you policed him up?
- How was the road in?
- Scenic.
We lost most of our ammo.
And one of our men.
Lieutenant, redeploy that
bazooka to the right side.
Yes, sir!
And get Ryan up here.
Ryan!
Ryan, front and centre!
Here comes our boy.
Told you he was an asshole.
Sir, Private Ryan reporting.
At ease.
Captain Miller, 2nd Rangers.
He wants a word with you.
This way.
All right.
Take a knee.
Private, l have some bad news.
Well, there isn't any easy
way to say this, so, uh...
so l'll just say it -
your brothers are dead.
We have, uh, orders
to come get you...
'cause you're going home.
Oh, my God.
My brothers are dead.
l was gonna take 'em fishing
when we got home.
l'm so sorry, James.
l can't tell you how much.
How...how did they die?
They were killed in action.
No, that can't be.
They're both...
That...that can't be.
My brothers are still
in grammar school.
You're James Ryan?
Yeah.
James Francis Ryan from lowa?
James Frederick Ryan, Minnesota.
Well, does that...does that
mean my brothers are OK?
Yeah, l'm sure they're fine.
Are you sure they're OK,
though?
We're looking for
a different Private Ryan.
How do you know?
How do you know the foul-up
isn't that his brothers
are OK and that...
Lieutenant,
l'm sorry for the trouble.
l just wrote them a letter...
l got to get home.
l got to get home right now.
Shh, take it easy.
- Where's our Ryan?
- l don't know.
You in touch with your CO?
- That figures.
- What unit's he in?
Baker Company, 506.
- The guy with the broken foot?
- Charlie, l think.
You think? Yeah.
Ryan? Don't know... Man!
Where was your drop zone?
Just inside of Vierville.
Vierville?
How did you end up here?
You got me, sir.
C-47 took heavy fire.
Pilot tried to get out,
turning every which way.
Took more fire in the drop.
Got messy. l ended up here.
l haven't seen a single guy
from my stick, sir.
Anybody there have a big mouth,
say where the drop was?
No, sir, but they had
the same rally point as us.
Show me.
My men are beat.
We'll hold up for three hours
then pull out after dark.
Got anything left in this town
like a three-star hotel?
Something with clean sheets
and room service?
How about a nice comfy church?
- We'll take that.
- Any news?
How's it all falling together?
Well, we got
the beachhead secure.
Problem is Monty's taking
his time moving on Caen.
We can't pull out
till he's ready, so...
That guy's overrated.
No argument here.
You got to take Caen
so you can take Saint-Lo.
Take Saint-Lo to take Valognes.
Valognes, you got Cherbourg.
And Cherbourg, you got Paris.
Paris, you get Berlin.
Then that big boat home.
We sure could
use you around here,
but l understand
what you're doing.
You do?
Yeah. l got a couple
of brothers myself.
- Oh.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
No, l mean it.
Find him. Get him home.
What's with your hand?
l don't know.
lt started when they brought
us down for embarkation.
lt comes and goes.
You may have to get
yourself a new job.
This one doesn't seem
to agree with you any more.
What?
- What?
- Nothing.
What was the name
of that kid at Anzio?
He was always walking around
on his hands,
and singing that song about
the man on the flying trapeze?
Yeah, Vecchio.
He was a goofy kid.
Remember he used to pee
a ''V'' on everybody's jacket,
for Vecchio.
For victory.
Vecchio.
He was so short.
- Wasn't he a midget?
- How did he become a Ranger?
Got shot in the foot once.
He could walk faster
on his hands.
He could run faster
on his hands than...
You see, when...you end up
killing one of your men,
you tell yourself it happened
so you could save the lives
of two or three or 10 others.
Maybe a hundred others.
Do you know how many men
l've lost under my command?
- How many?
- 94.
But that means
l've saved the lives
of 10 times that many,
doesn't it?
Maybe even 20, right?
20 times as many?
And that's how simple it is.
That's how you...
That's how you rationalise
making the choice
between the mission and the men.
Except this time,
this mission is a man.
This Ryan better be worth it.
He'd better go home
and cure some disease
or invent a longer-lasting
light bulb or something.
l wouldn't trade 10 Ryans
for one Vecchio or one Caparzo.
Amen.
Look. There it goes again.
Sir...
are you all right?
Look, we're gonna
move out in two hours.
Why don't you get some sleep?
l don't know how he does it.
What's that?
Falls asleep like that.
Look at him.
He's lights-out
the minute his head's down.
Clear conscience.
What's that saying? ''lf God's
on our side, who's on theirs?''
''lf God be for us,
who could be against us?''
Yeah, what did l say?
Well, actually,
the trick to falling asleep
is trying to stay awake.
How is that, Wade?
My mother was an intern,
she worked late nights,
slept through the day,
so the only time we got to talk
was when she'd get home.
So l used to lie in my bed
and try to stay awake,
but it never worked
'cause the harder l tried,
the faster l'd fall asleep.
That wouldn't have
mattered in my house.
My ma would've shook me awake,
chatted till dawn.
That woman
was never too tired to talk.
Probably the only time
she could get a word in.
Funny thing is,
sometimes she'd come home early,
and l'd pretend to be asleep.
Who? You...your mom?
Yeah.
She'd stand in the doorway
looking at me.
And l'd just keep my eyes shut.
l knew she just wanted
to find out about my day,
that she came home early...
just to talk to me.
And l still wouldn't move.
l'd still pretend
to just be asleep.
l don't know why l did that.
We only got a couple hours.
Go to sleep.
Captain? Sir?
Corporal?
How you doin' there?
You all right?
Yeah, l think this is
all good for me, sir.
Really?
How is that?
''War educates the senses,
''calls into action the will,
''perfects the physical
constitution,
''brings men into such
swift and close collision
''in critical moments
that man measures man.''
Yeah, well, l guess
that's Emerson's way
of finding the bright side.
- You know Emerson, sir?
- l know some.
So where are you from, Captain?
What'd you do before the war?
What's the pool up to?
You know, l think
it's around 300, sir.
Well, when it gets up to 500,
l'll tell you and we'll split
the money, how about that?
Well, sir, l feel it's my duty
under your command
to suggest we wait until
it gets to a thousand, sir.
What if we don't
live that long?
- 500?
- 500 would be good, yeah.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Get some sleep, Corporal.
Yes, sir.
Who's got sulphur powder?
Medic! My buddy's bleeding!
He needs a tourniquet!
- Wade.
- Yes, sir?
- Do what you can.
- Yes, sir.
Hold on, fellas.
lt won't be much longer.
How we doing here?
All right.
Yeah, doing all right.
Don't worry about it.
Doc's in town.
lt's all right.
The 29th lnfantry's breaking
through, they'll be here soon.
Plasma. Anybody got plasma?
- Captain. Hey, Captain.
- Soldier, want to fill me in?
Uh, yeah.
Lieutenant DeWindt, sir.
99th Troop Carrier Squadron
carrying 327th Glider lnfantry.
This one was mine.
l was the pilot. 22 dead.
l ended up without a scratch.
Took my co-pilot's head off.
Well, who are these people?
The guys we came with,
they headed off first night.
Other guys keep showing up.
One, two, half-dozen at a time.
Then some officer'll
patch together a mixed unit,
head off to make trouble, sir.
We're looking for
Private James Ryan.
Baker Company, 506 of the 101st.
No, you got me, sir.
A lot of guys
come in and out of here.
Check that squad.
- See if Ryan's in it.
- Yes, sir.
Smell that leg right there.
ls it south of cheese?
What?
Keep moving. Keep moving!
l'm Juden, you know?
Ju-den.
Yeah, l couldn't
pry him out of there,
- l'd need a winch.
- Yeah.
Stars.
Yep, Brigadier General Amend,
Deputy Commander, 101st.
Some fucking genius
had the idea
of welding steel plates on
to keep the general safe
from ground fire.
Unfortunately,
they forgot to tell me
until we were getting airborne.
That's like flying
a freight train.
OK?
Gross overload.
Trim characteristics
all shot to hell.
l nearly broke both my arms
keeping her level.
And when...and when we released,
l cut as hard as l could,
tried to gain altitude
and still keep from stalling.
Came down like a fucking meteor.
Here's how we ended up.
And the others,
they stopped easy enough
OK, though, you know?
We were just...we were
just too damn heavy, you know?
The grass was wet.
Downward slope and all.
22 guys dead.
All that for a general?
One man.
- Lot of that going around.
- Fubar.
Fubar.
Y'all got that right.
l looked in a German dictionary.
There's no ''fubar'' in there.
- Upham.
- Yes, sir?
There's more paratroops.
Find out if one's Ryan.
Yes, sir.
You might want
to check these out, sir.
Dog tags.
More than l really
want to count, sir.
l've...l've covered
a lot of bodies, sir.
Jackson...
start going through those.
Yes, sir.
l'll help.
What do you think? He in there?
lf he is, l'll find him.
l bet he is.
10 bucks says l nail him first.
- Who we got...?
- You don't stand a chance.
- You think he's in here?
- Just keep looking.
All right. Gary lanico.
Ben Rubino. Mike Cessacchio.
All the Guineas
are buying it, huh?
Oh, come on,
not the right name.
Wee Willie Winkie,
that's your buddy.
We gotta find this prick.
Where is this sonofabitch?
Don't mix them up?
Keep them in your pile.
How will l know who's here?
Why don't you just shut up,
Reiben, all right?
Everybody be friends.
Cranky there, huh?
l got a winner.
What you talking about?
Ryan.
Ryan?
Look at that, Mellish.
You're a genius, you really are.
R-l-E-N-N-E.
That's Rienne. That's French.
You know what that means?
lt means nothing.
- Three of a kind.
- All from New York.
Do you need
a hand with that?
l got a full house.
Got you beat. Straight flush.
You were looking at my tags.
You're cheating, you know?
Ryan.
Fuckin' unreal, this guy.
Do you need a hand with that?
Can you read that shit?
Jesus, look at
this poor bastard.
They're not bulletproof, huh?
Guess not. All right?
What's between his ears?
Sort of what you
fellas got between your legs.
We got to give him that.
Not bad, Jackson.
What the hell are you doing?
The whole Airborne's watching.
These aren't chips.
- All right, all right.
- Put 'em back in!
He's not here.
Put 'em back.
Maybe we should split
into groups, huh?
Wander the woods,
calling his name.
He'll hear us
sooner or later. Ryan!
That might be a little hard
to do, Captain.
Maybe the locals... Hey, you
know... uh, excusez-moi.
Parlez-vous Ryan, James Ryan?
Merci. Merci beaucoup.
Ryan! Anybody know Ryan,
101st Airborne?
Ryan? You know a guy named Ryan?
Private James Ryan from lowa?
Anybody know a Ryan?
James Ryan?!
Hey, Joe, doesn't,
uh, Michaelson
pal around with a Ryan
from ''C'' Company?
l think so.
Bring him up here, would you?
You know Private Ryan?
You're gonna have
to speak up, sir.
Speak up, sir!
My hearing's not good!
lt comes and goes!
A grenade went off by me!
Got it, got it.
Do you know Private Ryan?
Who?
- Private Ryan? James Ryan?
- Jimmy Ryan?
James. James Francis Ryan.
No, no, no. James Francis Ryan.
Get me a pencil,
something to write on.
Quick! Come on, a pencil!
A small one, sir.
Write this down.
James Francis Ryan,
question mark.
lowa, question mark.
Do you know know him?
Read the message. Look.
Yeah. Of course
l know him, sir.
Where is he?
Yeah, yeah.
We missed our drop zone
by 20 miles,
ended up by Bumville
or some damn place.
We were coming here
to the rally point,
ran into a colonel
who was gathering up men
- to go to, uh...Ramelle...
- Ramelle.
Babysitting a bridge.
That's all l know, sir.
Great! Great!
Thank...thank you.
Write ''thank you.''
Read, and thank you.
You're welcome!
Assemble on me.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
Ramelle.
We're here. There.
Ramelle...
is on the Merderet river,
just south-west of us.
You know anything about
this bridge, Captain?
Yep. The target has
always been Cherbourg.
We can't push on Paris
without a deep water port,
Rommel knows that,
so he's gonna try to get
his armour across the river.
Then he can hit us in the flank
when we turn to Cherbourg.
That makes any village with a
bridge solid-gold real estate.
Let's go.
Captain.
What the hell is that?
A radar site.
Must be out of action.
Looks like there's
something in that...
sandbag bunker
right under the station.
See it?
Yeah. That's my guess, too.
What is it?
Machine gun. Probably MG-42.
Jesus. ls that
what got those guys?
Maybe one of them's our boy.
No, their patches are 82nd.
l don't know
how fast you guys are,
but let's detour this way,
they'll never know we were here.
So, Captain,
let's just go around it.
l hear what you're saying,
but we can't.
l'm with Reiben
on this one, sir.
- We left them 88s.
- For the Air Force.
The Air Force won't spend
ordinance on one machine gun.
Uh, Captain...
We skip it and still
accomplish our mission.
l mean, this isn't
our mission, right?
That's what you want to do,
just leave it here?
Let them ambush
the next company?
No, sir, l'm simply saying, it
seems like an unnecessary risk
given our objective, sir.
Our objective is to win the war.
Sir, l just, uh, l don't have
a good feeling about this one.
When was the last time
you felt good about anything?
All right, three runners
with suppressing fire.
Mellish, you hook to the right.
l'll go up the middle.
Who's going left?