Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Will you look at that
fellow over there?
I've never seen anything
so disgusting in all my life.
I'll tell you something.
He's staring.
I think
he's looking at us.
I think we're
being picked up.
Oh, it's too awful.
Can you believe it?
They can let creatures
like that in here.
I mean, really. It's...
Anne, what's the matter, huh?
Anne?
Oh! Oh, help someone, please.
Oh! please, help.
Damn it!
You're 35 years old, Mr. Vale.
Why are you such a derelict?
Such a piece of human junk?
The answer's simple.
You're a scanner,
but you don't realize it,
and that has been the source
of all your agony.
But I will show you now
that it can be
a source of great power.
Let them in.
Not much of a place, is it?
Still, didn't pay for it, so...
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
We can talk now.
I would like to scan
all of you in this room
one at a time.
I, I must remind you
that the, uh, scanning experience
is usually a painful one,
sometimes resulting in nosebleeds,
earaches, stomach cramps, nausea.
sometimes other symptoms
of a similar nature.
There's a doctor present
Dr. Gatineau.
I know that you've all
been prepared for this,
but I thought I'd just
remind you just the same.
Uh, there is
one other thing.
No one is to leave this room
once the demonstration has begun.
At this point I'd like
to call for volunteers.
Anyone. It doesn't matter.
Fine.
Just, uh...
Sit right here, please.
Now, I'd, I'd like you
to think of
something specific.
something that will not
breach the security
of you organization.
And that you will not object
to having disclosed
to this group.
- Something, uh, personal, perhaps.
- All right.
Yes, I have something.
- Do I have to close my eyes?
- It doesn't matter.
All right.
Yes, I have something.
Move everybody out! Now!
Call consec leader!
I want you to come with me.
I didn't do anything.
I said I want you to come with me.
Come on.
Gatineau, come with us.
Down there. Quick!
Move it!
Get down!
Give him a shot of ephemeral.
Come on!
OK.
Take it easy.
All we need is to get
stopped by a cop.
Ah, it'd serve 'em right.
Why the hell
did they have to send us
to the old factory?
If this guy's a scanner
they don't want him
down at central.
They're afraid of him.
He's a scanner.
Hey, where's security 2?
- He's moving up fast on the left.
- Hey, man, what's happening?
Ray, what the hell's
the matter with you?
You gotta pull back
behind them, man.
Come on!
Ray, I'm gonna kill you
if you don't do it.
Ray!
Oh, my god.
Don't stop! Move it!
No, we got to get 'em
out of there!
We've got to get in there.
They're charred, man!
You can see them burning.
Let go of me!
Those people are dead!
Get up.
Let's get out of here, man!
Come on!
You want to get us killed?
All right. All right. Pipe down!
Last night...
We at consec chose to reveal
to the outside world
our work with those...
Telepathic curiosities
known as scanners.
The result
6 corpses...
And a substantial loss
in credibility
for our organization.
So, this morning
we have a new director
of internal security,
- Mr. Braedon Keller.
- Thank you. Mr. Trevellyan.
Gentlemen,
we're in the business
of international security.
We deal in weaponry
and private armories.
We do not trade
in fantasy and pipe dreams.
Let us leave the development
of dolphins and freaks
as weapons of espionage to others.
Now, with all due respect
to Dr. Paul Ruth,
I recommend that we drop
our scanner program immediately, sir.
Dr. Ruth, what's your response?
Mr. Keller, who composed
our audience last night?
We had 25 financial
and political V.I.P. s
from all over North America.
Were these V.I.P. s
carefully screened?
The screening process used
was very sophisticated, yes.
And yet an assassin managed
to infiltrate this group.
Yes.
And killed 6 of our people.
How did he kill them?
We have reason to believe he...
used scanning techniques.
Then do you suggest, Mr. Keller,
that this highly-skilled assassin- very deadly
who embarrassed us all
in front of the community
we were trying to impress,
was himself a scanner?
We believe so, yes.
That, gentlemen, is my response.
The weapons capability
of these, uh, telepathic...
curiosities.
Is obvious.
If I may, doctor,
your program is based
on a list
of 236 known scanners,
- is it now?
- It is.
Of that number,
how many are now
working with us?
As of last night, none.
Well, then.
We don't even have
a program to drop, do we?
It shouldn't be
very painful for anyone.
Consec surveillance
has gradually lost contact
with all the names on our list,
and I submit that this...
this is not an accident.
I think we've lost them
to a program
far in advance of ours.
What?
I can't believe it.
I think you might
elaborate, Dr. Ruth.
In my study of the situation
I've come to the conclusion
That there is
a scanner underground
Developed in North America.
It has an organization
that's well-motivated,
and it has a leader.
Now, that's ridiculous, doctor.
You can't get 2 of them
to sit in the same room together
without going berserk.
You're making a very
provocative allegation, Dr. Ruth.
Who controls this group?
If you study the descriptions
in this report,
You will find that you
probably met him last night.
His name is Darryl Revok,
and he was on our list.
This is total fiction.
Mr. Trevellyan, I...
A moment, Mr. Keller.
What do you suggest, doctor?
Eliminate the competition.
How?
Contact a scanner who is as yet
unknown to the underground,
convert him to out cause
and then send him out
to infiltrate the underground.
Convert him, doctor? How?
They're all pathetic social misfits.
Unstable. Unreliable.
That is because their unique gifts
are not understood, Mr. Keller.
There is one point
about which there
is no doubt at all,
and that is that consec was attacked.
For our own peace of mind,
we have to retaliate in some way,
and I think
Dr. Ruth's suggestion
is a very interesting one.
Except that...
We don't have ant scanners left
to send into the field.
As a matter of fact,
I do have one,
still unaffiliated.
Very special one.
I don't suppose you speak much.
No.
It's not surprising.
With all those other
voices in your head
how can your hear
your own voice?
How can you develop
a self personality?
How do you feel?
I feel...
crystal clear.
How do you like...
clarity?
I'm not sure.
- I think I'm a bit afraid.
- Why?
I feel so exposed.
I can hear myself.
You hear your own voice?
- Yes.
- Good.
You called me a scanner.
What is that?
Freak of nature...
Born with a certain form of E.S.P.,
a derangement of the synapses
which we call telepathy.
Could be a disease, possibly,
or a result of radiation.
We don't really know why.
Who are you?
My name is Dr. Paul Ruth.
I'm a psychopharmacist by trade,
specializing in the phenomenon
of scanners.
The woman in the shopping mall.
What were you doing to her?
I wasn't doing anything to her.
It was her.
She was...
forcing me...
To what?
To think about her.
The 50 people that were in this room
they appeared to disturb you.
Why was that?
They talked too loud.
They talked, and they talked.
Really? I didn't see
their lips move, did you?
No, it was the other voices.
The ones without lips.
They were drowning me.
I couldn't stop them.
The injection I gave you, the needle.
What happened to the voices?
They stopped.
The drug is called ephemeral.
It's a scan suppressant.
It does nothing
when it's given
to ordinary human being.
when given to a scanner,
it prevents the flow of telepathy.
It stops the voices.
It can help you.
How do you know these things?
It's my profession.
This is Mr. Keller.
Will my car be ready this evening?
Tell us what you did, please, Darryl.
I drilled a hole in my head.
- Where?
- Kind of obvious, isn't it?
Right here.
Why did you do it, Darryl?
Why did you drill the hole?
Too much pressure.
Had to release some pressure.
You wanted to let the pressure out?
You wanted to let
something out of your head?
Maybe I'm so smart
I can't contain
the thoughts in my head.
You wanted to let something
out of your head?
What?
People.
There are people in my head.
Not enough room for Darryl.
You mean voices?
No. Whole people.
Arms, legs, hands.
What's that you've put
over the hole?
It's a door.
Put an eye on the door
so they won't know it's a door
and they can't get
back in
'cause this is the eye
you know?
Do you think
that will fool them?
Sure. Sure it will.
- I mean...
- I mean, sure it will, you know?
I mean, is that
the only way to...
No!
What do you know?
You don't know nothing
do you?
What's it like in there
eh, lady?
You want to see
how to get in?
OK?
Come with me, Darryl.
Get your hands off me.
Get your hands...
Get your hands off me!
That's me, isn't it?
As you were...
Without ephemeral
without guidance.
Is he still like that?
Worse.
How could he be?
At the age of 22
he was extremely self-destructive.
Now, at the age of 35,
he is simply destructive.
In many ways, Cameron,
he is your enemy.
And mine.
But I don't even know him.
He...
knows you.
Somehow he was able
to gather a master list
of all the scanners
who were ever born.
He has sought them out
one by one,
asked them to join him
in an insane crusade
to destroy the society
that created him.
And me?
He was looking for you
but I found you first.
That's why
you can help me.
I don't understand.
All the scanners
who didn't agree to
join him were murdered.
These murders represent
a loss to mankind
of the most spectacular human beings
that ever walked
the face of this planet.
Now, you, Cameron,
and your brothers and sisters,
can bring a, a glory
and a brilliance
to our society that has
never been seen before.
We must stop Revok now.
Consec are not ready
to give up their program.
Paul Ruth came up
with a secret weapon.
What?
Someone you've been
looking for, I think.
A scanner.
Calls himself Cameron Vale.
I've seen him.
and Ruth knew exactly
where to find him.
He's in indoctrination right now.
Can he do anything?
What kind of shape is he in?
He seems to function...
But he's nothing to worry about.
He's weak.
Very weak.
Welcome to our
little psychic gymnasium.
Cameron Vale...
You'll please meet...
Yoga master Dieter Tautz.
Mr. Tautz has kindly consented
to be your psychic
sparring partner.
He has publicly demonstrated
on many occasions
that by the power of his will.
He can control his heart rate,
his alpha-wave rhythm,
and many other supposedly
uncontrollable functions
of the human body.
Are we ready?
Just about.
Proceed.
If you would be
kind enough to sit
facing this gentleman here.
I want you...
I want you to...
slowly release your scan.
Slowly, with focus.
I want it to touch his heart
but not his brain.
You understand?
Telepathy is not mind reading.
It is the direct linking
of 2 nervous systems
separated by space.
I want you to make a link...
from your brain...
to his heart.
I want your brain
to make his heart...
beat fast.
Now, if his heart
beats too quickly...
then he will take over
control of his heart...
and slow it down.
Don't worry about it.
All you have to do...
is make his heart...
beat...
fast.
Fast.
Now.
Fast. Faster.
Fast.
Fast!
End your scan.
End it!
Stop!
Stop him!
End it!
You were right, Dr. Ruth.
It was easy.
This man's name is...
Benjamin Pierce.
And these photographs
were taken in a prison
for the criminally insane.
Here's another one.
This is a plaster cast of him
at present on display
at the acrostic art galley.
He's our only lead,
a known scanner
who may or may not be part
of Revok's underground.
Why was he in prison?
He tried to kill his entire family.
His father, sister, mother...
At the age of 10.
It was in 1958.
A few years later, he was released.
What do they say here?
'Rehabilitation through art.'
The man has incredible power,
doesn't he?
Power?
Yes, he does.
I am Arno Crostic.
I'm pleased you came
to my gallery.
Are you an aficionado
of Benjamin Pierce?
I'm interested in buying this
piece for my apartment in Paris.
Yes?
But I don't think
it'll work out unless
I can get to meet the artist first.
I'm afraid no.
I hope it won't prejudice you
against acquiring this piece,
but I would lose
Benjamin Pierce for good
if I even approached him
with the idea.
You see, it's pair
of our agreement.
He will not meet
his public.
Maybe you could just
tell me where he lives.
Then I could approach him myself,
and you wouldn't be involved.
I'm afraid I can't.
Then maybe you could just...
think about...
where he lives.
Excuse me.
I'm suddenly...
feeling ill.
Arno, what's the matter?
- Are you all right?
- I will be all right.
Come on, Arno.
Let me take you back
to your office.
You've got to lie down.
That's it. Take me arm.
Benjamin Pierce?
Why don't you leave me alone?
I need some help.
You're the only one
that can give it to me.
Is that right?
Me?
Yes.
Then I think you're
in big trouble, chum.
I've heard you know a man
named Darry Revok.
Who are you?
I was told you were coming
to pay me a visit, Mr. Vale.
How did you know that?
Well...
I have friends.
I don't want them...
but I have them.
Scanner friends?
What do you mean by that?
I am one of you.
- You're one of me.
- Yes.
You know what I think?
I think you better tell me
what you really want.
It's the voices in my head.
They're driving me crazy.
How do you stop them?
Your voices.
My art.
My art keeps me sane.
Sane.
I don't have anything like this.
That's why I have
to find Darryl Revok.
You...
my friend...
are a liar.
Get out.
Look, I'm not leaving here
until you tell me
where I can find Darryl Revok.
No?
All right.
Well, then I'll get out.
No!
Find Revok.
These are his robots...
killers.
He'll turn you
into a zombie,
a robot,
a killer.
No, don't you let him.
There are others.
Other scanners.
Kim Obrist.
Good evening, sir.
Can I help you?
Are there any messages for me?
Your name, sir?
Cameron Vale.
Your room number?
802.
Yes, this package is for you, sir.
My name is Cameron Vale.
I've got to talk to Kim Obrist.
Come on in.
Oh, God.
They killed Ben Pierce.
Yes.
Come on upstairs.
Just wait here a sec.
Kim, Revoc got to Ben Pierce.
He's dead.
This guy's name
is Cameron Vale.
I scanned him.
He's for real.
He was there when it happened.
Sit down.
I know you.
You were at the gallery.
You were looking for Pierce.
I need help.
Scan together.
Scan together
and our minds will begin
to flow into each other
until they become one.
One nervous system.
One soul.
One experience.
Beautiful.
And frightening.
So frightening to lose yourself.
So frightening
to lose yourself.
To lose your will
to the group will.
To lose yourself
to the group self.
...to the group self.
No!
The power.
The power we can generate
we web focus our scans
together is fantastic.
Fantastic.
Terrifying.
Exhilarating.
No! Around the side!
Quick!
Hurry!
Get in!
Let's go! Come on!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org