Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
And 12 midgets.
12 spinning midgets.
That was as great
as I imagined it would be.
You look beautiful.
And pensive.
No, not pensive.
Just confused.
Women after lovemaking,
it's always so complicated.
Hey, I love your aftershave.
What is it?
It's Yardley.
I first used it when I was 16
and never changed.
I'm a very loyal soul.
Come here.
Do you have to put them on?
Well, they're quite sexy.
God, what makes
you smell so sweet?
Oh, you like it?
Just some fragrance.
Right.
Where are you going?
I have an idea.
I think it's time to celebrate
with some champagne.
I want you to stay.
I make a mean scrambled egg.
Stay.
That's my mother.
Oh, she's very attractive.
Yes, she was very beautiful,
but quite difficult.
Difficult?
How?
Unfaithful.
Say, can you please stay?
Nothing would
please me more. Come on.
I really can't.
Oh, why not?
My father.
He's feeling not that great.
Nothing serious?
No, no, nothing.
Just a tooth problem.
You know,
a little sensitivity
in lower seven.
I really should go.
Oh. So, let me
get back to the story.
I'm on stage.
I'm doing the
dematerializer trick
with this chick
from Manchester.
I don't know
where they get these people,
but she looked like
Sitting Bull.
And I got her in the thing,
and I vanish her
and everything
goes according to plan
exactly and she's gone.
And suddenly,
Strombel appears.
What?
Yes, Strombel's in there!
I got a tremendous hand
from the audience.
I wish
I could do it every night!
What did he say?
He gave me
the combination to a safe.
What safe, I have no idea.
I didn't see any safe.
Well, did you
accomplish anything besides
maybe a possible pregnancy?
I'll tell you what I did see.
His mother, Lady Eleanor,
has short-cut, brunette hair.
Yeah,
but not a hooker?
No, Sidney,
she's not a hooker!
I hardly think so.
She's practically royalty.
Christ,
you amaze me sometimes.
Your brain!
Back off. You know,
you're getting so upset.
I'm just trying
to figure out
the various ramifications.
I just don't like
this whole thing!
I feel disgusting,
all right, it's awful.
I don't like
the whole process.
Yeah, you want to think
he's innocent.
What's so bad about that, huh?
Jesus, this guy
must be some lover, you know.
I mean, all of a sudden
you're ready to dump
the whole story.
I must find out
what breakfast cereal he eats.
What am I talking about?
There's a combination
on the door
where he keeps his precious
musical instruments.
Okay,
so there is a combination!
I just got
to get in that room.
Do you have the combination?
We're not gonna break
into his room if that's
what you're thinking.
You gotta have the com...
I got to get in there.
No, no.
No, no, we're not
going to do this because
it's not legal... You...
Sondra, what's wrong with you?
This guy is
the son of a Lord!
They'll take us to
the Tower of London
and behead us!
Hi.
Guess what?
What?
Peter Lyman sent you flowers.
I assume your name
is Jade Spence?
Naturally I accepted for you.
Yeah, I'm Jade Spence.
What is going on?
Oh, Vivian...
Oh,
Peter's giving a party
on Saturday and
he wants me to come.
I... Oh, I guess
I'll have to buy a dress.
Well, he certainly
seems smitten with you.
If he's smitten with anyone,
it's Jade Spence.
Who is Jade Spence?
A would-be
investigative reporter
who's falling in love
with the object
of her investigation.
Of course we did.
Absolutely.
God bless you, sir.
I'm going to show you
a little thing.
I want you
to think of a card. Just think
of one of those cards.
Any one you want.
You got it?
All right, now, are you
happening to be thinking
of the seven of spades?
That's amazing!
How do you do that?
Just a little hobby of mine.
You know, I wish
I had more time to practice,
but, what with my oil wells,
you know, I never
get around to it.
Your daughter's
very beautiful.
You met my daughter?
Yes.
Yes, we're very proud of her.
She's a lovely girl.
Overcame a great handicap.
Yeah. You know, she was
learning disabled.
Her mother and I took
her to many specialists,
you know.
Now she's practically normal,
She's a charmer.
God bless you, sweetheart.
What is your sign?
I'm an Aquarian.
You're Aquarian?
And what is your persuasion?
Do you mean my religion?
Yeah, your persuasion.
I'm a Christian. What are you?
Yes, are you?
Me, I was born into
the Hebrew persuasion,
but, when I got older,
I converted to narcissism.
Dad?
Hmm?
Dad, I need
to talk to you right now.
Oh, I was just about
to pull some quarters
out of Mrs. Quincy's nose.
Right now.
I need to talk to you.
Really?
Yep.
Excuse me. I'll...
Where?
Would you stop doing
those nitwit tricks?
What is wrong with you?
You're supposed to be
a dignified businessman.
I told them it was a hobby.
The hobby of a rich merchant.
You know, so...
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Go down the stairs,
open the music room door.
I'll keep Peter busy.
I'll meet you down there
in a minute. You brought
the combination, right?
No, I left it
in my other jacket.
What?
Yes. And...
So, what are we gonna do?
You gotta go home
and get it then.
I can't get it
because the other
jacket's in the cleaners.
Sidney.
This is the problem
having a limited wardrobe.
But not to worry.
I have a mnemonic system.
I remember everything.
There you are. Mr. Spence,
trust you're having
a good time?
Yes,
a great time! This
reminds me of our party.
We threw a masked ball in
Palm Beach this year,
it was wonderful.
I came as a harlequin.
She dressed as Petunia Pig.
Honey, there's something
I wanted to ask you about.
Absolutely.
That was a mask, wasn't it?
Just... I love her.
Just a minute, okay?
Do you need a drink,
Mr. Spence?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
It's eight
blue horses.
No, no, no.
It's 10.
Ten spinning midgets.
No, it's 12.
Twelve jet planes
and eight... No.
Good to see you.
Have a nice time.
Nice to meet you.
Calm down, calm down.
It was... It was...
It was...
Eight maids a-milking
and three French hens.
No, no.
Sixteen, wait, 20 jet planes,
12 spinning midgets.
Eureka!
I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna
use the bathroom.
Sidney?
Sidney, is that you?
I'm locked in!
Oh, Christ...
What's the combination?
For some reason,
it's gone out of my mind.
Did you see Miss Spence?
I thought I saw her
going downstairs.
Downstairs, right.
It's
16 blue horses.
It's 21 jet planes.
And 12 midgets.
Twelve spinning midgets.
Oh, thank God!
I thought
I was gonna turn out to be
one of those skeletons
people find
when they sell the house.
Check the door.
Sixteen, 21, 12.
You couldn't remember
that number?
My mnemonic system failed me.
What do you want me to say?
Now exactly
what are we looking for
in here? This is all...
I'm not really sure.
You're not sure?
Well, you know,
don't break anything.
By God, we'll get caught
and God knows.
Hey, you know
the old dirty joke
about how
the French horn player
sleeps with his wife at night?
Sidney,
put that thing down!
Will you excuse me?
There's nothing
but musical instruments
in here.
I'm telling you,
we're on a wild goose chase.
Believe me.
Jade?
What's the matter?
Did you hear that?
I thought I heard something.
Oh, come on, come on.
Let's get out of here.
All we need
is to get caught in here.
Jade?
Ah, there you are.
I was searching for you.
The guests
will be leaving soon.
Yes, well, I was
just showing Father around.
He loves English homes.
Yes, I was very impressed
with your cellar.
I have
a wonderful cellar myself.
No wine,
but it's rodent free.
Well,
let's get a drink.
Please, Mr. Spence,
I haven't seen you
with a drink all night.
Can you stay the night,
please?
What?
Come on.
No, I can't.
Why not?
My father.
Oh, come on, I'll have
my driver take him home.
No.
I can't let you go.
You're too beautiful.
Look at you. I can't.
Jade?
Oh.
Jade.
Jade, it's 4:00 a.m.
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep,
so I thought
maybe some milk.
Hmm.
Jade, can I ask you something?
Mmm-hmm.
Would you consider
not going home at the end
of the summer?
I don't understand,
what more proof do you need?
What are you gonna tell
the police?
The guy
owns a deck of Tarot cards.
That's not a crime.
I mean, what, he was late
for a poker game?
I'm sure he's smart enough
to have an alibi.
What are we left with?
His mother has
short-cut, brunette hair.
I mean, look,
if we blow the whistle
on this guy...
I know. I understand.
...and he's innocent
and we can't make the story...
Then he realizes
that you're, you know,
you're a pushy little phony
who's been playing him
for a sucker
and he dumps you,
you know. I get it.
All right. All I'm saying,
is that in order to make
an accusation,
we gotta have proof.
Especially
about Lord Lyman's son.
You don't make an accusation.
We can phone in
an anonymous tip.
You know how many crank tips
the papers say the police get?
You're gonna phone one in
on Peter Lyman!
They'll hang up on you
mid-sentence.
Besides,
if the story's true,
I want to be the one
to break it.
You know
what Joe Strombel said?
He said,
"Get it first,
but first get it right."
Happy birthday.
Wow, thank you.
What's up?
You look so sullen.
No, I'm not. I just...
I get sad around birthdays.
Oh, yes, well,
I can understand that,
but I think we're both
still young enough
to enjoy the gifts.
Come on, open it.
Okay.
Oh, wow, it's beautiful.
You like it?
I love it.
Good. Here, allow me.
Gosh.
You shouldn't have.
I wanted to.
Hey, hey,
are you crying?
No, I'm too tough to cry.
Oh.
Though my nasal passages
do become congested
when I'm sad.
Oh, don't be sad.
It's your birthday. Hmm?
Oh, I wish I could
celebrate with you tonight.
I just have to go out of town
for a few days.
Really?
Yes, I just have
some business to take care of.
But we'll celebrate
when I get back, all right?
Okay.
Thank you so much
for the present.
It's beautiful.
I'll think about you
whenever I wear it.
You didn't tell me
it was your birthday!
I'll take you
for a magnificent dinner.
We'll go
to a great restaurant.
Really?
Do you enjoy
the McNuggets thing?
What about Indian food?
Do you like spicy food?
No, no, it's okay.
I don't really have
much of an appetite.
But you will when
they bring out the prawns
in hydrochloric acid.
It's fantastic, Sondra.
What's the matter?
What,
are you thinking of Peter?
No.
I don't know, it's just...
I wouldn't be surprised
if he asked me to marry him
one day, you know?
You come
from an Orthodox family.
Would they accept
a serial killer?
That's an expensive present.
The Lymans are so wealthy.
Yes.
It was almost
too extravagant.
I'd better get ready.
I still haven't found
my millionaire yet.
Oh, God, Sondra, what a mess!
It's starting to add up
against him.
Bits and scraps
are coming together.
God, it's you!
I sensed
you were falling in love.
I escaped again.
It's just circumstantial junk,
you know. A coincidence
here and there.
Too much smoke
not to be fire.
Look, I'm sure
you've been wrong
plenty of times.
Not wrong here.
Though I agree
you haven't got enough
to pull the trigger yet.
If you act prematurely,
not only does he walk,
your professional credibility
is wrecked,
sometimes for good.
Oh, I'm sure you want him
to be guilty.
You know, that way you get
your last big scoop.
I'm beginning to fade.
Sondra, don't let me down!
I wish you'd fade for good!
Get out of my life!
I'm not
cut out for this.
I should be
flossing molars for a living.
The bread is... You know,
I can make a meal
just with the bread.
I can do a whole meal,
just nothing but bread.
If I ate that much bread,
I'd be 20 pounds heavier.
See,
I never gain an ounce,
because, you know,
my anxiety acts like aerobics.
So I get the exercise.
Thanks for taking me out
for my birthday, Sidney.
Well, you know,
you're the daughter
that I never had.
Oh, that's so...
No, no, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
'Cause I never wanted
to have kids.
I didn't.
Because you have kids,
what is it?
You know, you're nice
to them, you bring
them up, you suffer,
you take care of them
and then they grow up
and they accuse you
of having Alzheimer's.
Could you
ever live in London?
Could I live
in London? No.
And I love London.
Don't get me wrong,
I love London,
but, you know,
apart from
the language problem,
I can't take the driving.
Because it, you know,
it's on the wrong side,
and I...
Every time
I drive a car here,
I'm convinced
I'm going to die in a crash.
Sidney!
What's the matter?
It's Peter.
You said
Peter was out of town.
Well, that's
what he told me.
Come on.
What do you mean, come on?
I ordered prawns.
Just pay, all right?
Just pay.
What do you mean, pay?
All I do is...
Fine, it's her birthday.
Come on.
Maybe he's got
another woman on the side,
and he likes you,
but he's sexually
attracted to her.
Thanks, Sidney.
Well, why doesn't he have
his chauffeur?
I don't know,
whatever he's doing,
he must want it to be secret.
Oh, I told you
he went the other way!
Can we go home, please?
It's starting to rain.
I can't believe
he lied to me.
Maybe he's doing
something that he's ashamed
to tell you about.
Maybe he belongs to
one of those clubs, or he's
a cross-dresser or something.
Or maybe
he does folk dancing.
Oh, I'm sure
it's probably something
that when he tells me,
I'll just feel foolish
for thinking he lied.
I'm sure. You know,
not everything in
this world is sinister.
You know,
just practically everything.
That Indian food
made me sick.
You hardly touched
your cobra salad.
How can you be sick?
Help!
A woman's been strangled!
Help, call the police!
Somebody call the police!
There's been a murder!
There's been
a murder upstairs.
Help!
Have you got a phone?
Call the police.
Could it be the Tarot Killer?
They found a Tarot card.
It's him.
I can't believe it!
She lives in this building.
It's him again.
They found the Tarot card.
Elizabeth Gibson,
another short-haired brunette.
We should have
gone to the police earlier.
Well, you know...
You said that they
wouldn't believe us
and they may not.
Sidney, it's about time
we show my story to
a real newspaperman.
By real, you mean what?
One that's living.
Vivian's father has a friend
that works at The Observer.
Well, it's very vivid
and rather shocking,
and there are some
genuine circumstantial
bits of evidence.
But let me give you a lesson
in professional journalism.
No newspaper should
or would ever run this story.
What? Why?
It would be
fatally irresponsible
and libelous.
All you have here
are a number
of titillating speculations.
Flamboyant theories that
tarnish a man, and a
well-known figure at that,
without a single shred
of substantial proof.
So his mother
was a short-haired brunette.
So he came late
for a poker game
and said he was going away
on a business trip
and he got caught lying.
Yes, but who keeps
a Tarot deck under
a French horn?
It's not against the law
to own a Tarot deck,
or keep it wherever you like.
You'd look
pretty foolish in court
with your accusations,
and that's
where you'll wind up.
Because he'd have no choice
but to sue you
and the newspaper,
and he'd win.
And to go to the police?
I'll come to that.
But first let me
continue my tedious
professorial lecture.
Vivian's dad and I
go way back.
He said you were
a journalism student.
Hmm.
You talk about getting a tip.
Okay, you won't
disclose your source,
but what you have done
is let your imagination
run wild.
No, no.
What if I told you
that my source happened
to be a certain Joe Strombel?
The late Joe Strombel?
Yep.
You mean, before he died
he gave a student reporter
a major story
and didn't follow
it up himself?
We didn't say
it was before he died.
What?
No, it...
He got the story
before he died,
and then he died
before he could follow it up.
Well,
why did he give it to you?
He didn't know he was dying.
I don't buy it.
I knew Joe Strombel well.
If he'd had a tip
that he considered reliable,
he would certainly
have pursued it himself,
from the grave,
if necessary.
What about how Peter
was in the neighborhood
the night
the murder was committed?
I realize as a student
how exciting it must have been
to think that you were onto
something so spectacular.
Hey, she is onto something!
This kid is a bloodhound.
Look at her!
She could sell the story
to any tabloid in town.
Hmm.
Now that I've preached
on the realities
of accurate reporting,
I want to tell you
how catastrophic
for everybody involved
it would have been
if you had, say, taken
the results
of your investigation
to a tabloid.
Today, the police
have apprehended
the Tarot Card Serial Killer.
And it most assuredly
is not Peter Lyman.
What?
Every paper in town
is going to press
with it as we speak.
It was a handyman
named Henry Banks
who has confessed.
Banks is a delusional paranoid
who's given Scotland Yard
information
that only the killer
could possibly know.
He's led the police
to two additional bodies
and his DNA
and a fingerprint
they found check out.
I know
this puts a crimp
in your scoop,
but Henry Banks is
the Tarot Card Serial Killer.
Not Lord Lyman's son.
Well, I can't say
I'm not walking on air.
Oh, Jesus, If I ever catch
that Joe Strombel,
I'll kill him.
I only hope
Peter forgives me
for what I've done.
For what?
I lied to him.
I'm not Jade Spence.
I'm a pushy,
duplicitous, ambitious
college student.
I lied to him,
over and over.
Darling, he lied to you, too,
so it's even.
His lies pale in comparison
to the enormity
of what I've done.
So marry him
as Jade Spence.
Don't tell him.
You know,
you don't have to be
Sondra Pransky ever again.
Marry him as Jade Spence.
Yeah, but I don't want to
have to get you a
Father's Day gift every year.
You know, I don't know how to
break this to you, honey,
but you were adopted. Okay?
Your mother and I,
we were at the orphanage,
we wanted
a handicapped child, and...
Ah, finally.
Just you and I all weekend.
Yeah.
I thought you'd like it here.
It's lovely.
Mmm-hmm.
Peter?
Yes.
I have
a confession to make.
Oh, God, so do I.
Oh, well, let me go first.
Actually, no,
let me, please,
because mine's
been bothering me all day.
I just want
to get it off my chest.
When I told you I was
going away for a few days
on business,
I was lying.
I know.
You know? How?
Oh, I saw you.
You saw me? No.
I was at dinner, and...
With your father?
Actually...
Well, anyway,
it doesn't matter. Really.
The truth is,
that a company my father owns
is about to merge
with a company
in the Middle East.
It's a very
sensitive situation,
and the less
anyone knows about it,
the better.
And we just didn't want
the press to sniff it out.
I mean,
that's no excuse, really.
I'm just very sorry
for the extreme secrecy.
No, no, no, it's fine.
I'm glad.
It's your own
secret information.
That's fine.
So your father took you out
for a birthday dinner
and you saw me.
I mean, how unnerving.
God, I mean, the thing
I hate most in the world
is lying.
Uh-huh.
What?
Peter...
Yes, Jade?
Oh, yes.
What did you want to tell me?
Uh...
Jade, there's nothing
you can tell me that...
My name is not Jade Spence.
It's not?
No. It's Sondra Pransky.
And my father
is not my father.
His name is Sidney Waterman.
He's a magician
called Splendini.
I'm a journalism student.
Don't ask me
what kind of crazy
misinformation we received
to believe you might be
the Tarot Card Killer.
I mean,
I didn't know you
at this time. Remember?
And, of course,
as soon as I got to know you,
I knew that
it couldn't possibly be true.
And the police have him now,
so everything's fine.
Of course,
along the route
I fell for you,
and now
I totally blew it, and...
Who told you this?
Oh, a newspaperman.
He's now deceased.
Very foolish.
He was eager
for his last scoop.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I just
totally understand
if you never want to
speak to me again
or if you
don't want to see me...
Miss Pransky.
Not only am I
not angry with you, but you...
You've
absolutely made my day!
What?
Just suspecting
that I could be such
an imaginative,
dramatic fiend.
I love it.
You do?
Yes.
I think it's one of the
funniest, craziest things
I've ever heard in my life.
I can't wait
to tell the chaps
at the club.
Peter?
Yes, darling.
I have to ask you something.
Yes, anything. Absolutely.
Why did you hide
that Tarot deck
in your music room?
How do you
know about that?
I was so paranoid. I...
It's crazy.
But I snuck in.
Oh, dear, it was going to be
a surprise.
I bought them for you.
They're Victorian Tarot cards.
You told me
you were into
that kind of thing.
What? Oh...
It was gonna be
a gift for you.
Oh, you're so...
I feel like such an idiot!
Darling, no, no, no,
never mind, never mind.
What a shame.
Let's forget about it.
No...
Huh? Let's just...
Now that we've confessed
our sins, let's move on
with our lives, huh?
Really?
Yeah. I want to hear
all about the real you.
And I assure you in advance,
I'll love it.
Oh, God,
you snuck into
my music room, did you?
So the reason
why he was skulking around,
was 'cause he had
this private family business
which is too delicate
to discuss, actually.
Sorry, I don't buy it.
What?
The man
is a liar and a murderer.
And I say that
with all due respect.
Sidney.
Child, I know
what I'm talking about.
Don't call me that, all right?
Do you remember
when we were out
on the estate,
I found a clue,
you thought I was nuts?
I thought you were nuts
so many times I can't
recall the exact one.
Do you remember this?
Do you remember this
little item? This clue?
Yes, Betty G.
Now, I checked
all the girls
that were murdered.
The one that was killed
the night we saw Peter
on the street, was named
Elizabeth Gibson.
So?
So Betty
is short for Elizabeth
a lot of times.
Oh, come on, Sidney.
That's a real stretch.
You're reaching now.
Look, supposing you wanted
to rub somebody out
and not get caught.
Nobody wants
to get caught, Sidney.
Look,
he wants to get rid of
Elizabeth Gibson.
Betty Gibson. Betty Gibson.
So, there's
a series of murders
with a guy that's got
a real style. A Tarot card.
They said
he was a total maniac.
He buys a Tarot deck
and let's say he hides it.
Hypothetically,
he hides it, let's say,
in a music room.
Let's say he hides it in,
let's say, a French horn.
Oh, Sidney.
In a French horn!
I'm losing patience with you.
I'm not saying the guy
did all the murders.
I'm saying that he just did
Elizabeth Gibson,
then folded it into the series
of the Tarot Killer
so he wouldn't get caught.
Henry Banks
confessed to all the murders.
Henry Banks is deranged!
He hallucinates!
My God.
Henry... And you know
those guys like to brag
when they get caught.
Henry Banks, you know...
Where are you going? The cops
will dump every unsolved
murder on Henry Banks.
They haven't
caught anybody in years.
Peter wouldn't hurt a fly.
Oh, really?
What about a fly who speaks?
What?
Yes.
Why would Peter
kill a prostitute?
Because it looks terrible
on his resume.
Who knows what kind of
sordid life this guy has?
Have you
completely lost your mind?
What is wrong with you?
Peter being
blackmailed by a prostitute?
It's ridiculous.
What are you putting
in your Metamucil?
You know...
Where are you going?
You don't understand!
It would kill his reputation!
Oh, can you bring
the water out?
Can I say one thing?
Can I just tell you one thing?
Joe Strombel
would not agree with you.
I don't want to talk about
Joe Strombel, all right?
Even a great reporter
can be wrong.
But he's not wrong.
Blackmail.
I see it all over.
You are a cynical
crapehanger
who always sees the glass
half-empty!
No, you're wrong.
I see the glass half-full,
but of poison.
And you're gonna wind up
drinking it!
You don't know anything.
You don't have a reporter's
instincts, okay?
You're some guy
who vanishes silk
handkerchiefs
and cuts
people's neckties off.
Do everybody a favor.
Go back to your card tricks,
all right?
Did you tell her?
I did. I told her.
And I made it seem
as though it all suddenly
just came to me.
I know I'm right.
She just won't listen to me.
She hates me.
Yeah. I...
You know,
sometimes, I got to say,
I worry about that girl.
I don't think
I'll be seeing you anymore.
Well, if there's a scoop
to be had here,
she's going
to get it for you.
You can only cheat death
so many times,
and I've used
every trick I know.
You look after her.
She's a decent kid.
And check
his Tarot deck.
See if a card's missing.
I'm a reporter.
I'm doing a story
on Elizabeth Gibson,
and I know she lived here.
I didn't know her.
I hardly ever saw her
come and go. She was quiet.
All right.
I knew
what she did for a living.
But whether she used to
entertain her clients here,
or not, I couldn't say.
Oh,
excuse me. I'm a reporter.
And I'm doing a story
about Elizabeth Gibson.
If there's any comments,
anything you know
about her that I...
What paper?
What paper are you from?
The Washington Post.
I'm one of the top reporters
on the...
Did you see
All the President's Men?
I was the short guy.
Why is an American paper
interested in this?
No, no, we are, we are.
We're doing a big story.
The Travel and Leisure section
is doing a big spread
on places
to avoid like the plague.
And so, I'm...
I'll make it
very worth your while,
you know and...
All right, all right,
all right. I knew
Betty Gibson.
Mmm-hmm,
and she was very tough.
But I don't think
that she deserved to die.
Did you say Betty Gibson?
Everyone called her Betty.
That was her name.
Really?
And did you know any
of her clients at all?
I mean, she knew
millions of men, didn't she?
She was very sexy.
You know.
Not that you'd know
that from those pictures.
She used to be a really
pretty baby-faced blonde.
You know,
the sort men go nuts for.
A blonde? But in the paper...
The pictures in the paper...
Oh, no, I know, I know.
She made the mistake
of cutting it off
and dyeing it black.
God knows why.
Maybe it's to please
one of her regulars.
She had steady clients?
Well, yeah, one for sure.
Look, these guys
never use their
real names, okay?
But there was
this one rich kid
that she saw a lot.
And his name was Peter.
Peter what?
Peter...
Peter Yardley. Peter Yardley?
Yardley. Yardley.
Hello?
Hello, this is Mr. Spence.
Sid.
Sid Waterman Spence.
This is Sid Waterman Spence.
Where have I called?
Oh, hello, Sidney.
It's Peter Lyman.
Sondra and I
are spending the weekend
at my father's country house.
You could have come.
That's okay. She gave me
this number to call.
May I speak with her?
Yes, one second.
Hi, Sidney.
Listen,
I got a treasure trove
of information here.
I just was snooping with...
On Elizabeth Gibson.
She's called Betty. Betty!
She's called Betty.
And she had some kind of
a long relationship...
A special relationship
with some young guy, Peter.
The last name
doesn't click,
but I'm sure it's the same.
This is crazy.
Look, stop making trouble,
Sidney. The case is closed.
Listen, this thing adds up.
You're alone up there with
a very, very dangerous man.
That's two verys.
You got to get back to town
right away.
Sidney, if I thought there was
a shred of proof,
I would never let
my personal feelings
get involved, all right?
The truth is,
I'm crazy about the guy.
I can't keep obsessing
over tantalizing
conspiracy theories.
You know, I'm sure
that he killed her
and made it look
like a Tarot killing.
You know,
you don't see it because
you got stars in your eyes.
Look, I don't...
This is crazy! I don't want
to talk about this anymore.
It's too upsetting for me,
all right?
Let me have my nice weekend.
I'll talk to you
when I get back.
Stop putting
these paranoid thoughts
in my head!
Is Sidney okay?
Yes, yes.
You know, I love Sidney,
I really do,
but he's just...
He's got a part missing,
you know, he's crazy!
Yes, really?
Mmm-hmm.
Like what?
We'll talk about it later.
Let me change, okay?
Mmm-Hmm.
Yes? Oh, yes, sir.
Yes. My daughter
is in the country
with Mr. Lyman.
And I'm gonna
be driving up there later
and she asked me
if I could pick up her red
cashmere sweater. She thinks
she left it upstairs.
Red cashmere?
Yes, it's a red sweater.
It's a kind of a red,
tomato red,
like a fire engine.
A red. A rouge.
I understand, sir. Red.
Yes, yes.
I'll see if I can find it.
Sir?
Oh, I was just
checking out the Stradivarius.
I play a few pieces myself
on the violin. Prokofiev
and Bartok, the Hot Canary...
But Mr. Lyman is the
only person to have the
combination to that room.
Yes, but he wanted
to share it with me
because, you know,
in case something happened,
you know,
life is very capricious.
A stroke, a sudden embolism
or lightning...
You know I...
Darling, I love you.
I mean that sincerely.
You're a wonderful woman,
you're a tremendous servant
and a credit to your race.
And I mean that. From
the bottom of my heart
I say that to you.
I notice you didn't
get the red sweater.
She probably left it
in another bedroom.
You know,
she's got a little problem
with promiscuity.
But...
So, I'll be going.
I'll call you.
We'll have lunch.
Mr. Lyman, sir, Mr. Spence
has been here and he's
been into the music room.
What do you mean?
A most unusual
sequence of events.
Mr. Spence came by
looking for his
daughter's sweater.
Said she'd requested it.
Next thing I knew,
he was in the music room.
Sir, I think
he'd been drinking,
from his behavior.
Yes, yes.
Yes. Okay, Margaret,
thank you. Goodbye.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Yes, it will be.
It's so nice
to be out here with you,
just away
from the rest of the world
and...
Hmm.
Yes, I often
come out here to read and,
well, and fish.
There's trout in the lake.
What are you thinking about?
You really want to know?
Yes.
Just how ironic life is,
and tragic.
Why?
Well, that I met you
by rescuing you from drowning
and found you
totally enchanting
and now we've come full cycle
and, alas, you're going
to have to drown.
What?
Oh, I imagine by now
Sidney's confirmed
that I killed Betty Gibson.
I mean, in my own defense,
there really was
no other way out.
At first I managed
to hide my identity from her,
but I saw her too many times
over the years
and she learned who I was,
and...
Well, it became
a constant demand for money
and I just
could not let that go on,
could I?
I mean, my whole life
and career
would be
just hostage to her
moods at all times.
So, I studied
the Tarot case,
I rehearsed my plan,
and, well, you know the rest.
If you do something to me,
Sidney's gonna find out!
He'll tell someone.
No, no, no.
You see, you will go
in a boating accident,
and Sidney will go
later tonight.
No one knows
of your relationship with him,
because, after all,
you're not actually father
and daughter, are you?
And no one will think twice
to investigate the death
of some obscure vaud...
Are you listening?
No one will think twice
to investigate the death
of some obscure vaudevillian
called Splendini, who is
really a stranger to me.
Help!
Help! Someone help me!
Yes, very quiet, isn't it?
This is the advantage
of a private lake.
Get off me!
Come...
Yes, police.
Yes, this is Peter Lyman.
I need the police immediately.
At the Lyman estate.
There's been
a terrible boating accident.
A woman has drowned.
It's awful.
Please come right away.
Thank you. Thank you.
They think they know
where the body is.
I'm so sorry, sir.
When last I saw her,
she...
She just said she wanted
to go out there to
communicate with nature.
Just to think
she wanted some
peace and quiet and...
She wasn't depressed,
or anything like that,
was she, sir?
God, no. No.
I mean, unless she was
keeping it from me.
You heard no cries for help?
No! No,
I was listening to music
in here, damn it.
It's just so ironic.
Because the way
I first met her
I rescued her
from drowning
in our club pool.
And she was a very,
very weak swimmer.
Hello?
I was faking it at the pool
to get your attention.
Actually, I used to be
captain of the Brooklyn
Community Swim Team.
Fascinating observation.
Lyman lost a cufflink
at the flat of a prostitute,
who was later killed
by the Tarot Card Killer.
Well, this upright chap
certainly enjoyed patronizing
some dodgy women.
Unfortunately
for Elizabeth Gibson,
she elected to blackmail him.
It's a beautifully
written story
and one of the best bits
of investigative journalism
in a long time.
And this paper
is proud to run it.
Oh, I have to
share the credit
with Joe Strombel.
An inspiration,
who taught me more
than I could ever
explain to anyone.
And to the late
Sidney Waterman.
Splendini.
A nice guy who helped out
with the investigation
and without whom
I never could have made it.
Sidney, wherever you are,
I'll never forget you.
How did you get here?
Me?
I couldn't get used to driving
on the goddamn wrong
side of the street!
You know,
I was driving up
to the country,
and in the United States,
I would have been a hero.
I would have saved her.
I would have...
But here, you know...
That's the one drawback
of living in London.
Granted, the theater's better,
there's many good
Indian restaurants.
Well, what did you do?
What do I do?
I'm Splendini. Magician.
Would you like
to see something?
Oh, yes, please.
Do we have time
for a card trick?
Yes.
I believe we have eternity.
I'm going to show you
a little trick now.
I just want to say
from the bottom of my heart,
I mean this sincerely...
I say this
with all due respect.
You are a wonderful group and
a fantastic group of people.
I love you and I feel that
coming back from you.
And you may be deceased,
but you should not
be discouraged.
Because, you know...
Don't think of being dead
as a handicap.
You know,
when I was a child,
I stuttered.
But with stick-to-it-iveness
and perseverance,
you know, you can never tell
what could happen.
Now, I want you
to take a card, Alma.
Go ahead,
take any card you want.
Just pick it. Pick it.
Go ahead, sweetheart.
I love you, sweetheart.
That's fantastic.
Split & Resynck: Xenzai[NEF]
--- --- Norsk Esel Forum --- ---
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org