Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Downloaded From www.moviesubtitles.org
A place like east, give you a
knife, fork and tablespoon.
Wrapped in a napkin,
two of them are used.
Most of coffees
they don't put the tablespoon.
To the small one they put it in the washing machine
of plates time and again.
Unconscious of value.
Not alone it passes the creatures of stories
but also to the objects.
there will be amusement in the chat tonight.
Him these making again.
That curious thing and seductora with the look.
Not it is unpleasant.
But you should know that recently
I left a bad relationship so...
I have just come out of bad several relationships.
I promise not to fall in love of
you if your you promise the same thing.
I promise it.
Favorite singer,
1, 2, 3.
- Cats Cradle.
Where he/she was born,
1, 2, 3.
- Nashville Skylight.
The movie but comic,
1, 2, 3.
- Hot summer.
- Cadyshack.
Types in dresses that original.
A woman to which he likes Cadyshack.
Why non habira of liking me?
All those feelings returned.
Then the third desire came,
I said that he/she wanted an alabaza head.
Clear, taenia in the list Dra. Mir...
but this serious but that a romance.
But that alone to be with somebody.
This serious love,
why to hurry the sex?
The whole day people take out
the cars of the front.
This bastard poor person of the mean
it has not been played in months.
- It is tragic.
- If, it is it.
You say that you look for ideas
for an infantile book,
how's it going these inanimate objects?
The tablespoon that you/they never use.
The lost stocking that you
it gathers with their lost twin.
The multireproductor of disks that
it is sadly out before
of finishing the cds.
- That is.
- It is this way.
Roderick.
I have looked for you all my life.
You are the best!
Salt.
That kiss confused me but there is not
anything a warm kiss after
a homemade delicious dinner.
Congratulations for the chef.
I was in the kitchen and the chef
he/she also believes that you are grandiose.
I sit down it, this is not...
- This well, alone you relax yourself.
- No, Roderick.
I adore you, seriously that if, alone I am
tangled with regard to the sex.
- This well.
- You are comely.
Very much if you want to know it.
It is alone that you remind me a lot
to the type with the one that my he/she suckles it left
after the divorce, it was not same
to you but it was a crossing entity your
and Bam Bam, of Picapiedra.
Not I am saying that never anything
it passed among us alone I say that...
If it is that it will happen.
It will happen.
- Truth?
- If.
Why to worry for that reason?
You are the best.
I will clean.
Your you can rent a movie,
something comic.
I suppose that one can say
that there I enter the madness.
Thank you, Miranda and I went to
retrospective wing of Fellini.
He/she said the but comic,
if it continued I live Goes him...
Did you already throw it to you?
Why the question?
- Did you already throw it to you?
Son, did you already throw it to you?
Allow me to tell them something, Miranda and me
we are building a
knot of trust and respect.
Pardon for even to believe that the love is something
but that a coalition of genital.
We have to discuss something.
- Shit.
- What does it happen?
Shit, shit.
Alone you hide me.
- Is there a half strange type?
- If, I already saw it.
I met him in a party of
poetry in Halloween.
Not I can believe that I went to bed with the one.
In halloween, 2 weeks ago?
I told you that it was tangled with the sex.
But that entangled these put to bed.
That is amusing,
we go to another part.
Bam Bam.
In the old times it was well
if a woman didn't go to bed with you.
For that was not as if him
he/she was making with somebody but
Where this the vixen of
Jane Austen when you need it?
I chose to remember the good times.
As Miranda me toward feeling
as if it was in only in the Earth.
That time that he/she read my report.
It is wonderful, seriously that if.
- But later in the lunch.
- How was your salad?
Wonderful, seriously that if.
CONDONE HE/SHE QUARRELS HE/SHE WANTS TO KNOW:
DID YOU ALREADY THROW IT TO YOU?
In conclusion, ahead, crucify me,
I refuse myself to live in a society
that it has reduced to the world in:
"Did you already throw it to you?"
- The answer is not.
Not I believe that you have seen it neither he/she undresses.
Wonderful, seriously that if.
Carajo!
Not I say that it won't happen
anything among us.
Dra. He/she looks...
That is, Dra. Mirabella Stones.
No!
Don't make fun, Miranda told me that
it had left a bad relationship
And nobody has never had gender
when leaving this way a relationship.
" We go very quick, I don't feel well"
If somebody wants to make it
with you, he/she will simply make it.
- The rest is empty data.
- That everything is, does one scheme?
No, it schemes it...
Clear, the wall has a connection.
I believe that it will be my death.
We go, cheer up, brother.
He/she looks at the kind side.
Although you went to a tropical island,
the 34 girls that are in the list.
they would go in jetskis to celebrate with you.
I don't like it, I don't want another
women, I want Miranda.
I have behaved well, it was something strange
at the beginning but I followed the current
sabotie the wedding, I lost the I deposit.
I played with the feelings of people
including me to myself and although
I don't care I, now if I care.
I found somebody that plays my heart.
And if they believe that the prediction...
- The love is sometimes but strong...
- No! It is not it!
I was so proud when
you buried the list in the patio.
Horoscopios, psychic, tarot letters,
attractions that predict the end.
Why should they know everything?
It is a good point, Sr. he/she remembers when
did he/she say that it schemes it a mystery it was?
It can have some flaw or something.
It is not of it schemes it, it is the progress,
he/she cannot make anything in this respect.
To the science and the logic
they don't care if we die.
Excuse.
My God, the solution was
before our the whole time
Which is it?
Sucks, God that good.
The sex is work,
"Will he/she be having a good time?"
and to think of their feelings
but with the alone suck you throw
and from time to time you play him/her
the nape if you believe that you this
putting lazy.
Seriously, if somebody offered a buffet
of coitus or a suck in a stick
he/she would take the suck.
They are sick.
I gave the heart to Miranda,
I want to have it in my arms
and to make him/her love feeling their to breathe.
Seriously you do believe that it would suck it to me?
Srta Nell has just put to sleep
to an entire fraternity in Ash-tree.
Death Nell? What is that they make another time?
It is the system, when a murderer in series
he/she has but of 10 you kill, they call each other.
I receive details.
seemingly it was the same one
fraternity that was forgiven
to sell the violation drug.
She put their own drug in the cake.
Does that entertain you Roderick?
I am revising my messages,
know-it-all schemes it this for
to receive another blow.
They love the concepts, the drawings.
They will publish it!
I owe you so much Rod.
Not there is way that we don't take place today,
I will be in your house at 8 o'clock.
It lists for the action.
I love you a lot.
- He/she is a very fortunate man...
- It is for their voice!
Not you need the list, she doesn't think of you...
I am for sure you sew very
important tonight they happened
Your penis in its vagina won't belong one to them.
But that the passes very well.
I would like to stay to talk but
I have an appointment with a lady.
Not I believe that he/she has seen it neither he/she undresses.
- Hello.
- Author.
Thank you that you/they eat excrement.
Lament so much to arrive late is
that it was a madness but I told them
to all that we would see them in the bar,
I invite, for the first time.
I thought that alone we would be
both, I made pasta
It is very sweet but we have to leave,
we are of celebration, my brother
and two Jessicas is already there
but it is not the great thing.
- He/she listens.
- Relax you.
Let us have a private party.
I thought that we had already overcome this.
No?
Miranda, you that you said that not
you were attracted to my but
that was before the trip,
before it lowered
the program of graphics to your laptop.
Why it is that the men believe that
the women are as thermometers
giants? every time that you/they make something
good for them, they put on but red
and but red and but and when we arrive
to the end, we have that follar.
That is not amusing!
- Shit.
- I sit down it.
Alone I will clean it.
Which are the words
that but they scare?
- " Let us be single friends"
It is like a bad comedy.
Alone that...
You know the difficult thing that it was for my to make
a true friend in the city?
He/she would die for you.
To who you believe that I dedicate him/her my book?
to my crazy parents?
To Roderick Blank, my friend.
Good celebration.
My God.
Shit that ugly celebration.
Your girlfriend finds out that her book
it will be published and...  it is terrible.
Not he/she was my girlfriend.
We are satisfied that the death
alone it has been an accident.
Alone?
Excuse, official wanted to give to Sr. Blank
the opportunity to say goodbye to their girlfriend
Not it is my...  can I be to alone with her?
My beautiful Miranda.
I never wanted this, alone he/she wanted.
They said that we would be never together.
But we will be the last in laughing.
Truth, love?
Now that I think it, maybe
that was not something good.
Him you my lover, this is sad.
It is desperate and disgusting.
But be like be, we have
that to leave the list.
To face to it schemes it, to the destination.
Stop soldier, we go you stop.
Allow it to leave, Sr. Blank.
This well, allow it to leave.
Poor person sweet man.
Poor person comely sweet man.
Pardon, believe me me also
he/she hoped it is a dream.
If it serves them as something my story
he/she has a satisfactory end.
But this it is not,
alone it is the number 67
My name?
4, 3, 2, 1.
New happy year!
- Nobody congratulates you.
- Thank You, Roderick Blank.
- Esther Fenchel.
- Your friends call you Terry.
No, but it is curious because
it is my husband's name, Terry.
Linda tie.
He/she leaves the bottle.
Gentlemen, The killer.
The prototype not!
To eat and to die from hunger.
To eat and to die from hunger
they asked me me to take a time
to take for a while away from all.
But there was not escape, notice several names
French and Italian in the list
so I thought of Europe, to listen
of the women you magnify
my friends concluded that he/she would have
the best vacations in my life.
I am glad them to enjoy it.
Good night, you have that follarme,
so they come to make it.
Without dinner, it grabs pencil,
I will give you the address.
Hello? if, badge,
it was a joke, I sit down it.
- Your he/she suckles I answer?
- If.
- Serious?
I sit down it a lot.
Why do you laugh?
In my own way he/she attempts
to fight against the list.
but once but the list
wise but that me.
because he/she will know a woman
that it would solve all my problems.
- Hope?
- It was.
Roderick?
I have attempted per years that my mother
get up, your you made it in 5 seconds.
Tell me your poison.
Hope Hartlight was the author of the book
of self-help but sold.
I found it warm, passionate
and a little old.
So I was not ataido to her.
But I won't get rid of making it
with her, so it passes their surprise
invite it to another appointment, imagining that
possibly we would have sex.
and it could continue ahead.
But it happened something...
Hope listens to myself, it guides me.
Hope helps myself with its literature,
we passed the time playing chess.
As for my friends,
what do they believe?
Hope was the mother nature
that he/she came to save their souls.
If you allow it to go, I will bring it.
You seem me of person's type that
he/she makes fun of the anniversary of one month.
You have changed me.
You cured me.
It is very pretty what you said.
Do you know? I have that autografiar
books in Vemont
I believe that you should go with me,
they have a grandiose hotel.
We can sleep until late,
when he/she doesn't work, clear.
You could stay there and to make all that that
want, until walking nude in the patio.
Hope didn't disappear amid
the dinner, takes him/her a couple of weeks.
How it is that the answer to
my problems are not enough?
If my friend had been with Hope,
I had been proud of the one.
I suppose that that it is the problem,
proud but not jealous.
And a man prefers to have the jealousies
of somebody before their respect.
I hate to have said that.
Maybe hope was not the but
good with the one that you were.
But it was so proud of you
The married ones are taking
a lot of fever for that reason.
It seems that you broke the rule
of the woman of but of 35.
I thought that we would not make an intervention.
Not we would use that word
but undoubtedly it is it.
This well.
They continue thinking that there out
this the suitable girl for the one?
News of last minute, the woman
well-known with Death Nell, accent its
driver's license in the one
place of their last attack.
It is what the authorities waited
the whole year and we have the sole right.
Chuck chuck DJ Harry Hunt during
a commercial of their morning program.
I appreciate what you/they said...
Hello?
Go up him/her, seriously they caught
to that satanic woman?
Not and it is said, fighter of the freedom.
Allow me to guess, he/she doesn't call himself Death Nell.
That such an intervention.
The name is Gillian Of Raisx.
Death Nell is Gillian Of Raisx
Gillian Of Raisx, x is silent
it was a name that it was I famliliar.
and when that happened it was because...
Well, this not this happening.
You what you/they are thinking, had
memorized the last name of the list
because nobody wants to think
in the last name, because
that means that...
What did you tell him/her?
To where it was?
- Fred.
- It is something comic.
Not it is as if it was the next one.
Maybe be not the next one
but if the last.
Another woman should have in the one
planet that he/she calls himself as her.
Their last name also
with a silent x?
Tanquilizate, that Gillian Of Raisx
he/she can that it is not Gillian Of Raisx.
As you can see the you schemes
this bringing near to Death Nell.
At the beginning it didn't leave but...
But coordinated, in this radio he/she would say
that inside a couple of weeks
the oracle will tell us where
Gillian Of Raisx stayed
in the precise moment of
their demurrage, I assume that
he/she could stop to have sex with
- Twenty.
women in next 2 weeks.
I have made it with 3 women
in all my life,
any if they don't count paying hence.
We can tell him/her that he/she doesn't have sex.
but he/she has to go but far from that now.
He/she has to take their mind for another route.
Read the book that he/she always wanted.
I see the models of airplanes like...
It is grandiose but I have
that to return to the suck.
Fred, you don't help.
Does he like the bicycle?
Not I can believe that they are you are
my conversations now.
This tormented, give him/her one.
What? ah, if.
The mentioned oracle,
sometimes wandered in capturing criminals
it has solved the mysteries but
big of our culture.
and I believe that if we can him/her
to give one of those.
Anyone?
Who do kill Nicole Simpson?
- These joking.
- It is this way, allow me to see.
Who do shoot JFK?
He/she requests other, that taking like 20 minutes.
- How many planets do they have life?
- Eleven.
Eleven, that everything is?
How many but he/she wanted?
- Does God exist?
- Already coarse.
Alone one.
Please, they are bad.
Not he/she wants to be in THE the weekend.
Enough.
There are 20 shields between her and you.
Be conservative, don't use none
before catching it.
And remember...
- A new existence Kingdom.
- Existence.
Without sex...
Not there is death.
Good luck
If!
I never believed that the letters of
their magazine was true.
Up to now.
My best friend was in bicycle
when key in a well.
Fortunately for my friend,
a bus in in route to a camp
religious stopped to make
what says the Bible and to help him.
They cleaned it and they put it
in the corridor of the bus.
He/she thought that they will help him.
In place they were helped themselves.
Among the girls of the bus they had
conversed about not having
lost their virginity
my friend's appearance in the highway
it was taken as a sign.
A pact was made, all would lose
the virginity and the one was the elect.
All virgins, all of 18.
There was 19 18 year-old cicas,
all virgins and in uniform.
They made a raffle and the
first were Mona Farlow.
Carajo.
Carajo!
One day that my friend never forgot was.
Some change before sending it?
I am curious,
was there a lot of blood?
That it cares, go the perversion
favorite of the man.
- You can die now.
- That is the problem.
Did I tell them the good news?
I will marry.
The fortunate one is Ethel Walters,
I hope they arrive to the wedding.
Do we know it?
Not him you, I have to put on
in contact with her immediately.
Are they made well-known the name?
Maybe you should go to bed.
Where was the driver?
it can be that they have been in another bus
but they could not have been alone.
The driver, doesn't believe recor...
The driver.
There is here inside a lot of action,
I want some that.
Now relax you, the blanquitas
they won't tell to anybody.
Not you can go to bed with me.
Roderick, I am Trixie,
I won't violate you, that knows it.
Leave me alone.
Salt, drinks big.
I have something for you, soon.
Angers to Australia, your flight comes out in
the morning, it begins to pack.
Not I can escape,
even so I would be.
I was in internet the whole night
I found another Gillian Of Raisx
- But their last name not...
- If, with a silent x.
He/she is a biologist marima of Sidney.
Which is the tusk in the picture?
He/she has big bones and a great one
appetite for the life, imbecile.
What is that in their face?
An eruption for its
exploration in the reef.
For heaven's sake, Roderick, you prefer to die
that to make it with a fat.
with a slight skin condition.
Not it is so slight.
I am for sure...
Buy you books for the airplane,
underline good conversations
If you won't seduce her...
If I like dolphins.
Without caring what happens,
thank you to be with me.
You are good friend.
- Is it good to not be lesbian?
- Send me a postcard.
With a koala in her.
Please you don't kill me.
If that wants, he/she listens, the oracle
it completed, we have confirmation
that Death Nell will be here
in the hotel Maitre.
I am in their room, not this here
in this precise moment but
their things if they are, friends.
I have chills.
Their room, is the day of the innocent ones?
They are 12: 10 am officially
second of April.
If, Roderick, is new plans for today.
This is incredible.
Not they know like it has been.
I found the truth of truths
and it is not suckled neither straws.
He/she is former, former fiancés.
He/she listens, it revises the names in the list
Does some name appear twice?
No, then you don't tell me that never
you joined with a former one it stops you already know...
Memory?
You are right, him toward with them
and then they returned for navidad.
And whenever it traveled to San Louis,
I always stopped in Diana Scott.
We will get you reelection sex,
I speak to you of wild sex.
He/she returns to Hope, the number 80, that that
they had it was real, she accepted you.
If, Hope, I have had so much women
interesting in my life that never
I was worthy of them.
Not listen to Beta, the one hates
the erections and the amusement.
What you have to make is
to find that school bus
and to join with the Bible rats
of the number 81 up to 99.
- Maybe to pass at 84 o'clock and alone...
- Mr.?
If, over there.
Make one of them to be changed
the name to Gillian Of Raisx.
Hold.
The theories in the table are good but
calm, Gillian arrived at the hotel
in any moment but us
we don't believe in trials or arrests
so I want you to wait and not
leave your house.
This well.
- I will call you then.
- Here I will be, thank you.
Seriously they did think that I would survive easy?
Did they want him to be this way?
You that I promised them an end
satisfactory but there was not
I triumph from return to Fiona, Hope or nobody but.
Not I will pursue a taxi
neither I will stop a wedding.
Neither there will be a reconciliation
in a train platform.
Neither neither I will travel to Australia.
To escape to the sins
of April 2 it would feel very bad.
I suppose that my true destination
it was in a hotel in the center.
It will go out with a lady called Death.
Any God or it schemes I could survive now.
And that felt well.
If you live with the sword
you die for the sword.
A sexual remaining position
Karmasutra"
The end comes closer.
And to arrive is the end.
All Fred revises.
My name is commanding Delta,
alone they enter, move.
Excuse, Srta. Death, Nell.
Do You Prefer Gillian?
I am no longer you afraid.
Death Nell this completed one.
You look at it, he/she doesn't know that to make.
To where you go? he/she returns.
You caused a shock there out.
Did you love me something?
No, me...
Hello.
There are agents away from your hotel
and in your room.
Thank you.
- Do you know that I don't sin truth?
- If.
Can I accompany?
Go.
This place is incredible.
I never heard of this place.
I discovered it the other night, there is not
many places here that they open up so late.
You know... ?
- I sit down it.
- Your dilo.
No, your.
This is strange for my.
He/she had never had a volunteer.
Some would make what is to have sex.
This has flavor to grape.
If you know that I cannot guarantee
when or if you woke up.
If, I understand.
It bothers you if I ask you,
tell me if it is very personal.
How did you arrive here?
In a sense but extensive.
Not it is as if he/she left it
to say to somebody or something like that.
Not him you...
Not I will talk about my childhood
because that is not...
My childhood was not better or worse
that the one of anyone.
Maybe a worse little bit but escape
There study poetry and chemistry, obviously
I am better mixing that speaking.
Not say that, I am enjoying it.
You are right, it is grandiose.
Alone I have read the things that came out in those
newspapers after the incidents
but what what you painted was
after the number 7?
My ecstasy, your alienation
it is not anything of tolerating.
It is good.
Where was it? clear, before
to be able to graduate fall in love.
My husband was all it that you
it supposes that a girl wants.
I was their princess, the era
my charming prince.
Can I prove your food?
I change you for that tomato.
Not you have to continue if you don't want.
To tell the truth, it feels well
decil the bad thing aloud.
But when I said that it was
their princess.
Not it was mataforico.
Every week a new disguise
of princess and a wig.
In that way it is better,
as the he/she said it.
At the beginning it was amusing
but later it was no longer it.
It became rude one day...
- Do I hit you?
- No.
You know, I put to 20 men in coma
when you put that punishment class
the short answer is if.
It hit me and toward
all that was happened.
But anything above the neck,
the princess and the pirate.
The princess and the Viking,
the princess and the magician.
Occasionally it mixed it and we made
"The music's sound"
it could not be a crime,
the era my husband.
I didn't complain neither toward questions.
but if somebody wanted to the
main character with ashtray
it was very good.
But I improve my posia, he/she gave me
much material to work.
You are good listening, seriously.
Then I arrive San Valentine's day.
Something came out good, my situation without
it thrills, my inability of changing.
but undoubtedly all he/she will write it.
And later...
Should I have been happy not?
They were about everything but
they could not wake up,
they thought that it was in coma.
And there it was when I had the vision.
Carajo.
Do you know? I like to think that I put something
interesting there out in the atmosphere.
The idea of a capable woman
of humiliating a man.
to be bad or without some reason.
Good, the women have to fight
day and night with the impositions
of the man forever so
I planned to take control for a while.
I suppose.
It is this way as I rationalize it.
I left.
This well, we all are you leave.
They are single games, names.
To who loved, to
who really loved.
Did you give the heart?
Did they break yours?
Somehow...
he/she leaves you exhausted.
I always like that word.
Taciturn, dissipated, not well wornout,
those they are good.
But fatigue sounds what is.
And that better cure that to sleep?
To sleep a lot.
I pay, I insist.
Roderick.
Would you care it?
You want him to take two for
if the first don't work?
Alone he/she thought that since we are together.
While I put one in your mouth your...
These sure one?
If.
Not I will lie, I am flattered.
You would should.
Do we go to my room?
Not to that.
A different one.
If.
So that is everything,
the end of my history.
Good, of one of my histories.
He/she suckles, potato, I found a totato
for the picnic.
Seriously you are the farmer.
I believe that we already know that
there will be for the picnic.
Totate soup.
What do you find?
The history of like I wised up,
as I knew my wife.
As I learned that sometimes the answers
they are disguised questions.
The list becomes trained that the one
who that, where and when
it is never as important as the because
and the because neither it is so important.
If everything is a game, sometimes
the best thing that can make it is
to press the reseteo button.
For the first time in my life I am me
treatment of adding him/her the mature being
contentment, happy,
for the time being that this well.
The life resembles the death
they receive all like it or not.
But at the end, honestly
To who he cares a carajo?
Downloaded From www.moviesubtitles.org
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org