Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Roll camera.
And... begin.
Nice pussy.
Miaow.
You're very content
right now, aren't you Ellen?
You live in a nice house...
You wear pretty clothes.
And you're married to a kind man
who's promised to love you forever.
You have no inkling of what lives
at the bottom of the flower box.
No sense of longing.
No notion even of death itself.
And...
...end. And print it.
Wolf, have we established pathos?
Perfectly, Herr Doctor.
And in one take.
Very well let's get the film
to the lab immediately.
I'll need to see rushes tomorrow
before the train in the morning.
Albin?
Yeah, Friedrich?
Hurry and strike your set,
as you never
hesitate to remind me, it's costing
our investors a fortune daily.
Shooting outside the studios will
cost them much more, Friedrich.
But such is the price of genius.
Thank God, an end to this artifice.
Nicely done, Greta.
You are developing in a number
of lovely ways.
For a moment I even thought I saw a
premonition of evil cross your face.
It wouldn't surprise me with all the
spooky shit you've been saying to me.
I told you, it's important
for the realistic effect.
But why do we have
to leave Berlin just now,
at the start
of the theatre season?
- Albin, has your man arranged the cars?
- Yes, two.
Do you have any idea the parts I've
been offered at long last? The salaries?
Will that be enough?
It has to be... they're
the only cars in the region.
Herr Doctor, you're ignoring me.
There was a time when you
didn't ignore me.
Why would you possibly want to act
in a play when you can act in a film?
Atheatrical audience gives me life,
while
this thing merely takes it from me.
Greta...
Ellen is a woman who discovers...
the ultimate expression of love...
in the most exquisite pain imaginable.
Does that sound familiar?
It's a very demanding role.
It is the role that will make you
great as an actress.
Consider it
a sacrifice for your art.
Work quickly, ladies and gentlemen,
we have a train to catch!
Hans...
Albin, what did you give the cat?
Laudanum.
It's hard to keep the damn thing docile
under the lights. Why, did it show?
It looked a little pickled.
Not as much as Greta.
Things seem to be
well in hand here.
Friedrich.
Friedrich, we have to talk
about the vampire.
Not now, Albin,
it's nearly dark.
Wrap things up for me here,
will you?
Make sure the imbecile Gustav
does not miss the train.
And I'll see you all
in the morning.
But what kind of clothes
should I pack for him?
What kind of make-up?
How tall is he?
Please tell me, Friedrich?
Does anybody know
where he's running off to?
Perhaps he has a woman.
Or a man.
We cross the border into Czechoslovakia
a few hours into our journey.
Apparently Herr Doctor's already
filmed some of the exteriors there.
He has?
You didn't know?
No.
Strange. Well, you can assume we'll be
filming all of Hutter's scenes there.
The scenes between him
and the vampire.
I thought Dracula lived
in Transylvania.
Strictly speaking,
this is not Dracula.
The author's widow wouldn't
sell us the rights to the novel.
So who's playing Count Dracula?
I mean, Orlock?
His name is Schreck.
Max Schreck.
Apparently he was in the Reinhardt
Company when Murnau was directing.
Schreck? Are you sure
you have the name right?
He's a character actor.
Who told you he was
playing the vampire?
Herr Doctor told me.
I never heard of any Max Schreck
in the Reinhardt Company.
Herr Doctor told me he was
with Stanislavsky in Moscow.
Oh dear, one of the
Russian school then.
As part of his preparation,
he submerges
his own personality into that
of the character he's playing.
That is why he's not travelling
with us.
Herr Doctor told me he went
to Czechoslovakia weeks ago.
To absorb the flavour of the place,
I suppose.
Herr Doctor also told me...
that when we get there
and start filming...
Max Schreck will only appear to us
in full make-up and costume...
as the vampire.
And furthermore...
we will only film him at night.
And why wasn't I told about it?
I'm the producer.
Well, he told me.
Tell me you're not too pretty
to work for me?
Yes, sir.
I love the cinema.
Friedrich, I just realised this morning,
our financiers, they don't know
what picture you're making.
The crew don't know
The cast don't know
what picture you're making.
And now I don't know what picture
you're making. Are you happy?
Albin...
I know, tell them nothing.
- Ah, yeah, there he is.
- There he is, getting on the train.
Gentlemen, I amn Albin Grau,
producer and art director
of this picture.
Is it true Murnau is filming
Stoker's Dracula?
Friedrich Wilhelm Murnau is Germany's
greatest film maker.
In a class with such masters
as Griffith and Eisenstein.
At present he is supervising
every detail
of this unique
on location expedition.
- The major part, who's going to play?
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
- Will you be filming in Germany?
Paul, Paul.
Our battle, our struggle,
is to create art.
Our weapon is the moving picture.
Because we have the moving picture...
our paintings
will grow and recede.
Our poetry will be shadows
that lengthen and conceal.
Our light will play
across living faces
that laugh and agonise.
And our music will linger
and finally overwhelm
because it will have a context.
As certain as the grave.
We are scientists engaged
in the creation of memory.
But our memory
will neither blur... nor fade.
What is this?
It looks like... blood.
Good evening.
Herr Doctor...
we've been expecting you.
- The wagon train has arrived.
- And here's the lead mule.
Well, what a terrible
journey that was.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
Don't tell me, we have
a busy schedule tomorrow?
No. Exterior shots of the inn.
Some shots in here.
Arrival of Hutter's carriage.
Welcome.
I'd like to plan for these night scenes.
When are they to be filmed?
They will be filmed soon...
They won't require...
much planning.
But I need extra help
to set up the lights.
Surely you can give me
some notice so I can prepare?
Herr Doctor,
where are the extras?
You're looking at them.
Herr Doctor,
hese people cannot act.
They don't need to act.
They need to be.
Wolf?
Herr Muller?
I was... Sorry, Wolf.
All right, Hutter, it's been a fitful
night but you wake refreshed...
eager to continue your journey to
the castle of the nobleman
who may very well make
your fortune.
Wait, Gustav.
What is that beside you?
Yes, pick it up.
It's a book...
about vampires.
Ah... yes...
now you remember.
It was put there last night by the
superstitious peasants, the ones
who warned you not
to enter Orlock's castle.
The ones who warned you
not even to dare to speak his name...
Nosferatu.
The unclean, the undead...
least you evoke
the creature itself.
Very good, Gustav
Herr Doctor...
Albin...
- I am sorry, Herr Doctor, but...
- Albin!
End.
Albin, a native has wandered
into my frame!
Wolf.
Wolf!
What is the matter with everyone?
She will not let us go on filming,
unless we replace the crosses.
Am I really
being bothered with this?
Herr Doctor, I warned you.
You should be more concerned
about these things.
The crosses are not for decoration.
We will put them back.
They just overwhelm
our composition.
Albin, the camera.
- The head light should be sufficient.
- Henrik, what's this scene number?
Twenty-three.
Quickly.
Yes... Albin, that's fine,
he'll take care of it.
Go in, Henrik.
On either side, you open the door
when I give you the cue.
Ready? Are we ready?
Yeah, yeah.
And roll camera.
Iris in.
And...
...begin.
Gustav, you walk in very slowly.
Very slowly... yes.
Feel your bag, make sure
you have your contracts.
You're afraid.
Who was the person
who brought you?
You must go into the castle.
The castle calls you...
The gates suddenly open.
You must go in.
That's excellent, Gustav.
Go forward.
And, end.
Wolf?
Yeah, it's okay.
I'm in charge of set construction. Who
built all this? We have an agreement!
Albin, I sent some local workers
ahead this morning.
I'm sorry I didn't explain to you.
Please, there's a generator
in the courtyard,
just past the tree on the right,
in the background. Get it working.
Henrik, take this camera.
- We have an agreement!
- Yes, stay here for a moment.
Wolf, your camera is here.
Set it up quickly as possible. Yes?
Roll camera.
Gustav...
you move forward very slowly,
heading always for the tunnel.
This is perfect.
Just a dark hole...
...that has been unexplored,
untouched...
...for a long, long time.
And then...
one night...
something crawls out.
Hutter...
meet Count Orlock.
Gustav, you must follow him
into the tunnel.
Yes, going in.
Make your way down.
And...
...end.
Wolf?
My God.
Wolf!
Yeah, got it.
Remarkable.
The overture to our
symphony of horrors.
Genius, Hutter. Genius.
He's not from the
Reinhardt Company.
Congratulations, Gustav.
Yes...
I was good, wasn't I?
I saw his face...
his face.
Where did you find him, really?
In that hole.
Gustav...
this was your finest moment.
Good, Gustav.
Gentlemen, let's pack up.
Shooting is completed for the night.
That's it? We came all the way
for one scene?
I would have driven anywhere at
any time for that look of Gustav's.
I would like to congratulate Schreck
on his extraordinary appearance.
For the remainder of the shoot,
he will be Count Orlock.
To himself and to all of us.
Just leave the man alone.
He will be completely authentic.
He is not interested in our questions,
or our praise, or our conversations.
He's chasing an altogether
different ghost.
Friedrich. Come quick, it's Wolf!
Muller, I can help you.
Help me.
Albin, you have the cameras safe?
Go, quickly.
- Is my room ready?
- Yes.
Nosferatu.
Ah, this is too much.
Answer me, Herr Doctor. Is this
some stunt to evoke fear in us?
Henrik, stop being so theatrical.
You'll wake the whole house.
Go on up, Wolf, and have a brandy.
You'll feel better in the morning.
What's happened?
He's ill, obviously.
Take him upstairs
and then go outside and help Herr
Grau with the camera equipment.
All right? Come on.
Bring the cameras
straight to my room...
prepare for tomorrow.
Albin, we need to clear the table.
We'll need the ink-well,
the quill,
and the contracts.
Yes, I...
I'd like it darker
and smokier. Dustier.
Which case, Paul? Move
that lamp to the far side and...
and you, spread some dust
on the corner. On the...
Ah, there you are.
It's incredible, no?
I wish you could all see your faces.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Max Schreck
who will be portraying
our vampire, Count Orlock.
As you no doubt have heard,
Max's methods are somewhat...
unconventional.
But, I am sure you will come
to respect his artistry in this
matter.
Yes, places everybody.
May I have the chair, please?
Quickly.
Count Orlock, you will sit here
at the head of the table.
Please.
Very good.
In this scene, the Count is reading
the papers you've brought him...
and you are about to make a
considerable amount of money.
No, no make-up!
Forgive me, Herr Doctor.
Albin clear the set!
Elke...
Count, you're reading
your documents.
That's it.
It isn't right.
Well, try acting it,
for God's sake.
What should it say?
It's meant to be a contract...
a real estate contract.
I'd like some make-up.
Well, you don't get any.
All right, are we ready to begin?
Elke, the phonograph.
Iris in.
And...
concentrate...
begin.
All right, Orlock, very good.
You are reading your papers.
Read your papers very intensely.
After all, how often is it that you
get correspondence from the living?
No, don't look up.
Concentrate on your papers.
Not that you actually care about
the details of the contract.
All you're interested in are all
those juicy throats waiting for you
the moment you get to Germany.
Ah now, Hutter,
even though it may repel you...
creep in... creep in.
Let us see the expectation
on your face.
You're about to make
the biggest sale of your life.
Point out a few details
of the contract. Yes...
Tell him that, that's
particularly beneficial to you.
Reach into your bag.
This will seal the deal
and something falls out.
Count, what is it?
On your left, on the table.
It's a locket.
This is Greta Schroder.
No, no, you don't know her.
He's supposed to ask who it is.
No... End.
Jesus, Max...
Henrik, can you explain to him...
his motivation?
All right, Count...
think about this...
What is it that inspires...
the most longing in you?
That is most desirable...
and yet most unattainable?
The light... of the sun.
That is the emotion. Use it.
Nosferatu, you read your papers.
Roll, bitte.
Who is this woman?
It's Ellen, my wife.
She has a beautiful bosom.
Oh Jesus...
Gustav, just snatch it back
from him.
Yes. Go on.
And, vampire, you sign the papers.
Take your quill,
sign the papers.
Yes, go on.
I understand we are going
to be neighbours.
Very nice addition, Count. Yes.
And, Hutter,
how does that make you feel?
Yes. Snatch back your papers.
You're happy to be his neighbour?
And, iris out.
End!
Excellent.
Give the lip-readers a thrill.
Wolf, do you have it?
Yes, I got it.
Wolf, have you got it?
Yes, I said I got it!
Excellent. Thank you.
Do you think Schreck is all right?
We have left him up at that castle.
He's not in danger.
He's a fine actor, but,
all this preparation,
it's very strange.
You think it is strange enough for him
to go so deep inside his character
that he forgets he's
Max Schreck altogether?
God knows I forgot.
Schreck's peculiarities are
like love-making games.
You believe them
when they happen
but they always stop short of
anybody being seriously hurt.
The woods decay...
the woods decay and fall...
the vapours weep their burthen
to the ground.
Dinner?
You set a very mean table.
No rats?
There was a time...
when I fed...
from golden chalices.
But now...
Don't look at me that way!
In my old age I feed...
the way old men pee.
Sometimes all at once...
sometimes drop by drop.
I told you...
I feed erratically...
often enormously.
Yes, Max, you may give
the locket to Elke.
Gustav, this is a scene from
the previous night. You have met
your host he has brought you home
to his castle, he's giving you a dinner.
You can start eating.
Very well. Excellent. And, Orlock,
you're merely reading your papers
and totally ignoring your guest.
Good.
Wolf, roll camera...
and...
begin.
Yes.
A thought occurs to you.
Iook at your host.
Very good, Gustav.
Do you think...
he might have been the stranger
who drove you to the castle?
You watch...
is he even human?
How does it feel to be
eating next to him?
Knowing that you're spending
the night with him...
in the castle, alone.
You watch him.
Orlock, drop your paper.
You look at Gustav.
Gustav, keep watching him.
Take your right hand
and reach for the bread knife.
Watch him...
breathing.
What will happen?
Reach out, take the loaf of bread...
and cut yourself a slice.
Yes, slicing, slicing...
You are slicing.
Ttoward you, toward you...
watching him...
...slicing, slicing,
watch out...
slicing...
Watch your finger!
Damn it!
Look, Nosferatu!
Blood, blood!
Damn it, Murnau.
I really did cut myself!
- Paul, go and check the generator.
- You did that intentionally!
- Calm down!
- I'll see to the light.
- That knife was sharpened like a razor!
- Gustav, remain in character!
Jesus Christus get this off me!
Schreck!
What is the matter with you?
He's a Stanislavsky lunatic, that is
what is the matter with him!
I contracted you in secrecy
and at great expense.
Herr Muller, when will you have your
equipment functioning properly?
I am tired of your
lack of enthusiasm!
I saw you.
Gustav...
bring the girls to the car.
- I am not happy!
- Gustav, move.
Herr Doctor,
the man is barely breathing.
I told you to fix the generator!
No, leave the equipment
and take the camera.
We are done here for today,
Herr Doctor.
Albin!
Help me.
Everybody to the automobile.
Herr Doctor, we're leaving.
No...
He stays.
Albin...
Yes, Friedrich?
Do you think Wolf's assistant
can finish this film?
Paul? No. He has
not enough experience.
What about you?
You are the closest we have
to a photographer.
What are you talking about?
The film ends here.
No, Henrik...
this film will go on.
Henrik, this film cannot survive
even the briefest interruption.
The financiers would take control.
They hate your script.
Actually, it may be advantageous
because it makes the crew very edgy
and I like that.
Do you hear
what you are saying?
You're out of your fucking mind,
you're a fanatic!
Please, don't behave like children.
I'll get a new photographer and fly
him back here within the week.
Henrik, when you wrote
this scenario,
you had demons of your own
to work out, did you not?
Now I have mine.
Albin...
you're the producer...
keep this company together.
How dare you
destroy my photographer!
You idiot!
Did I kill some
of your people, Murnau?
I can't remember.
We have an arrangement!
Don't pretend you mourn,
Herr Doctor. I know you.
Why him, you monster?
Why not the script girl?
The script girl...
I'll eat her later.
No, you will not!
Our bargain, you agreed
not to hurt my people!
Listen to me,
do you understand?
This requires that
I go back to Berlin
to find another photographer
and then to fly him back here.
And you will control yourself
while I am away.
I don't think we need
the writer any longer.
I don't expect you
to understand this
and I am loathed
to admit it myself...
but, the writer is necessary.
All my crew is necessary.
Do you understand?
I don't think the ship is necessary.
What?
The ship...
The ship?
My God, what
are you talking about?
I have a dozen scenes on the ship.
But I won't sail.
Then I will replace you
with a double!
I will do every scene
of yours with a double.
You, you will have no close-ups.
None whatsoever.
How dare you speak
to me that way.
I have shots!
I am the director!
Why didn't you mention this before?
You want to eat the writer?
Be my guest.
That will leave you to explain
how else your character
is supposed to get to Bremen?
Yes...
I will...
shoot the scenes at sea
around you.
But you will still have
to sail to Heligoland
for your death scene.
Or else what?
Or else?
Or else...
...no Greta.
We shoot her scenes there.
I'll go to Heligoland...
but I won't sail.
Heligoland is an island.
So?
So it can only be reached by sea.
Or air.
And if I agree to fly you in...
you will leave my people alone.
Or else what?
Don't think I can't harm you.
Tell me how you would harm me...
when even I don't know
how I could harm myself.
But thy strong hours indignant
work'd their wills...
and beat me down...
and marr'd and wasted me...
and though
they could not end me...
left me maim'd to dwell
in presence
of immortal youth.
Immortal age...
beside immortal youth.
And all I was in ashes.
Albin, what is
the most wondrous thing
you have ever seen?
Er...
I saw ectoplasm once.
Ectoplasm?
What is ectoplasm?
It's the mystical
substance of ghosts.
I saw a spiritualist pull it out
of his mouth in Italy.
What did it look like?
Seaweed.
Is that what we look like
when we die?
I hope not.
What was for you the most,
wondrous thing you ever saw?
I once saw Greta Schroeder naked.
No?
Yes.
That beats ectoplasm.
Jesus, Max, you scared me to death.
How long have you been listening?
We've been looking all over
the place for your coffin.
Maybe it isn't his resting place.
Didn't we have
something to say to him?
Max, the great Friedrich Wilhelm
Murnau went to Berlin
- to find a new photographer.
- Wolf is probably dead.
So you can take
your funny ears off.
Albin, please,
the man is an artist.
Ask him some vampire questions.
When did you become
a vampire?
I can't recall.
Where were you born?
Were you born?
I can't remember.
It's not funny any more.
Count Dracula wouldn't say,
"couldn't remember".
I read that book.
Murnau gave it to me.
Now, this is a golden opportunity.
Speaking as a vampire,
what do you make
of the book's technical merits?
It made me sad.
Why sad?
Because Dracula
had no servants.
I think you missed the point
of the book, Count Orlock.
Dracula... hasn't had servants
in four hundred years.
And then a man comes
to his ancestral home
and he must convince him
that he,
that he's like the man.
He has to feed him...
when he himself
hasn't eaten food in centuries.
Can he even remember
how to buy bread?
How to select cheese and wine?
And then he remembers
the rest of it...
how to prepare a meal,
how to make a bed.
He remembers...
his past glory
his armies, his retainers,
and what he is reduced to.
The loneliest part
of the book...
comes when the man...
accidentally sees Dracula...
setting his table.
But if you're so lonely
why don't you make more vampires?
I can't, I'm too old.
Although...
I seem to remember
I was never able to.
Then how did you become
a vampire?
It was woman.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Schreck, the German theatre
needs you.
We were together in the night
and then she left me.
At first I had a painting
of her in wood.
Then I had a relief of her in marble.
And then...
I had a picture of her,
in my mind.
But now I no longer
even have that.
What was I saying?
This schnapps they make
in these parts.
I haven't tasted it in...
Take it easy there,
old boy.
Henrik...
what an actor.
Yeah.
Dedication.
Herr Schreck.
Herr Doctor.
You wanted reality,
Herr Doctor, here it is.
Ah, I'm not a doctor, but I have
dabbled in pharmaceuticals.
- You're the new cameraman, right?
- Yeah.
- We tried shoot it now.
- Ah, good.
- Art can never move as fast as life.
- Sure it can.
So, what's the lens?
It's thirty-five millimetre, sir.
Not my ideal weapon of choice,
but I suppose it'll do...
Are you loaded?
- Yes, sir.
- Good, so am I.
Move the camera ten centimetres
to the right
and I'll contrive a possible two
shot, but, wait for my signal.
- Did you get the shot?
- Yes, sir.
And the gate is clean?
The gate's clean, sir.
I hadn't time to properly prepare
the shot...
What I should have done was filmed
the thing in slow motion.
It would have been
incredibly moving.
What's that, sir, slow motion?
Well I run the film through
the camera too fast...
When it's projected at normal speed,
things appear to be unnaturally
slow.
Gives everything
a kind of resonance.
It's a shame you won't have
the chance to demonstrate
your more esoteric skills
on my production.
I'm Albin Grau, he producer.
And at dawn, Hutter tried to fathom
the horrors of his nights.
Excellent.
Fritz, roll camera.
Iris in.
Begin.
And end.
Excellent, Gustav.
Extraordinary discipline
in the face of ridicule.
Fritz?
Yes, well,
that's his performance style.
Yes, I'd like to move in
for another angle on the crypt.
Mark the shot
with some chalk.
I am exhausted now,
and I'm hungry as well.
You will get a hot meal in Wismar
right after we're done with the ship.
And, end.
Have you ever
considered acting?
No, really, you have
a very interesting face.
Are you a producer?
Why can't Herr Doctor film in a
studio like everybody else?
Henrik, would you take my dog
for me?
- And thank you. Lovely.
- Yes.
Wismar, is there anything here
that even vaguely resembles
a cabaret?
I mean, I'm suffering for my
art, Albin, believe me.
What's going on here, anyway?
You know, Friedrich tells me
to lock my door at night.
And Gustav says
everybody's vanishing.
And you can imagine what
they're saying in Berlin.
Hello, Greta.
Hello.
You look vaguely familiar.
Where did we meet?
Morocco.
- Yes, you brought me treats.
- Ja, ja.
What was your name again?
It's...
Fritzie.
- Fritzie.
- Yes, Fritzie.
Fritzie?
- Would you care tojoin us for a drink?
- No, no.
We have to pre-light the set,
yeah?
What? What set? What the hell
are you talking about?
We need you to see the sets
with us tonight.
Well, give me back
my dogs then.
Here.
- Thank you, yes.
- You're welcome.
Left all alone as usual.
Come here, Fru-Fru.
She's here, isn't she?
The glorious child.
No.
I want to see her now.
No!
I won't act for you again
until you bring her to me.
You are destroying everything.
My people have to trust me
for you to get what you want!
You and I are not so different.
Greta is in your last scene,
that is when you can have her.
After my death scene?
Yes.
Don't expect realism there,
Murnau.
What do you mean?
Don't cheat me, mortal.
You will stay away
from her.
from my crew!
I will finish my picture!
This is hardly your picture
any longer.
You are ready?
Yes, Henrik.
Right...
He was amazing
because he has...
What a horrible smell.
Mind your head.
This is it.
He's in here?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
That answers that question.
How did you find
this place?
I followed Murnau here.
I think you're in the wrong
part of the building.
There's probably a sadistic
brothel upstairs.
What's wrong?
It's all right.
Everyone back to bed.
Greta...
Greta, what is it?
Greta, Greta...
What's happened, Greta?
Please.
It's morphine.
Morphine?
Photography and pharmaceuticals by
Fritzie. That's just what I need.
Friedrich knows all about it.
What do you mean,
he knows about it?
He knows all about it.
She's fine.
Don't worry, get some sleep.
Are you all right there?
This set is not ready.
Can we get any natural light
in here?
The set is not ready, and you're
talking about natural light.
What's the matter
with you, Albin?
You seem a little anxious
lately.
You don't understand, I'm ruined.
I'll never make another picture again.
My reputation gone
and you talk about natural light.
Please, Fritz...
Don't worry...
- It's the same on every picture.
- Not on my picture!
Friedrich open up.
It's me, Albin.
Friedrich, let us in.
Ah, Jesus!
What is it?
It's laudanum,
that's what it is.
There is no Max Schreck.
If he's not Max Schreck,
who is he?
I don't know.
Where did you find him?
In a book...
when I was a student.
A series of paintings portraying
a long line of despotic kings,
rumoured to be vampire
living in Slovakia
for hundreds for years.
I had forgotten all about it
until she gave me that other book.
What other book, Friedrich?
Dracula.
Then I went to scout locations
and there he was
living in an old monastery.
What kind of bond did you make
with him?
That he would play the part of an actor
playing the part of a vampire.
Why?
What did you offer
him in return?
Everlasting life...
and Greta.
Greta?
How could you do
this, Friedrich?
I did it for science.
To preserve it for posterity.
Friedrich! Friedrich!
He's he's gone.
Come on.
What are we going to do?
The call is for two o'clock.
Albin, listen to me.
There's no way
off this island.
What about the aeroplane...?
No, I already checked it.
The fuel tanks are empty.
God!
No.
We're going to have to film
Schreck's scene tonight.
You know I don't like these late
shoots, Friedrich.
Where is everybody?
Why don't I have an assistant?
Greta...
Did you put on this make-up
with a broom?
Stop fussing, Albin.
You look beautiful.
Can I have a cigarette?
Sure.
Where's my script, Henrik?
He's indisposed.
What's the matter with him?
Greta, don't ask so many questions,
we're busy.
Thank you, darling.
Why does everybody look
so depressing?
Hey, who died?
Jesus! Look at you.
Friedrich.
Herr Doctor!
Yes, Greta, what is it?
What's the shot?
What are we doing here?
Can you stand for me?
Look at you.
Yes, very well.
Now, let us take her robe,
Albin, please.
And she'll need
her wooden stake.
Also, Greta, you will be here,
lying on the bed.
Yes.
Now, Greta...
Good.
Now...
in this scene...
you make the ultimate sacrifice
for love. Yes?
Yes.
You will seduce the Count...
and...
with your wooden stake,
just before, you die,
you will despatch him. Yes?
Thank you. Very good.
Now...
In other words,
all you have to do...
is, as they say, relax and the vampire
will do all the work.
You had me leave rehearsals in Berlin
just to do that?
Hey, watch it, handsome!
Fifty-two, one.
And for your lean in,
please, Herr Schreck.
Thank you.
And, Albin, her shoes, please.
Yes.
We must go.
Friedrich.
Yes?
I don't wish to question
your authority, but,
are you sure you know
what you're doing?
Yes, exactly. Roll camera...
And, Fritz, ready?
Higher.
Albin.
And...
iris in.
End.
What happened?
- I saw he, he casts no...
- I'm tired of waiting.
- Calm down.
- No, he casts no reflection.
I see him. No, look at him.
Look at him!
Look! Please help me.
Help me please, Friedrich.
- I'll give you something to calm you.
- No, don't do that.
- Just to calm you. Yes?
- Albin, look at him, please.
Please, please, please.
No.
But still, I don't understand
what... No!
It is the role that will make you
great as an actress.
Consider it a sacrifice
for your art.
That's better, now we can work
in peace.
I want her now.
No, I need a shot f you clutching
your heart first.
My death scene?
Yes, you must do that
for me.
Very well.
Roll camera... and begin.
Yes, Count. You kneel down. You'll
have your head on her shoulder,
but you're not feeding, Count.
No, you're not drinking
her blood now,
because you have been drinking
her blood all night.
In fact, you can barely move.
You are intoxicated with,
with blood and desire.
Greta, can you hear me?
Yes?
Flutter your eyelids.
Yes, now, Greta, you start...
to awaken...
Find your stake.
Yes, where is it?
Now, Count, as she raises her stake,
what do you see?
Yes, a wooden stake, exactly.
You look at her...
betrayed.
Yes, you turn...
You rise...
You look around.
The sun is coming.
You grab your heart
in anguish.
Yes, and you start to die.
Yes, you start to die alone.
In anguish.
Die, you you fucking rat bastard.
Vampire pig,
schweine-hund shit!
Yes, die alone! Yes, the weight
of the centuries burns you!
And...
End!
Fritz?
Ja, got it.
That's enough, Murnau.
Hey!
Okay, ja.
I want her now!
Go to hell, Murnau!
Begin!
Very good, yes.
And slowly we need
to move the camera.
Friedrich...
Friedrich he cut the chain
we're trapped.
So, you would
break our bargain?
You think you know so much...
but I can still kill you.
I can break your necks...
drink your blood...
And I could you tried
to trick me!
It's daybreak, is it?
So what? All I need...
is to sleep in darkness.
I will stay here until dusk...
and then...
only I will walk out alive.
Idiot.
Frankly, Count, I find
this composition unworkable.
Could you return to your original
mark, please?
If it's not in frame,
it doesn't exist.
Then finally you must turn
to meet the sun.
The death of centuries...
moon chaser, blasphemer...
monkey, vase of prehistory.
Finally to earth
and finally born.
Yes...
Yes.
You take the sun.
Albin, could you quickly
collect the wooden stake
and return it
to it's rightful place?
It is necessary
for the final frame.
To remind us of the inadequacy
our plans...
our contingencies...
every missed train,
the failed picnics...
every lie to a child.
Softly, please.
Our work is nearly complete.
Our very own painting
on our very own cave wall.
Time will no longer be a dark spot
on our lungs.
They will no longer
be able to say:
"You would have
to have been there".
Because, the fact is, Albin...
we were.
Is there one among you who might wear
the mantle of camera assistant?
Could I possibly impose on you to
collect the slate at my feet
and provide me with an end board?
Turn it.
Thank you.
I think we have it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org