My mother made an amazing amount
of noise when she ate her food.
It was as if she was trying to taste
the entire world.
Sometimes I just couldn 't stand her.
Sometimes I hated her.
Sometimes I thought
she was ruining my life.
What kept me going was knowing
one day I'd leave her.
Come on, baby, surfing safari
I'm gonna take you
Surfing safari
Let's go surfing now
Everybody's learning how
Come on and safari with me
-I hate this song.
-I Iove the Beach Boys.
-I hate them'
-How can you hate them?
-They're happy and sunny.
-You'II Iearn to Iike that.
That's what CaIifornia's aII about.
Next stop, SaIt Lake City.
SaIt Lake City, Utah.
-The capitaI, right?
-I don't care.
You do. Don't mumbIe.
You care. You're very good
at capitaIs.
-Idaho? Pooh Bear.
-Stop caIIing me "Pooh Bear. "
But you are my IittIe Pooh Bear.
Come on. Come on. Idaho?
-Boise. I don't wanna pIay'
-Do a hard one for me.
I don't wanna pIay.
-Oregon?
-PortIand. Too easy.
-It's SaIem.
-SaIem?
I don't wanna do this anymore.
I don't wanna be in Utah.
2000 miIes between us and Bay City.
Okay'
I miss Bay City.
This is Iike being kidnapped.
-I wish I'd been kidnapped at your age.
-So do I.
Grandma always said
Mom was a strange child.
-She's absoIuteIy moribund'
-Gwenn Purvis has cancer.
-That's worse.
-I didn't give it to her.
You didn't give it to her.
That's funny.
-You're gonna die one day too.
-But not in this town.
My mother never wanted
to stay in Bay City.
I think she married Ted...
...because he was so nice and clean.
Being an ice-skating instructor
made him seem cleaner.
She missed my real father,
who was Egyptian, dark and romantic.
One Christmas Eve,
I heard my parents argue.
I knew nothing until he was gone.
He left in our brown Valiant.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You're awfuIIy quiet.
-You said we'd see a reservation.
-When we get to one, we wiII.
Don't mumbIe. How can you be
an actress if you can't speak?
I don't want to be an actress.
I bet we won't even stop in Las Vegas.
-That's what's wrong'
-You said you had his number.
I said we'II Iook him up, okay?
Your father Ieft in
the middIe of the night.
So what? You Ieft my stepdad
in the middIe of the afternoon.
-I miss Ted.
-He's boring.
-Why'd you marry him?
-None of your business.
-He ran around with other women.
-Not true'
You made it up. You wanted him to,
to catch him and get his money.
-You IittIe snoop'
-And Ted's not a homosexuaI.
-I never said that.
-You did.
I inferred it, but I never said it.
"Light in the Ioafers" isn't the same.
AII right, Mother.
Ted said he Ioves you.
He was worried you saw other peopIe.
You probabIy were.
That's it!I've had it with you'
You miss Ted so much, go find Ted.
Get out of the car'
-You said we'd see buffaIo.
-Tough shit!Get out of the car.
Ted wiII teach ice-skating
for the rest of his Iife.
Cousin Benny wiII be
a mechanic.
LoIy won't Ieave the bank.
Your cousin HaI drinks Iiquor.
SyIvia and the baby can
bareIy breathe there.
I now have a job teaching
in the Los AngeIes schooI system.
My M.A. in earIy education was wasted
in that dink junior high.
So forget about buffaIo and Indians.
You're a beautifuI girI
with great potentiaI.
I won't Iet you be nothing
in a nothing town.
You are 1 4 years oId.
You've aIways had food
and a pIace to Iive.
Stick with me, you aIways wiII.
I'm your mother.
And I know what is best for you,
because that is my job.
Your schooI is in BeverIy HiIIs,
the best schooI district in the U.S.
You'II be a chiId actor,
whiIe stiII a chiId.
You don't have a job
in the L.A. schooI district.
I wiII. I have an interview
and a great outfit.
-You hungry?
-I don't know.
-Excuse me?
Great!So am I.
So. . . .
Look at that. Is it the most
beautifuI car you've ever seen?
No. I hate that car.
I miss the PIymouth.
Baby, nobody misses a PIymouth.
-It's your coIor.
-It is, isn't it?
Look at this. It's so beautifuI.
-How's it feeI?
-SubIime'
-We can't afford this.
-I have savings.
I'II dip into my retirement fund.
This car doesn't beIong in Bay City.
Neither do we.
We'II drive to BeverIy HiIIs
in this car.
This pIace Iooks expensive.
I'II worry about that.
Now we're in BeverIy HiIIs,
maybe we'II caII you "Heather. "
-It smeIIs nice. How much is the room?
-It's $1 200.
A night?
I don't know that it's Iarge enough.
-Do you have any viIIas?
-Not right now.
Mom, I'm tired.
Where wiII we sIeep tonight?
Sweet Pea, you are just as pretty
as these girIs on TV.
I think you're prettier.
Sweetie? Are you aII right?
You've been in there over an hour.
Okay, weII, I'm gonna go to sIeep
now. And I think you shouId soon. . .
. . .because you need your beauty rest.
Okay? Okay, good night.
I miss everyone in Bay City so much.
I don 't know how I'll survive
without Benny.
And my best friend, good little Mary.
Serious Mary, Benny and I...
... we were inseparable.
I made this for you.
It's tin and painted on one side
with goId dust.
-It's not reaI goId dust.
-Ann, we're ready to go'
Where do you want
the cookies and the sandwiches?
Mom, thanks.
You didn't give her aII the cookies?
CaII us from the road.
-You'II visit us.
-She doesn't have a pIace to Iive.
-Stop worrying about it, Ma.
-Even a job.
-She's got the schooI job.
-She does not, just taIked to someone.
When wiII you have faith in me?
When you see things as they are.
-Don't take any wooden nickeIs.
-Right.
Okay, thanks.
Sorry, Ted.
I'II write.
Ann! Come on
or I'II Ieave without you'
Benny'
Ben'
You destroyed the photos
of me in my underwear?
I did, Mary. I promise.
Let's go! We'II caII from the road.
-I Iove you.
-I Iove you too, Grandma.
Ann! Just in case you find
a skating rink out there.
Thanks, Ted.
I Iove you. You're the best
stepdad a girI couId have.
Here's a good one:
"PooI, waIk-in cIosets. . .
. . .security, vauIted ceiIings. "
-VauIted. I Iove it.
-Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I couIdn't heIp
but overhearing.
I thought I might heIp you.
I'm GaiI Letterfine.
-Westside ReaIty.
-Oh.
-What do you want?
-Something in BeverIy HiIIs.
-I'm AdeIe August. My daughter, Ann.
-Hi.
Hi.
She's not awake.
We're from Wisconsin.
-I don't know anyone from Wisconsin--
-I'm awake.
-You Iive in BeverIy HiIIs?
-Santa Monica. FormerIy BeI Air.
FormerIy Brentwood.
I've had many formerIies in my Iife.
I'm fine now.
I'm singIe, I'm free and I Iove it.
-Most of the time.
-Excuse me.
-She wants to be an actress.
-Don't they aII?
Operator.
TeII her it's her granddaughter,
and I'II pay her back.
What do we have aIong BeverIy Vista?
BeverIy HiIIs-adjacent.
It's not posh, but it's within
the schooI district.
What are you doing? You okay?
GaiI found something.
She's raising three teenagers aIone.
Husband ran off with an accountant.
Come with me whiIe I pee.
She didn't say so,
but I think she has a gIass eye.
It makes somebody interesting.
You know what I mean?
Interesting in a mysterious way.
You want a ride?
Ann, there you are.
Your mom wants you.
-I saw her.
-I think we might've found a pIace.
It's hard making changes,
but you have to get used to it.
-Life is fuII of them.
-Where did you go?
I was taIking to you.
I come out and you're gone.
You didn't get the job.
It's in the bag, baby.
-Are you serious?
-Yes'
-I hate my hair.
-It's an asset.
-I want to cut it.
-Over my dead body.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-They're dressed for the beach.
-The smart girIs are inside.
Baby--
I hate you.
We'II taIk about that Iater.
Good Iuck'
How about "good Iuck" for me?
How do I Iook?
Just back off'
This is our new speech pathoIogist,
AdeIe August.
-She's from Bay City, Wisconsin.
-America's DairyIand.
-Wisconsin. George FrankIin, history.
-History?
-Room 1 2 is to the right?
-I'II show you.
Thank you so much.
Not exactIy Bay City,
but you get used to it.
Did they throw out that furniture?
Is that garbage?
UnbeIievabIe.
Don't scratch the car.
On days off, we'd drive to relax.
We drove just anywhere.
She was in awe of the homes...
...and palm trees and movie stars
on public sidewalks.
She was in love with Beverly Hills.
-I Iike the circuIar driveway.
-I want the corner room.
-I'd cIimb out that window.
-I've got the one overIooking the pooI.
That one's a beauty.
With the cute bIue shutters.
Look at this house'
This is the house I want. BeautifuI.
It says, "By appointment onIy. "
-It says, "Do not disturb occupants. "
-It'II be fun.
It's okay. It'II be fun.
PIease think about it.
-You're the reaItor?
-Can I heIp you?
What a-- He gave me a kiss'
-This is CaIIey.
-You must be the owner.
I'm AdeIe August,
and this is my baby, Heather.
Can I heIp you?
We have no appointment but my
husband, a doctor at UCLA--
-That's minutes from here.
-ExactIy.
We drove by and had to stop.
We'd Iove to see the house.
-Do you mind?
-Not at aII.
Here's my card,
and a setup on the property.
The house is from the 1 920s.
It has aII its originaI integrity.
We aIso have a wood-burning firepIace.
There are seven in the house.
There's so much Iight.
It's a very happy house.
-Happy, isn't it?
-Happy.
Here's a beautifuI, bright bedroom.
There's the pooI.
It's a IoveIy master suite.
No, it's my daughter's bedroom.
She's away at coIIege.
-Where is she?
-Back East. Princeton.
I want to go to coIIege back East.
-You must miss her terribIy.
-But we're so proud.
Daddy wiII be here next week.
I want him to see this house.
I'II show you the master bedroom.
It's got a great waIk-in cIoset.
It aIso has a fantastic
Jacuzzi tub. . . .
Hello?
-What's up, pervert?
-Who is this?
-It's Hot Stuff.
Ann.
-Hey, Benny.
-Where are you?
CaIIing from someone's bedroom.
What are you doing?
Hal's taking us to the park.
He got that new truck.
-Why are you whispering?
-How's Grandma?
She's fine. You're in
someone's bedroom?
I'II write. Get my Iast one?
Yeah, I got them all.
I Iiked the one where
she kicked you out of the car.
She's crazy. I think I might
kiII her in her sIeep.
-I have to go.
-Heather Ann. . . .
That was so much fun.
-You said we'd buy it'
-I said we might.
And that my father's coming,
he's a doctor?
Why were you in the daughter's room?
CaIIing Benny.
What? Ann'
I had to say your dad's a doctor.
She gets money from her husband.
She'd think I couIdn't afford it.
Oh, and Iike you can afford it.
You couIdn't afford the bathroom.
Be optimistic
Don 't you be a grumpy
When the road gets bumpy
Just smile and be happy
-Good morning, AdeIe.
-Morning, George.
-Grand CouIee Dam. Ever been there?
-No.
Hoover Dam?
No.
I'm not reaIIy into dams.
"I'II get a Iawyer and sue
for invasion of privacy.
-Stop reading my diary, Mother. "
-CooI.
-Did she say anything?
-Never did it again.
-I wish they'd Ieave me aIone.
-I Iove being aIone.
-Hi.
-Hi, Peter.
-You run good. You got good form.
-Yeah.
Not a cIoud in the sky today.
-You ever read T.S. EIiot?
-What?
Four Quartets. ReaIIy good.
Why do you run with a book?
BaIance, I guess.
Kariba Dam. It impounds
the Zambezi River, forms Kariba Lake.
-It's nice.
-I went to paint it after coIIege.
You painted pictures of dams?
It was my dream:
traveI the worId and paint.
What happened?
I don't know. "One dam thing
Ied to another dam thing. "
I became a history teacher.
But one of these days--
One of these days.
Oh, my God. Get away from my car'
Look what he's doing'
No. Stop it'
Look how deep--
Look what he did to my car'
Mom, it's just a scratch.
Just a scratch?
Do you know how much it costs
to fix "just a scratch"?
I can't work at this schooI.
I can't taIk to you! No sympathy'
The tiIes are aII cracked.
Chipped.
We're sinking.
I have to keep us afIoat.
Every time I think we're starting
to get somewhere. . .
. . .everything faIIs apart.
Jesus'
Nothing works in this apartment'
It's just a scratch on the car.
Maybe if you got yourseIf. . .
. . .an after-schooI job
you'd know what I'm taIking about.
You don't know what things cost,
how to manage money--
What is that now?
-You didn't pay the biII, did you?
-I paid it'
Maybe I won't even pay the biII again.
Maybe we'II. . . .
We couId Iive. . .
. . .in the dark. . .
. . .Iike IittIe bears in a cave,
huh, Pooh Bear?
Just. . . .
Okay, Iet's go to Denny's.
Ann?
-Ann, where are you?
-I'm going to bed.
I reaIIy thought I paid it.
I reaIIy think I did pay it.
I Iove you. Say hi to Benny
and UncIe Jimmy and Aunt CaroI.
Lots of kisses. Bye.
Hi, Mom. How are y'aII doing?
What isn't fair?
I put her on because Ann
needs a decent home. . .
. . .so we need cash for a down payment.
What I need from you is some heIp.
SeII my Iand, that's how.
It's the Iand that Daddy--
She hung up.
Grandma hung up on you?
Yeah.
-Let's dress up and go out to dinner.
-What?
You Iove that French pIace.
That's what we need.
We need a bed for me,
a desk, sheets, toweIs. . .
-. . .not to eat in a French restaurant.
-Honey.
My daddy used to say:
"When Iife's rough. . .
. . .and you onIy have a dime,
get your shoes shined. "
Get dressed.
They raised their prices.
Why don't the two of us--?
-Want to hear our speciaIs?
-We know what we want.
-I'd Iike to hear the speciaIs.
-We have veaI St. Jacques--
We'II have two smaII saIads
and share the veaI, right?
I'm hungry. Why don't you
have the veaI St. Jacques?
-I'II have the duck a I'orange.
-Any appetizer?
-I'II have the shrimp in garIic sauce.
-And to drink?
-Just water.
-BottIed. A big bottIe, pIease.
Okay. Thank you.
Know what? I'm hungry
and we're not at Denny's.
So, if someone sees me eat
duck a I'orange. . .
. . .who knows what effect
it'II have on my Iife?
Sit up straight. You're sIouching.
I took out a newspaper ad once.
" 15-year-old seeks home.
Neat, pretty, good student. "
I got 79 replies.
I never opened them.
I was afraid of the temptation.
-"Passion. "
-Our first Christmas away from home.
Do you customize scents?
No? That's a shame.
My mother paid enough of our bills
so we could buy presents.
Lavender. What do you think?
We didn't buy too much.
-I don't know what to get Benny.
-What did you get me?
-Nothing.
-You did.
What did you get me?
No, don't show me.
Ann, hi! Isn't it obscene,
aII this money being spent?
-I'm Janice PerIeman.
-I'm Ann's mother.
-She's my mother.
-Hi.
-You two Iook aIike.
-No, I Iook Iike my dad.
-Just his chin.
-I Iike your chin, I do.
I gotta go. My mother's waiting.
Christmas Day, we're having
a party from 4 to 8.
-WiII you come, both of you?
-Thanks. That's sweet.
ReaIIy? I'II teII you more at schooI.
Everybody's coming. Bye.
Everybody Iikes her.
She's on student counciI.
Her brother edits the paper.
-What does her father do?
-I think he's a doctor.
WeII, it might be fun.
-You wanna go?
-Do you want me to go?
It'II be a chance to show ourseIves
off. The car's Iooking great again.
Great.
Her mom Iooked very eIegant.
You're eIegant, Mom.
We both are. We've got taste, huh?
PeopIe see us and say, "That's an
attractive mother and daughter! "
Where do they Iive?
-Why are you doing this?
-Which one is it?
-That one. Now Iet's go home.
-Oh, my God'
It goes aII the way around the bIock'
We're both going to a party.
Do you wanna taIk to her again?
Just say Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas'
Merry Christmas to everybody.
I Iove you.
Give a big hug to Benny for me.
Okay. I Iove you. Bye.
I'm gonna go get dressed
and try on my new neckIace.
Mom, it's 4:00.
Are you going to get dressed?
It takes you an hour to get ready.
The party wiII be over by then.
-You said you wanted to go.
-I want to get up the pine needIes. . .
. . .and vacuum those cIosets.
Maybe wash the kitchen fIoor, because
I reaIized what wiII make me happy. . .
. . .is to Iook around this pIace,
and see it's spic-and-span.
It's one fun thing
we can do for Christmas.
Then you shouId go.
AII your friends wiII be there. And
that boy, Peter, wiII be there, right?
-What are you going to do?
-Don't worry about me.
I've got a miIIion things to do.
I want our first Christmas
in Los AngeIes to be perfect.
Aren't things bad enough here?
Why are you doing this to me?
You're right. I'm sorry.
You want me to drive you there?
-Want me to drive you?
-No, I can waIk.
AII right. WeII, then go.
Go ahead.
Otherwise we'II just hang around here
aII day taIking about our siIIy Iives.
Oh, gosh. I just had
the strongest memory of my father.
I'm going.
I'm sorry you never got to know
your grandfather, or your father.
But I know it means something to you
to find your father, sweetie.
I promise, we wiII.
-I'm going.
-Okay.
Maybe we can taIk about your father
when you come back.
I'II be here. I'm not
going anywhere. I'II wait.
I'm sorry.
I thought I couId go. . .
. . .but I couIdn't.
You know what we need?
Some sugar in our bIood.
You wanna get some ice cream?
-I don't want ice cream.
-Sure you do.
Is that what I want, Mom?
It wouId cheer us up.
Okay, Mother, Iet's get our sugar.
-And they've got a new fIavor.
-Great. Let's go.
I'II get your jacket.
-Just one IittIe--
-No. We're cIosed earIy today.
It's Christmas.
Christmas'
Merry Christmas, officer.
You're not working today?
You see that red curb?
See that "No Stopping" sign?
Oh, my God'
I'm so sorry. I had no idea.
She needed an ice cream.
-Don't bIame it on me.
-I'm expIaining to him--
-I hate it when you do this to me.
-Do what?
-It's our Christmas tradition.
-I didn't want ice cream.
-Ann?
-She'II be back.
-Excuse me, she won't be back.
-You stay by the car.
-Lady, wait by the car'
-AII right'
Ann, come here.
Ann! Wait.
I toId her not to park there.
I didn't even want any ice cream.
-She's trying to beat a ticket.
-She has Iots.
-Now, now'
-Don't taIk to me Iike a IittIe girI.
You don't even understand.
I'II Ieave her one of these days.
I'm sure you wiII. But not today.
-Why not today?
-You shouId Ieave when you're caIm.
When you're rationaI.
You Ieave her when you're ready
not to come back. Understand?
You from Wisconsin?
How do you know?
-Your pIates. You Iiving here now?
-Yes.
-Hi, Ann.
-Hey.
-I want you to register that car.
-Yes, sir.
-Get a CaIifornia Iicense.
-Yes.
-And pay attention to posted signs.
-Yes, sir.
When I roII by again,
I don't want to see your car.
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
Merry Christmas, Ann.
Let's move that vehicIe.
Did he just wink at you?
That's an unusuaI Iaw enforcement
officer. What did he say to you?
He said never to do that to me again,
or you'II be taken to prison.
You'II never see me again, and
you'II have to eat ice cream aIone.
-He didn't say the ice cream business.
-Yes, he did.
-He wants to adopt me, I'm pretty.
-Not funny. Don't do this again.
-Don't you do it.
-No, you.
No, it's you.
I was just trying to get out
of a parking ticket.
-You didn't get one.
-Thanks, Ann.
Your fiancé wiII be back here
to see if we moved the car.
I will always love that policeman.
He told me what I needed to know.
I'll always carry a soft spot
for the Los Angeles Police Department.
I wish he had adopted me.
Grandma told me that my father
got remarried and lived in Reno.
How many Hisham Badirs
could there be in Reno?
Hi. Do you have a number
for a Mr. Hisham Badir, pIease?
B-A-D-I-R.
Residence. H-I-S-H-A-M.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
When I was young, my mother hummed
one of my father's tunes...
...before we went to sleep.
He wrote my mother love songs.
Sometimes I would imagine
my father coming to rescue me.
Hi, Ann.
HeIIo, Peter.
You got that isosceIes
triangIe thing straight?
That baffIes me.
I got a new trumpet.
You wanna see it?
-I'm working, Peter.
-Sorry.
-Your mom's reaIIy pretty.
-I'II teII her.
What's your dad do?
He's a songwriter.
I wrote some songs.
You wanna hear one?
Not now, Peter.
You wanna feeI my puIse?
It's beating reaIIy fast.
Ba-boom, ba-boom, ba-boom.
ReaIIy fast.
I've toId you,
the tiIes are chipped.
No water pressure.
Cabinet's handIes are broken.
You don't have a Iife.
Can't you fix--?
I am taIking to you. Hey'
Mom, your pants'
I can't taIk to you Iike this.
Listen, I am teIIing you that--
Not onIy is the tiIe chipped,
the carpets are fiIthy'
I've got a fungus on my foot.
Who Iived here, a hockey team?
I can't Iive Iike this'
But you can Iive in an empty pIace
for six months with just a mattress?'
Damn it'
Turn it down'
I hate this pIace'
I hate my job! I hate my foot'
You're not having sex
with anyone, are you?
What?
-You know.
-No, I don't know.
-We have to move.
-We can't. We have a Iease.
What do you mean, am I having sex?
We moved anyway.
Over the next year, we moved a lot.
We got used to it.
Oh, honey, Iet me heIp you.
-It's apartment number eight?
-Yeah, eight.
This one had furniture,
thanks to Miss Letterfine.
Gail and Mom
have become good friends.
It's so coIorfuI.
My mom dragged me to an audition.
She wouldn 't give up her fantasy
of me becoming an actress.
Ann?
We did our work and kept healthy.
--and exhale from your navel
to your backbone.
We went to the beach
and felt sorry for people back home.
-Where are you going?
-Over there.
-There's no one there.
-I need peace and quiet.
-You wanna be near that beach cIub.
-Yes, pIease.
Here's a good spot.
-You've a cute body. Show it off more.
-Show off your body.
-I pIan to. Where are you going?
-Japan.
Heads up'
Sorry about that.
That's okay.
Ooh.
You're strong.
WiId thing.
Ann. Come here, sweetie.
This is Dr. Spritzer.
This is my daughter, Ann.
-Ah, a big girI.
-Oh, yes, we're more Iike sisters.
-So you're the actress.
-Not me. My mom is.
SiIIy, don't be shy.
He's an orthodontist.
He works with actresses.
He did Heather LockIear, her teeth.
I was teIIing him that
we were discussing your overbite.
She has a nice smiIe.
The bottom is strange.
They don't Iook so strange.
Josh! Come on'
Be right there.
-AdeIe, you pIay good baII.
-You too.
Take care of those teeth.
An actress has to smiIe.
-See you.
That's probabIy his wife.
-Why did you taIk about my teeth?
-It won't Iast.
-Mom? Mom'
-Here I am.
Guess what? Benny's coming.
-I missed you.
-Hey, come on.
Hi.
What do you think, Benny?
You got more Mercedes on one street
than aII Wisconsin.
-Benny wants to see a movie star.
-Who?