Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
I'm looking for a mechanic.
Anybody here fit that description?
I might be able to help you.
What do you need?
I need it fixed right away. I need
someone who knows what they're doing.
I'm not that busy.
So, what's the problem?
I'm not sure. Maybe you ought to
get under the hood and check it out.
Yeah, maybe I better.
Looks okay from here.
Great customer service.
Little bit of cleaning,
little bit of paint...
...this place will be ready
for business.
About time for me to play
in the Super Bowl.
Those guys are gonna take you apart.
Okay, we're gonna do it this time!
Ready?
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah!
Hike!
To the left. You can do it. Cut back.
Here it comes.
All right!
Okay, suckers walk. Suckers walk.
Hey. Hey, suckers walk.
Go on. Suckers walk. Come on.
Suckers walk!
- Hey, Frankie, what's that mean?
- It means everything's okay.
So how do you think I did?
Pretty good with the sixth graders.
You really know how to make a guy
feel great, you know that?
What's the matter?
We don't look too happy today?
I'm missing you already.
Pretty soon you'll be so sick
of seeing me...
...you'll pray to have some time
on your own. You know that?
- I don't believe you.
- Yeah, believe it.
Now that's Italian.
- I gotta go.
- No. No.
- I gotta go. Yes. Yes.
So I'm not so good against 10-year-olds?
I should try a different sport?
Yeah, golf.
- Golf?
- Yeah.
- Wanna see my swing?
- I'd like to see you in whites.
- Some swing.
- You see me on the golf course?
You're lucky I have a sense of humour.
I would take that personal.
Time to go to work.
- All right, be good.
- Bye.
Wait a minute.
I got something for you.
What's this?
It's supposed to bring you luck.
It's nice.
Thanks.
I could use it.
- How'd it go, Frank? Good furlough?
- The best.
- Did you see that game?
- I have to admit, I missed it.
- It was awesome.
- Was it?
- Yes. You missed a good one.
- I missed a good one?
- I had more fun than you this weekend.
- I bet you did.
Here you go, Roger.
- How's the diesel running, Jimmy?
- Forget it. It stops, it stalls.
- It don't go.
- You got water in the fuel line.
Open your mouth.
- You sure?
- I'd bet time on it.
- Take it off.
- All right.
I'll see you later, Jimmy.
- I'll give you more starch next time.
- Yeah, do that.
Say hi to the wife.
How you doing there, man?
Frank! What'd you bring me?
Here you go. Go kill yourself.
- I thought you'd bring me a girl.
- I had one...
...but the guards decided to keep her.
I can't depend on you.
Let me ask you something else.
- Did you go see the garage?
- It's beautiful.
- No garage I ever stuck up was beautiful.
- This one is.
Can I tell you something?
I'm getting out soon. I don't come cheap.
But you know I know my way
around cars. You need help, call me.
- I fix them, I don't steal them.
- I was framed.
What? I was framed.
- What is this, Jimmy?
- I don't know, but it's official.
Crack 210.
- On your feet, Leone.
- What do you want?
- Take him.
- What are you doing here?
- You're being transferred.
- Transferred where?
- That's not necessary.
- Step back! He's in our custody now.
You got the wrong guy!
Transferred where?
Talk to me. Where am I going?
- Get in there now!
- Where am I going?
Hey!
Where are we going?
Hey! Talk to me!
Let's go, Leone. Come on!
- Get his ass out here!
- Come on, get out!
- Where the hell are we? I wanna know!
- Shut up!
You got the wrong man!
You made a mistake!
There's no mistake.
Welcome to Gateway, Leone.
- Drumgoole?
- That's Warden Drumgoole, convict.
- Captain.
- Move him!
Move your ass!
Let's go. Come on!
You'll be issued one bar of soap,
two rolls of toilet paper per month.
Somebody steals...
Turn your ass around!
Somebody steals them, or you lose
them, wipe your ass with your shirt.
You have one uniform.
Your number is 5-1-0. Remember it.
This is C-wing. You will eat, shower
and take your yard time with your wing.
There's 6 counts a day. Miss one,
you're in the hole. Miss two...
...I will put you in the house of pain.
Convict...
...two things.
One: I am Meissner.
Two: Never fuck with Meissner.
Inside.
- Sir, what about the cuffs?
- Let him get used to them.
You better watch your back, man!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Nineteen-one.
Nineteen-one! Crack it!
Oh, yeah, you better not
eyeball me, boy.
How were your accommodations last
night? Like your mama used to do you?
- You did his mama, didn't you?
- Twice.
Hey!
Open the door! You hear me?
Hello, Frank.
In the old days, the warden would've
come down that private passageway...
...to this execution chamber to witness
the putting to death of a criminal.
120 men and 4 women were electrocuted
in that chair before it was retired.
Beautiful, isn't it? When I came here,
it was falling apart. I restored it...
...put it back into working order to
remind me of how things ought to be.
It's nearly five years since you
escaped from Treadmore.
- Time flies when you're having fun.
- In all my years as warden there...
...you're the only one who escaped.
- So I read in the papers.
Yes, you did.
You and your lawyer saw to it...
...that everything made it
into the papers. The media.
Distorting the facts,
making a criminal into a hero...
...and a warden into a criminal.
You took my future away from me.
You and those politicians. They sent
you to Norwood. That's a country club.
I ended up here in Gateway,
the worst shit-hole in the system.
You don't remember, do you?
I asked you.
No, I begged you, Drumgoole.
Do you remember that?
I had two weeks before I was released.
I asked for one hour to visit...
...with that old man before he died.
- I was doing my job.
There's a lot of ways to do your job!
You could've given me an escorted leave,
could've had armed guards.
You broke the law.
You broke the law, and I was punished!
- I got five years. I paid my debt!
- Not to me. But you're going to.
I've only got six months left
on my sentence.
In Gateway,
six months could be a lifetime.
This is hard time. You have no rights
here unless I give them to you.
You feel no pleasure unless
I tell you you can. This is hell...
...and I'm going to give you
the guided tour.
Okay, tough guy. Open your mouth.
Roll your tongue around.
You trying to kiss me, huh?
Let me see your ears.
What are you looking at, asshole?
- You check his nose?
- Checked it.
Good.
This is a delousing chamber.
Don't breathe.
X ylon-profic gas can be harmful to
your lungs. Stand with your legs apart...
...arms out and away from your body.
When I tell you, take a deep breath.
Hold it for 30 seconds.
Start now.
Ten seconds.
Not yet. He can take more.
Braden...
...you'll learn that inmates are physically
more capable than you could imagine.
If you underestimate them...
...it will cost you dearly.
Watch out for the birds.
- What the hell you doing?
- Sorry.
Yo, Billy, get that weight.
Move it, ace. That's my spot.
That's my spot too.
- Any spot that isn't yours?
- Nope, they're all mine.
You wanna use it, you gotta pay.
Not so fast, ace.
I'm not gonna gouge you.
That little thing around your neck,
that'll buy you a spot for the day.
- Put a fucking hole in your heart.
- All right, break it up! Break it up!
I said, break it up! Back off!
Spread 'em. Back off!
- All right, Weber, drop the shank.
- There ain't no shank, Braden.
- All right, let's go.
- You motherfucker!
- Spread 'em, goddamn it.
- You're making a big mistake, asshole.
- You go in the hole for carrying that.
- Where's your witness, your evidence?
Well, where is it?
- He saw it.
- He didn't.
- You saw him carrying the shank, right?
- I didn't see nothing.
- You're making a bad mistake, Braden.
- Get him the fuck out of here!
He would have put that shank in you.
What did you cover for him for?
You got your rules, we got ours.
Hey, hey, hey. I do know the face,
and I do know the name.
Hey, Frank. Frank Leone, right?
Name's Dallas.
I was in Treadmore
right before you busted out.
- You were on A-block, weren't you?
- Yeah, I was on A-block.
- Good memory.
- Treadmore doesn't have an A-block.
- Watch your feet.
- Okay, dig it.
Look, look,
I was there on transfer, man.
Less than two hours,
but I know all about you.
- You're looking at a devoted fan.
- D.T.A.
D.T.A., okay. What's that, man?
Don't trust anybody.
Words to survive by. Watch your feet.
- D.T.A.
You gotta trust somebody.
Let me hip you to the joint.
See this fat tub of shit?
That's Manly. His partner's Wiley.
They're sadistic pigs.
They ain't happy unless they hurt you.
I mean, if the warden wants to put
the boot to you, he uses them.
The black dude in the booth
is Captain Meissner.
Now he runs the guards, okay?
He's one bad dude.
We already met. I gotta do my work.
Okay. Okay. Cool. Cool, man.
So listen, Frank...
...when you decide to make your break,
and I know you will...
...you come talk to me.
You come talk to Dallas.
Okay? Anything you want,
anything you need, man...
...I can get it. Anything.
All right? Okay?
No way. No damn way!
You're always crying about how you
need a man who knows engines.
I brought you the man, Homes.
Look, don't "Homes" me.
The only thing you brought is trouble.
- Come on, Eclipse.
- I heard all about you, Leone.
Whatever is between you and
Drumgoole ain't coming in here.
The boys ain't got no problem with me.
I ain't got no problem with the boys.
Come on, Eclipse.
You're making me look bad.
- I promised the dude a job. You owe me.
- I don't owe you or nobody nothing.
Hey, you! Get your face out of that
motor! Get your face out of there.
You don't know nothing about motors.
Stay away from it! Okay?
It's been a while since I've seen
an old 265 small block.
That's the last time
you're gonna see one in this shop.
Come on. Frank, we can work this out.
We're all gentlemen here.
It's his place. He knows what he
wants. It's okay. Thanks anyway.
Thanks. You made me look beautiful.
I appreciate the endorsement.
Hey, Frank. Hold up, man.
You didn't want this job anyway, man.
Greasy fingers, oil on your clothes...
- Don't worry. I'll take care of you.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
- All right?
- Prison joke.
I lost my watch. Why don't you give me
a hand looking for it.
Roll your ass on out of here, man.
Officer Vazquez, you ought to
put on a few pounds. You look frail.
Frank, I meant what I said. I'm gonna
get you something good, easy, cool.
- You're gonna love it.
- Shut up. Get inside. Shut up. Inside!
Here's your shit from Norwood, Leone.
All right. Lock in!
Problem?
No, I got no problems.
I wanna know what's going on.
All I know is that he's in
the general population...
I don't give a damn about the general
population! I wanna know about Frank.
- I'm not leaving...
- Calm down. He's all right.
He was a model prisoner at Norwood.
Why bring him here?
Routine transfer.
- Hey, Frank?
- What?
Hey, man.
- It's hot in here, man.
- I know. But at least it's easy.
I know, man.
I'm sorry, I didn't do too good.
Walk with me. I gotta show you
something. It's important.
- No. Here, you try.
- No. Come on, man.
- You'll like it.
- I'm not into hard labour.
- It's cool. It's easy.
- Okay. There. I'm burnt out. Come on.
Come on, you're gonna love this.
Watch the steam, Frank.
I got these off this old trustee.
He did the plumbing here.
Everybody thought he was a nut.
Doesn't mean he wasn't smart.
- Come on, hurry up.
- All right, cool.
The tunnels under every cellblock,
they lead to the steam plant, okay?
I go out across the steam lines.
Dig this.
I shimmy, okay? Across the
steam pipes to the sally port, okay?
Over there, there's trucks coming
and going. I wait for my time...
...l'm on a truck that's leaving.
I'm dearly departing Dallas, man. Huh?
You're the doctor. Operate.
I want your professional opinion.
Let's run it backwards. I see these
trucks. They stop running at 9:00.
At 9:00, the tower guards are at full
staff and all the inmates are awake.
Before you go 10 feet, every con in the
joint knows you're gone. And this thing...
...this shimmy?
- Shimmy slide.
You're gonna shimmy slide across
200 yards of steam pipe...
...running at 160 degrees
and get away with it?
You try, they'll change your name from
Departing Dallas to Deep-Fried Dallas.
- Just a thought, man.
- The thought that counts.
- I got a plane to catch. Thanks a lot.
- Hey, Dallas?
You got a cigarette?
It's my last one. Here.
Go ahead. Finish that.
It ain't much,
but it's the thought that counts, right?
Last call. Mess hall, last call.
Mess, coming up.
Looks like some delicious garbage
stew. Just like Mom used to make.
That's why I shot her.
- Can I have some gravy, please?
- You want some gravy?
- Here's your gravy.
- You got it all over my food.
- Move!
- What's your problem?
- Nothing. Move it!
- What's that kid's story?
In for murder.
Claims he was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Waiting while his buddy bought beer.
Didn't know the guy was packing heat.
Two guys dead. Kid's doing
the Big Bitch now: Double life.
He'll make parole when he's about 400.
Move it!
What are you, a slow study or what?
Screw that guy.
So I didn't get a chance
to make the reservation...
...so why don't we get a seat
over there.
- What are you doing?
- Taking this.
- Why don't you go take something else?
- I'll throw you through this table.
- Want some cake?
- Are you chumping off on me?
- Not hungry. Want this?
- Who are you?
Nobody. Here.
- I'm on a diet. This spot taken?
- Why don't you stand up to that dirtbag?
Shut up.
He just saved you a lot of healing.
What's your name?
Why does anybody need a name
in a joint like this?
Helps when you get mail.
Oh, yeah. I need a name?
They call me Killer.
That's original. Did you think that up,
or did someone give you a hand with it?
- I call myself what I want, okay?
- Okay.
Killer, this is Dallas. I'm Frank.
Dallas, what do you think this is here?
- Wanna give me an idea?
- These might be peas.
They might not.
They might be toxic waste.
Who cares? It's all crap.
- Eat vegetables to grow big and strong.
- Stick your vegetables. Nobody asked.
We got 325 other killers in here.
Most, unlike you, live up to it.
Put your leg in the aisle.
Be ready to move.
Hey, nobody tells me
to do nothing, all right?
You always gotta be ready to move first.
You just might make it to first base.
First base.
There's a name for him, huh?
- It's good to be outside.
- It's cold.
It's not that bad.
It's good to keep moving.
How come you got this up attitude?
How can you be up in this joint?
It's a mindset. Your body has to
be in here, but your brain doesn't.
As long as you keep moving,
you don't become a piece of this place.
- What's that, like, guru stuff?
- Yeah.
- Maybe I should become a guru.
- You getting sarcastic?
Fucking birds.
Fucking birds don't eat in the rain.
- Yeah, well, they'll come back.
- You save your bread for me tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
Put that on your list, okay?
Thanks.
Why you talking crazy, man?
It's a waste of time.
To you, it's a waste.
To him, it's all he's got.
That's more than you got.
In here, you gotta respect that.
You don't get much, and what you got,
you gotta protect. You know that?
You don't know nothing yet.
Come on, let's run.
- Come on, Frank.
- Bitch, bitch, bitch.
I'm gonna get wet.
Send you my laundry bills.
Feel something, Leone?
Wanna play? They're a man short.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Hey, punk! When you gonna paint your
nails and answer to the name "bitch"?
- You got a big mouth. Keep it shut.
- You fucker, I'll tear your ass off!
You wanna play? We'll play.
You talk too much. Let's play.
Goddamn right we'll play. You
and I'll play later, you little fuck.
You want more, Leone? We got more
for you. Come on. Come on.
- Stay down!
- That's a cheap shot!
- What kind of game is this?
- This ain't no game. This is a lesson.
- Got something to say?
- Yeah.
- Say it! Say it!
- First down!
Fuck you. That's your last one!
You're dead, Leone!
You'll never last the fucking game!
Get in there, hit him.
Come on, get in there.
Set!
Hut-one. Hut-two. Hut-three.
I'll beat you up, man.
Frank!
Hut-one. Hut-two. Hut-three.
Fuck up! Get over on that other team.
That's who you're playing for anyway.
- What took you so long?
- You need the help...
...and I need the exercise.
So call the play.
You're dead, Leone!
- Shit, what hit me?
- F-train, son. F-train.
Don't lay down on me now. Come on.
Come on, Leone.
Come on, you son of a bitch!
All right,
I'm going over tackle on two.
All right, Frank!
Ready.
Set.
You're dead!
Hut-one.
Hut-two.
Go, baby!
Come on, Frank!
We did it!
Hey, come on Wiley. Come on, man!
Next time I want, you give.
Move it. Out. The game is over.
Let's go. You don't listen, do you?
- You okay? Come on. Come on.
- Put him down!
You ain't no doctor. He's on his own.
Get inside.
Real badass, huh?
See you inside, Leone.
Count time, 10 minutes. All inmates
will return to their wings for count.
Let's go, men!
You won't break me.
Still interested in the job?
Yeah, I am.
You sure know your way around
an engine. Who taught you?
This old man named Galleti.
Took me off the street
when I was 14.
Taught me that I could do something
besides hanging out on corners.
- Where is everybody?
- It's quitting time.
- Is that who you broke out for?
- Yeah. I owed him.
Tell me, what put you in the joint
in the first place?
One night these punks broke into the
garage and put a beating on Galleti.
The whole neighbourhood knew about it.
The cops knew.
But these punks were connected,
so the cops didn't do anything. I did.
So after all the smoke had cleared...
...these guys were in the hospital, and I
was doing time for aggravated assault.
- Care to join me in a little contraband?
- Why not?
I can see why they call you Eclipse.
- I do block a lot of sun, don't I?
- That you do.
I had a guy on the outside that used
to get me good Havanas. Not this crap.
But someday... Someday.
Yeah, someday.
- That's not bad.
- At least they're cheap.
Eclipse, what do you
got hiding back there?
That's my baby.
- Good bodywork.
- Call this here vehicle Maybelline.
- Hello, Maybelline.
- This is my baby.
Nice.
There it is. '65 Ford Mustang V8.
Two eighty-nine, with 225 horsepower.
- When did you last turn her over?
- She's been dead for 15 years.
Couple guys tried to get her going
and couldn't. I'm a body man myself.
- Mind if I give it a try?
- It's a dead issue.
Nothing's dead around here
until it's buried.
Save the headstone, man.
Easy, easy...
Eclipse. Nothing's dead till
it's buried. Did I tell you that?
I love it!
- A toast. Let's do the poem, all right?
- What poem?
- The poem.
- It's a jailhouse poem.
- Something we all wrote.
- Excuse me.
When we're in a sober mood
We worry, work and think
When we're in a drunken mood
We gamble, play and drink
But when our moods are over
When our time has come to pass
We hope they bury us upside down
So the warden can kiss our ass
- Amen!
- I like that.
- You like that, huh?
- It's a little catchy.
This is the best.
I mean, this is good, man.
- What's wrong, man?
- Nothing.
I wouldn't smoke around this, but
it tastes as good as any dollar wine.
Check, please.
Wait.
When my moods are over
And my...
That's not it. Wait a minute.
You married,
or thinking about it, or what?
Are you proposing to me?
You're not my type.
- No, I'm not married.
- Not married?
- Plan to get married when you get out?
- Yeah, that's the plan.
- You know, I had this really nice girl.
- Yeah?
She was nice. And we were in love.
And we started talking
about getting married.
She's got three brothers, like,
about 1 percent retarded, these guys.
They throw a beating on me.
Some guys don't appreciate romance.
Don't take it personal.
She wrote me for a while.
Then it just stopped.
That's when it hit me: I ain't
ever gonna be with a girl again.
I'm gonna end up like Eclipse,
kissing pictures in magazines.
There's so many things I ain't done.
- I ain't never learned how to drive.
- What?
I ain't never learned
how to drive a car.
I hope we don't get a speeding ticket.
I'd hate to end up in jail.
Don't be a wise guy. You wanna learn
to drive? This is the best I can do.
Okay. Now cut it sharp.
That's it. All right.
Hang a left on 42nd Street. We'll go
to Broadway and check out the action.
Broadway?
We're doing circles in a garage.
Come on, First,
work here with me, okay?
You wanna stay here
or check out the action?
I wanna check out the action,
of course.
- Turn left on 42nd Street.
- I got it.
Look, the place is jumping.
Look at the action here!
Check out those ladies!
Wanna come for a ride in my new car?
- Hey, baby!
- They ain't responding.
They're not your type.
When were you last in Atlantic City?
- I ain't never been there.
- You are now. What do you think?
- I don't know. What does it resemble?
- It's the best. Look at the lights.
The Boardwalk
is jumping day and night.
It's hot music. You got high rollers.
You got parties.
You got money. You got gambling.
You got 10,000 chorus girls!
Hey, baby, wanna come for a ride
in my new vehicle?
Man. Yo, that was great, man.
I hate to tell you, your engine just blew
a rod. You're ready for Indianapolis.
You got the touch.
Frank, let me ask you one favour, man.
I appreciate the drive
and everything...
...but none of this is real unless I
hear this engine kick over just once.
If I turn the engine on, the guards
will bust in here and grab us...
...and throw us in the hole forever.
Forget it.
Come on, Frank. Just for 10 seconds.
It'll last for the rest of my life.
You're such a pain in the ass.
Come on, Frank. Let me just
hear that engine. We built it, man.
All right, go on. Ten seconds.
Yeah! All right, looking good!
- Ain't that great?
- It's beautiful, baby.
Hit it, one time!
All right, one more time.
Damn it, Frank.
Okay, turn it off.
You got it, you did it. Turn it off.
Hey, kill it, Frank. Come on, man.
Come on, First. Turn it off.
If I turn it off I ain't never
gonna turn it on again, right?
That's right.
Please, turn it off, First.
- First!
- Sorry, Frank.
Oh, shit!
Frank, turn it off
and get him out of that car.
Get him out!
Frank, get on that kid.
Stop that kid!
Look out!
First! First!
First, turn it off, you crazy bastard!
All right, stop that car now.
I repeat, stop that car now!
They're gonna kill you!
- This is Meissner. Stop firing.
- The warden said...
- Goddamn it, I said stop firing!
- Hold it, hold it.
First, turn it off! Hold it. Hold it.
Look out! Look out, Frank.
Look out, man!
Get out of the car!
They're gonna kill your ass.
- Did you see that ride?
- Are you crazy?
- It's beautiful. I can drive.
- It's beautiful...
All right. You're one crazy
son of a bitch, you know that?
Move!
- You bought yourself a trip to the hole.
- Leave Frank alone!
Let's go, let's go. Break it up!
Break it up! Let's go.
Let him go. You have the wrong man.
- Take Leone to the hole.
- Back off.
- Six weeks.
- It was my fault, sir!
Save it.
Get off me.
Captain?
I want five inmates. Give me a bat.
I wanna break up this car.
Hold it right there, now!
I want you to watch this, Leone.
Back to the honeymoon suite!
Night.
- You should've been notified...
- Why is he in isolation?
- I don't have that information.
- You don't have it?
Then I wanna see
the goddamn warden!
Not today.
Every hour when the light comes on,
you'll stand, face the camera...
...and state your name and number.
Name and number!
Leone, five-ten.
Face the camera.
Name and number.
Leone, five-ten.
Leone. Leone. Leone.
Name and number.
Leone, five-ten.
On your feet. Name and number.
Give Mr. Leone half rations
the rest of his time.
Yes, sir.
Name and number!
Get up!
He seems a little sluggish.
Wake him up.
Cold enough?
- Wanna see my swing?
- I'd like to see you in whites.
- Some swing.
- You see me on the golf course?
You got a little cruel streak.
Leone, five-ten.
- Upright. Name and number.
- Leone, five-ten.
You'll be praying for some time
on your own. You know that?
- I don't believe that.
- Trust me. I know about these things.
Leone, five-ten.
Water.
Name and number.
Name and number!
Marilyn Monroe.
Thirty-seven, something, thirty-five.
Crack 121.
Listen, I didn't mean it.
No, I didn't say anything at all. No!
That's enough.
- Who ordered this?
- The warden.
Does the warden hate him enough
to kill him? 'Cause that ain't my job.
Mr. Sensitive. He thinks
we're treating Leone too rough.
Forget which are the cops
and which are the cons?
- You want me? Come on!
- Break it up!
Damn it, I said break it up!
Break it up!
Your stick, Mr. Braden.
Pussy.
Get out of my sight, before I shine
my boots with your face...
...you fat piece of shit! Go on!
Time's up.
Remember what I told you, Frank.
Roll with the system. Roll with it
or it's only gonna get harder.
Yeah, and it's getting shorter too.
So, what's new, Mr. Braden?
How's the family? Good?
How are the Jets doing?
Don't forget to check your bed.
Hey, Frank.
Somebody die in here?
Ain't a very good welcome home, is it?
Hey, big man.
Sand. The whole engine block
is full of it. It was Chink.
What are we gonna do about it?
- Forget it.
- Forget it?
We poured everything we got into this
car. No way we can let Chink slide.
- Let it go, First Base.
- Let it go?!
Aren't you the guy who says
you gotta protect what's yours...
...watch each other's back,
you watch mine, I watch yours?
I guess that was a bunch of jive,
now that you're a short-timer.
You're incredible. What?
You think this is your car?
This ain't your car.
This is the warden's car. Did you
think that Chink Weber did this?
Drumgoole did this.
Come on.
Did you think we were gonna
take our dates out in this car?
Maybe rotate it on weekends.
Ernie, why don't you take it Friday.
Dallas, take it Saturday.
And Eclipse, you got it Sunday!
Is that what you thought?
It's his! This lift is his, these
tools are his, the garage is his!
This whole goddamn place is his.
And you better remember that,
because once you buy into this...
..."our car," "our thing" concept,
man, you're his too!
Just let it go.
- I thought you were our leader.
- Goddamn it, I'm not your leader!
And this ain't a gang.
We're convicts.
We're prisoners, we're inmates.
We're here. And as long as we're
here, we're gonna stay his.
We're his.
Nothing's ever gonna change that.
You gotta face the facts.
Now, you guys are standup,
no doubt about it.
But I got three weeks to get out of
here. And in three weeks, I'm walking.
Ain't nothing gonna change that.
That's all I care about.
It's nothing for nothing, man.
He's right.
Leone, how do you like my belt buckle,
boy? Yeah, I know. I like it too.
A little souvenir
that reminds me of you.
Tell me, what are you
going to do about it?
You mean six weeks in the hole
killed your guts and your appetite?
It ain't over, you son of a bitch.
- Anybody call this spot?
- You guys don't need reservations.
- You on a diet, Frank? Huh, man?
- Cutting back a little bit.
- Take some of my food.
- Here you go. Don't worry about it.
- Bread.
- Thanks.
Some tomatoes.
You'll be all right. Celery stick.
I ain't playing football.
Don't worry about that guy. He's a
lifer. You only got a few weeks to go.
Forget about him.
A miracle just happened.
First Base finally learned something.
I doubt it.
- Okay, who's gonna say grace?
- Grace.
She was terrific, wasn't she?
- I thought I could rely on you, Weber.
- He won't be pushed.
Because you're not pushing
in the right place.
Everyone has a weak spot, Weber.
Find his, or I'll have
to find a new yard boss.
- Welcome to the Gateway Stakes.
- I feel like a steamed vegetable.
- Let's start the race.
- All right. What's your bug's name?
- Dirt Creature.
- Three-to-two on Dirt Creature.
- First Base, what's your bug's name?
- Rear Entry.
Rear Entry's 4-to-5.
Place your bets.
Two'll get you three, five'll get
you four. Five'll get you four.
Everything I got on Dirt Creature.
- I bet the house on Rear Entry.
- The window is closed. All bets are in.
Gentlemen, start your insects.
- On your marks, get set...
- Come on, Dirt.
Boom! They're off.
I've got a steak dinner
on this victory.
Come on, Dirt. Come on.
You can't do that.
We got a steward's inquiry.
You can't push your bug!
It was a come-from-behind
victory by Rear Entry!
- We're gonna rerun the race.
- Hey, no rematch.
- Hey! What are you guys doing?
- Shit.
- Pea! You're on the wrong detail.
- Stand up.
Get you ass up here!
Clean up the gym.
- We got a rematch later, all right?
- Sure.
I'm getting out of here.
I'll pay up later.
Now, asshole!
Give me a break. I gotta get
dressed. You know what I mean?
Hey, watch out for my bug.
I'll take care of him
for you, really. Delicious.
- Come on, let's do it today!
- All right.
- Clean this place up.
- It's already cleaned.
- What are you, deaf?
- Shut your mouth and do it.
Come on. One by one, come on!
Come on.
Get him down there.
Pull his head.
I told you we'd play later,
you little bitch.
Hey, Leone!
- They got First.
- I can't hear you.
- What did you say?
- They got First Base in the gym.
- What is it?
First!
Twenty years old.
This kid's twenty years old.
I told you.
I know. I know.
You want me, you got me.
You fucking Nazi.
Get him. Get him!
- I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
- Come on, fight. Fight!
Kick his ass!
I'll kill you.
Son of a bitch.
Do it.
Crush his face!
- Do it!
- Take him out!
Drop it! Drop it!
God.
Linen run!
Get a move on.
I'm trying to make a living here.
Frank, my man. Florence Nightingale.
- How you feeling?
- All right.
- Three weeks and you're out, man.
- Feels like three years.
Come on, man.
Three weeks is a blink.
What'd they do with the kid?
They sent him home, man.
What'd you think? You know.
You know, the kid told me once...
..."Your body has to be in prison, but
your mind can be wherever it wants."
He tell you that?
Listen, I brought you
some toilet paper...
...in case, you know, you want
to write some poetry or something.
Hey, Colonel Klink.
Let me out of here, man.
Frank, man,
it wasn't your fault, okay?
Remember that.
Roberta, have Miss Lowell photographed
for an I.D. For visitation.
I'm reinstating
Mr. Leone's privileges.
Yes, sir.
- I want to make sure Frank's all right.
- He's fine. He's recovering.
In three weeks he'll be out, and you can
look forward to a happy life together.
- Thank you for coming.
- Thank you, warden.
Okay, look into the light.
- Hi, baby.
- Hi.
Hi, come here, you.
- I was so worried.
- You look great.
Thirty-minute visit, Leone. Compliments
of the warden. Don't waste it.
- How do you feel?
- Good, thanks, sweetheart.
Thirty minutes. You need any help,
just give us a call, huh?
- Are they all like that?
- Don't worry. You look great.
You look...
Don't tell me what I look like.
I can't stand it.
I've missed you so much.
No more separations. Promise?
I promise.
- Time's up.
- Nice view.
- What's the matter with you?
- Time's up.
- The warden said half an hour.
- He changed his mind.
What do you mean?
I wanna talk to the warden.
What you wanna do is keep your mouth
shut, fix your clothes and get out.
- Come on.
- Don't touch her.
What did you say?
- Don't touch her? You don't learn, pal.
- Hey, I'm leaving.
Three weeks.
Three weeks. Three weeks.
Leone.
Come here.
Do I know you?
No, you don't know me, Frank,
but I know you.
I was at Treadmore with you.
A-block.
- Treadmore don't have an A-block.
- That's right.
- We got something else in common.
- Yeah, what's that?
We're both getting out soon.
You in a few weeks.
Me, I'm gone the day after tomorrow.
What happened to you?
One beating too many.
I served some hard time in this place.
We both have, am I right?
Yeah, you're right about that.
You need anything when I get out?
Can I get you anything?
- No, I'm all right. Thanks.
- I'm just lucky, I guess.
I got a job lined up. Temporary, but
it pays a grand for two hours of work.
- That's not bad, is it?
- What do you gotta do?
I just gotta rape this bitch. I get an
extra hundred every time she screams.
- I'll kill you for that!
- Payback time, Frank.
- Chink says hello.
- You touch her, you're dead!
Hey, bailiff! Guard!
Guard! Somebody!
Manly! Manly! Guard!
- What's your problem?
- I gotta use the phone.
- You know your privileges. No phone.
- That guy is gonna kill my girlfriend.
- What guy?
- The guy that was just here.
- The guy in the wheelchair!
- What are you trying to pull, Leone?
Don't play with me, Manly.
Please, I gotta warn her.
Everybody's got problems, Leone.
Get some sleep.
Goddamn, you fat motherfucker!
Goddamn!
Hey, Frank. Doing some
spring-cleaning, huh, man?
Dallas, come here.
Yeah?
- What is it, man?
- I need some help.
No questions asked.
You're busting out?
You got less than three weeks.
Just help me.
- This is gonna take days.
- I need it tonight.
I can't do that.
Everything is gonna be locked up.
There's a con getting
out of here tomorrow.
- Chink Weber paid him to get Melissa.
- I understand.
I'd love to help, but I can't do
the impossible. You're hurting my arm.
I'll take you with me.
No shit?
- What's the plan?
- You'll know when you gotta know.
Going for the tunnels, huh, man?
You just be here, all right?
Convict, move it out of there!
Hey, use some bleach on that, Frank.
I'm coming out, Colonel Klink.
Linen run.
- Evening, Officer Vazquez.
- You're late. Get in there.
- Yes, sir.
- Quick.
- I'll be real quick.
- Still making that jailhouse booze?
Absolutely not, sir. I'm on the wagon.
I joined Alcoholics Unanimous.
- You got some line of shit.
- It's bad on my nervous system.
- Makes me talk too much.
- Just make it quick.
Yeah, I'll be right out, sir.
Right out.
No. Help! Oh, shit!
Help me!
Come on, Frank. Let's go.
Okay, come on. That's it.
- All right, we got 10 minutes. Move it.
- All right.
Sweet dreams, Moby Dick.
- Frank?
- Come on.
The tools, man.
You got it.
Okay, here I go.
Oh, God. I'm jumping.
Man, there's rats in here.
- All right. I'm all right. No!
- What?
- This way. It's a shortcut to the plant.
- It's this way.
No, man, I remember the map.
It's this way. I'm positive. Let's go!
D.T.A., Frank.
Ain't that what you taught me, man?
D.T.A.
Right on schedule, Frank.
I'm sorry, man.
You were my ticket out of here.
Damn you!
You had me set up the whole time?!
Not the whole time. I got
30 years to go, man. Thirty years.
The warden made me a deal.
Dumb bastard!
They made me a deal, man!
A deal!
We don't make deals
with escaping prisoners.
What the hell are you talking about?
- You said if I delivered...
- Shut up.
- You're going back to the population.
- Population?
You can't do this to me, warden.
You can't do this.
I snitched him off.
They're gonna kill me. I'm finished.
Tough.
Look, I came through, goddamn it!
We had a deal!
That's enough.
You're gonna kill him.
This is an automatic 10 years, Frank.
It's 10 years for a second
escape attempt.
I knew you'd cross the line. I told
them you were a hard-core criminal.
They'll believe me now.
And you better believe me.
You better believe that you'll
be doing hard time here...
...for the rest of your life.
Manly, you know what to do.
Some dealmaker.
See...
...shit does float, doesn't it?
Hey, you know what else?
You don't have to worry about
that psycho hurting your girlfriend.
We decided to keep him in here.
Didn't we, officer?
She's not my type.
We'll teach him a lesson.
We'll graduate you with honours.
Turn on the steam.
Turn on the fucking steam!
Put him in it.
Get him in there.
Bring him in here! Come on!
Come on!
Rape this.
My face! My face is burning!
My face!
I'll kill you!
School's out, punk.
Frank.
Frank, don't leave me here, man.
I'm sorry.
Take me with you.
Let him go, Manly.
Let him go.
What are you gonna do with that?
You okay, Frank?
I'm okay, Dallas.
You can trust me, Frank.
You can trust me.
- Put it down, Dallas.
- Put it down.
- I won't hurt you anymore.
- Oh, yeah?
- You don't wanna do it.
- You fat piece of shit.
Don't do it, Dallas.
- What, are you trying to scare me?
- Dallas, don't.
- You won't do it.
- Oh, yeah?
- You don't got the balls to do it, punk.
- You're wrong.
- Stoolie.
- Put it down.
- You're wrong!
No!
Switch to backup. Sir, we've got
a power outage in C-wing.
Get some men to that utility quarter.
You better have a good reason for not
telling me you knew Leone was escaping.
I've got a dead officer and
a dead inmate.
And I don't have any answers.
Do you?
I was trying to save an informant's
life by keeping it secret.
Why would a man who's got
three weeks to go try to break out?
We can ask him
when we catch him.
Busted cable, utility corridor.
He's going to the roof.
Bring up zone two.
Can't you get any more light in there?
Captain Meissner.
This is Osner.
I'm in the well room.
Looks like this is where he went out.
Sir, that has got to be at least
200 yards underwater.
- Do you really think he made it?
- Maybe not, Mr. Braden.
But until you bring me a body,
I've got an escaped prisoner.
- This is Drumgoole. I want sector four.
- Meissner, sector four.
- What do you have?
- Right now, nothing, sir.
I'm thinking of calling in the
local and state police.
No! No outside agencies.
I repeat, no outside agencies.
This is an internal matter.
He's alive, I want him.
- Arm a tactical squad and meet me.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Braden, you will
continue this search.
You won't get away with it.
You know that, don't you?
I could've got out.
But I'm not going to spend my life...
...running from you.
Paul, look at this.
Get your ass inside.
Whoa, hold it.
- You can't use me as a hostage...
- Shut up! Shut up!
You recognize that chair?
You built it, didn't you?
Now get in there. Get in there!
Don't even think about moving.
You think you're gonna take me
to hell, huh? I'll show you hell!
All right, over there.
Move your leg!
Dallas, he fried,
the way you're gonna fry.
First Base, you took him downstairs,
you broke his goddamn neck!
I'm gonna fry your brains.
What do you know? It's a perfect fit.
Move! Move!
You can't make this work.
You're not smart enough. You're stupid.
You're scum.
Shut up! I'll show you scum.
You can't kill a man. You're not
a murderer. You don't have the guts.
Ten more years.
Isn't that what you said?
How about 20?
How about 30?
No, it doesn't matter what they give
me because you won't be satisfied...
...till you got me for life.
Make a hole.
Take it down!
I ain't doing life for nothing.
Come on. Lean on it, man!
They're gonna break that door down.
And they're going to take
your skull apart!
You're going to beg me
to let them kill you.
- Come on, break it down!
- Meissner!
Harder, man. Harder!
Come on, lean on it.
No!
Take out the glass!
Shoot! Shoot me!
- Don't shoot!
- Shoot!
He has his hand taped to the lever.
No!
- Don't shoot!
- Hold your fire. Hold your fire.
Come on, shoot!
Hold your fire!
Relax. Just relax.
Glad you're here, Meissner. This
wouldn't be official without witnesses.
He's bluffing. He's wants me to take
responsibility for his escape attempt.
I don't want a confession.
You set me up. You set everything up!
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I'm talking about Chink Weber!
The goons.
The cop that was gonna rape Melissa.
Dallas.
The killing of the kid.
Guilty on all counts.
Prove it! That's your problem.
You can't prove anything.
I don't have to prove nothing.
I came here for an execution.
I demand to be released from here!
No!
Don't do it, Leone. Don't do it.
Take it easy.
You deserve payback.
Frank!
Please, Frank.
Don't kill me. It's true.
I confess, Mr. Meissner.
Everything that he said was true.
I set him up. Everything.
Please.
Don't kill me.
Don't...
See you in hell, Drumgoole.
Works better with this.
Take him to the hole, Mr. Meissner.
Mr. Braden, take the prisoner
to the hole.
- Cuff him.
- Yes, sir.
Somebody get me
out of this chair.
Come on.
Thank you, Mr. Meissner.
I said take him to the hole.
I can't do that.
Take the warden into custody.
- I said take him. What are you doing?
- Cuff him.
Stop it! I am warden of this institution,
and you will obey... Stop that!
That was just a stupid confession to
try and save my life. Are you crazy?
No, but you are.
Until this matter's resolved in a judicial
inquiry, you'll remain in our custody.
I'll have your ass for this.
I'll have your ass.
Move him!
I only wanted to do my time, captain.
You'll get your chance.
Move him.
Hey, Ernie.
Hang in there, Frank.
Hey, Frank?
- Eclipse.
- Take care.
You too. Thanks a lot, big man.
Yeah. That okay?
It's all right.
Got this one from
Fidel Castro himself.
- See you, big man.
- Okay.
Hold it.
Crack the outside!
- Know what I'll miss most about you?
- What's that?
Your incredible smile.
- Take care of yourself, Leone.
- Thanks, captain.
Lock 'em!
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org