Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My God.
There's an awning on the new store.
There's still soap on all the windows.
So?
They're hiding something.
I don't think so, Nettie.
I think it's just going to be
some kind of antique store is all.
I'm never going over there.
Hey, Raider. How are you, buddy?
Good to see you.
- Hi, Nettie.
- Hi.
- Is Polly around?
- Gosh, yes. It's lunchtime.
Hi.
- Morning, Frank, Father Meehan.
- Hi, Alan.
Good afternoon.
- Smoked turkey on rye?
- Not today.
Think I'll try one of your specials today.
So I'll have... What's that? I'll have that.
Delicious salami...
...provolone, lettuce, tomato, mayo,
and two kinds of mustard in a pita pocket.
I wouldn't.
Okay, how about smoked turkey on rye?
Good order.
- Smoked turkey, rye!
- And a big piece of Nettie's apple pie.
So how's your day so far?
A little crazy, actually.
Did I tell you I got the photos back...
"You won't believe your eyes.
"Needful things.
"A new kind of store.
"You won't believe your eyes. "
It says so right there.
Then it must be true.
So, who's the new owner?
Nobody knows.
Not from around here is all.
Aren't you supposed to be in school?
Got a cold.
Hello?
- Is anyone here?
- I'm here.
The door was unlocked. I didn't bust in.
Of course it's unlocked. I'm open.
You've been here before.
- No.
- Sure you have.
I never forget a face.
Who are you?
My name is Leland Gaunt. And you are?
Brian Rusk.
Nice meeting you, sir.
I'm equally pleased
to make your acquaintance, Master Brian.
Now, what would you fancy?
- Fancy?
- What would you like?
Everything that's here is for sale,
but not everything that's for sale is here.
I have a basement, you see.
Are you from overseas somewhere?
I'm from Akron.
- Where's that? England?
- That's in Ohio.
What do you know?
There's Wilma Jerzyk
and her husband Pete.
What do you suppose they're up to?
Buying feed for their turkey farm?
Roast turkey?
No, she's a crazy person.
Now, what'll it be? A Walkman!
- A mountain bike.
- I already got one.
- Air Jordans.
- I don't know.
- Sure, yeah, I guess.
- Of course not.
Those are just objects, aren't they?
Just things. Nothing really important.
Suppose you had one wish, Brian.
What would you say?
- A wish?
- One wish. Just one. To make you happy.
What would make you happy again?
Let's see, where do we start?
- What could I possibly have around here...
- Mickey Mantle?
- Little before your time, wasn't he?
- Yeah. I meant the baseball card.
I mean, me and my dad,
we used to collect them.
Topps or Fleers?
Topps. We had a whole collection
of 56 baseball cards.
Al Kaline, Whitey Ford, Roy Campanella,
guys of that caliber?
We have every Yankee
except Mickey Mantle.
I mean, Moose Skowron was over $65.
Skowron is one thing.
Mickey Mantle.
That's got to run $600, $700.
You asked me.
I believe I might have something
that'll make you very happy, Brian.
Stay right here.
My God. Look at my butt.
- I look awful.
- No, you look fabulous.
Pol, you know how...
...you're always saying
that I'm not all that serious about us?
This is your camera, right?
I don't look like this.
- I'll commit suicide if I look like this.
- Polly, I...
Will you marry me?
Sure, whenever you're serious about it.
I gotta check Nettie.
Make sure she doesn't burn the French
fries again and put me in the poor house.
Polly...
I am serious.
Mickey Mantle!
"Topps, 1956."
Signed, "To my good friend Brian. "
Wait a minute. Brian is my name.
That's impossible.
"Best wishes, Mickey Mantle. "
Now, close your eyes, Brian.
Close your eyes.
Now, then. How much would you pay
for this card, Brian?
Mickey Mantle. Topps, 1956.
Signed, "To my good friend Brian. "
No, listen, all I got here...
The buyer must never tell
the seller how much he has.
If you can't tell a lie, then be still.
The first rule of fair trade, Master Brian.
- So what do you think?
- I can't breathe yet.
It's not as great as it looks.
I got it off the TV.
Such a liar.
- Put it on?
- Yeah.
Does that mean yes?
- Yeah. Yeah?
- Yes.
No.
95 cents!
Now we're getting somewhere.
Not quite enough, okay?
But an intriguing offer nonetheless.
Let's call it...
...half the price, shall we?
Yes. Half the price is 95 cents.
The price you paid cash.
The rest...
...the other half is a deed.
You understand?
- A deed?
- A trick. More like a tiny prank.
No big deal.
And no one's ever going to suspect you.
I promise.
Do you remember that lady we peeked at
buying feed across the street?
Yeah, Wilma Jerzyk. The turkey farmer.
You know where she lives?
Out of the car.
I said, "Get out of the car. "
Now.
Is this your name on this goddamn ticket,
Ridgewick, or is it a forgery?
- You're parked in the crip space.
- The what?
- You can't come in here...
The handicapped space.
We've told you about it before, Buster...
What did you call me?
Did you call me Buster?
Touch me again, I'll throw you in the cell!
I mean it!
It's Danforth! Danforth Keeton III...
...who is Head Selectman
of this piss pot little town.
I could get you fired off the force in two...
Make that one second flat.
- Am I getting through to you, Norris?
- I told him to write the ticket.
In that case, my mistake.
Jesus, Dan,
what in hell's got into you today?
Nothing got into me! I'm just sick
and tired of self-important little pricks.
- Pusillanimous assholes...
- That's enough!
I try to do a lot for this town.
I accomplish a lot for this town.
In fact, I am this town. And I am sick
and tired of this goddamn persecution.
- I am not persecuting you, Danforth.
- He called me Buster!
- You know how I feel about that.
- Then he'll apologize.
Won't you, Norris?
- Don't know that I will.
- You will.
Now.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry that I called you Buster.
- Yeah, you mama's boy. You candy-assed...
Shut up, you bloated,
cigar-sucking used car salesman.
Boats, shithead!
I sell quality preowned yachts,
you miserable fucking scuzz bucket...
Shut up! Shut up!
When I moved here, I thought,
"Great, I'm out of the big city. "
I'm in a place where people won't be
crawling up each other's asshole every day.
Where maybe my biggest nightmare
was gonna be getting a cat out of a tree.
But forget that!
Everybody is insane everywhere!
So you guys just fight it out between you.
One of you kill each other,
and who's ever left, I'll throw in jail.
You can do it. I know you can.
He's not gonna bite.
But what will I say?
You introduce yourself. "Hi. I'm Nettie. "
Then what?
Nettie, just go. You'll be fine.
Go on.
Hi. I'm Nettie.
Thank you.
It's only 19th century. I'm sorry.
Enjoy your purchases.
What's this? Some old wood chisel?
It belonged to a cabinet maker
at Château de Versailles...
...in the days of Louis XVI.
Look at this, Pete. Looks pretty old.
Yep.
My God. I didn't think we had room
for another soul in here.
Hi. My name is Nettie.
That stupid dog barks at me once more...
...I won't bother complaining
to Sheriff Pangborn again.
- I'll come over your place, skin him alive.
- No, not in here. Dear God, please!
- Throw her Baptist ass in the street.
- I will not.
Dear ladies, let's all be friends.
Can't we all be friends?
Not in this life.
Please, not in my place.
I'm sorry. Ladies, excuse me!
Miss Jerzyk!
Pick it up. Go ahead. Go on.
Don't be afraid, Miss Cobb.
No. I had one just like it years ago.
But it got broke.
- My husband...
- Your husband?
Then it's Mrs. Cobb.
Although my George has been passed on
for some time now.
- He died, untimely.
- I'm so sorry to hear that.
No need to be sorry.
It's been seven years since he was...
Murder is awful.
- I didn't mean to.
- Of course not.
It wasn't you who took that meat fork
from the drawer...
...and stuck it in his throat.
Are you leaving, Mrs. Roberts?
I'll have to think about it.
It is a lot of money.
You think about it. So will I.
You baked this?
Of course.
Homemade every day from apples
picked down at the Mayflowers'.
Polly Chalmers, my boss, sent it over.
Go ahead. Take him.
- I'm scared I'll drop it again.
- You won't drop it.
Come, Mrs. Cobb.
Please, sit down.
Listen.
Sometimes I think I can hear
the tiniest laugh.
I like you, Netitia.
I won't yell at you, like George did.
You moron!
No!
I think it should be yours, Netitia.
I need to go to work.
I'll see you soon. I'll drop by for a bite.
Mr. Keeton eats there most every day,
does he not?
Yeah. Danforth Keeton.
And everybody calls him Buster
behind his back.
Why is that? Pray tell.
I don't know.
Maybe someone should play
a trick on Buster.
Teach him to be nice.
My husband played a lot of tricks on me.
Maybe it would be fun
to play one on someone else.
Nobody would ever know it was you,
I promise.
Welcome to Needful Things.
Alan Pangborn.
- The sheriff around these parts.
- Leland Gaunt. Owner.
- So, what can I sell you, Sheriff?
- Me?
Nothing. I got everything I need, thanks.
Fair enough.
How about a piece of pie?
Your fiancée Ms. Chalmers sent it over.
- My fiancée?
- Such a pretty lady.
You're a lucky man, Sheriff. I'll be back.
Goodness.
I wish I had some cheddar cheese.
But beggars can't be choosers, can they?
Certain we haven't met somewhere before,
have we?
What, you and me?
In a big city.
You look familiar, Al.
You look out of place here, actually.
You don't mind my saying so,
so do you, Leland.
So, where are you from?
Ohio.
Akron, to be precise.
Pittsburgh.
I'm from Pittsburgh.
So, why did you leave?
I was a cop there,
and I got tired of all the shit going down.
And one day I just lost it.
I hit this guy.
Way too hard.
I reckon he needed some killing.
But it was still wrong.
Of course it was.
Yeah. So I left, and now I'm here.
So am I.
- Reverend.
- Sheriff.
- Alan, thanks for coming!
- Afternoon, Father.
- Hi, Sheriff.
- I got this in the mail this morning.
"Listen up, you mackerel snapper. "
- Excuse me.
- "We've tried to reason with you...
"... but it's been no use.
We have put up with your Popish idolatry...
"... and even with your licentious worship
of the Babylon whore...
"... but now you've gone too far. "
"Babylon whore. "
I mean, saints preserve us.
"Heed our warning.
Give up your plan to turn this town...
"... into a den of thieves and gamblers,
or you will smell the brimstone.
"'The wicked shall be turned into hell. '
Psalms 9:17.
"The concerned Baptist men
of Castle Rock. "
It's that idiot, Reverend Willie Rose.
Maybe you shouldn't have
called it "Casino Night. "
For God's sake, Alan.
It's only a little charity gambling.
I mean, I don't know why
it upsets the Baptists so.
I'll go talk to Rever...
When I was younger,
people got along better!
I'll go talk to him.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
You do that, Alan.
And when you do,
you tell Rose that if he tries to bump us...
...he'll find out just how hard
we "mackerel snappers" can bump back!
Pete, get me a gobbler from the pen!
I feel like turkey tonight.
You feel like turkey every night, Wilma.
Wilma!
- What happened?
- Mud!
Mud and shit! Goddamn turkey shit!
Why'd someone go and do that?
- Because I told her I'll kill it.
- Told who?
Dot.
- Yes, just a sec. It's for you.
- Me?
Okay, it's the square key. All the doors.
Don't forget the lights.
You can do it. You'll be fine.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- Night.
Hi. This is Nettie.
I know what you done, you crazy bitch!
Done what?
Fucking with me
was the worst mistake you ever made.
I'm going to get you for this,
you understand? You and your mutt!
You don't dare!
You stop bothering me and my Raider!
- He's a good doggie!
- You won't see me coming!
Guy sounds like he's havin'
a fucking pepoleptic fit.
Yep.
Don't kick the Rock-Ola, Hugh.
You hear me?
How you doing at the tracks, Dan?
Horses finally running your way?
Every time, Henry. Every goddamn time.
I'm gonna kick that jukebox wide open,
you don't fix it, Henry.
All right. That's it. You're out of here.
Give me that back.
Any of you fellas heading up to Castle Hill?
Hugh needs a lift.
Pink slip is what Hugh needs.
For a city employee making
an ass of himself in a public tavern.
Yep.
Nice to have friends.
You know, Henry? They do it at night.
They come in,
and they take out the mirrors...
...and they put in a piece of one-way glass
and stick a camera on the other side of it.
Then they watch you,
and they laugh at you.
And they take down every
single word you say.
Yeah.
- You're drenched to your soul.
- They threw me out!
- I'm sorry.
- Here.
Let me help you peel this thing off,
before you catch your death.
You got a nice jacket in the window.
A classic early-'50s beauty.
Warm as toast. Dry as a bone.
It's just like the one I used to have
in high school, before I was a bum.
When I was a kid.
I'll bet there are quite a few people
in this shit pit of a town...
...who wouldn't believe
you ever were a kid.
I know. It's not fair. I try so hard.
Not hard enough. So they crushed you.
They buried that wonderful boy
deep inside you.
- Which boy?
- This one.
We'll find him again, Hugh.
We'll resurrect him together.
Because, all of a sudden,
it's 1955 all over again.
It was the best hour
of the best day of my life.
- God, I loved that jacket.
- Which jacket? This one.
This jacket, Hugh.
You could recover, retrace your steps.
Take charge of your life again.
God, this is still so beautiful.
Say, Hugh, do you happen to know...
...a nice little Baptist lady
called Nettie Cobb?
Sure. Crazy old wretch killed her husband.
How much do you want for it?
- Mr. Gaunt?
- I am he.
Reverend Rose, sir,
of the First Baptist Church of Castle Rock.
May I take this opportunity
to welcome you to Castle Rock...
...on the good Lord's behalf?
- Why not?
- Excellent.
It's my unusual urgency when I ask,
what faith, sir, are you?
- What faith?
- Religion.
- You're not Catholic, are you?
- You might say that I am...
...nondenominational.
- I knew it!
Then you will have little objection
to my placing this in your front window.
I couldn't possibly do that.
You see, I, like you,
am here to serve everyone.
However, by way of compensation...
...perhaps I may offer you something,
which might interest you.
Say, how about an objet d'art?
What is your preference, Reverend?
Asian, Roman?
That is 2nd century, Reverend.
Wasn't it St. Augustine who said,
"Make me chaste, O Lord.
"But not yet, not yet"?
Father.
Reverend.
"Paper packages tied up with strings
"These are a few of my favorite things"
Yes. I'm so thrilled.
Thank you, Mr. Gaunt.
Treasure Island. First edition, actually.
Signed by Robert Louis Stevenson himself.
- It's magnificent.
- Take a gander.
If it's too hot in here, Mr. Jewett,
just say the word.
I'm afraid I have a tendency
to turn up the heat.
Hello, Ms. Chalmers.
- My goodness. What's wrong?
- Where did you...
How long have you been there?
I was just hoping for a cup of coffee.
I didn't realize you were closing.
Coffee? Sure, no problem.
- You're Mr. Gaunt.
- And you're Polly Chalmers.
I'm sorry, I don't shake hands. I have...
Arthritis. Forgive me. I forgot.
You've been having a devil of a time
with it lately, haven't you?
Yes. How did you know?
Nettie told me.
Here.
Just a tiny thank-you note
for that remarkable pie.
My Lord.
I don't think I ever had
a tastier cup of coffee.
You wouldn't, by any chance,
have something in the way of a doughnut?
Something I might dunk, Ms. Chalmers?
Please, we're going to be neighbors.
Why don't you call me Polly?
Go on.
Oh, no! No! No! Shit!
- Dan, it's me.
- Jesus! What the hell are you doing?
You scared the hell out of me,
sneaking up on me like that.
- Put the gun down, Dan.
- Yeah.
Another couple of seconds, I would've been
out of here. You would've missed me.
- What can I do for you?
- I had a call from the state auditors.
Yeah?
We have an Appropriations Committee
meeting next week to discuss budgets.
- Guess what. It's on my calendar.
- They wanna be there.
They want me to bring them printouts,
shit from city hall.
Yeah, you know those bastards.
They're on some kind of fishing expedition.
What the hell's going on?
I've been having some bad luck
at the track lately.
So I borrowed some money from the town
petty cash fund to cover the shortfall.
Jesus, Dan.
I'm gonna pay it back.
I was gonna pay it back before next week.
- Honest to God.
- How much we talking about here?
- $20,000.
- $20,000? Jesus Christ!
I'm getting a loan on my dealership
to pay it back, from Boston.
When?
Any day now.
Two days, four days, next week.
Four days?
Done.
You stall them for me, all right?
- Yeah. I will. Till Monday.
- Okay, thanks a lot...
- Believe me, I'll make it worth your while.
- Like hell, you will. Just pay it back.
I just meant if you wanted a deal
on a new boat. It's all I meant, I swear.
Whatever you want. And for Polly, too.
- I'll get her a deal on...
- Monday!
How's my boy?
You have something that's mine, Brian,
that you haven't finished paying for.
- But you said I could have it if...
- The dealing isn't done, you see...
...until Mr. Gaunt says the dealing is done.
And away they go!
She's A Hell-Raiser breaks on top
and goes straight to the lead...
... followed by Confucius Sings and Mr. Lee.
Lots Of Luck having a go wide, turning.
She's A Hell-Raiser...
Yeah! Boy, what the hell?
- That was pretty fine.
- Fine as paint.
- Can I...
- Careful. See, this is no ordinary toy.
- What is it?
- You see, the man who sold this to me...
...his father made their fortune from it.
Every morning he'd take
the day's racing form...
...and run its races
before they ever happened...
...one by one, right on this board.
He'd give each tin horse
the real name from the paper...
...do it just by touching and whispering.
- A brand-new name.
- Citation.
Sea Biscuit, Well Away...
- Seattle Slew.
- Man O' War.
Whoever were running that day.
Wind her up, let her go.
Run the whole damn slate that way!
Northern Dancer.
Eight, ten, a dozen races.
Then go right to the track,
and bet on those fillies...
...that won on this astonishing toy
from Japan Incorporated.
He'd rake in the cash, Dan.
Rake in the goddamn cash.
Rake in the cash.
How much?
Good day to you.
- Good morning, Father.
- Father.
- What do you want?
- Coffee and the usual.
Hey, Corn Cobb.
- What's the button on your boob?
- You're crazy.
- You leave me alone!
- Take it easy, Nettie.
Put the knife down.
Put it down.
Okay, Wilma. What'll it be?
Raider on rye, a little glass of puppy pus,
and two nice doggie eyes.
- Why don't you just order up or get out?
- Wilma.
- Shit.
- It's okay.
I'll go talk to her.
April Dreaming, Junction Salute.
She's A Hell-Raiser.
Tammy's Wonder, Easy Sweep.
That's My Boy.
Yes, okay, little puppies.
You ready now? Let's run a good race.
- Ready, set, go!
- And away they go!
And it's Tammy's Wonder. April Dreaming.
Junction Salute on the outside.
And Easy Sweep is far back.
- Into the far turn.
- Neck and neck!
- Tammy's Wonder on the inside...
- Tammy's Wonder!
Tammy's Wonder's gonna go on to win.
Tammy's Wonder from April Dreaming.
We've got Love My Martinis, Trentier...
...Doubter's Ridge, Rancadoo...
...By George, and Confucius Sings.
Little Chinese puppy.
Okay, fellas, now, let's go.
Make money for daddy!
And they're off!
- It's the white one, the red one.
- Danforth?
It's the green one. God, they're beautiful.
Look at those beautiful horses!
Run, run, run! Come on!
Come on. Come on, horsies.
Who's gonna win here?
- Danforth?
- Goddamn it! Go away!
I'll be out when I'm out.
- Aren't you going to work?
- I am at work!
Would you like me
to go down to the bakery...
...and maybe get some
honey-dipped doughnuts?
Yeah. Honey-dipped doughnuts.
Yeah, toilet paper, a nose job.
Just leave me alone!
You ready now? Let's run a good race.
Ready, set, go! They're off!
And they're coming around the corner.
It's a runaway victory!
Yeah! Come on, come on!
Yeah!
Good boy. Sit.
Stay. Mommy's got to go scoot
and do something for Mr. Gaunt...
...before it gets dark.
But don't you worry.
Mommy's going to lock all our doors
from now on.
Stay.
Lovely day.
Come on, girls.
The crowd is tense.
Brian Rusk doing the pitching.
And let me tell you, he is really
sensational. He's working on the no-hitter.
We're in the bottom of the ninth inning.
A count of 2 and 2 on the batter.
Two men on base,
but Brian has walked them both.
Right now, he's checking the runners
leading off first and second.
He's gotten the sign from the catcher,
the runners lead away...
... and here's the pitch.
Strike three! How about that?
Will he make that no-hitter, or will he not?
Brian Rusk. Man alive!
Is he really sharp today.
Sensational control
of his 90 mile-an-hour fast ball.
Still the chance of the no-hitter,
and he's ready to work.
Rusk has got a swift curve ball
that's dipping and darting.
And his fast ball, they can't touch it.
Brian Rusk is delivering a performance...
... that can take the Yankees
to another World Series.
How about that?
Brian Rusk is ready, and he delivers.
And the pitch...
Jesus Christ.
Good girls.
Yessiree.
We're having fun now.
Raider!
Little pal!
Raider. How they hanging?
Good fella. Yeah. Ain't you?
And ain't you got a face
just cute as a baby bug?
Yes, you do.
And you know what I got?
I got a beautiful jacket.
Yes, I do.
And you know what else?
I'm gonna keep it.
They're rounding the bend,
and yellow, and white, and pink...
"Punky Boy. " Yeah.
"Gasco Thunder, Hooded Lady,
Mr. P, Lotsa Luck, and Rosie D...
"... Punky Boy, Raise The Dead,
Frank's The Name, Gimme Shelter...
"... Sudden Fame. "
God! I'll kill him! I'll fucking kill him!
Ridgewick!
Raider?
Mommy's home.
Raid?
What the fuck?
That bitch!
You killed my doggie, you bitch!
You broke my microwave, you crazy fuck!
Wilma?
See the windows?
They're busted!
Wilma? You all right?
Come on, bitch.
Come for me, if you're coming.
Wilma.
There's nothing quite so invigorating
as a crisp fall day in New England.
- Don't you agree?
- Mr. Gaunt...
Leland.
I'm sorry. I can't even think.
Believe me, Polly, I know you're in pain,
so I shall dispense with the small talk.
I'll give you the item I called you about
and send you home.
- Give it to me?
- More or less.
But let's leave that until later, shall we?
When it rains, it pours.
They're after me.
Go upstairs, Mr. Keeton, to my apartment.
Make yourself a nice cup of tea.
- I'll be with you in a minute.
- I don't have a minute.
Go upstairs.
It was funny.
They were actually feeling much better.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org