Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yo, we should just play this
straight up.
Those cats will fold under pressure.
We can take these fools
with our eyes closed. Come on.
No doubt, but I don't wanna diss them
in front of their home crowd.
D, I got you.
I got y'all.
-All right, man.
-Come on, let's do it.
All right, all right, y'all, that was hot!
And the winner is....
Sphere and the Thug Unit!
Who wants next?
Let's get it going on in here.
-Y'all want some of this?
-We got next.
Let's go.
All right, all right, y'all, let's get
it popping in this mall!
You haven't seen him pop.
Come on, come on.
-Hey, got that.
-Get out of here!
-Get back.
-Break it up.
-Get back. Get back.
-We good.
All right, all right, let's hear it
for the Thug Unit.
Yeah!
Give it up for the Goon Squad!
What's up?
I think the Goon Squad got it, y'all.
No, no, no.
Double or nothing says you got lucky.
It's on.
-Let's go! Let's go!
-What the hell are you doing?
Man, I'm out.
What the hell you walking away for?
I say we double up on these niggas.
-You know this ain't our spot, D.
-Sphere's crew don't know us.
Don't know
what we're bringing, period.
-The more paper we take home.
-Did you see that cat?
If he thinks he's being hustled,
that's paper we won't spend.
-Why are you acting all scared?
-I'm not.
-I'm acting smart. You try it!
-Don't I always got your back?
Don't I always have your back?
-You know I got it, man, but I'm....
-If you ain't with it, just go home.
-Like you could do this without me.
-For real, DJ.
We ain't shit without your brother.
You know, it's gonna get
nasty up in here!
-Don't wanna let stuff get out of hand--
-Don't sweat it.
We came too far to turn back now,
baby boy. I want this.
You want this? I knew you'd say
something like you want this.
That's all this is about. Typical DJ.
It's not just about you,
it's about all of us. We're a team.
Well, this team's about to double up
on their asses. Come on.
All right now, y'all ready to rip this?
Let's get it going on up in this mall!
Let's go!
It's over! It's over!
All right, all right, y'all!
This one, hands down,
the Goon Squad!
You're dead! You're dead!
Goon Squad! Goon Squad is up.
I'm telling you, man,
we're taking over L.A.
-Believe that.
-Yeah.
Hold up, guys.
-Hey, man, what's your brother doing?
-Man, I don't know.
-I got a little something for y'all.
-All right. All right.
That's what's up.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, man.
We gotta take Von home.
His mom's gonna trip.
I have your mama.
-He'll get a beating.
-Miss Williams ain't banging on me.
-Why you gotta do my mom like that?
-I was doing her like that. Last night.
Give me my money!
I got it! I got it!
-I want my money.
-The money's mine.
I want it.
Where's my money?
Get out of here.
D!
-Let's get out of here! Let's go!
-Let's go. Move it!
Get up, D!
Come on!
I'm sorry, man, I'm sorry.
Somebody do something!
We'd like to welcome
all arriving passengers to Atlanta,
We are so glad
to have you here, DJ.
You're in Atlanta, we'll get you
a Hawks jersey or something.
Honey, nobody watches the Hawks.
That's your uncle's way
of saying welcome to Georgia.
You'll get used to the humidity.
You must be so excited
to start school.
Or nervous.
But don't be. You'll do just fine.
You know that's where
I met your uncle.
You guys went to Truth?
I did. Your uncle was working there.
Come on, let me show you
up to your room. This way.
That's your bathroom over there,
and this is your room.
If you get tired of campus food,
you're more than welcome...
...to spend your weekends
here with us, anytime.
You know,
whatever makes you comfortable.
Thanks.
DJ, I didn't get a chance to tell you
at the funeral...
...but you know we loved him.
I know how close you two were.
I gotta run and show a house...
...so when I get back,
I'll make us all some dinner.
Okay?
Honey, go ahead
and help yourself to some apple pie.
I know it's your favorite.
No, no, thanks.
You know I had to call in a favor
to get you into this school.
-Don't make me look bad.
-Nate.
-No, that's cool. I'm listening.
-Good.
Because the rules are very simple.
There's three things
you have to deal with.
First, you must keep your grades up
at all times.
Second, I'm in charge
of your work study program...
...but you'll not be
treated differently...
...nor will you behave any different
than my other 26 employees.
-And third?
-If there's a strike three, you out.
Period.
DJ?
What the hell is going on, man?
I'm not gonna sit out here and act
like I wanna be here when I don't.
This whole college boy thing
is not for me, man.
You're the only thing
your mama's got left.
There's no way I'm gonna let you
put my sister through any more pain.
So you better make this college thing
work out. Can you appreciate that?
Get your black ungrateful ass
in the goddamn truck.
What'd I say, man? Get in the truck!
At least you don't have a problem
with waking up early.
Looks like you're just in time
for registration.
Next.
Yo, yo, hold my spot real quick.
-This is my spot, thanks.
-Excuse me?
-There was a girl saving my space.
-Nice try.
You have to wait in line
like everybody else.
You saw me
behind the sister with the fro.
Next.
Now, one of you come up
to the counter.
I'm just saying it's a little early
to tell, Mom. That's all,
No, I'm not saying I hate it,
I'm not quitting. I promised you I'd try.
That's my word.
I love you too.
Okay. Bye.
All right.
There are only a select few things
of mine that are absolutely off-limits.
My toothbrush, my toothpaste,
my shaving cream, and my condoms.
Magnums, of course.
You know about the gold packs?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Other than that, playboy,
anything else of mine...
...you're welcome to. Rich Brown.
-DJ.
-Nice to meet you, sir.
The Deltas
are having a little barbecue.
-I've got some juice, I can get you in.
-I gotta work.
-Classes ain't started yet.
-I got a job.
Okay, I feel you. Which--?
Never mind.
All right, bro. In that case, I'll holler.
Yes.
Come in.
Don't just stand there, man.
Sit down.
Is this your office?
Awfully nice digs for somebody
who cuts grass.
No, I don't cut grass.
But you do.
You ever wonder
where them trains be going?
They probably be going to Japan
or something.
-Japan?
-Oh, yeah, they can't cross water.
You going to college?
Don't say that when you get there.
I'm just playing with you, man.
The key to success in going to school,
what you do, you get a group of girls...
...you get them
to do your homework.
When they do your homework,
you get A 's,
-How's it going, man?
-I'm still standing.
Get in, man.
I'll give you a ride back.
Come on. Come on.
Pass the ball. Pass the ball.
Yeah, baby. Go deep. Go long.
They're getting the
very same education as you...
...so don't pay them any mind.
Oh, check it out.
Oh, that's old news, brother.
I've been there and done that.
-You're lying.
-I'm not lying.
Rich--
DJ, right?
My new roommate, DJ.
DJ, that's my friend Noel.
Good to meet you, brother.
Now, Thetas.
Everybody got quiet like
y'all can't get down!
What?
Are we the Pythons?
-What the hell are they doing, man?
-They're stomping the yard.
Yes,
Where are you from?
-The Thetas are representing.
-All day.
Smooth it out now.
Funky and you know it,
clap your hands,
Smooth!
-Yo, I meant to--
-Smooth!
-Theta Nu!
-Theta what?
Theta Nu!
Get him out of here!
Yo, get your hands off me, dog.
Fool, you're about
to get your ass whooped.
Throw his ass to the wolves!
Can I get up here, man?
Because I can't see.
-Yeah?
-Hey, isn't that your boy, DJ?
Hold it, G.
Listen, man.
I don't know
if you're crazy or stupid...
-...but you gotta keep it moving.
-Hey, Zeke!
When you're done playing
with your bitch...
...we're gonna show you
what a real ass-whooping look like.
Line up, Mus!
Mus, march!
Mus, hut!
Back it up! Back it up! Back it up!
Mu!
Gamma!
Xi!
The seven-year champs are here!
-T-H-E-T-A!
-Nu!
-What?
-T-H-E-T-A!
Who's that creeping in my window?
Now! Theta Nu!
What?
T-N-T!
Explosive, explosive, explosive,
Wolf pack, march!
-M-U!
-Gamma Xi!
Gamma Mu Xi!
Wolf pack attack!
Mu!
The seven-year champs are here,
-Hey.
How are you doing?
Aren't you that guy that was fighting
with that girl in the line?
Yeah, but it wasn't like that.
April!
-Hey, babe.
-What's up, baby girl?
-I thought I told you to wait for me.
-I know, I had to go to the library.
-Who's your friend?
-DJ.
DJ was just passing by.
Oh, yeah. I remember you.
You're the idiot
that tried to break our step line.
Yeah, well, it seems like DJ
has a thing with lines.
You see those flags there?
You don't mess with the Mus
and you don't mess with my girl.
I'm gonna bounce.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Here, it's all about the haves
and the have-mores.
Either you come in first place
or you're not even in the game, player.
Oh, yo, guys, this is DJ.
You know Noel, this is Byron, Paul.
-That's Easy over there.
-What's up?
Yo, get that camera out of my face,
man.
I was saying Theta Nu Theta is
gonna wipe the floor with Mu Gamma.
-How's that?
-Because I'm gonna join.
Dude, why are you pledging
Theta anyway? They tired.
-They pull no women.
-They never win step championships.
-So?
-"So?"
-What else is there?
-What about history?
What about tradition?
Give me my damn hat.
-What about legacy?
-A legacy of losing.
He's just saying that
because his father was a Theta.
Anyway, DJ,
please ignore their ignorance.
You need to roll with us
to the Rep Yo' City Blast tonight.
-Roll with us.
-To the what?
Where my St. Louis folks at?
S-T-L, show some love.
You know how we do it every week at
the Phoenix! Give me love, Miami.
C-H-I,
my Chicago folks in the building.
Show some love.
Give it up for the A hometown people.
Where you at? Show your A.
I see you, Jamaica.
Do your thing, mon.
Watch out for the lovely ladies
in blue and white. I see you.
-What's up, sir?
-What's up?
You good, man?
Oh, damn, Rich.
You hanging with the freshmen now?
-What?
-Oh, no. This is my roommate.
This is DJ. DJ, this is Grant.
That's nice. But see,
this section is for upperclassmen.
You know what we call freshmen?
We call them bootlickers,
because that's all they good for.
You know
what we call guys like you?
-No, what?
-Pretenders.
-You're gonna wish I was pretending--
-You don't know me.
Okay, okay! Okay, okay!
And on that note,
we gonna go to the bar.
Y'all have a good night.
Why you so sensitive, dog?
It's a little freshman hazing.
We all have to go through it.
Straight up,
that dude is whack, man.
Well, maybe.
But he's Zeke's prodigy.
-Who the hell is Zeke?
-He's the head of Mu Gamma.
Seven-time national step champs.
And your boy, Grant, he's next in line
to take the throne.
-Just chill.
-You're killing me with that.
Every week, you know
how we do it in the Phoenix.
Go to the dance floor.
Rep your city, wherever you're from.
It's about that time.
We got N-Y-C, obviously.
I hope he had a condom on.
What's he doing?
-Didn't think you were coming.
-What are you doing?
Come on.
Don't play at being jealous.
I'm not playing at anything.
It was just a show.
Well, I didn't like it.
It's not like I was doing it for real.
I was just adding a little flavor.
Keep yourself looking this fine,
you ain't never gotta worry.
Excuse me?
Hey, Grant. Where are you at?
Your city needs you.
Sit down with your girls,
have another drink on me...
...and watch your man do his thing.
He's just being a man.
There isn't a single woman in here
that wouldn't kill to be with him.
-Don't make it easy on them.
-You know you don't deserve that.
It's not that big of a deal.
Didn't I tell you to keep
your distance from my girl?
See, now, I thought you was just
pretending again.
New York City, where you at?
Rep your city, it's your turn!
Grant, they need you on the floor.
When I'm done,
you better be gone...
...bootlicker.
-I can take care of myself.
-I know you can.
No, really. Grant is not someone
you want to mess with.
Somebody's gonna have to
bring him down a notch.
What the hell is this nigga doing?
What's this? It looks like we got
a new addition added to the mix.
Hey, yo, kid.
What city you representing?
I ain't repping nothing. Just me.
Oh, don't clown him. Don't clown him.
You'll hurt him, Grant. Don't hurt him.
Y'all know
how Grant does it, y'all.
Give it up for G, Grant.
New York in the house!
Oh, snap!
Is he clowning St. Louis?
Is he breaking on Jamaica?
Wait a minute.
Oh, he's clowning everybody!
He's clowning on the Chi guy!
Oh, this is crazy.
A-T-L, are you gonna take that?
Miami! Even Miami!
Wait a minute.
Is he coming at Grant?
Wait, he's killing him!
That's my roommate.
Give it up, D!
Oh, no, he didn't. Yes, he did.
Yo, goodness.
So I guess you thought
you were defending my honor, huh?
-April, what are you doing?
-I'm just talking.
You don't have to let this dude
talk to you like that.
-Let's just drop it.
-No. What did you say?
Somebody'll have to teach you
how to talk to a woman.
-You gonna show me?
-I already schooled you once tonight.
-How much do you wanna learn?
-What, you think you funny, nigga?
Nah...but she clearly does.
-What? No, no, no, Grant.
-It's all good, baby.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Hey, stop.
Grant, stop it, stop. Stop.
-Let's go.
-Stay out of this.
All right, just chill. Grant.
I ain't got nothing against you,
but I told you already.
-This is my roommate, man.
-You do what you gotta do.
Noel, I thought
you was gonna pledge Mu Gamma.
-I was gonna--
-I guess you can kiss that goodbye.
I'm gonna bounce.
We got unfinished
business, bootlicker.
-Indeed.
-Come on, let's go.
I got myself here.
I can get myself home.
Maya, will you take me home?
Chill out, man.
This is a friendly visit.
I'm Zeke,
president of Mu Gamma Xi.
You know Grant.
We saw you at the Phoenix
and we were impressed.
Ain't that right, Grant?
Yeah.
I got work to do, man.
Wolves!
Y'all heard the man. Get busy.
Now that you got time
on your hands, let's talk.
Look, I brought Grant with me
to show you...
...that we don't have
any hard feelings.
You're a straight-up guy. I like that.
Working your way through college.
That's admirable,
but this whole gardening thing...
...can't be getting you any play
with the ladies, man.
Never had any problems
in that area.
Okay,
now I'll get straight to the point.
Mu Gamma Xi has the strongest
alumni network, period.
One phone call from us
when you graduate...
...you've got a high-paying job
just like that.
So you want me to join your frat?
If you step on our line.
Step on the line. I don't step, man.
I battle.
-What's the difference?
-Pussies step.
You should think about what you say
before you say it.
Wolves!
That's enough.
Let's let Mr. DJ get back to his....
His gardening.
-You were right.
-I told you.
I'm telling you, Sly.
You didn't see
this dude punk Grant.
Look, I'm sure he's a cool dude,
I just don't think he's Theta material.
You mean he's too ghetto.
I don't care where he's from.
I don't think he got here
based on his SAT's.
Okay, fine, so he's not the archetype
of a Theta, but what he--
We got other pledges to consider
who have more impressive résumés.
Thank you.
But are they gonna help us
win Nationals?
Okay, okay,
so that's what this is about?
What are you thinking? Aren't you sick
of living in Mu Gamma's shadow?
I'm sorry. Mind if I join you?
Suit yourself.
I'm here to talk to you
about Theta Nu Theta.
You're kidding, right?
No.
-What about it?
-Members of my pledge committee...
-...feel you'd be an asset to the house.
-No.
Mu Gamma's murdered your asses
for seven years.
You're here
because you think I can help.
You know, you're cocky for a brother
that's got one trick.
Please spare me, man.
Spare you, fine.
There's a screening process.
All applicants go through it.
You want to apply?
That's up to you.
Mu Gamma comes here
offering me a sweet deal.
And the best you can come up
with is I can apply?
If a sweet deal is really what
you're looking for, Theta ain't for you.
A fraternity, now, that's a brotherhood
of men who forge a lifetime bond.
Okay, once you are a Theta, you will
always and forever be a Theta.
Now, you can go out of here,
you can leave Truth...
...as a young educated brother
from the 'hood.
And homey, that's great.
But if you pledge Theta, you're gonna
get that same education...
...and you'll become a member
of our lifetime brotherhood.
-Yo, what's up?
-Hey, hey, what are you doing?
You almost just ran me over
with that thing.
-I didn't mean to scare you. My bad.
-What?
It's the dance thug from the club.
So can we move on from that?
Move on to what?
I don't know.
You getting to know me?
I have a boyfriend.
So, what's up with this Grant?
What is he, a professional student?
Grant is in a six-year law program...
...and his father's a partner with a Wall
Street firm, so when he graduates--
It's funny, because I didn't take you as
the type of girl that could be bought.
Bought?
Bought.
Wait, I didn't mean bought like that.
I didn't mean bought like that. Listen.
-What?
-Let's just start over.
-Start what over?
-Have lunch with me.
I'm tutoring.
Tutor what? What do you tutor?
Yo.
-Hi, can I help you?
-I'd like to sign up for a tutor.
Okay. What subject?
What subject
does April Palmer tutor?
-History.
-History it is.
How'd you pull this off?
What?
What, you think I set this up?
Well, it's an awful big coincidence,
don't you think?
What you take me for?
Some kind of stalker?
Like I'm gonna work that hard
to get your attention.
I mean you're fine, but you ain't
all that, you know what I'm saying?
Did I set this up?
Can I use your pen?
-Yeah. Okay.
-Thanks.
So where do we start?
You can start by moving over there.
-Really?
-No, I'm serious.
It works better if we can sit
across from each other.
All right.
This is gonna be good
reading material for you.
Time to go.
-Thank God. I'm starving.
-So let's go eat.
I can't.
Why?
You know why.
Why are you staring at me?
Okay.
I'll make you a deal.
Ask me any question
from the history lesson, I get it right...
...we go eat.
Okay.
What was the difference
between Republicans'...
...and the Democrats'
political response...
...to the Great Depression
in the 1930s?
Some other time maybe.
But by political response, were you
referring to the Republicans' belief...
...that the marketplace
will correct itself...
...as opposed to
the Democrats' New Deal?
Because the way
you phrased it was....
I'll get my uncle's truck.
I'll drive.
So I heard the Mu Gammas
are trying to recruit you.
So are you gonna pledge?
Probably not. I don't wanna step.
Being in a fraternity is about
a lot more than just stepping.
Wow, you sound just like them.
-You should check out Heritage Hall.
-What's that?
See for yourself.
Oh, it's right up here on the right.
How does a nice young girl like
yourself know about a place like this?
We gonna take five. Be right back.
There's a lot of things about me
you don't know.
I didn't know you can do that.
I'm surprised.
Let me show you how we do it in A.
All right, I'm not mad.
I'm not mad at all.
-Really?
-No.
You wanna sit down?
No.
-I can't do this.
-What's wrong with this?
-We're just having a little fun.
-I know. We just need to go.
Let's heat it up.
Yo, this one. Look at the map.
I'm telling you, it's this one.
Quit playing, man.
All in!
-Since when?
-1932.
Bring it home!
Come on!
Pledges, turn...
...and face big brother Zeus!
Pledges, unmask yourselves!
Pledges, Mu Gamma creed!
The year of completion,
the manifestation,
1932 was the year our fathers
founded Mu,
Camaraderie in gray,
we're a wolf pack of brotherhood,
Fangs of power, fur of protection,
Battle cry:
By the rising of the moon!
Bring us our destiny, sir!
Oh, brother, we gotta keep pushing,
I wanna be a Theta Nu one day,
So, big brother,
would you help me on my way?
Oh, brother, we gotta keep pushing!
We gotta keep moving!
We gotta keep fighting!
Oh, brother, we gotta keep pushing!
We gotta keep moving!
We almost there!
Pledges of Theta Nu Theta,
face front!
Reveal yourselves!
Pledge Porkchop,
please introduce yourself!
Porkchop!
Extra gravy.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org