Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Is that for us?
- No, it's for you.
- What is that?
- A mantrap.
They used to use it
for catching poachers.
Hello, Amy.
- Hello, Charlie.
- Where do we put it, Mr. Sumner?
- Oh. Here in the back.
- Oh, it's heavy, Mr. Sumner.
I'm surprised
you still remember me.
Where do we put it, Amy?
Anywhere you want.
It's your birthday present.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Don't scratch it.
- Why are you surprised?
- How long has it been, Charlie?
- Three summer holidays in six years.
David, this is an old
friend of mine, Charlie Venner.
My husband, David Sumner.
- Mr. Venner.
- Please call me Charlie.
You work around here?
Sometimes.
- Will you give me a hand, please?
- Yeah.
- David's a mathematician.
- What are you going to catch?
- Peace and quiet.
- Oh, an arithmetic teacher.
- Well, uh-
- No.
He's writing a book...
on the computer analysis
of the celestial-
Good try. Here, why don't you
put this in the trunk, Amy.
Let me.
Maybe, um, Charlie could
help us with the garage, David.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
This fellow Norman, uh-
- Scutt.
- Yes.
- He's, uh, taking forever.
- Me and Bobby'll do it
for you, Mr. Sumner.
Me and my cousin Bertie will be out
tomorrow. We'll get it up for you.
Yes? How much?
- Oh, reasonable.
- Okay, thank you.
- We're at-
- Back at Trencher's farm.
We'll be there, sir.
Good. Good.
Where are you going?
David?
- Where are you going?
- Cigarettes.
Okay.
Uh, a couple of packs of
any American cigarettes, please.
- Time, gentlemen, please.
Finish your drinkin', gentlemen.
Let me have your glasses.
Henry Niles.
I thought he was to be put away.
Oh, we can take care
of our own here. Usually do.
Remember when
I took care of you, Amy?
But you didn't.
Remember?
There was once a time,
Mrs. Sumner...
when you were ready
to beg me for it.
Take your hands off me.
Come on, gentlemen. Drink up.
Let me have your glasses, please.
Bloody early, Harry.
Harry...
I think I should have another pint.
Sorry about my uncle, Harry.
I think he's a bit taken with drink.
Oh.
I do beg your pardon,
Mr. Harry Ware.
- I'll pay for
the American gentlemen's cigarettes.
- Oh, no, that's okay, l-
That's all right.
I got it, sir.
Garage coming along?
Norman fixing it up all right?
Yeah.
And I'll pay for the glass.
And I'll even pay for the little bit of
plaster to put on your bleedin' finger.
But I do think I should have
another pint to take me home.
The bar's closed, Tom.
- Come on, Tom.
- Oh.
It is, is it?
We'll see about that.!
- Take it easy, old man!
- Old man, you say?
All right, Tom.
You've had your fun.
Pay the man and leave.
Ah.
Oh.
I do beg your pardon,
Mr. Magistrate.
But what I am, I am.
What's the damage, Harry?
Call it a quid, Tom.
Let's call it, uh...
30 bob.
Will that do then, eh, Major?
Go home, Tom, will you...
or you'll be up before me
on a fresh charge.
Come on, lads.
Work to be done.
- See you tonight, Harry.
- All right, Tom.
I showed him, eh, lads?
Uh, they're paid for, sir.
They are now.
- Stupid cow!
- Get off!
What was that about?
Who was that big guy
with the beard?
Why?
Is he any relation
to your friend Charlie?
Yes.
How well do you know
this fellow Venner?
Stop teasing.
- Did you ever go out with him?
- Stop.
- Hmm?
- Leave me alone! Stop it!
- Stop.
- Tell me.
- I'll stop the car.
I just want to know.
Tell me.
Stop. I'm telling you.
- You asked for it.
- Okay.
All right, drive the car- Ooh!
- Ooh! Ooh!
You asked for it!
Chicken!
- You're nuts!
- You're terrible! You're wicked!
- Oh, by the way-
- Yeah?
- Venner did try to get fresh once.
Yeah? So?
Nothing happened.!
- Ba-bum
Ba-ba-bah-bum
Ba-ba, ba-bum
Hi.
You'll have some help tomorrow.
Charles Venner and his cousin
are coming to help finish the garage.
We'll have the garage finished
before Chris gets the rats out.
- Hello, miss.
- Chris?
Yeah, Chris.
Oh, yes. Mr. Cawsey.
The rat man.
- Want help with this, sir?
- Yes.
It's a real antique, sir.
- Rare, they are.
- My wife is a collector.
But I end up with them.
I find it's a bit large
for my prey, sir.
- Won't do at all.
- Don't count on it.
- Do you like it here, sir?
- Very much.
- I hear it's pretty rough
in the States, sir.
Have you seen some of it, sir?
Bombin', riotin', snipin',
shootin' the blacks?
Can't walk down the streets, they say.
Was you involved in it, sir?
I mean, did you take part?
See anybody get knifed?
Just between commercials.
Wanna put that down there?
No, I'm just glad I'm here
where it's, uh, quiet...
and you can breathe fresh air
and drink water that doesn't
have to come out of a bottle.
It isn't water that I drink
out of a bottle, sir.
Those two fellows will be up
to help you tomorrow.
- You gonna have a crack at her, Norman?
- No.
Ten months inside
is enough for me.
- They got anything worth taking?
- Nope.
Except, uh...
these.
- You bloody fool.
- It was nothing.
She's got a dozen or more.
Full of perfume.
You like my trophy?
Bugger your trophy.
I want what was in 'em.
I could do with
some of that too, Normie.
Charlie Venner.
He had some of it years ago...
when she was here with her father.
Venner's a bloody liar...
and so are you.
Tell her, smell her
Lock her in the cellar
Kitty, kitty.
Where are you?
Kitty.
Kitty, kitty.
Kitty, kitty, kitty.
Want a drink?
I can't find the cat.
Doesn't answer my call.
Do I?
You'd better.
Why did you hire
Charlie Venner?
I didn't. You did.
Kitty.
If she's in my study,
I'll kill her.
What?
Nothing.
That your daddy's chair?
Every chair is my daddy's chair.
I'm glad we came.
- What are you doing?
- Kiss me.
Mmm.
- You're an animal.
- Mm-mmm.
Why'd you take my heater
out of the study?
Because it's going upstairs.
What happened?
It's not going upstairs.
It's freezing in there.
Hello.
I can see you're working at top speed.
Is he in there studying?
- You'd better do something.
- My husband will think
all Englishmen are lazy.
- Let me help.
Hey!
Yeah, come on over here. This way.
Watch your fingers, Chris.
What was so funny with them?
They just think
you're strange.
Why, because I'm American?
Mmm, no. No.
Just strange.
Do you think I'm strange?
Occasionally.
You act like you're 14.
I am.
Wanna try for 12?
How about eight?
I freak out for eight-year-olds.
- David?
- Huh?
Will you please
get some lettuce?
Okay.
Oh, and fix
the damned toaster.
What does she think
I'm doing here, playing games?
What is this,
grammar school?
Jesus Christ.
Uh, we're leavin' now,
Mr. Sumner.
- Mr. Riddaway be givin' us a lift.
- Fine.
Oh, I was just sayin'
to your missus...
that in a funny sort of way I feel
closer to rats than I do to people.
Even though I kill 'em for a living.
Their dying is my living.
Smell a rat, see a rat, kill a rat.
That's me, Chris Cawsey.
I'd be lost without 'em.
It's true. I tell you straight.
Cleverest thing you ever see
around these parts is a rat.
Rats is life!
Shove up,
you overgrown bastard.
How's your day been?
Been up in a fat sheep, have ya?
Oh, you fluffy fleecy darlings
You with the dark brown eyes
David?
David.!
Dinner's ready.!
Did you hear me?
- Hello, Major.
- Evening, Major.
- Evening.
- Will you be having a pint
with me then, Major?
Not tonight.
I'll buy my own.
Otherwise
we'd never get out of here.
You know that.
Yes, I do know that.
Thanks, Harry.
Excellent.
- John.
- Evening, sir.
- Fancy a game?
- Aye.
- Evening, Harry.
- Evening.
John Niles, come here to me.
- Is this for a drink, Tom?
- No, this is for the truth.
Your brother.
Been hangin' around
the girls again.
You'd better keep a closer watch,
or we'll be puttin' him away.
It's all right, Pa.
He's only throwing the ball
to 'em a little.
A little's too much
for that sod.
Watch your tongue, Norman.
I'll watch nothin'
except my own ways.
You watch your brother,
or I'll do it for you.
If he ever makes
a mistake again in any way...
I'll be the first
to have him put away.
David.! You've been at it for hours.!
Aah!
- Gave me a fright, you did.
- You watching him, are you?
Just lookin'.
Do you fancy him?
He's sweet, I think.
Want anything?
Want a tomato?
- No, thanks.
Want a grapefruit?
- Hey, hey.
- Your move.
Okay.
Check.
- No, thank you.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
"This move now...
"puts black into
a desperate plight...
"with no possibility of mobilizing
his disorganized pieces.
"Therefore, he begins
to return material...
"to make progress
in developing at any price.
Two pawns down,
white can conveniently-"
Hey, I bet I can undress,
do my exercises and get into bed
before you make your next move.
- Is it a deal?
- You're on.
- Ah! No cheating.
- I'm not cheating.
Shh, David.
Aha! I have it.
No, no, no, David,
just a minute.
You're supposed to do a hundred.
I did a hundred. I counted
by binary numbers. Make your move.
- Binary numbers.
- Make your move.
- Wait a minute.
- Come on.
- What about that one there?
- No.
- Uh-
- It's difficult, isn't it?
Terribly.
Just a minute.
I think I have it.
Um-
Ooh.
That puts you in.
- Jesus!
- What are you doing?
I gotta get my watch off.
You're an animal.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
I'm just setting the alarm.
Are you finished?
- Wait a minute.
- Oh, no. What now?
David.
David, what are you
doing down there?
- Looking for a chess piece.
- What are you doing?
Take a look.
- Whoa. Did you find it?
- No, not that.
Wait a minute.
Let me give you a hand.
Aah.!
David, no.!
- No, wait! Wait a minute!
- You see it? Huh?
- No, I didn't find it.
- I think it's a rook.
No.! Aah.! No.!
Mmm.! I love you.!
I never cheat.
Look, Amy,
don't play games with me.
I've got a lot on my mind.
You're not being fair.
I'm just trying to help.
If you want to help,
then get your friends to finish.
Get the garage makers and the
rat catchers- Get them all to finish!
- Oh.
- A-And fix the toilet
and clean up the kitchen.
That would be a terrific help!
I love you, Amy,
but I want you to leave me alone.
Okay.
I'll leave you alone
with your blackboard.
Don't play games with me.
No.
Don't do it, Amy.
They were practically licking my body.
Who was practically
licking your body?
Venner and Scutt.
I congratulate them on their taste.
Damn rat catcher staring at me.
Why don't you wear a bra?
Why should I?
You shouldn't go around without one
and not expect that type to stare.
Look...
if you could hammer a nail, Venner
and Scutt wouldn't be out there.
Listen, Amy, uh...
fixing the toaster
and getting the garage built...
is not exactly the reason
I came here in the first place.
Are you saying
you'd be happier if we hadn't left?
We left because
I got a grant to do work...
which I haven't found
the time to do.
You left because...
you didn't want
to take a stand, commit.
Commit to what?
Huh?
I was involved with my work.
You want something out of me
that is not right to deliver.
That's not what I was there for.
But I know why you're here.
Why?
Could it be because there's
no place else to hide?
I'm here because you once said...
y-you thought
we could be happier here.
Remember?
I'm sorry.
Are you sorry sorry,
or just sorry?
Sorry sorry.
Then come here.
I'm gonna take a bath.
Why?
You don't need one.
I think I do.
Hey.
By the way, I never claimed to be
one of the, uh, "involved."
Don't forget
to draw the curtains.!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Thinking?
Mm-hmm.
- Don't want to come
for a walk, do you?
- Sure.
When?
In a little while.
Hey, hey, come on.
Come on.
Hello.
Good evening.
Kitty.! Kitty.!
Kitty, kitty.
David, I can't find the cat.!
Can you forget the cat
and let me work for a minute!
Kitty.!
Kitty, kitty, kitty.
- Kitty? Kitty, kitty?
"Kitty, kitty.
Kitty, kitty, kitty."
- Shit.
- Here, kitty, kitty.
Other side, sir.
- Hang on. Hang on.
- Hold it, hold it.
- Wait for him for a minute.
Where be the blackbird
- Oh!
- Hey, let him pass!
Let's see how good he is!
Whoo!
- You're out of your mind.!
- Hello, Henry.
- Hello, Janice.
Henry! Come here!
Oh, he's all right.
Aren't you, Henry?
Henry, how many times
I gotta tell you, boy?
You don't listen.
Come on.
Come on, Henry.
We're going home.
What do you want?
You'd have known for sure what
she was after 20 years ago, eh, Tom?
- Now, now, that'll do.
- They still down at the hall bingoin'?
- Yeah.
Tell her I'm behavin' meself.
I'll be along soon.
Bobby.!
Run along now.
- Hello, David.
- Hi.
Bobby!
Take care of your sister, mind.
I will, Dad.
- Bye, Mr. Sumner.
- Good-bye.
I'd like a scotch, double...
with ice.
Cheers.
- Evening, Major.
- Mr. Sumner?
- Yes?
I was about to call up to your farm to
welcome you into our little community.
I've just been welcomed.
- I'm John Scott.
- Hello.
I saw your car outside. I thought
perhaps we could drive up together.
I wanted to have
the good Reverend and Mrs. Hood...
talk you into joining us at the
church social this coming Thursday.
The vicar will run me home.
Can I buy you a drink, Major,
before you go?
No, thank you, Tom.
We're in a hurry.
Buy 'em all one.
- Good night, Major.
Watch out for sheep.!
- You got your
Wellington boots on, Major?
Now, some men
goes for women
And some men
goes for boys
But my love's
warm and beautiful
And makes
a baa-in' noise
- Amy, nice to see you.
- Major, why haven't you
been out to see us before?
- Shearing time. My apologies.
- I see you brought
my drunken husband home.
- Come on, I'm not drunk yet.
Certainly not my fault.
- Hi. I'm David Sumner.
- I just brought him home.
- Barny Hood.
- Reverend.
- My wife.
- Mrs. Hood.
- Hello.
- Well, well. Please sit down.
- Barny. Louise.
- Hello, Major.
- What are you drinking, Reverend?
Scotch.
The reverend and his wife...
came to invite us to a party
at the church hall next week, David.
Oh.
Well, it's, uh, going to be more than
an invitation, Reverend, isn't it?
Major, you gave away
our secret plan.
- Who said anything about money?
- I was thinking of about five-
I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
And I expect to see you both
at the social and at the church...
when you can spare the time.
Time is a little difficult to find
these days. Uh, so are cats.
By the way, Amy, did you find
your, uh, kitty, kitty, kitty?
No.
At least give us some hope
about your coming to church.
- Yes. After all, hope is your business,
Barny, isn't it?
- Yes, and faith.
- And charity.
- Thanks.
- Amy's been telling us
why you came to Wakely.
- To write, to meditate.
- Why did you come?
I was drafted.
- Well, tell us what you do.
- Okay.
I'm a, uh,
astral mathematician.
Oh. Never heard of it.
- That's because I just made it up.
I'll get you another drink.
I have a grant to study, uh...
possible structures
in stellar interiors...
and the implications regarding
their radiation characteristics.
- Am I boring anyone?
- Radiation- That's
an unfortunate dispensation.
It surely is.
Yes, indeed.
As long as it's not
another bomb.
You're a scientist.
Can you deny the responsibility?
Can you?
After all, there's never been
a kingdom given to so much bloodshed...
as that of Christ.
- That's Montesquieu, isn't it?
- Oh, really?
Who's he?
Somebody well worth reading.
We'd better leave
these good people.
Yes, well, you won't let me
walk home, will you, Barny?
Mrs. Hood,
you're very lovely.
- I'll get your coat.
- Does God bore you, Amy?
In the areas of boredom, Mrs. Hood,
God is not my problem.
You were... awful
to the reverend.
No, no, no, no.
I wasn't.
He's all right.
I like him.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
His wife is very attractive.
Oh.
Yes, she is, isn't she?
- Here, I think l-
I think you need some help.
- David.
- Hmm?
What's a binary number?
Uh, zeroes or ones...
plus or minus.
In sequences of twos.
- Hey, that's right.
You're a bright lady.
You're not so dumb.
Sometimes I need help.
When?
Like, um, now, maybe.
You got it.
What's the matter?
Scutt or Cawsey.
I've locked all the doors
and windows downstairs.
Let's keep them locked
from now on. All right?
Great.
Did you hear me?
What?
Scutt or Cawsey.
- Why?
- To prove to you they could
get into your bedroom.
I don't believe that.
Well, who else
is around all the time?
Amy, uh...
we've left all...
the doors unlocked.
I mean, it could have
been anybody passing.
- "Anybody passing"?
David, a complete stranger
comes into our house...
and decides to strangle our cat
and hang her in the wardrobe?
- Somebody passing?
Cawsey or Scutt.
Here, Charlie.
It's bloody heavy.
Lousy way to make a livin; though.
You gonna look at them all day?
Would you feel better
if I went out and talked to them?
Not necessarily.
Perhaps we could just pack up and leave.
Nobody's leaving.
Why? Because we paid for a year?
Look, Amy,
I'm not going to...
just go out there
and blatantly accuse them.
You don't have to accuse them.
You could start by mentioning that our
cat was strangled and see what happens.
You can believe in the possibility,
can't you?
Okay. Okay.
I'll go out and mention to them
that the cat is missing...
and I'll ask them
if they've seen her.
All right,
let's see what it's good for.
- You don't think that's enough, do you?
- Not quite.
Perhaps you'd like to write them
a note on your blackboard.
Well, I thought he might enjoy it.
- How are you?
- Fine, thank you, sir.
- How's it, uh, going up there?
- It's all right, sir.
Yeah. Want a smoke?
I like the smell of those
American cigarettes, Mr. Sumner.
Can you give me a hand with that
mantrap? Just wanna get it in the house.
Uh, right through here.
Right here by the fireplace.
Thanks.
Amy, listen.
I'm gonna catch them off guard.
- When?
- Right now.
Open or closed, Mr. Sumner?
Uh, gee, I don't know.
Uh, open it.
If you can.
Sorry, Charlie.
Bite, sir.
I can appreciate that.
Be careful.
Watch that hand
on the spring.
Pretty dangerous thing, sir.
- This is the, uh, safety lock, sir.
- Right.
Where would you like it, sir?
Uh, put it right over
the fireplace there.
You fellows like some beer?
- Very nice.
- Oh, very welcome.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Uh, cheers, miss.
- Mr. Sumner.
- Huh?
Would you like to
shoot with us sometime?
Oh, I've, uh-
I never hunted much.
Oh, but you've, uh,
shot, Mr. Sumner?
Just once or twice,
but that was-
Be easy then.
You should try it, sir.
Living here at Trencher's, with good
shootin'outside the door. Eh, Norman?
Right. Right, sir.
When?
How about tomorrow, sir?
Okay. Thank you.
That m- That might be... fun.
I'd like that.
Thank you.
What about the garage?
It can wait.
We'll meet at Wakely
at about half past 8:00.
- You know the pub?
- Yes, I do.
Well, we'd better
get back to work, sir.
Thank you for putting that up.
That's all right, sir.
Oh, I, uh,
I don't have a gun.
But, uh-
will this do?
Ah.
There'll be plenty extra, sir.
Good.
- Thank you for the drink, sir.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks for the drink, sir.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Hey, Charlie, Charlie.
Wait, wait, wait.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org