Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Fucking Federales, dude.
I got weed on me.
I'll meet you on the other side.
Don't worry, I'll take care of this.
Hold on. Back up here.
Excuse me.
Let us into Mexico, please?
Okay, so, thank you!
I guess I checked out, then.
Look at that! I guess our RV is tore up.
Well, guess we'll have to take a plane
the rest of the way.
Oh, well. Come on, let's go.
- Dude, what happened in there, man?
- Nothing. Really cool people.
So, come on, let's book.
What, really?
I mean, everything okay in there?
- 'Cause you look really pale.
- Yeah.
That's because I wear sun block,
you ass. Okay?
So, come on, let's grab that airplane
and get out of here.
- So, what happened in that room?
- Drop it.
- Drop what?
- Okay, look, they...
Oh, come on! I come in peace, brother.
Come on.
You guys, the plane's boarding.
Hey guys, I need to tell you something.
What, you're quitting?
Come on, no, it's...
No, no, I'm not quitting.
It's actually the opposite.
I wanted to thank you guys.
I took this job 'cause I needed it,
but I also took it for other reasons.
I figured a trip into the jungle would
be a kind of a forced sobriety for me,
and that's something
I really need in my life.
My name's Bill W.
And I'm an alcoholic.
- Hey, Bill.
- Hi, Bill.
Because of that, I've never really fit in
anywhere, you know?
I want to tell you guys.
Couple days ago, I took my last drink.
And then I did yesterday, and, well,
God willing, this'll really be the last one.
'Cause we're going to the jungle and
I got some tough times ahead of me.
But you guys
have been really great to me.
And I just want to say that you've
really made me part of your family
and I wanna say thank you for that.
- That's so sweet.
- Thank you.
Whitaker, that is some of the finest
words I've ever heard in my life.
And just hearing them makes me feel
like I'm a better person.
So, fuck it, man. Take a bow.
He was like, "I'm an alcoholic."
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Strange Wilderness?
That's us.
I'm Pete, and this is the rest of them.
Hi, I'm Cheryl.
- It is so nice to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
Yeah, Bill told me
what Pierson did to his wife.
Bill's a good man.
Shouldn't have happened to him.
He's upset. That's why he asked me
to get you to Gus Hayden.
- That's great. Great.
- Now for the bad news.
Pierson's got about
a three-day jump on you.
- Oh, no.
- But, hey, don't worry about it.
We'll find him.
Tell you what, we'll go up to Gus's
and we'll head out from there
and make up for lost time.
- All right.
- By the way, my name's Dick.
Dick what?
Just Dick.
Dick?
Dick.
Like Cher, but Dick?
He's fucking... Who is this?
Dick, Dick, Dick, Dick, Dick.
Gotta have more name than that, Dick.
Nope. Just Dick.
You say, "Dick," I come running.
You come where?
You like your name? You like Dick?
Do you ever let your dog
lick your name?
Yeah, do you like it?
Is your name Dick?
I don't wanna get started off
on the wrong foot with you guys.
Does your name ever shrink
if you go in cold water?
Snicker one more time, I'll kick
your balls up in your fucking neck.
- Check.
- 10-4.
Copy that.
Our trail's about 23 clicks west of here.
Right.
Does your name ever get hard
in the morning?
Shut the fuck up.
On our way to hook up
with legendary tracker, Gus Hayden,
we encountered many jungle animals,
including our furry relative,
the monkey.
Monkeys make up over 80%
of the world's monkey population.
Hundreds of ants are eaten each year
by monkeys.
Researchers believe
that these numbers would be far less,
if ants were the same size
or bigger than monkeys.
Wow, look at that.
Those balls are sensational.
To a lion,
these balls are called a "sack lunch."
Over here,
we spot some South American gazelles.
This gazelle is eating a flower.
This lion is eating the gazelle.
But he'll probably spit out the flower.
These giraffes can't quit each other.
I think it would be a good idea to tie
your brand new jeans to their heads.
That way, your jeans
would get that distressed look.
These birds are saying howdy
to the zebra.
Actually, they're not saying howdy,
they're eating the shit out of him.
If we held a microphone up to the zebra
and he could talk like,
you know, Mr. Ed or something, it would
probably sound something like this,
"Oh, my God. Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
"Did one of you just
shove your beak up my ass?"
All right. We'll walk from here.
All right, let's go, chop-chop.
It's about three clicks that way.
Stay on the trail. Follow me. Let's go.
Let's go!
All right. You're about to meet the
world's greatest tracker, Gus Hayden.
Welcome to paradise.
I hear we're gonna have a little fun.
I shoved my knife through
the top of his skull into his brain.
Then I grabbed my hand grenade,
pushed that into his head hole.
And I shoved him back down into the
tunnel and ran like hell.
Hey, Gus.
That was a great Vietnam story.
But I think...
You wanna let go of Fred there?
I think you're close to killing him.
Sorry, I forgot about you there, partner.
Anyway, the little gook bit me,
and that's how I got this scar
right here on this thumb.
Cool.
So, Gus, tell us,
what are we in store for tomorrow?
We'll break camp at 0600.
I want you all to understand that when
we head into the Coconga Wilderness,
we'll be going into a bad, dark place
where death is about as routine
as a change of pants.
Well, this crew here?
We've been through some
pretty hairy adventures of our own.
And I know you got that little scar
there on your thumb,
but we've gotten a few scars
over the years ourselves.
- Isn't that right, Fred?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, look at this one.
Eight years old. Fell off my bike.
Shit.
Check out this guy. See that?
I was doing some Bondo work
on a '67 Pontiac Sky Chief
and I was drunk, as usual,
and caught this on the hood ornament.
Nasty.
But... Hey, two days sober today, guys.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Well, I don't have any scars,
but I have this really great birthmark.
See?
You see this right here?
Dog bit me when I was a kid.
I was blowing in his face,
and he nipped...
Well, now.
You're talking scars, I got one for you.
About 10 years ago
I was scouting out a location
for a mining company in the Amazon,
when I was ambushed
by a tribe of Aloha pygmies.
They tied me to a post and did to me
what they do to all white men.
They cut my scrotum with a sharp stick.
Then they ran away.
My testicles unraveled down
to the ground.
I scooped up my testicles
from out of the dirt, rolled them up,
shoved them back into my sac,
and then sewed it shut myself.
Looks like a quilt. A ball quilt.
Okay, well...
I'd love to sit here
and swap some more scar stories,
but I'm all out.
I'm tired.
Yeah, you know what? Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna saw some logs, myself.
- Yeah.
- All right. All right.
Must have the worst nightmares ever.
Pete.
- Hey!
- What?
Dude, that tracker guy left,
and Cheryl ran off with him.
Cheryl? Cheryl!
What? She ran off with Gus Hayden?
She's gone, he's gone,
and all our shit's gone!
- Hey, you're probably in on it!
- No!
He left me just as stranded as you all.
He took my bunker jeep.
We got nothing!
- Shit! Why would Cheryl do this to us?
- No, no, no.
I saw her eyeing that fucking psycho
across the campfire last night.
Shit! Shit! God!
Shit! Shit!
God!
All right, calm down!
Everybody, just pull yourself together!
Bill, I need you to take an inventory
of everything that's left, okay? Go, now.
Okay. We got one sleeping bag,
so I think we're pretty much fucked.
No, I think we're gonna be okay.
I think we're great. Let's go find Bigfoot.
What aren't you hearing?
He took the map!
We can't find Bigfoot without a map!
Yeah, but we can't give up, okay?
We can't!
'Cause my dad wouldn't give up.
You know that. You knew him.
I mean, he'd always make it work out.
And I'm just like my dad!
All right. Okay.
I'll lead you through the jungle.
I'm going as far as Temescal,
but after that, you're on your own.
- Okay.
- That jungle is thick.
I don't think anybody's
ever even been in there.
You know, you should quit now,
while you're alive.
Nope. Not on my watch.
Guys?
I don't wanna die.
For the first time in 11 years,
I'm seeing the world through sober eyes
and it's exhilarating.
See, I have so much to live for
right now.
I want to find a nice girl
and settle down and have kids
and dance with them in the moonlight
and everything.
I want to do it all, you know?
Fucking beautiful. Take a bow, man.
He was like, "I'm wearing a blue shirt
and I'm sad in my heart."
I didn't think you were gonna do that!
Okay! Cooker, you need to...
Is that a thong you're wearing?
What the fuck did you say?
Do you have a thong on?
Yeah, I'm wearing a thong.
I'll get the sleeping bag.
Dick, there any snakes in this shit,
or what?
Don't worry about fucking snakes.
Fuck you, dude.
Shit, a porcupine.
Hey. Hey!
I think it stopped. I think it stopped.
- Oh, God. This is insane.
- All right.
No. It's gonna be okay, I think.
It's gonna be okay.
Come on, let's just keep moving.
It'll be okay.
- What the fuck was that?
- Just keep going. It's gonna be fine.
- Come on.
- Hey, come on!
Guys, guys, guys, just a monkey.
It's just a monkey.
Jesus.
- You guys!
- Oh, shit!
I have been tracking you for hours.
Why did you leave me back there?
Well, we thought you ran off
with Gus Hayden.
You really think I'd do that?
Yeah.
Gross.
I'd wanna fuck even you guys
before I'd wanna fuck him.
- Hey.
- All right.
You guys, I woke up
and he was stealing all our stuff,
so I pretended like
I wanted to go with him
and I convinced him to give me this.
The map.
You convinced him?
What'd you have to do?
Just a little something. Okay?
I took one for the team.
I have a map.
- Me, too. I got a map.
- I got a bunch of maps.
I have an atlas.
I have some old Civil War maps
that are worth quite a bit.
I have a map of the moon.
It's like... You can feel it.
I got a whole map store.
Maps everywhere.
If we get back to the RV,
I got a Thomas Guide.
Like a hundred pages of maps.
Come here, you guys!
Just kidding. I don't have a map.
I'll tell you, I will be damned.
I will just be damned.
You know, with that map
and my jungle survival skills,
just might be able
to help you find Bigfoot after all.
Yeah!
Dick! Dick! Dick!
- We love Dick!
- Yes, we are.
Yes, we are. First, though,
we gotta cross the Mohate River.
We're almost there.
Just straight that way.
Okay, you're doing great, Fred.
- Thank you, thank you.
- You're doing great.
- Cooker, I'm proud of you.
- Hey, Dick. I'm proud of you in turn.
You're the best. You're the best.
Now, I know a secret quick way through
this jungle,
and we can get to the rocky cliffs
and maybe cut off Pierson.
Now, here's what you're gonna do.
What the... Oh, God!
Don't come in here! No! Stay out!
Oh, Dick!
Here's another one
of those piranha bastards.
Fucking eat all these fucking stupid fish.
We were gonna make it,
and then these bastards ate Dick!
- How's it feel to get eaten, fish fuckers?
- Yeah!
- How's it feel to get eaten?
- Stupid... Stupid fish!
You think we'd just let you get away
with eating Dick,
you sons-of-bitches,
pieces of river trash!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Hey, wait a minute.
These are the fish that ate Dick, right?
Yeah!
All right, just go with me here.
If Dick is in the fishes,
and we're eating the fishes,
doesn't that mean we're eating Dick?
What the fuck?
- It's gonna be okay! Come on! Fred.
- No!
Not one single thing has gone our way!
And I guarantee you
Pierson found Bigfoot's cave days ago.
Come on, Fred!
Don't be so negative, okay?
Come on...
Our luck is gonna change, I can feel it.
Oh, my God.
You guys have to come with me.
I think I found something.
- It's Pierson's team.
- Holy crap.
Fred. Get over here, Fred.
Mr. Wah I'm So Bummed Out.
Pierson's Gonna Find Bigfoot First...
I don't think so, buddy!
Looks like our luck is changing.
We came out on top! Come on!
Oh, yeah. Oh, right. This is tragic.
Amen. Okay,
let's gather up their equipment, guys.
Sweet axe.
Gentle clouds of Nazareth
Massacred in Ecuador
Life's too fucking short
Ask that guy
Hey, that's Sky Pierson.
- Oh, my God!
- Gaulke.
- Hey.
Hi, Sky. Wow, long time no see.
So...
I'm sorry. Sorry about that.
I just had some bad fish.
So, what happened here?
Attacked.
Coconga pygmies.
Horrible.
Hey, Sky,
could you feel this?
Dude.
What are you poking him for, man?
The guy's dying.
His upper half of his body
is not connected to his lower half.
- Yeah, I know. Jesus Christ. What?
- Hey, Pete, Pete.
You gonna punch him in the face
like Bill asked?
Oh, shit. Forgot about that.
It's your call.
Oh, man. I don't know.
I'm kind of on the fence about it.
It's not like he's in any position
to punch you back.
Fred, it has nothing to do with fear.
I mean, don't you think it's a little
excessive, punching him in the face?
He's missing the lower half of his body.
Gaulke.
- Hey, we're back.
- Gaulke, you still here?
Yeah, we're here.
Hey, the cavalry has arrived.
Sky.
Oh, Sky.
Let's go.
Pick up what you can carry,
especially the camera equipment.
Let's get the hell out of here.
See, I could've sworn
these are the markings!
They're right there on the map.
Well, then, where the hell is the cave?
It says it's on the map, but it's not there!
Hey, does anyone else
get the feeling that,
like, we've been going in circles
for a while?
Shit! Shit! Shit! Fucking shit!
Shit!
Fuck! Such a fuck up!
Give me that fucking map!
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
You said that Bill Calhoun
took a real picture of the map, right?
Yeah, Pierson was holding it
in his hands.
Okay. Bill was using
two security cameras.
It's a mirror image. Look at the "N".
The map got printed out backwards.
Flip the picture.
Cheryl, you are a genius!
Okay, so wait.
So all the directions are reversed.
So then that means
that the cave is not here.
It's gonna be over, around here.
Come on, let's go!
That's it.
That's the cave. It's gotta be. Map.
See? Turn the map.
Rock formation fits with the hill.
That cave is his cave.
How do we know he's in there?
I can feel him. Okay, come on.
We're gonna move closer,
but stealthily, like that of a cheetah.
Oh, my God, I can hear him.
He's in there. Holy God. Okay.
This is probably the most important
wildlife discovery of our time,
and we're gonna chronicle it.
Okay.
Okay, over there. Cross, cross.
This is crazy.
Okay, set up the camera.
Okay, listen up.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna do an intro throw announce,
and then we're gonna
slowly steal inside
and catch this amazing creature
in his natural habitat, okay?
Okay, ready?
Oh, remember. Okay, listen. Junior!
- Listen.
- I am.
Do not spook him, okay?
He is probably very,
very frightened of us.
- Okay.
I got sound if you wanna go.
Ready, rolling.
And five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Talking now.
Hi. I'm Peter Gaulke,
and this is Strange Wilderness.
Camped here, waiting to film Bigfoot.
That's right, you heard me, Bigfoot.
Animals have long been known
as animals, not human,
and have been described as stupid,
cowardly, aggressive, dimwitted,
low beasts, eager to kill, eager to eat,
eager to fornicate,
eager to stampede all...
But is it animals we describe,
or is it mankind?
Perhaps this Bigfoot creature can
bridge the divide between us and them.
Perhaps his gentle ways can teach us,
remind us
that peace and harmony
are necessary if mankind is to survive.
What?
Oh, fuck!
Hey...
Does anybody remember what that
big bastard said before he came at us?
I think he said, "Huh?"
Like he wasn't sure what was going on.
- No. It was more of a growl.
- Yeah, totally.
Actually, you know what?
It was more like a death growl.
It was like, "I'm gonna kill you."
I mean, I heard that.
- Yeah, no, I did, too. Yeah.
- Yeah.
I heard it, too.
- Didn't I?
- Yeah. No. Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- That's what he said, man.
I've just, you know,
I've just never killed anything before.
But it was in self-defense, so...
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah. The lady's right.
This mythological beast
was engineered by the French.
Fuck, I was so blind to not see it before.
It was designed by the French
in the early '50s
to fuck and eventually
kill American people.
He would've come
and fucking killed all of us.
You know what?
Like, if a mosquito is buzzing
around your ear, do you let it go?
Like, "Keep on bothering me
and, like, sting me
"and let me get West Nile Virus?"
No, you fucking smack it, like we did.
Only we did it with guns.
- I don't know, guys. I mean...
- What?
Well, I mean...
- Fuck him, right?
- Yeah.
That prick deserved to die, right?
Big, hairy, carnivore son-of-a-bitch.
You see the way he came at us,
all up in our face and all...
Fucking fuck you, you fuck.
- Yeah!
Fucking cocktease.
But, you know, I've been thinking.
Maybe it's not the best way
to end our show, though?
You know, actually killing Bigfoot?
Yeah.
Probably not gonna fly
with the TV station.
Peter, I have a little idea.
Those sharks
ate the living shit out of me,
like my leg was a fucking piece of corn
on the cob with butter on it.
I was yelling at them
that I wasn't no seal.
"Hey, it's me, Danny-boy!"
But they didn't understand
my human language.
So I got this fake leg now.
The doc comes in my room,
and he asks me what kind I want.
What the fuck?
It turns out he's talking about
the wood or some shit.
Mahogany, pine, or balsa?
So, that gets me thinking,
"I should put a jackhammer on there,
"so when I walk up the sidewalk
I could bust up the cement."
Okay. All right, listen up, everybody.
We're gonna have him eating out
of our hands when he sees this. This.
The television show of the century, huh?
Yeah.
- Bring it.
- Let's do it.
- High five!
- Good luck.
We were all shivering with excitement
as we carefully moved in
for the first ever contact
with the legendary Bigfoot.
What we found inside the cave
shocked us all.
Apparently, the Bigfoot
had been experiencing depression
and hung himself.
Forced to live like an animal
in a cold dark cave,
I imagine any one of us
would've done the same thing.
Unlike that dude on fire
at the peace rally,
we sprung into action
to revive the Bigfoot.
But it was too late.
It made me feel so crappy.
And so ended our fantastic adventure,
"The Search for Bigfoot."
Join us next week
for a show about beavers.
Are you insane?
Did someone drop a safe on your head?
That's the craziest shit I've ever seen!
- Hey, quit shoving me, man!
- Yeah, what's that?
Man, you've been a dick since day one!
- Yeah? Fuck you!
- Get out, assholes!
- Fuck you, Judy.
- Yeah.
You know what? This is all because of
you and your stupid idea
about faking Bigfoot's suicide.
You know, I should've never listened...
I should've never hired you!
That's the most un-American thing
I've ever heard in my life.
Excuse me, could you keep it down?
Hey, sweetheart, we're having
a private company meeting here.
So why don't you keep it down, okay?
Hey, hey, we're in the middle
of a fucking conversation,
you turn around to hit on some chick.
Hey, why you all up in my waist, man?
You feeling froggy, huh?
- Why don't you take a leap?
- I can't. That's fucked up.
You shouldn't talk to someone like that.
You stone-wasted half-man party punk!
Shut the...
Whoa, seriously, man. Come on,
he's pathetic. Take it easy on him.
Fuck you, Cheech.
You suck as a soundman, dude.
You stupid fuck. Go buy some sandals.
Go buy some sandals.
You want to fight? I'll fight your fight.
I haven't fought in 10 years.
I'm fighting tonight.
What you got? What you got?
Let's see. Throw down, bitch.
Throw down, bitch.
Hey, you know what? He's right, Fred!
You suck as a soundman, okay...
All right, that's it. I'm calling security.
Oh, no, honey,
you are not calling security.
- You understand me?
- Hey! Hey!
And that is the whole ridiculous story.
No, I haven't seen anybody in,
like, over a year.
You know, things were said.
I think they're a lot better off
without me around anyway.
I'm such a failure. Oh, shit.
Hey, thanks for listening, okay?
I'll talk to you tomorrow. Great. Bye.
Nobody's home!
Pete.
You know
when you yell out "Nobody's home,"
people know you're home
because otherwise
who the hell would be yelling out
"Nobody's home."
Brought out a smile.
Well, you won't return my calls,
so I thought I'd personally
hand-deliver a hello.
No, I just couldn't hold it all together.
You know what I've always been
wanting to tell you,
all the times you have
beaten yourself up...
Times were different then. It was easier.
You know something?
Your old man
could never have survived today.
I loved your dad, you know that,
but he didn't have the tenacity
and the heart that you have.
You were born into a wildlife family.
Like your old man used to say,
"All it takes is one good idea."
Yeah, he used to always say that.
With one good idea
anything can happen.
- But it's up to you.
- Yeah.
What do you say?
I say, "Let's do it."
- Pete Gaulke's back!
- Yeah. Right.
You know what? Thanks, man.
I mean, I really get...
- Hey, do you mind if I tap a bowl first?
- Go ahead.
You know, because... Where's it?
You know,
I have a bunch of great ideas,
and they seem like great ideas
for about 10 minutes,
and then I'm sitting here for a while
and all of a sudden they seem stale.
And then I forget about them,
I don't write them down anymore...
I mean, I think what I need to do is
really kind of...
Oh, God. That little guy is gonna think
he's a shark.
Hey, wait a minute.
What a hell of an idea for a show.
A show about sharks, huh?
- One good idea.
- Good idea!
Yeah, buddy!
All right.
Hot Dog Hell, can I help you?
Yeah, I need six hotdogs,
I need six cokes,
and the best damn soundman
in the business.
I need Fred Wolf's ass in this car now.
Pete! Holy shit, man. You know what?
I've been going through it in my head.
Fifty different ways
on how to apologize to you
for what I said that day, man.
We're all sorry
about all the stuff we said.
Hey, man, the world keeps turning,
you know?
Hey, dads may die
and you may miss him every day,
but you still have your friends.
That was beautiful, man. Take a bow.
Asshole!
Why are they using such bad language?
Yeah, I called Lawson,
and he was mad at first.
He said, Bigfoot thing
was the craziest thing he ever saw.
Well, then he never saw R. Kelly's
Trapped in a Fucking Closet!
But he said
if we could get a shark attack on film,
he'd put us back on the air.
So get in the fucking car and let's go!
Get in there!
Excuse me. I didn't say... Hey, hey, hey!
Hi, Ed, how are you?
We got a shark episode
with a shark attack.
Hi, I'm Peter Gaulke
and this is Strange Wilderness.
The ocean. Many words
have been used to describe it.
And now you can add one more.
Dangerous.
Why? The shark.
It was one year ago today,
that Danny was brutally attacked
on this very spot
by one of these killing machines.
In today's show, we'll be taking
a close look at this mysterious creature
that should be named
"the asshole of the sea."
Menacing and terrifying,
the shark has been menacing
and terrifying for over a decade.
Sharks can only be found
in two places on earth,
the Northern
and Southern Hemispheres.
This shark is called a Hammerhead
because his head looks like a hammer.
These sharks
are attacking Nicole Richie.
Yes, the shark is a... What the fuck!
Look at that thing's teeth.
Okay, you guys ready?
I've never been more ready
in my fucking life.
It's like that shark was gnawing on me
like a rawhide stick.
- This one's for you, Danny.
- How old are those?
Three weeks old.
For you, Danny.
Oh, my God, it's gonna come up.
Give me that shit.
All right, let's do this.
Fred, lower the steak.
All right, come on. Let's do this.
That's him. That's that same fucker.
There's a fin. I see a fin.
- I see it, too.
- Hey, shark!
We got something for you,
you fucking asshole!
Oh, my God, he's...
That was awesome.
Fuck you, motherfucker!
How did that shit taste?
That did it.
Pete...
Pete, people love shark attacks.
Besides, Pierson's dead,
so you're back on the air.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org