Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It looks like she drug
in a real crowd, don't it?
Sure does.
Looks like it's gonna be
a full house tonight.
Hey, what do you say we run in
and check out the show?
How we doing here? We all
set? Hey, big crowd, huh?
Yeah, and not one of them's
got a pot to piss in.
I never should have let myself
get talked into this dumb benefit.
I could be making some real money tonight.
All right, let's get this thing started.
And now back home again
the one, the only
Ellen Aim!
Lying in your bed
and on a Saturday night
You're sweatin' buckets
and it's not even hot
But your brain
has got the message
And it's sending it out
To every nerve
and every muscle you've got
You've got so many dreams
That you don't know
where to put 'em
So you'd better turn
a few of 'em loose
Your body's got a feeling
that it's starting to rust
You'd better rev it up
and put it to use
And I don't know how I ever thought
that I could make it all alone
When you only make it better
And it better be tonight
I'll be there for you tonight
Even if you don't have
anywhere to go
You go down on the pedal
and you're ready to roll
And your speed
Is all you'll ever need
All you'll ever need to know
Darlin', Darlin'
You and me
we're goin' nowhere slowly
And we've gotta get away
from the past
There's nothin' wrong
with goin' nowhere, baby
But we should
be goin' nowhere fast
It's so much better
goin' nowhere fast
Stalkin' in the shadows
by the light of the moon
It's like a prison
and the night is a cell
Goin' anywhere
has gotta be heaven tonight
'Cause stayin' here
has gotta be hell
Dyin' in the city
like a fire on the water
Let's go runnin'
on the back of the wind
There's gotta be some action
on the face of the earth
And I've gotta
see your face once again
And I don't know where I ever got
the bright idea that I was cool
So alone and independent
But I'm depending on you now
And you'll always be the only
thing that I just can't be without
And I'm out for you tonight
I'm comin' out
for you tonight
Even if you don't
have anywhere to go
You go down on the pedal
and you're ready to roll
And your speed
Is all you'll ever need
All you'll ever need to know
Darlin', Darlin'
You and me
we're goin' nowhere slowly
And we've gotta get away
from the past
There's nothin' wrong
with goin' nowhere, baby
But we should be
goin' nowhere fast
Everybody's goin'
nowhere slowly
They're only fighting
for the chance to be last
There's nothin' wrong
with goin' nowhere, baby
But we should be
goin' nowhere fast
Godspeed
Speed us away
We're goin' nowhere fast
Godspeed
Speed us away
We're goin' nowhere fast
Godspeed
Speed us away
Now!
Hey, what the hell do you think
you're doing? Get off the stage!
Hey, you guys
shouldn't be doing this!
Hey, we don't want
no trouble!
Let me go!
No!
Put me down now!
Let me go! Let me go!
Help me!
Get them!
Them Goddamn son-of-a-bitches!
Hang a one-eight.
What's with that guy?
Watch out!
These guys are gonna pay!
Someone help me!
Stop it!
Can I help you?
Coffee.
Cream and sugar?
Just black.
Oh, you guys really know
how to come through a door.
What are you trying to prove?
We just came down from Kings
Park looking for a good time.
You guys already missed all the
excitement. The party's over.
The Roadmasters are hungry. And
when they're hungry, they eat.
The Bombers have brought this
act through The Richmond already.
All you're doing in here
is looking like punks.
Is that right?
We're just gonna
have to mess the place up.
And after we mess your place
up maybe we'll mess you up.
Oh, you got a problem
with this, pretty boy?
Try it again, punk.
Go on, go home!
What do you think
of my new car?
It looks great. Why don't you
sell it and buy me a new window?
Tom, come on, slow down.
Reva, there's no point in stealing a
car, if you're not gonna ring it out.
When are you
ever gonna grow up?
Why should I?
This is more fun.
Let me give you
some news, Tom.
The Bombers and this guy Raven
Shaddock, they stole Ellen Aim.
How the hell did that happen?
Oh, shit!
Goddamn cops!
Okay, buddy, what the
hell do you think this is?
We don't go for that kind
of speeding around here.
Now let's see your license.
Sorry, Officer,
I must have left it at home.
Tom Cody. It's been a couple of years
since I've had any trouble out of you.
Hey, Ed, I just came home
to visit my big sister.
You're not gonna have any
trouble with me. Glad to hear it.
We don't need somebody coming back
here trying to give us a hard time.
Come on, Ed, he just got back.
Give him a break.
Yeah, I'll give him a break.
Get out of here, Cody.
Yeah, and anymore driving like
that and I'll give you a ticket.
Asshole!
Who the hell
does that guy think he is?
Well, he's always been a real bad ass.
I busted him a couple of years ago.
He had a pistol in the
glove compartment of his car.
A real punk, huh?
Yeah, he belongs in jail with all
the other juvenile delinquents.
You sure I'm not gonna be cramping
your style with any guy tonight, huh?
No, not tonight.
I bring one in now and then
but there's nothing steady.
I never seem to find
the right one.
Yeah, I ain't having much luck
in that department myself.
Look, Tom, you were always
real close with Ellen.
She wasn't like all those tramps
you used to run around with.
Reva,
it didn't work out, okay?
Well, somebody figured out
how to make it work with her.
She's been living with a guy
named Billy Fish. Who's that?
He's done some rock joints in The
Battery. He started managing her act.
Yeah, she was always
interested in going somewhere.
Tom.
She's not just your old girl.
Reva, what do you want from
me, huh? You know what I want.
You want me to go rescue an old girlfriend
who's shacked up with another guy?
Thanks a lot.
Tequila.
Hey, Tom! Tom Cody.
It's been a long time, pal.
How's your hammer hanging?
How's it going, Clyde?
Well, not so hot. I got beat
up trying to save your old girl.
I could use a little help with those
guys. You should have been there, Tom.
It would have been like the old days when
we were in school. We'd have kicked ass.
Hey, bartender, you gonna
shoot the shit all night,
or do you wanna
get me another drink?
Hey, Tom, would you get a
load of this little heinie?
She thinks she owns the place.
I'm just trying to
get myself a drink, pal.
Well, maybe you've already
had enough, babe.
You gotta be kidding me!
Do I look like I'm kidding?
You know, maybe you
ought to pay up as well.
You've been driving up a tab here all
night and we're not real big on credit.
Are you trying to say that I can't pay?
Yeah, let's see the color of your money.
There. Happy? Yeah. But
now I don't like your face.
You know, everywhere I go
there's always an asshole.
Hey, you got any preferences?
I've always been
a tequila man.
Let's get out of here.
The name's McCoy.
I'm a soldier.
At least I was up until about
a year ago, ran out of wars.
Yeah, what's your spec?
Motor pool. Nothing fancy.
But if it's got wheels I can
drive it and I can fix it.
That's funny, I just got
out a couple of months ago.
Been R and R ever since.
Yeah?
How'd you like the army?
I liked shooting the guns,
but I didn't win no medal.
Hey!
Is that your car?
Yeah.
Nice. Yeah, I know. I just picked it up.
Hey, Cody? That's your
name, right, Cody? Yeah.
You got a spare bed?
You want a quick tumble, huh?
Hey, you may have a rough time
with this one,
and I don't wanna hurt
your feelings, but...
You're not my type.
Yeah, I guess it kind of figures. I
ain't had much luck with women lately.
Yeah, well, you'll live.
Something tells me that getting girls
isn't exactly your problem in life.
Maybe some other time, huh? I
doubt it, but anything's possible.
Hey, look...
About the spare bed.
I'm just passing through this
district. I don't know anybody.
I'm between jobs and last
time I heard hotels cost money.
Get in.
My sister's got the bedroom, I got
the spare, that puts you on the couch.
Thanks, man, I appreciate it.
Yeah, no sweat.
There you go, McCoy.
I'll see you in the morning.
Hey, you always walk around packed,
huh? I told you, I'm a soldier.
Yeah, well, don't go pointing that
thing at me, I wouldn't like it.
I don't go pointing it,
unless I'm gonna use it.
Yeah, right.
No, you don't get by on pride
It'll run over you
But since you let me down
I'm hard to be around
I don't know
what I'm gonna do
He could never be you
Okay, you got it.
I'm gonna go and get her.
But I ain't doing it
for nothing.
You tell this Mr. Billy Fish to meet
me at the diner tomorrow at 12:00.
Me and him are gonna talk
some business.
Oh, there's a girl I picked up in
the Black-hawk sleeping on the couch.
Give her some coffee
in the morning, okay?
How come she's sleeping
in the front room?
Why don't you go ask her?
Hey, Pete!
Hey, look, I really needed a place to
stay, so thanks for the use of the sofa.
Oh, that's okay.
You're the first girl Tom
ever brought home that used it.
Yeah, well, sometimes it helps a
guy out if you don't make it so easy.
He could use a little help in that direction.
Maybe he ought to meet a few more like you.
A fellow came through here a
couple of months ago. Tapped out.
Had to part with this outfit
after a card game.
Real unhappy about it, too,
'cause it's all custom stuff.
I tell you, if Tom wasn't going
for being number two to her music,
so he just took off.
He was crazy about Ellen.
He was just the kind of guy
who doesn't like to admit it.
Yeah, sure, I know the type.
I'll tell you something.
Some people never talk about their
feelings, they got them deeper than anybody.
Other people never talk about their
feelings 'cause they ain't got any.
What's your story?
Me? Just looking for work.
You must be Billy Fish?
Yeah. So what gives, and make
it fast my time is valuable.
You want Ellen Aim back,
I'm gonna get her.
You and what army?
I can see you two are gonna
get along just fine.
I want 10 grand. Easy. All
you gotta do is earn it.
I'll earn it
and you're gonna help.
Reva told me you used to
live in The Battery.
I started out there.
It's the shits.
I wouldn't go back
to that dump if you paid me.
You're going! I need somebody
who knows their way around.
I don't think so.
It's not my scene.
If you want your meal ticket
back, get in the car
or otherwise the deal is off.
Look, Cody, you sound pretty
dumb, but nobody's that dumb.
I'm the one paying you.
That means you go get her, I wait
here and you bring her back to me.
You smart guys.
You always figure you can hire a
bum like me to do your dirty work.
Well, not this time!
Can you really get her back?
You got a better volunteer?
All right, I'll go.
She's real important to me.
You know The Battery's
gonna be nothing but trouble.
Yeah? Well, I'm getting
paid for it, right, Fish?
That's right, Cody. You
cut me in, I'll back you up.
I don't think so.
Hey, what's your problem?
We're not taking no skirt along.
Look, I don't think
you can handle it, okay?
What do I gotta do?
You know, people don't exactly have
written references for this kind of work.
You should know that, Cody.
I need the job. I'm plenty good
enough and I ain't gonna let you down.
Listen, skirt, let me make it
simple for you. Take a hike.
All right. I'll cut you in for 10%,
but get this, you're working for me.
I tell you to do something, you do it.
You don't do more or you don't do less.
And if you start dragging
your ass, I'm sending you home.
Got it.
Hey, what is this?
Get serious.
I'm not paying you any extra to take
some sweetie pie along for company.
You drive.
Don't worry about it. They always
hire bums like me for jobs like this.
Look, I'll take you through The
Battery where the Bombers hang out,
but I'm not taking any risks.
I'm not paying you to add
any thrills to my life.
That's not how it works. You
got a real big mouth, Fish.
Look, butch, I buy and sell more
people more valuable than you every day.
You know, it's hard to figure
out what's more pathetic,
the way you talk
or the way you dress.
Let me tell you something.
These clothes are worth more
than you make in a year.
I can see working with you two
is gonna be a real dream.
If they got her anywhere,
they got her at Torchies.
It's a real knockdown joint, no
class. I used to book bands in there.
It's right in the middle of
a big factory. It's the shits.
You'll love it, McCoy. It's just your
style. Okay, Cody, what's the plan?
How do you figure on handling all
these guys and their motorcycles?
You start killing Bombers, we're gonna
be in worse shape than we're already in.
I don't have to kill anybody.
The motorcycles don't run so hot
when I'm shooting holes in them.
Some neighborhood. Everything's
dead. What a place to come to.
Just keep going straight ahead and
then make a left under the bridge.
What are you?
Giving me orders now?
Look, I know my way around.
That's why you brought me
along, remember?
I'll take care
of giving the orders.
Get under the bridge,
pull over and kill the lights.
Well one bad stud
moved in my neighborhood
He's big and man
I know he ain't no good
He don't wear no hat, and
Lord he don't wear no shoes
He just hangs on the corner
singing old country blues
Oh, well, one bad stud
One bad stud
I said, one, one, one, one,
If he likes your baby,
you can kiss your baby goodbye
'Cause the girls all love him
like a schoolboy loves his pie
He loves his whiskey,
he loves his rock 'n' rye
Yes, he loves his whiskey
You know it takes ten bottles
to make that fool get high
Oh, well, one bad stud
One bad stud
You know, you're making
things real hard on yourself.
You act nice, you and me fall in love
for a week or two and then I let you go.
Nobody gets hurt.
You see,
I ain't such a bad guy.
I just get excited
around pretty girls.
Oh, well, one bad stud
One bad stud
I said, one, one, one, one
From now on either of you make any
mistakes, I'm making you walk home.
Walk? I'm not gonna walk
around here, I'd get killed.
You got it.
What about you, McCoy?
Are we gonna do it or are
we gonna talk about it?
You're right.
The main drag
is around here somewhere.
What the hell's that? Guess
you don't know who I am, do you?
Things have gotten kind of
funny around here.
All kinds of strangers coming
around, sneaking through the alleys.
What the hell we talking to this
creep for? Let's get out of here.
My gosh, you're scared. What's
even funnier, you're afraid of me.
I'm just trying to get away from
you. We got some business here.
Oh, you're dumb,
and you're short. Real short.
You're after that girl, aren't
you? What makes you say that?
Come down a back alley, 10:00 at
night carrying a bunch of guns,
I don't figure you're here to give
The Battery a new coat of paint.
Where they keeping her?
Torchies, second floor.
Don't tell them I told
you, though. Pay him.
Yeah, pay me.
I'm not gonna pay this jerk!
Listen, shithead, you give
him some of your money,
or I'll give him
some of your money.
Don't call me "shithead. "
Hey, you gotta
keep moving forward.
That's the whole point of things,
and I thank you now, I appreciate it.
Why don't you buy some soap?
I don't need this guy
to tell me she's in Torchies.
I said they had her
at Torchies. I am a shithead.
Okay, Fish,
you get back to the car.
I want you in that doorway over there
in 15 minutes and I mean 15 minutes.
Are you crazy? They'll notice
me in a second down there.
Don't worry about that.
I'm gonna give them a couple
of other things to worry about.
What about her? I thought she's
supposed to do the driving?
Get moving! And you better
be ready when we get there.
Do you trust him
or are you just desperate?
You take the front entrance.
I'm going topside.
If you can work your way upstairs to
help me out, fine, if not I'll handle it!
Just what I always wanted to
do, Cody, take on the Bombers.
Hey, baby!
I've been around the world
And every man bleeds the same
But when the lights are dim
You never know who's to blame
I don't want no scars to show
I don't want no one to know
So I'll be killing time
in the blue shadows
No other place for me to go
No other place for dying slow
So I'll be killing time
in the blue shadows
I've been around the world
I take credit
for the things I've done
But when the lights are dim
I'm not the only guilty one
I don't want no scars to show
I don't want no one to know
So I'll be killing time
in the blue shadows
Hey! How you doing, babe?
Come around here much?
Only when I wanna check out
some real action.
Well, you're talking to
the right guy. Says who?
Says me. I like a guy
that's got confidence.
All right.
No, that way's
the card game, huh?
We're going down here.
We got a party room.
Check it out, huh, baby? This is
the party room. How you like it, huh?
I've had a lot of good times
here, so, let's party, huh?
Hey, killer. Can I take my jacket off first?
Yeah, you can take off whatever you want.
All right.
Now, listen to me, buddy.
There's just one thing I want you
to do, and that is to keep quiet.
Hey, come on, babe,
what is this thing loaded?
We're gonna play a little game.
You Bombers are gonna like it.
It's called "lights out. "
No other place for me to go
No other place for dying slow
So I'll be killing
just killing time
So I'll be killing time
in the blue shadows
I've been around the world
I take credit
for the things I've done
But when the lights are dim
I'm not the only guilty one
Knock, knock.
I don't want no scars to show
I don't want no one to know
So I'll be killing time
in the blue shadows
Go ahead and take that money,
sweetie.
You better pray you make
it out of The Battery.
I don't think
she's after the money.
You know poker's
a real interesting game
especially when you've got
all the best cards!
Next time it'll be right in your
nuts, pal. You know what I mean?
Guys, it's been a slice.
Who are you?
McCoy. I'm a big fan.
Yeah, great,
come on, let's go.
Who is that guy?
Look out, it's surrounded! Get
this guy out of The Battery.
Move it! Move it!
This way. Follow me!
Jesus, Ellen, am I glad to see you.
I thought you were gone forever.
Cody, get in! This ain't no
time for checking out the sights!
Take off! I'm gonna run
these guys for awhile.
I'm staying with you...
You're not going with him!
You stay in the car!
Stay with your boyfriend!
McCoy, meet me at
the Grant Street underpass.
Right. If we don't see
you, Cody, have a nice life!
McCoy, can't you drive
this car any faster?
I don't want any Bombers
sneaking up on us!
Let's get our asses
out of here real quick!
And where's this Grant Street
anyway? I never heard of it before!
You sure you know where you're going?
Turn it off, Fish! You sound pathetic!
Well.
Looks like I finally ran into someone
that likes to play as rough as I do.
Yeah, this must be your lucky
night. I'm lucky? I guess maybe I am.
And you're dumb. Real dumb, if
you think you can pull this off.
I think you're forgetting
something. I got the gun.
I can get guns, smart guy. Lots of them.
Now why don't you tell me your name.
Tom Cody. Pleased to meet you.
I'll be coming for her, and
I'll be coming for you too.
Sure, you will,
and I'll be waiting.
Listen, I say we give it a couple of
minutes then get out of here, okay?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about saving our ass.
We got a lot to live for, Ellen.
He came and he got me! I'm
not going back without him.
Don't worry about him. He's getting
paid a lot of money to look after Raven.
What money? What do you think
he's doing this for love?
You think he's doing this
'cause he's your biggest fan?
He's getting paid, dear.
He takes his chances!
Hey! Too bad, Billy.
Looks like Ellen's old flame
decided to show up.
Okay, we're on the move.
What's this old flame stuff?
Didn't you know?
Ellen used to go with Cody,
real hot and heavy from what
I hear. You know what I mean?
What, is she kidding?
Let's not get into it now, okay,
Billy? Hard news, huh, shorty?
Look, Cody, we've had our differences,
but it looks like we got it made now, huh?
We'll just zoom along here
for a couple of hours,
then we're home and dry.
I got news for you, it ain't that
simple. We gotta bury the car.
Bury the car? What are you
talking about "bury the car"?
He means we're gonna
get rid of it, stupid.
He's gonna get rid of the car?
What's wrong with the car?
This is what I'm paying you
all this money for?
To come up
with these brilliant ideas?
Why don't we just hand ourselves back
over to Raven and ask him to shoot us?
You two go ahead. I wanna talk
alone with Tom for a minute.
What are you talking about?
What are you going with him for?
Hey, I don't like
the way this looks, Ellen.
I'm paying the bills around
here. How about some respect?
So what do you wanna talk to me
about? I got a lot to say to you, Tom.
No, you don't.
You have nothing to say to me.
You wanna talk to somebody,
go talk to your boyfriend.
Look, what was I supposed
to do? I had all that work.
Things were going real good. Things
were starting to happen for me.
Yeah, so, bye-bye,
Tom, right?
You're the one who took off
and joined the army.
Let's forget all this.
It's history.
From now on I'm just like you. I do
what I'm good at and I do it for money.
Is that why
you came and got me?
That's right. Billy Fish
is paying me 10 grand.
I just can't believe you'd do that.
Maybe you'd better get used to the idea.
I wonder what
they're talking about?
Who says they're talking?
Cute.
It was just a joke, man,
you know what I mean?
How big a thing
do you think they had anyway?
From what I hear it was real major.
Yeah, well, she's with me now.
Yeah, right. Against a big
tough, good-looking guy like you,
Cody don't stand a chance.
I hope you two got
everything straightened out.
Yeah, we got a lot straightened
out. It was a real eye opener.
I think I hurt your girlfriend's
feelings. I'm real sorry about it.
What does he mean he hurt
your feelings? What'd he say?
Did he say anything about me?
What'd he say? Tell me!
I'm tired
I'm thirsty
I'm wild eyed
In my misery
Timeless
In your finery
A high price
For your luxury
Sorcerer
Who is the master
Man and woman
on a star stream
In the middle of a snow dream
Sorcerer
Show me the high life
Come over
Let me put you on ice
I'm tired
When I need you badly
Wild eyed
In the middle of your dream
Timeless
Hey. Hi, you guys. Hey, what's
the hurry? Where you guys going?
We're nobody, we're going
nowhere. Nobody goes nowhere.
Look, knock it off, we're not
interested in conversation, okay, moron?
I know you. I know who you are, dig?
I love your stuff so much, I really do.
Look, if you love me so much,
why don't you just go away
and leave us alone.
No, look,
I'm your biggest fan, really.
Let me go with you, okay?
I won't be any trouble.
And I'll tell you guys something,
you gotta get off the street,
'cause the cops know the guys that hit
The Battery will be coming through here.
Shit!
We gotta get
a new set of wheels.
Great, we just got rid of the old
wheels. Wonderful leadership, Cody.
Hey, what's the matter with you? Are
you looking to get yourself run over?
Me and my friends need a lift.
So what? This ain't no muni bus!
Need a lift real bad.
Now look, let me make it real clear.
Nobody tells me where to take my bus.
You dig?
Well, we're very flexible.
We'll take you where you wanna
go. Anywhere you wanna go.
You just say the word
and we're with you.
You folks just hop right in.
Just make yourself at home.
I'm driving.
Hey, Bird, what the hell
you doing, man?
Hey, how you guys doing?
My name's McCoy. Don't worry,
we're not gonna hurt you none.
That's great.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
We're the Sorels. I'm Bird.
These are my associates.
This is Lester. My man
B.J., and that's Reggie.
Aren't you Ellen Aim?
That's right. It is Ellen Aim.
Hey, Ellen, you guys need
an opener or anything?
I mean, we're good.
I mean, we're real good, but we just
can't seem to get anything going.
Hey, look, what gives? I handle
the management and the booking.
Now, you guys just shut up
and leave Ellen alone.
Look, I know how tough it
can be getting the right gig.
Baby, you don't
even begin to know.
Man, what did I tell you guys?
Will you just cool it?
Hey, if you got any chance at all of
missing the cops, it's through here.
Yeah, so what are our
chances? Horrible and terrible.
Oh, that's just great.
Look, we don't wanna mess
with any of these Ardmore cops.
They busted me
a couple of years ago,
threw my ass right in jail
'cause I wouldn't pay them off.
What'd they bust you for?
Disturbing the peace. They said I
got out of line in some bar, you know?
Great.
I love a girl with class.
This is great, just great. You
wanna help change this tire, shorty?
Changing flat tires isn't
exactly my line of work, dear.
If that's the case, then
why don't you just shut up?
Why don't you just shut up?
Then I try and write songs,
you know.
I just can't seem to figure out how
to do it right the way you do it.
You know, I can't figure out how you
work out the rhymes and the melodies
and you make it all come out.
Somebody else writes the songs,
Billy buys them or steals them,
I can't write for shit.
I always thought those were
your songs. I just sing them.
Yeah, but when you sing them,
you make it yours.
That's the way it is, right?
I guess so. Who knows?
The famous Sorels sure put a
lot of money into that bus, huh?
Listen, Cody, I didn't know you had
a thing with Ellen in the old days.
You better get some smarts.
Learn to adjust to the fact that
you're out of the picture now.
You see, Cody, I do things for her.
Things that a guy like you could never do.
Things that matter
in the real world.
You know something?
The only trouble with kicking the shit
out of you is it would be too easy.
You keep your hands
off the suit, buddy.
Come on, hurry the hell up with that
flat tire, already, let's get going.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one
Countdown to love
Ten
Remember when you didn't
love me
Nine
Now all the time
you're thinking of me
Eight, life is great
You're all I'm living for
This is my countdown to love
Oh, this is
my countdown to love
You are the one love
in my life
I know you feel that way too
Oh, what a thrill
when I'm holdin' you near
All of my wild dreams
come true
Four
Forevermore you'll be my lover
Three
It's you for me
there'll never be another
Two
Together forever
we'll be as one
Pretty good, you guys.
Oh, this is
my countdown to love
Cody? All right, Ellen,
Baby Doll, down in back.
Fish, McCoy, we're working for the
Sorels. Fish, you're the manager.
I'm way ahead of you, Cody.
What, do you think I gotta be a
genius to know what you're going for?
I'll handle this.
I'll talk us through.
Hey, guys, how's it going? I'm
the bus driver here for the Sorels.
We're on our way to play a gig
at an after hours joint.
The Sorels. The singers.
You know them, right?
No. Never heard of them. You know
what's going on here, don't you?
Look, man, all I know
is we're running real late.
Well, babe, some outfit just broke into
The Battery and burned half of it down.
Really?
Knock off the crap, will you?
As far as I'm concerned anybody
that goes into The Battery
and does some damage
deserves a medal.
Well, let me tell you how we look
at it. Look, cut the shit, okay?
You guys got a big job to do, we're
trying to get where we're going.
Now, let us through, or you wanna come
to some kind of financial arrangement?
Well, what do you
think, Harry?
Well, I think what we got here
is a model citizen.
I knew you guys
talked my language.
Keep it coming.
You guys take a big bite.
That's right.
Nice to see there's some
integrity left on the force.
You know, you're just a little
too anxious to buy us off.
Spade musicians
with a big wad of money.
All right,
everybody off the bus!
All right, now this is
how we're gonna play it.
You're gonna walk off this bus
like there's nothing wrong. Get me?
All right, down on
the ground! Do it! Now!
Get over there!
Don't worry about it, fellows.
We'll be out of your face in no time.
You know, some of you guys
got some cute little asses.
Be a real shame if I had
to blow them off! Stay down!
Oh, shit!
All right!
Son-of-a-bitch!
Come on, man, let's get
out of here! Come on!
Go! Go!
Shut the hell up!
McCoy, pull out in a back
alley, we're gonna dump the bus.
First he dumps the car,
now he's dumping the bus?
Code 99! Code 99.
Blockade at Cross and Ardmore.
Suspects armed and dangerous!
Repeat, armed and dangerous!
Broke blockade!
Heading north on Ardmore.
Cannot pursue. Do you copy?
God damn it, this is the blockade
at Ardmore, come back to me.
Come on.
Come on! Come on!
We had a $1,000 in that bus!
I lost my clothes, the luggage is
gone, all the sheet music is gone!
This is great.
We're on our way to the
Richmond. No bus, no nothing.
You shouldn't have stopped,
Bird.
He ain't a real
social kind of guy, is he?
Really? Gee, I think
he's a real sweetheart.
Cut him some slack, will you?
He was there for you tonight.
Yeah, he really
earned his money.
You know, you got a real
funny way of saying thanks
when someone saves your ass.
Why don't you go sit with
your pal Billy over there.
I guess he's more
your kind of guy.
Yeah, I think maybe I will.
Don't worry, babe, everything's
gonna be okay from now on.
We're gonna be great.
Hey, Reva, Ellen Aim's back.
And guess what? Tom's with her.
Is he okay? Oh, he
looked all right to me.
Chief?
Tom.
Reva, cut it out. We made it.
Everybody's in one piece.
What about that, Ellen?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm all right, I guess.
No, she's not. She's tired,
and she's been roughed up.
I'm gonna take her back to the
hotel so she can get some rest.
This whole thing started 'cause I
had to do a gig in this shit hole.
I should've stayed the
hell away from this dump!
Is that the way
you feel about it, Ellen?
Yeah, I guess I just wanna
get away from here.
Get back on the road.
Now you're talking, kiddo.
Come on, let's get out of here.
I hate you for taking money
to come and get me.
That's telling him, Ellen.
I guess she doesn't like you much,
Cody. She doesn't seem real thankful.
Yeah, one thing about you,
Cooley, you catch on real quick.
Yeah, that's right, Buddy,
and I get the job done.
Good. Because I think
it's just starting.
What the hell does he
wanna talk about? Tom Cody.
I want Tom Cody.
I wanna nail that son-of-a-bitch's
head to the sidewalk
under that marquee
that says Ellen Aim on it?
And just to prove to you,
I'm gonna be a nice guy,
I'm coming in
with just two of my men.
After I take care of Cody,
there'll be no more trouble.
You do your job, man.
Keep the peace.
Hey, Cody, I need a drink.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Maybe I can get lucky and pick
a fight with that bartender.
No, not this time.
Hey, McCoy, look, I'll get
you your money later, okay?
Is that all you got to say is,
"I'll get your money to you later. "
Yeah, that's all I gotta say.
What else do you wanna hear?
Hey, look,
I did real good back there.
So what? I'm all out of medals,
besides you're getting paid.
You know, Reva, Ellen Aim
was right about one thing,
your brother's a jerk.
What's your problem? You're
feeling pretty sorry for yourself...
Don't start on me, Reva.
She comes back to town,
tells you and everybody else
it doesn't mean a goddamn...
Yeah and the worst part is she
runs off with that creep Billy Fish.
You know, Tom, I didn't ask
you to go out and get Ellen Aim
because she looks great
on stage.
Well, what the hell do you
care... I care about you!
And this town!
Look, if you're gonna fight, you're
supposed to fight for something.
You and Billy Fish are the
same. You're both selfish!
All you two
are really worried about...
Hi, Ed. I came to talk to your brother.
Come on outside.
Raven says he has to face you
alone. Right here in The Richmond.
I'm ordering you to get out of town,
Tom. I want you on a train tonight.
If Raven comes in here
to face you,
I'll be waiting for him
right here with a lot of guns.
I'm throwing his ass in jail.
I am not gonna sit around
and watch two maniacs
play out some little game
about personal honor.
I want you gone. If you're
still in town tomorrow morning,
I'm throwing your ass in jail
right next to Raven.
Look, you did real good
rescuing her, Tom.
You surprised me. 'Cause I
didn't think you had it in you.
Now, surprise me again.
Do something else real good,
be on that train tonight.
Yeah, come in.
Hey, I'll get It.
Who is It?
What the hell are you still doing here? Oh,
hey, look, see you guys later, all right?
I've been expecting you I
know what you want. Ten grand.
I'm as good as my word.
I pay on time.
You know you play rough,
Cody, but you do a good job.
You should do
a little more work for me
when you get a taste of
what that money'll bring you.
Then you'll realize I'm the
one with the brains around here
and you'll start
treating me a bit nicer.
You know, nobody ever had
a hold on me the way you did.
I would have done
anything for you.
A long time ago I would have
thought you were worth it.
Not anymore, babe.
Where do you get off
talking to her like that?
She's way out of your league,
musclehead.
This is the grand I promised
McCoy. You can keep the rest.
You know what's wrong
with that guy? He's stupid.
I'm sorry, Billy.
What are you sorry about? Where
are you going? Where you going?
Tom!
Tom, wait!
What was I supposed to do?
I hadn't heard from you in two years.
You didn't even write me a letter.
What did I do
that was so wrong?
You gotta go away.
You fought enough fights,
you can let this one go.
With both of us gone, maybe...
What do you mean "both of us"?
Us! I wanna go with you.
We could be together.
You'd really come along with
me? In two seconds I would.
Please?
Well, if it isn't
my old pal, Tom Cody.
How's it going?
Great till you got here.
I've just been talking
things over with Clyde.
You remember he and I
used to be real close.
Hey, Tom, tequila, right?
Here's what I owe you.
You did real good back there. I
couldn't have got her out without you.
Maybe I rode you a little
harder than I should have.
Don't get sentimental on me. I
wouldn't know how to handle it.
Hey, I got a problem with
Ellen I gotta talk to you about.
Yeah, I understand
about these kind of things.
You know, Cody, I was actually in
love once myself. It didn't work out.
You're the kind
that makes bad picks, huh?
He was the worst. He lied to
me all the time, cheated on me.
Well, if I ever run into
him, I'll give him your best.
Of course, you know,
that's before I was a soldier.
You're real crazy about Ellen, aren't
you? Yeah, I don't know. I guess I am.
Hey, there's nothing wrong with
it. Nothing to be embarrassed about.
I ain't embarrassed. I just
know it ain't gonna work out.
Ellen and I are going in different
directions. It's nobody's fault.
Maybe you're right, 'cause you don't
look like no back-up singer to me.
Look, I'm gonna need your help tonight.
I gotta do something I don't wanna do.
Come on.
Tom.
This is not The Bayside.
This is something back in The
Richmond I gotta take care of.
What are you...
You get as far
from here as you can.
You run until you hit The Bayside
and you can hang out there.
Sure, tough guy.
When's this train take off? I
gotta get back to The Richmond.
We don't.
Look, lady, I gotta get
moving. It's important.
Well, you ain't gonna
get there on this train.
Hey! Maybe you better think about it.
The Bombers have gone crazy.
They're doing everything they
can to seal off The Richmond.
Let's go.
What the hell
are you doing here, Clyde?
I told everybody to get off the
streets until this thing is over with.
Yeah, but I wanna see
Raven run from up close.
Just stay out of the way.
Well?
Real simple. There's no showdown. Tom
Cody ain't here and neither is the girl.
I don't get it.
Get off your bike, Raven.
I ain't too crazy
about jails, Chief.
I got a better idea for you.
Holy shit!
They're here! They're here!
I told your friend Cody
I could get a lot of guns.
Hey, get out of my way!
What the hell!
What is this?
You can't get away with this.
You think you can ride into any
town and kidnap anybody you want?
Now, get the hell out of town
and leave these people alone.
Sorry I'm late. I got
something special in mind.
I brought them along
just for you.
Well, my plan went to shit.
Let's see how you do.
Kick his ass.
Nice, huh?
Get him!
Drop him!
Tom!
Let's get out of here!
No more timing
Each tear that falls
from my eyes
I'm not hiding
The remedy to cure
this old heart of mine
I can dream about you
If I can't hold you tonight
You know something, Waldo,
we're gonna be rich.
Yeah. Long live rock and roll.
I can dream about you
If I can't hold you tonight
You know how
to hold me just right
Moving sidewalks,
I don't see under my feet
Great, huh? My new discovery. I'm
gonna take them right up the ladder.
Yeah, they ought to make you
a lot of money, Fish.
Look, don't worry, Cody, I'm not
gonna stand in your way with Ellen.
I know how it is
between you two.
There's one thing
we both know, Fish.
She needs you a lot more
than she needs me.
Yeah, she needs me,
but she loves you.
She'll get over it. She's
used to me being unreliable.
Is that what I'm
supposed to tell her?
You're okay with words. You'll
make her feel better than I could.
Take it easy, Cody.
Thanks.
I'll take it
wherever I can get it.
Climbing up
from the pain in my heart
'Cause it's you that I need.
I can dream
Everybody!
Yes, I can dream
I don't understand it
I can't keep my mind
off loving you
Love you forever
Ooh, now baby
I'm caught up
in the magic I see in you
There's one thing to do
I can dream about you
Guess you're just gonna cut
out, huh? Yeah. You know me.
Yeah, I know you. You're
the guy with the right hook.
Is that it? Is that
all you've left to say?
Look, I know you're gonna be going
places with your singing and stuff,
but then I'm not the kind of guy to be
carrying your guitars around for you.
But if you ever need me
for something, I'll be there.
I can dream about you
I'm gonna press my lips against
you and hold you tight to me
I can dream about you
You know you got me spellbound
what else can it be
I can dream
Dreamin' about you
I've got a dream
'bout an angel on the beach
And the perfect waves
are starting to come
His hair is flying out
in ribbons of gold
And his touch
has got the power to stun
I've got a dream
'bout an angel in the forest
Enchanted by
the edge of a lake
His body's flowing
in the jewels alive
And the earth below him
starting to shake
But I don't see
any angels in the city
I don't hear
any holy choirs sing
And if I can't get an angel
I can still get a boy
And a boy'd
be the next best thing
The next best thing
to an angel
A boy'd be the next best thing
I've got a dream
'bout a boy in a castle
And he's dancing
like a cat on the stairs
He's got the fire
of a prince in his eyes
And the thunder
of a drum in his ears
I've got a dream
'bout a boy on a star
Lookin' down
upon the rim of the world
He's there all alone and
dreamin' of someone like me
I'm not an angel
but at least I'm a girl
I've got a dream
when the darkness is over
We'll be lyin'
in the rays of the sun
But it's only a dream
and tonight is for real
You'll never know
what it means
But you'll know how it feels
It's gonna be over, over
Before you know it's begun
It's all we really got tonight
Stop your cryin' hold on
Tonight
Before you know it it's gone
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Let the fire be started
We're dancing for the restless
and the broken-hearted
Let the rebels begin
Let the fire be started
We're dancing for the
desperate and the broken-hearted
Let the rebels begin
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Before you know it it's gone
Say a prayer in the darkness
for the magic to come
No matter what it seems
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Before you know it's begun
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Before you know it's begun
I've got a dream
when the darkness is over
We'll be lyin'
in the rays of the sun
But it's only a dream
and tonight is for real
You'll never know
what it means
But you'll know how it feels
It's gonna be over, over
Before you know it's begun
It's all we really got tonight
Stop your cryin' hold on
Tonight
Before you know it it's gone
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Let the rebels begin
Let the fire be started
We're dancing for the restless
and the broken-hearted
Let the rebels begin
Let the fire be started
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Before you know it it's gone
Say a prayer in the darkness
for the magic to come
No matter what it seems
Tonight is what
it means to be young
Hey, Cody, how do you
like my new wheels?
I found it
in the middle of the street.
Somebody just dumped it. Finders
keepers, you know what I mean?
Maybe you need
some company, huh?
Yeah, I don't mind
if you tag along.
I guess this is
my big chance, huh?
Hey, cool down, big guy, I already
told you, you're not my type.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org