Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Donna, you've read me all wrong.
I wasn't trying to hit you up
for a loan.
I know you weren't.
Look, Christi Ann,
your store does well...
and if that rep knows
what she's talking about, then...
it's not a favor.
It's a good investment.
Are you serious?
Okay.
Yeah, let's do it.
But you have to promise me
you'll finish that script...
and start sending it out.
No more excuses.
- Okay.
Gee, this is crazy. Why am I gonna
show my new men's clothes?
I just started making these.
- They look great to me.
- Thank you.
Alright, the word's out, lots of buzz.
All the critics are gonna be there...
mostly because of the celebrities.
You know, I'm not sure
who I hate more frankly.
Actually, no, that's not true. I hate
them all. But I do love this dress.
Please tell me
you're sleeping with him.
- No, he's just an employee.
- Put him on the runway.
- Well, I don't know if I'm...
- No, you have to.
It'll be a fun surprise.
Think about it: hot new designer
puts warehouse boy on catwalk.
It's brilliant. It's a tease.
Leave them wanting more. I gotta go.
- This is the last box.
- Will you do me a favor?
Will you try this on?
I wish I was as confident as you look.
Will you model this for me?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Thank God. I need as many pillars
of strength around me as possible.
Christi Ann, this looks fine.
Hey, come on now.
This is all good.
It's exciting!
Look, no matter what
the critical people say...
might as well enjoy
what's going on.
Come here.
- You got brothers and sisters?
- Yeah.
I mean, I got a brother
and I got a sister.
- Older, younger?
- One's older, one's younger.
Why do people always ask this?
I don't...
Who cares about
somebody's brothers and sisters?
- Do you talk to your parents a lot?
- No. We got an understanding.
What kind of understanding?
I left when I was 17.
I gave them one of these.
What's that?
What does that mean?
My mom and dad weren't
very bright people.
Which would've been okay
if they were nice...
I mean, there's plenty of dumb
but sweet people in the world.
But, I don't know, they were shitty
too. They were just mean people.
- How were they mean?
- They just always said mean things.
You know, told me I was a fucking liar
and a goddamned bullshiter.
I go to a therapist. I've been going
for three years actually and...
I've learned that you have to move on,
that you have to forgive them.
Right, yeah.
I mean, I forgive them. Like I say,
they weren't bright people.
They had me.
They didn't abort me.
I mean, they raised me, kind of
a fucked up way to do it, but...
maybe them being so harsh
made me the way I am today...
you know, like resilient?
Gotta thank them for that, huh?
Yeah, so whatever.
That's why I gave them one of these.
'Cause what it means is...
you did your best to love me.
I did my best to love you back.
We just reached a point where
there's nothing left to say, so...
...good luck.
- I like how you explain things.
You ever thought about writing?
- Me?
- Seriously.
- Come on!
Seriously. You definitely
have a way with words.
I think you should write stuff
down, you know? Not to...
not to be rich or famous
or anything, but to...
to express yourself.
I'm gonna get you a notebook
and a pen. Just try it.
Just jot stuff down.
Okay, yeah.
Good luck with the show.
We can't wait to see it.
Thank you.
See you on the front row!
Thanks.
"See you on the front row"?
How ass-kissy was that?
Honey, you don't even
need to be kissing her ass.
She's just a manufacturer.
I gotta go.
- Thanks for coming.
- Sure.
You know, I think you're
making me addicted to sex.
Thanks.
And, you know, I've never...
given a blowjob to a guy in a car.
I'm just gonna... I just wanna...
You've gotten really good at that.
When you're through with that can
you please call the silk place back...
and tell them that you're
repped by me? They'll knock off 20/º.
Where is everybody?
Joe's helping out Christi Ann
at her store.
Good. Did you get
any writing done today?
- Yeah, yeah, no, it's really cool.
- So what you writing about?
Never mind.
Just keep getting it down on paper.
Okay.
Had the printer print up like
100 copies of my script today.
Getting ready to send it out
to agents.
- Great.
- Tell you what...
when you're ready to take a break,
why don't you come inside?
Okay. I will.
I'm sorry! I know, I'm a bad little slut
and you're the big strong man!
That's right.
I'm not done fucking you.
I'm gonna fuck you harder
and you're gonna like it.
Oh, no, no!
Don't punish me! Hey!
- Baby, I can't do this anymore.
- Why? What's wrong?
This... this whole routine
of me holding you down and...
your begging me to stop...
it's fucking weird, I don't know.
It's just...
Well, you seemed to enjoy it just fine
every day for the past three weeks.
I know. Look, at first I did.
It's just lately...
It's 'cause I care about you,
and I don't wanna do that...
...to somebody I care about.
- Look, we're just playing. Come on.
I mean, we're just...
Why are we even having
this conversation?
You have a simple job, Stanny.
Are you telling me that you can't
fulfill it? Because, you know what?
There are a lot of guys in this city
that would be more than happy...
to do this without complaining.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Is that all that I am to you?
I think you'd better
take the blindfold off now.
I'm such a fucking idiot.
I'm an asshole.
I mean, I was like ready to tell...
What?
I think I'm falling
in love with you.
Okay. Can you untie me, please?
I think you and Joe
need to move out.
Joe, get up. We gotta go.
Seriously. I'm not fucking
around, man. Pack your shit.
Stanny, what did you do?
I didn't do anything shitty. I stopped
being shitty. Figure that one out.
Come on, we got a pretty good deal
going on here, man.
How long did you think this was
gonna last, you know, seriously?
Okay, it's been a fun month
or two, but...
we milked this for as much
as we could. The milk's gone sour.
What did you?
Joe, what the hell's going on?
- We're leaving.
- Hold on!
- Did you get in a fight with Donna?
- What the fuck you think?
I guess we're gonna go and try
and find our own place.
No, I don't want you to go.
I don't want either one of you to go.
Well, you don't always get
what you want.
- Take care.
- Wait! Wait!
Hold on one minute!
Hold on.
- Donna, what's going on?
- I guess they're leaving.
And you're just gonna sit there?
Yeah,
what am I supposed to be doing?
What happened?
It was just getting too...
...I don't know, too weird.
- Too weird?
Why is it that every time you like
a guy things get too weird?
- Who says I like the guy?
- You're full of shit.
And I don't have time to sit here
and listen to you lie to yourself...
because they're leaving!
What do you wanna do?
- Well, Joe doesn't have to go.
- Joe goes wherever Stanny goes!
And I'm not about to let him do that
because you got this thing about...
What? This thing about what?
I don't know,
but you've got this thing!
And...
if you look at me and tell me
that you don't like the guy...
fine, I'll say goodbye
to both of them.
Tell me what happened.
He said he thought
he was falling in love with me.
Okay. Well...
the guy who loves you
is walking out the door right now.
Is that what you want?
Let's get out of here.
This is friggin' humiliating.
She asked us to wait a minute,
so we're gonna wait.
- It's been over a minute. Let's go.
- It's an expression, Stanny.
Okay? It's like "hold on a sec".
It's more than a second.
Okay, it's a stupid fucking
expression then.
Just...
don't ask me to say it to you
'cause I can't, Stanny. I'm sorry.
- I just can't say it to you.
- Just... just let me love you.
I was close.
It's alright.
I'm sorry. My mind's just
on the fashion show.
Don't be sorry.
Joe, how come you never
slept in my bed?
You never asked me to.
Well, will you sleep here with me?
I mean...
just for the next two nights
until the fashion show.
Well...
sure, girl.
Be happy to.
- What about the cuteness?
- What about the dumbness?
- You're dumb.
- No, you're dumb.
- What about the sweetness?
- Guys, do it in private! Jeez!
You guys, really.
Why don't you just
give each other hickies?
You have rug burns on your elbows.
You broke your nails
scratching his back!
I chipped my tooth last week...
'cause we were doing it
doggy style...
and she friggin' jerks her head
back right into my jaw. You did!
My God, Christi Ann!
Remember back in college...
when I was giving a blowjob
to that guy...
that would not take the beret off?
My God. the bathroom is in-between
our two bedrooms...
which is right next to this
little tiny living room.
So I'm ready
to come out and spit...
and there's like ten people
in the goddamned living room.
So I come out and my mouth's like
this 'caused it's all full of his cum.
And I come out and
everybody starts laughing.
And then I start to laugh...
and then everyone's jumping back
out of the way...
'cause they're like terrified I'm gonna
spit up right there on the carpet.
So I got running into the bathroom
and I spit out and...
I get a standing ovation.
That's disgusting. Ew!
Honey, you know
what I was just thinking?
- How adorable you are?
- No, I think pretty highly on myself...
but I ain't best described
as adorable.
No, I was thinking about
how we first met and all.
It's funny, I used to be
so choosey.
Like every girl I dates
had to have a perfect ass.
Joe and I used to argue
about it all the time.
If the girl had like
a big square man ass...
forget it. I couldn't do it.
And it's funny when I met you...
I was like, "This chick is hot-looking,
but what does her ass look like?
So we get naked
and we start fucking...
And I'm like,
"Wow, this chick has a big ass!
But I'm diggin' it. It's great."
It's like you converted me.
Now I'm like all the black and Puerto
Rican guys I used to give shit to...
'cause they always went for the
big booty. I love big asses now.
It's weird how like your taste
could change like that.
How about how adorable you are?
Don't fuckin' touch me. I cannot
believe you just told me I was fat.
I didn't say you were fat!
I said I love you no matter
what your body looks like.
Another sacrifice to the beer gods.
Man, Donna's making me insane.
Yep. Well, you're in love with her.
Yeah. Still, she's got
some mental problems.
Women just have
more emotions than we do.
And they don't think of all the things
they're thinking as mental problems.
That's just their
daily way of thinking.
And he repeats himself. I think
he's borderline schizophrenic.
We argue and I explain to him
how he's being ridiculous.
He admits it.
He apologizes for it and then he does
it again the very next day!
Well, what're you arguing about?
It just depends on what
you're fighting about.
It has nothing to do
with what you were fighting about.
She always gives me this
psycho-friggin'-logical bullshit...
I ain't in touch with my feelings.
After about an hour of yelling, I just
say, "Yeah, whatever. You're right".
And then the next day we have the
same argument like a bad rerun!
You're lucky.
Joe seems a lot more sensitive.
- He tries.
- Yeah, he tries.
Bro, just make it look like
you're trying. Don't say nothing.
At most just say, "I wish
I was more aware like you guys.
- But I'm still learning".
- He says that? That is so sweet!
And Stanny can be so great.
I mean, he really can.
And that's why it kills me
to get rejected like that.
What does she expect me to say?
I feel like saying to her...
"All those years shoveling concrete
I had a lot of shitty days.
Would've been really nice to just
lay on a couch on a doctor's office...
and talk about my feelings".
It ain't fair!
I worked so hard
to get to this point.
My therapist is so proud
of my progress.
But this whole relationship
is putting me in a tailspin.
You're not thinking of breaking up
with him, are you?
No! Well, thinking about it
but no, I mean...
we've come this far and
we should try and get through this.
You ever cry in front of her?
No.
You don't cry ever, do you?
You ever cry in front of Donna?
Yeah, I suppose. This once.
And he cries.
- Really?
- He cries a lot, actually.
And more and more lately.
Joe doesn't cry
in front of you, huh?
Well, no.
Just take it in a notch, Stanny.
I know you, man, you don't let shit go.
- This chick could turn on you.
- No.
You kidding me?
This chick is crazy about me.
You really love her, don't you?
Joe, I never loved nothing
like I love that girl.
Joe is... he'll open up. He's the type
of guy who grows on you.
He's somebody you
fall in love with slowly.
Love him like a friend.
You don't say "I love you"
to each other?
- No! You don't say that to friends.
- Yes, you do. We do.
- I mean, you know I love you.
- I love you too!
- But guys don't say that as friends.
- You're right.
- Joe, I fucking love you, man.
- I love you too, bro.
Christi Ann...
you gotta relax.
I want you to know something, okay?
Sex isn't about...
talking dirty or...
some silly new position.
It's about trust.
Do you trust me?
It's tender...
soft.
I'm gonna kiss you delicately.
If it makes sense, give it back.
This is going to be a great show.
Yeah, it is.
- You're amazing. Okay.
- Thank you.
This is insane!
I think you're gonna get backers.
I've gotten so many cards
I can't even keep track!
That's awesome.
- Do you know that guy over there?
- Mark.
He's like, "Come to Europe.
You know...
the fashion season's
just starting".
Like, he told me I could be making
a couple grand a day just doing this.
- Is he like for real or what?
- Well, he owns a modeling agency.
- He's for real.
- It was nice for him to say it and all...
but I don't know if he meant it,
you know?
Christi Ann. I want you to meet Arthur.
He's an editor from Vogue Magazine.
Love your show, very elegant.
Nikki, you don't care about fashion.
You're just here for the
party afterwards.
How can you blame me?
You always seem to have...
the most entertaining guests.
I'm sure he's already
told you ladies...
but Nikki sold his first
screenplay last year.
And now he's in production
on his next film.
Congratulations.
Of course when I sell
one of my scripts...
I'm gonna have to surround myself
with a bevy of beautiful men...
which I'll have to secretly blow
because I have a boyfriend.
You know...
you always have to talk about cock
and fucking and it's really disgusting.
Excuse us.
I am trying to host a party here
so back the fuck off.
Okay, can you not
embarrass me, please?
Can not talk like that
in front of me?
Stop smoking that thing in my face.
I smoke wherever I want.
How do you like that?
You're drunk.
You're such an ass.
- Stanny, you won't believe this shit.
- I've figured it out. Relationships...
it's all about control. If you're
in control you don't get hurt.
'Cause everyone's afraid
of getting hurt.
I gotta tell you what this guy
was saying to me.
You know what?
These girls, they just own us.
It was never about sex.
It was about...
being able to give us shit
and we couldn't give shit back.
I know Donna can be shitty
at times but Christi Ann...
Yeah, yeah, she's more subtle at it.
You don't even realize you got
a leash around your neck.
You know what?
You ain't always right, Stanny.
You ain't always right about shit
and you're wrong about that girl.
Yeah, right. You're falling all over
these phony who wants to be...
...a high-class designer.
- Why do always do this?
Why is that every time
I like a girl...
you say she's no good
'cause of something?
You say it like she's trying
to split you and me up or something.
You know what?
- I think it's the other way around.
- You really think...
that that girl
considers you her equal?
Brother, that girl considers
herself above you.
I'm just saving you
from a painful fall!
My girlfriend's got me buying
every goddamned thing here.
That's wonderful! Or maybe not.
I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for her.
I'm blowing cash
on that dress, this skirt...
Don't even listen to him.
- He can afford it. He's a lawyer.
- Lawyer my ass.
She's got one hand in my pants,
one hand in my goddamned wallet.
- Your illustrious model.
- He's not really a model.
He's actually my personal cabana boy.
Come with me right now.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Great. Okay, talk to you later.
Don't be showing up
at my girlfriend's house.
You guys are boyfriend
and girlfriend now?
- That's cool.
- Yeah.
So maybe you don't need
to be stopping by here anymore.
Christi Ann invited me.
You wanna push it?
We'll settle this old school.
What? We're gonna break dance?
Look, shit. I forgot
to tell you about him.
Tell him about me what?
I'm standing right fucking here.
Don't talk about me like
I'm a piece of friggin' wood.
Easy, fella, you don't gotta...
"Easy, fella"? Do I look like a fucking
horse to you?
Do I have fucking hooves?
Don't fucking say "easy fella" to me!
Did you say the word "fuck"
enough in that sentence?
No, let me add a few more.
Fuck you. And fuck you too!
Let's just all cool out.
- Stanny!
- Wanna try to grab me again, fucker?
- Easy, fella, just...
- Quit saying "easy fella" to me!
- Just chill the fuck out!
- Stanny!
- Don't you lay a hand on me!
- I'm not gonna lay a hand on you.
Didn't even lay a hand on him.
I knocked him on his ass
with my elbow.
Stanny, get in the goddamned house.
And, Damien, you can go!
- I hope you're proud of yourself.
- I hope you're proud of yourself...
using that stupid fuck
to get a reaction out of me.
Yeah, go ahead, keep fooling yourself.
At least you're fooling somebody.
- Joe, I'm gonna cum...
- You motherfuckin' shit!
Thank you, Joe.
Was that good?
Was that good, Joe?
Do you want me to get you a towel?
Just fucking listen to me, alright?
You realize what you do to me?
You insist that I throw you down
and treat you like a cheap whore...
'cause it's the only way
you can get off.
Then in daily life if I show
any form of aggression...
or jealousy, you freak the fuck out.
Do you know how confusing it is...
...to be in a relationship with you?
- What we do in the bedroom...
and what we do in our relationship
out in the real world...
those are two goddamned
different things, Stanny.
So just as long as we do everything
the way you want on your terms...
then we'll be fine.
Why do you have to be
so combative with me?
I'm not the combative one, okay?
This is what you do. It's not funny.
You pick fights with me and then
you yell at me for fighting!
I'm not the one who's fucking
yelling here, okay, buddy?
You instigate me to do shit.
Then when I do you get to point out
how fucked up I am.
'Cause you're so pathetically afraid
I might realize how fucked up you are.
Oh, I'm the fucked up one?
I'm the fucked up one?
Honey, I gotta fucking hold you down
and call you a whore for you to cum...
and you say I got self-esteem issues?
You know what?
Fuck this and fuck you...
because I am not gonna do this
with you, fucking asshole!
- I am through!
- Be a fucking rich bitch crybaby.
It doesn't affect me anymore 'cause
I'm done back-peddling just so...
I don't notice what a goddamned
psycho you are. You're a head case.
I am not the fucked up one.
I am not the psycho, okay?
I'm not the one that's hit people.
You should be in goddamned therapy!
You're the one who's fucked up,
just like your goddamned parents.
- You're just like them!
- Well, I don't have the luxury...
of your rich parents to pay for
your goddamned therapist, alright?
And you know what? All that
money you waste on that bullshit...
I'll solve your problem right now
in three words: eat less food!
You're a fucking asshole,
you know what?
You're a fucking asshole.
And I loved you. I did.
I loved you.
I don't know why. I don't know
why I did! I was stupid!
I was really dumb! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I did this to us!
I did it and I'm sorry!
You gotta go!
- Here we go again.
- No, it's for real this time, bro.
- What happened?
- I stopped thinking with my dick.
No, I take that back.
I stopped thinking with my wallet.
You think if I had a job I'd be putting
up with that bullshit?
I just wanted to sleep late.
I've been working hard my whole life
and I wanted a break.
We got a break.
Now what?
Now what? I'll get myself
a job tending bar at night...
write during the day...
I'm gonna be a starving artist.
Look, you don't gotta come
with me, alright? Stay here.
This works for you.
Doesn't work for me.
Stanny, just calm down.
Just sleep over it. Maybe you'll feel
different about it in the morning.
I ain't gonna feel any different
about it tomorrow, Joe.
Where the fuck are you
gonna go at three a. m?
Bro, just go back to the party.
Go have fun, alright?
Don't worry about me.
Just try and get
some sleep, alright?
So...
I think I'm gonna take
that guy up on that offer.
What guy?
That agent guy. He...
said he'd get me a plane ticket
and that his...
agency has some sort
of a deal with a...
hotel in... Milan.
It's in Europe.
I leave tomorrow.
- The fashion season starts soon so...
- I know when the season starts.
It's kinda cool though, right?
I mean, never been to Europe.
Shit, I've never been anywhere.
How am I ever gonna
repay you for this?
I think it's a great opportunity.
- Christi Ann.
- Hi!
- Hi. These are my friends. Justin.
- Justin.
- And this is Carlos.
- Hi. How you doing?
- Thanks for the invitation...
- Yeah.
...for your party.
- It was fantastic. The show...
- So you'll be back in four months?
- Yeah, when the season ends.
Well, good luck.
You too.
Well, at least your show
was a big hit.
And to think I didn't want to go
to California with you.
- Wherever we go, we go together.
- Yeah.
This is gonna be a tough act
to follow, though.
But I bet there's all kinds of
different countries and shit in Europe.
Man, my best friend's gonna be
a friggin' supermodel.
We're gonna be balls deep
in ass over there.
Wow...
...what a summer.
- Tell me about it.
Goddamn it, I smoke too much pot.
I'm sorry that it didn't work out
with Stanny.
Yeah. I'm sorry too.
Guess it's just
you and me again, kiddo.
They sure were funny.
Yeah.
You said we'd look back
on this and laugh.
We're crazy, aren't we?
Yeah.
But we're damned great at it.
My God!
- You're gonna miss her, ain't you?
- You're gonna miss Christi Ann?
Joe...
look, I'm starting
to like this LA thing...
like writing movies and...
I don't know if I'd like Europe
all that much.
- Bro, you gotta come with me.
- No. This writing thing, I gotta do it.
Well, I don't wanna go
over there all by myself.
I don't think you really want
to go there in the first place.
Look, I gotta leave that house,
but you don't.
And what I said about you and
Christi Ann last night, I was wrong.
I mean, thank God girls bitch at us:
make you dress better, motivate you.
I ain't the expert on relationships
obviously, but I know this:
you don't wanna leave your girl.
- Did you love Donna?
- Despite how much I hated her...
I always will.
You think I'm in love?
Do you think you are?
Me and you ain't breaking up.
Go on, get out of here.
You wouldn't kick me out or nothing
if I told you I loved you, would you?
I love you too.
So it's kind of a happy ending,
for Joe and Christi Ann anyways.
Don't worry about me and Donna.
You know real life,
it ain't like the movies.
Life is just a bunch of stories
you go through...
and they all end sooner or later.
But it's okay. I'm gonna go
find my next story.
Hope you do the same.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org