Slow it down, Bob.
Need a doughnut break.
We're having chest pains.
Keep it moving, flabby.
Opening night
is less than a week away.
Where in the script does it say that
Truman Capote has a fat, saggy ass?
In the very beginning. "Enter Capote,
followed by his fat, saggy ass."
-Hi, Walt.
-Oh, Suzie-Q, looking good. Ruthy.
-Let's have drinks again soon.
-I'll call you.
Nice. When did you
have drinks with her?
The other day. Didn't I tell you?
She stopped by.
-Well, where was l?
-You were....
Oh, that's right,
you were taking a nap.
-So did you make a move?
-I wanted to. I couldn't get her alone.
Had that friend, Ruthy, with her.
She's like a frigging shadow.
-Hi.
-Pole. Pole. Pole.
Okay, now that's seven mushroom,
three onion...
...two regular cheese
but one with no pickles.
And we have six fries, four Pepsi,
and two 7 UP.
You got 180 seconds,
or that food is free.
Keep your wallets handy, boys.
I keep flip-flopping whether
to go with the suit or the kimono.
Hey, guys, we've got a tester
on number six.
Okay, thanks, Mim.
What did Robert Morse do in it?
He did both,
but he had the budget for it.
We got 1 2 American Charlies,
seven with fungus, three tearjerkers...
...two bare-assed, hold the pom-poms
on one and frog sticks.
We could do it with three hands
tied behind our backs!
Rocket, I need four Pepsi
and two 7 UP on number six.
Don't forget, you've got two
Diet Pepsi on number nine.
You got it, Mimmy.
Three 7 UP coming up.
-No, it's two 7 UP--
-I got it. I got it.
Looks like
they're having serious trouble.
Come on. Come on.
1 2, 1 1, 10, 9...
-...8, 7, 6, 5...
-I'd go with the kimono.
...4, 3, 2--
-I'm sorry, boys. Maybe next time.
-Thanks, Mimmy.
So close.
You downloaded another picture
of your lnternet pal.
What's her name, Poon Tang?
-Her name is May Fong.
-So she says.
She could be
a 50-year-old circus freak...
...with six teeth
and a set of hairy walnuts.
Nice.
They paid 3.5 million.
We could've gotten it for 1.2.
I want my drink.
Well, hallelujah.
We finally got our drinks.
Root beer machine
had to be changed.
What the--? Hold on, pal. Diet Pepsi.
We ordered Diet Pepsi. Are you dense?
I'm Rocket. Dennis works
at the post office. Need stamps?
Oh, so you're a smart-ass, huh?
Oh, you idiot!
These are my good pants!
Oh, those are her good pants.
Honey--
Unbelievable.
-I want to talk to the owner.
-All right, right behind you.
Which one of you two
is in charge of this dump?
Your damn busboy just ruined
my wife's pants.
Well, I'm sorry about that.
You know, club soda's good for that.
I'm sure you think it's very progressive
to hire Jerry's Kids...
...but keep the freaks in the back...
...washing dishes,
away from the paying customers.
You are absolutely right.
How many times have I told you, Walt...
-...we don't want freaks here.
-He tells me. I never--
-Ever! Ever, do you?
-For some reason. I don't know why.
We're on top of it.
We're gonna handle it right now.
Rocket, let me talk to you
for a minute.
You know, we have a rule about freaks
in this place. We don't like them.
And we don't want them.
So, Rocket,
you see that door over there?
Would you escort
this freak through it?
No problem.
Right this way, please.
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't forget your bag.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Would you like those root beers to go?
All right, burgers on the house!
-He's just kidding, you cheap bastards.
-No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
No, yeah, he is. He is.
-Nice stop, guys. Way to go.
-Thanks, Stan.
Great game, Walt.
That was a huge win.
Thanks, Stan. I was seeing
the puck well tonight.
-Walt, how many saves you guys have?
-I had 1 1, and Bob had 26.
Bob-o was standing
on his head out there.
Check this out.
Wow, she's new. Hey, Dave,
how about another tall one?
You got it.
How about you there, Bob?
No, I'm cool.
I'm the designated walker tonight.
Got it.
I taste ice cream.
You got a dart in your head,
you dumb shit.
Hey, Romeo, how about you invite your
friend May out for a visit this spring?
Vineyard can be romantic
that time of year...
...and we so horny.
No, I checked the Farmer's Almanac.
It's supposed to be a muddy spring.
No, it's gonna be sloppy.
I don't want her to come out--
Seriously, man, I just--
You know, I want it to be right.
-I'm trying to be smart.
-You overanalyze this stuff.
What is that supposed to mean?
You should be talking to this chickie-poo
down at the bar.
-No.
-Come on.
-Come on. Get over there. Say hello.
-No. No. No, don't do it.
-No way. Cut it out. Stop it.
-Go on. She's smiling at you.
If she wanted to talk to somebody,
she would've brought a friend.
Hi. How are you? My name's Bob Tenor.
But I'm really more of a baritone.
Hi, Bob.
This is my brother, Walt.
Look, if you're ever in town--
I mean, I know you're in town now...
...but I mean, if you're ever in town
and not in a bar....
That came off wrong. It sounded
like you were a skanky whore.
I'd love it if you'd come by
Quikee Burger...
...which is my restaurant that I own
with my brother, Walt.
You met him.
Time's up, Casanever.
-Can I join you for a drink?
-Sure.
-Okay. What's your name?
-Debbie.
-Hi, I'm Walt Tenor.
-Nice to meet you.
Dear May,
thanks for the latest photo,
I look at it whenever
I'm in need of a smile,
I'm sending a picture of me at work,
Hope you like it,
Yours, Bob,
I' m starting to cramp.
-Hey.
-How's the letter coming?
-Good.
Yeah, what do you got?
It's personal. You know,
I don't go nosing into your business.
I'm sorry.
Mind typing on your knees?
Okay.
Here we go. There you go.
Turn around.
-Shouldn't you study your lines?
-Not necessary. Locked and loaded.
Then help me stack the wood.
I can't. I could pull something.
It's a performance day.
Aren't you a little bit nervous?
What's a four-letter word for snatch?
Grab.
You're not even a little bit nervous?
What's there to be nervous about?
Well, you're up there in a one-man
show, in front of all those people.
You know, I'd be crapping myself.
It's my ninth year,
I think I'm just....
I feel like I'm over it, you know?
-I guess that's how you have to be.
-Well....
You're doing that blinking thing.
Are you gonna have a panic attack?
-No, I'm cool.
-Are you all right?
-You all right?
-No, I'm not gonna--
-I'm gonna--
-Oh, God. Take it easy.
-Calm down.
-I think I'm dying.
-I'm dying.
-You're not.
-Oh, God.
-You're having a panic attack.
-Come on. Take it easy.
-Get my bag.
Wait, I'm having an arrhythmia.
Here you go. Breathe into the bag.
Short breaths.
Concentrate on the breathing.
It's nine years in a row!
I don't want to go on-stage.
Why do I have to go on-stage
with you?
You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine, all right?
You're gonna have fun tonight,
all right?
You're gonna have fun.
Any normal person with a normal sense
of self-preservation...
...would understand that
all an artist has is his life.
And what he observes
as he passes through his life.
And any serious writer hanging out
for years with the rich, well...
...my God, you'd have to be deluded
to the point of derangement...
...not to realize that that writer
was taking notes.
My God, I even told them.
They knew I was writing this book.
What did they think I was there for?
The intellectual stimulation?
The wit?
The spiritual uplift?
I brought the intellect
and the wit to the party.
Okay, okay, he's coming.
He's coming.
Bravo! Bravo!
-You were just wonderful!
-Thank you, Mim.
Yeah, Walt, you were great.
Bob, you sucked.
-Hey.
-Come on, Rocket, I'm not an actor.
So, what's up for next year?
-Oh, I don't know.
-Oh, come on, tell them the big idea.
-What is it?
-He wants to do a musical version...
-...of Bonnie and Clyde.
-All right!
-You were awesome last night.
-Thanks.
Is everything all right?
You seem a little--
Remember when we were little and we
first found out we'd never be separated?
-Sure.
-Made a blood pact that day, remember?
Yeah, we promised we'd never hold
each other back, no matter what.
And we never have. Right off the bat,
we made a hell of a team.
Trick or treat!
Get them! Get them!
Man, those freaks are fast.
Strike one!
Let's do it! Now, come on!
Get out there!
Break. Break. Break. Break. Okay,
come on. You keep it clean, now.
You're out!
Your kings and queens!
Right, Betty!
So, what's your point?
Here, sit down.
Oh, jeez.
I want to be an actor.
Yeah. Of course.
Look, I'm sorry, man.
I know I freaked out yesterday...
...but I'll go on-stage with you again.
You can even sing if you want to.
I'd never stop you from doing that.
I mean, I want to be a real actor.
I want to move to Hollywood.
-What?!
-I think I got the chops for it.
Those people last night were moved.
-I got to them.
-Look, those were your friends.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I just meant....
Look, man, we're from
Martha's Vineyard, okay?
You know, people here....
You know, we're lifeguards
and fishermen.
We own restaurants.
We do not star in movies.
What about Meryl Streep?
She's not from the Vineyard.
She shot one movie here.
She stayed on a couple extra
weeks because she liked it.
-What are you--? What is your point?
-Well....
Okay, look, I'm gonna
put it to you this way.
Who were the last conjoined twins
who were nominated for an Oscar?
I can't believe I'm hearing this
from you, of all people.
Isn't that what people told us
our whole lives?
We couldn't do what normal
people did. Never stopped us.
By the way, Hollywood just happens
to be in L.A. where May Fong lives.
I'm not ready for that.
She's crowding me as it is.
Crowding you?! She's been
your lnternet pal for three years.
You haven't even met her!
Look, man. What about me, man?
I have a business here.
If things work out,
we can open a Quikee Burger in L.A.
Yeah, or better yet, maybe
you can get in the movie biz too.
What am I gonna do
in the movie business?
I don't know. You could be
my stunt double.
-Your stunt double?
-Yeah.
If I gotta do, like, a dangerous stunt,
you could do it...
...so that I don't get hurt.
Come on. I need to do this
while I still can. I'm getting old, Bob.
-Walt, you're 32.
-Going on 50.
Listen, I can't help it
you got most of our liver. Okay?
I'm aging faster.
I got bags under my eyes.
And you? Time's passing. You got
nothing to show except for pictures.
-You haven't been laid in five years.
-Hey, how would you know?
I don't know, Walt.
You know,
we got a great thing going here.
-lt might not be the same--
-lt might be better!
Have you ever thought about that?
Three months, we go,
we see how it works out.
If it doesn't, we come home.
I'll be happy because I know we tried.
Okay, Hollywood...
...but you're gonna owe me
bigtime for this.
Bye.
Bye, Bob.
You sure this is the right
Hollywood and Vine?
-According to the brochure, it is.
-Show us your power, Lord.
Lord, Lord, hates the sin,
but loves the sinner.
-Show us your truth, Jesus.
-Holy smokes.
Hey, freaks!
Yo!
Hello!
Fade out!
My wife's not out there, is she?
No, I haven't seen anybody.
That psycho midget's
been riding my ass...
...to finish this screenplay I've been
working on for the last two years.
This is it.
Clean sheets and towels.
There'll be a pot of green tea
in the office every morning.
-Name's Moe if you need anything.
-This is great.
Do you have a room
with a double bed?
Sorry, this is all I got.
But tell you what I can do...
...I'll see if I can get a queen bed
in here in about a week or two.
-See you guys.
-Thanks, Moe.
Give her a call.
Let her know we're here.
What--?
This is serious. We have
a lot of things to do out here.
Not the least of which
is get you into a casting agency...
...without them laughing you
out of the room.
Why would they laugh?
I mean, look at you.
You're pale as a ghost.
We gotta get you a tan.
Okay, what's a four-letter word
for voiceless, ends in D?
-Surd.
-Surd?
Surd with a U.
I gotta tell you, this crossword's a lot
easier than the one I'm used to at home.
Well, well, well,
what do we have here?
-Hey!
-Hi.
-Are you new around here?
-Got in this morning.
-My name's Walt.
-Hey, I'm April.
-This is my brother, Bob.
-Hey. Bob Tenor.
Have a seat.
So you guys are brand-new.
-Our first California sunburn.
-We're official.
You're gonna love it here
at the Star.
I've been here, like,
two and a half years, and--
Hey, you guys are stuck together.
And I still love it here.
We're like one big happy family.
So where'd you get this done?
No, no, we were born like this.
Cool. Cool.
And where are you guys from?
Massachusetts.
Bob here's a lover/grillman...
...and I came out
to give acting a shot.
Oh, my God! I'm an actor too.
-Oh, yeah?
-You're an actor?
Yeah. Well, no.
I mean, I want to be one.
Right now I'm just
kind of a lingerie model.
Oh, my God! So am l.
No, he isn't.
No, seriously, like,
do you have an agent?
No, no, not yet. How about you?
No, not momentarily,
but I did have one.
This colostomy bag
named Morty O'Reilly.
-Hey, you want a beer?
-Yeah.
I've had better luck on my own.
Every morning I read Back Stage West.
-Can I see?
-Yeah.
And it lists all the open casting calls.
Yeah, you don't even need
an agent with that thing.
Bob, check this out. Right here.
"Wanted: Tall, handsome,
distinguished actor...
...to play Robin Hood
for the new millennium."
-That's you!
-That is me!
-That is you!
-ls that me?
-Yeah, it's you!
-lt is me.
You guys are fun.
Listen, ye all, and hear me now.
The sheriff of Nottingham
will come forth...
...but he will not bend
this merry band of--
Of brothers!
He will--
Who put you up to this?
It was Lovett over at CAA,
wasn't it?
Joan, get that SOB on the horn
for me, will you, please?
Did you bring a headshot
and list of your credits?
You know, I was supposed to do that,
and I forgot it at home.
Sometimes I think he'd forget
his own brother if I wasn't sewn on.
Okay, thank you for coming.
We'll be in touch.
No.
I'm sorry, but the message
that we're trying to get across...
...is that Dubble Bubble doubles
the taste, not causes birth defects.
I don't know.
Maybe you were right, Bob.
Maybe this is a pipe dream.
Yeah. Probably time to face facts.
If you haven't made it
in the first 72 hours...
-...you should probably just pack it in.
-Right.
I bet Meryl Streep wasn't out here
six hours before she got her big break.
De Niro too.
And Steve Buscemi?
With his pearly whites...
...he was in town 45 minutes
before he got his first role.
-Are you making fun of me?
-You bet I am.
I know you were born without a liver,
but you got some backbone, didn't you?
-You gotta admit these past couple of--
-I'm not gonna admit anything.
How do we know
the Lion King producers...
...aren't looking for some
conjoined hyenas as we speak?
Know who will get the part now?
Those Schappell sisters from Oregon
who are stuck at the forehead.
Why? They're country-and-western
singers, not actors.
Because you quit, that's why.
Right.
-Maybe I was a little hasty.
-Good.
Hey, don't worry about anything.
I happen to have a little plan that's going
into effect first thing tomorrow morning.
All right.
You're a great brother, Bob.
Yeah, I know, now zip the lip.
Let's get some sleep.
I like your plan.
The car's only plan A.
Plan B is to get you an agent.
Right.
Retirement home? Are you sure
we got the right address?
This is what he gave me.
Maybe we should try someone else.
April said this Morty guy's a total sleaze.
But you said he's the only one
that would give us an appointment.
I want you to know up front...
...that O'Reilly only represents actors
who are truly committed to their craft.
That's me, Mr. O'Reilly.
I am fully committed.
Committed enough to pay
my $200 up-front service fee?
Which, of course, is used to defray
the costs of registration fees...
...entitlement paperwork
and what have you.
-What are you doing?
-I'm showing him how committed I am.
You're showing him
how stupid you are. Here.
We'll give you $100 because
you're only representing one of us.
Look, I'm gonna level with you.
Siamese twins
ain't the easiest sell I've had.
We're not Siamese. We're American.
I think what my brother's saying is,
he'd prefer the term "conjoined twins."
Okay, but I should let you know...
...I'm not one of those run-of-the-mill
suits. I'm a full-service agent.
-Meaning?
-I get 25 percent.
-Well, what does he get in return?
-Seventy-five percent.
Well, I gotta tell you,
I think he seemed like a real player.
I guess.
Oh, my God. It's her.
Who?
Don't, don't, don't, don't gawk.
Don't do that.
She's famous. She probably
hates when people gawk.
I like that part, but I just....
I think we gotta at least go by
and say hi.
A minute ago,
we couldn't even look at her...
-...and now we're gonna go say hello?
-Hey, Bob, relax. It would be rude not to.
I'll do all the talking.
Excuse me, Ms. Streep.
Sorry to interrupt your lunch.
I know this is completely
inappropriate...
...but my brother Bob
is a big fan of yours. He just--
He wanted to come by and say hi.
-Hi.
-Hi, Bob.
We're from Oak Bluffs
on Martha's Vineyard.
I've been there.
Yeah, I know you have. Actually,
we're friends with Timmy Sheehan.
-Who?
-Timmy Sheehan.
Remember, he waited on you one time
at Jimmy Sea's restaurant?
Remember? You autographed
his menu for him.
I did.
I know because
I read it and it said:
"To Timmy, a good waiter.
From Meryl Streep."
But the way you signed the P,
it looked like an L...
...so we used to call Timmy
all the time and say:
"Hello, this is Meryl Streel calling."
We were just busting his nuts.
True story.
I think I remember him.
I ordered some food,
and he brought it to me.
That would be him.
He's a real character.
I can't believe you just come
to a restaurant and nobody bugs you.
Well....
Let's go.
Well, let me go.
Nice meeting you.
You know, by the way,
if you ever just wanna...
...get away, have a little hang time,
we're at the Rising Star apartments.
It is a pretty sweet setup.
We got a barbecue pit there.
Gas. He does steaks and chops.
We got a pool, a little grassy knoll area,
and feel free to just come by any time.
Okay. I'll keep it in mind.
-Great. And bring the posse.
-Okay.
Bring the posse.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
I do remember you guys.
Homecoming '87.
Oh, my God! I was at that game.
With seconds on the clock,
it's fourth down, one yard to go.
-Safety cheating.
-Check. Check.
Check. Check.
Apache 36. Apache 36.
Okay, let's go.
Hike.
I'm wide open.
Touchdown, Vineyard.
Sharks win, 22-21.
That was you!
He actually is the one who scored
the winning touchdown.
Well, you threw him
a hell of a block.
I've always told you that.
You never give yourself enough credit.
As you can see, I'm on crutches.
I was wounded during the Vietnam War.
Had a hunting accident
while hiding in Canada.
Tried that Viagra stuff the other day.
I didn't get an erection,
but I could walk for three hours.
Did a benefit for
Jehovah Witnesses...
...all's they wanted to hear
were "knock, knock" jokes.
Then the three of us just sat there
and talked for, like, an hour.
Meryl--
She asked me to call her Meryl.
Very knowledgeable on the film industry.
She says I should plug away...
...because I have twice the presence
of most actors she's met.
-Well, you do.
-Thanks.
Anyway, I told her my first love's
the theater back home...
...felt I had to give
Hollywood a crack...
...but if I ever go back, I should call her.
She's dying to go to the Vineyard.
She might even star
in a show with me.
-Really? Walt, that's great!
-I know.
I love it when famous people
are not dickwads.
That's the Streeper, perfectly normal.
As normal as you and me.
Stop. Anyway....
-Can I ask you a personal question?
-Nine inches.
I wasn't gonna ask that.
Nine inches?
Yeah, it's about nine inches across.
No, actually, what I was
gonna ask you is...
...if you guys ever considered,
you know, getting separated?
There's a lot of great plastic surgeons
here. A lot. I mean, just look at these.
Well, our problem can't really be fixed
through a simple cosmetic surgery.
We share a liver.
He's got most of it.
There's no way they can just nip
and tuck so you both get some?
There is and there isn't.
The doctors at Mass General told us
they could split us up at no risk to Bob...
...but there's a 50-50 chance
that I wouldn't make it, so....
Oh, God, no.
I don't blame you for not doing it.
No! No, no, no, I wanted to do it.
Bob wouldn't allow it.
Oh, Bob.
Yeah. He's really something.
Hey, are you even sure
you need a liver?
My friend had his appendix out
and he's okay.
Okay. I'm gonna
take a little sleepy now.
Good night.
I'm not here.
Hello.
No, he is currently unavailable.
Can I take a message?
-Oh, hey, Morty.
-I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
You know, l--
He is waking up from his afternoon nap.
Hold on, please.
Hello!
You're kidding me. What--?
Of course I'll be there.
Thank you, Mr. O'Reilly.
Thanks a lot.
I got a job.
What?
It's a motion picture
called Pavlov's Dog!
I start tomorrow morning
at 9:00 a.m.!
Do you hear that, Bob?
I'm a working actor!
Great!
Hey, it gets even better.
In five minutes, you have a date
with the girl of your dreams.
Bobby!
Come on.
Bobby.
Would you calm down?
I thought you'd be happy about this.
Oh, God. How could you?
-How could you?
-lt was easy.
I called information, I got her number,
and I called her before you woke up.
Thank you.
No, she is from California, Walt,
she's not used to Siamese twins.
Siamese?
Hey, what happened to conjoined?
Oh, just cut the bullshit!
We're gonna freak her out!
Excuse me.
Hello?
May I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for Bob Tenor.
-Apartment five.
-Thank you.
-Have you been honest with this girl?
-Yeah.
-By and large.
-Well....
-Didn't tell her about yourself, did you?
-Of course I did!
I just....
I didn't tell her about you.
I can't deal with you right now.
The pictures!
What about the pictures, Bob?
-I cut you out of them.
-Oh, well, that's great!
That is really, really great!
That says a lot, brother.
-Ashamed of me, huh?
-No, I'm not ashamed of you.
I just don't know how I feel
about myself sometimes.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-What am I gonna do?
-We'll go out the back window.
-Yeah, okay, we'll make a run for it.
We're not running anywhere.
Hey! Where have you been hiding?
Hi, Bob.
-Just go ahead and tell her.
-Live your own life.
Hop in!
Well, well, we finally meet.
-I can't believe you're actually here.
-Yeah, I know. It's amazing, huh?
You look a lot bigger
than in your photos.
Well, I would hope so,
or else I'd only be three inches tall.
Hi, I'm Bob's brother, Walt.
I spoke to you on the phone.
Walt, meet May.
Nice to meet you, Walt.
-You never told me you had a brother.
-I never told you I had a brother.
Are we going somewhere?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I made dinner reservations.
Tenor, party of three.
I believe we had an 8:1 5 reservation.
-Can I help you?
-We'll have two Jumbo Jacks, please.
A Sourdough Jack, three fries,
and three medium Pepsis.
-Two Jumbo Jacks, one Sourdough,,,
-Got a favorite parking spot here, Bob?
,,, three medium Pepsis,
Anything else?
-So how was the trip here?
-Oh, awesome, awesome flight.
Yeah, you should've seen it.
We played cards.
-Cards are fun.
-Yeah.
Grand Canyon.
-We flew right over the Grand Canyon.
-Oh, yeah?
Yeah, it's, like, real different from
the Vineyard, with the big hole and shit.
And it was orange.
Do you guys remember
that Allen movie, Annie Hall...
...where the guy goes out with the girl
and to ease the tension...
...he suggests they kiss
at the beginning of the date.
-Yes!
-Do you remember this?
-That's a really good scene.
-The best is when...
...Diane Keaton's brother says he's
gonna drive into the truck...
...and kill everybody in the car.
Yeah.
May, I think there's something
I should tell you.
Yes.
Go ahead.
You see, the reason
that I'm acting kind of strange--
-I think I'm dying!
-Lord.
-I think-- I can't--
-Are you okay?
-I can't breathe!
-Oh, my God.
Should we get out?
No, you're having a panic attack.
Here, breathe into this.
-You don't like me, do you?
-What?
You're disappointed with me.
No! No, you're awesome!
You're even better in person!
-No, I'm not.
-Yes!
Oh, yeah.
You're a hottie. Absolutely.
Just breathe into there.
No, no, no. Oh, God, I'm, I'm, I'm--
I'm so embarrassed. I waited so long
to meet you, and now I'm blowing it.
-No! No.
-No. No.
You're not blowing anything.
No blowing.
You're so much better than I could--
I'm actually happy you're having this...
...because it means
we have even more in common.
-I freak out too.
-He does.
-You really have panic attacks?
-Oh, all the time.
I was actually just about to have one,
and then you beat me to the punch.
Hey, sorry...
...to have Walt here
tagging along on our date.
You know, he can be a little clingy.
You know, it's his first time
out on the Left Coast...
...and, you know,
he's heard about the gangs...
...and the Crips and the Bloods, and....
I was less nervous about it.
I actually looked into joining the Crips.
But I found that the Bloods
had a better dental plan.
No. No, sir, that's not true.
They wouldn't take me.
-I had a lot of fun tonight, Bob.
-Yeah, me too.
Well, anyway...
-...I guess this is it.
-Yep.
Will you walk me to the door?
-I wanna get out and stretch my legs.
-Sure, sure.
Yeah.
The sidewalk's safer.
I'm gonna walk you guys
right to the front door.
This is beautiful, by the way.
I got an early-morning call time.
-Good luck tomorrow, Walt.
-Oh, thank you very much. Thanks.
You guys have probably seen enough
of me. I'll just get out of your hair.
-Good night, Bob.
-Good night, May.
-Yes! Yes!
-Hey. Hey, hey.
-Good kisser?
-Yeah, I'm not bad.
-Oh, that's good. That's cute.
-That is good, huh?
-No, no, no! It's not funny! Come on.
-Who's your daddy?
-You're my daddy.
-That's it.
-So, what's this Pavlov's Dog about?
-I don't know.
They didn't send me a script.
Probably one of those Disney movies
with the talking animals.
"I'm Pavlov."
-Hey, great makeup job, fellas!
-Thanks. You too.
Am I just talking to hear
my brains rattle? I'm hot!
Do you hear me? I am hot!
Look what it says here, Howard.
Who's hot, who's not. Cher, red-hot!
You're hotter than hot! You're on fire.
There's no question about it.
Then answer me this. Why am I doing
this lame-ass TV show...
-...when I should be doing movies?
-Because you signed a contract...
...and the network's holding you to it.
Honey and the Beaze isn't lame-ass.
You're a sassy lawyer
who uses DNA evidence...
...to free wrongly convicted minorities.
This is cutting-edge stuff.
Oh, cut the crap, Howard.
Come on, this TV show...
...makes Touched by an Angel
look like Trainspotting!
Before I busted my nut to get you
this gig, you were two weeks away...
-...from being the corner square?
-Center square.
You told me they wanted me
for center square.
I did say that.
And you see, what happened is...
...Alf was able to free up his schedule,
and, well, they want--
If you didn't get lucky with one lousy
indie film, you'd be begging for this job.
Let me explain something
to you, okay?
First, that lousy little indie film
has grossed over 200 million dollars!
And secondly, I don't beg.
And you know why I don't beg?
-No.
-Because I am a fucking Oscar winner!
Cher.
Oh, hi.
Can I help you?
Sorry, we're looking for stage 32,
and a little lost.
Thirty-- There's no 30--
Let me have a look at that.
You're on the wrong lot. You want
stage 32 at Half-Mast Studios.
-That's across the street.
-Oh, well....
So that would explain
why the guard was shooting at us.
Sorry to bother you.
What?
You're Cher.
-Oh, boy.
-l-- Sorry. I'm sorry.
-I'm just a bi-- I'm a big fan. Big.
-He is.
Big fan of your work.
And I'm an actor too.
-You guys are an actor?
-No, no. Not him. Not him. Just me.
-I'm a short-order cook back East.
-Yeah.
He does that, and I'm out here right now
just kind of going through it, you know?
Living it right now. It's going well too.
I got a couple of things going on.
I'm doing a gig
across the street, actually.
I have an agent. Could I just trouble you
for an autograph?
We're busy.
-Right. Okay. No heat on that.
-Wrap it up.
All right, well, just keep on keeping on.
Do what you do.
That really puts things into perspective,
doesn't it?
"That really puts things into perspectiv--"
Just get me out of the stinking show!
So this is your first job, huh?
Yes. Yes, it is.
Actually, I was wondering...
...is there somebody around
who might have a script?
I haven't gone over my lines.
They're just gonna set up
the scenes...
...and then they're gonna let you all
just kind of wing it.
Improv. This director
sounds very progressive.
I guess.
Who exactly is in this film?
Phil Rupp, Lolly Gagger,
Marianna Trench...
...and Rebecca Romaine-Staymoist.
Phil Rupp.
Never heard of him.
-You're kidding.
-No.
You never heard of Phil Rupp?
Oh, he's done over 500 films.
Hey, what exactly is Pavlov's Dog
about anyway?
Pavlov's Dog? It isn't Pavlov's Dog.
It's Pavlov's--
--Dong. Scene 1 4, take one.
And, action.
That's it, Phil, you spring to life now.
Good. Excellent. A little more.
Give me some more.
I want some more. Nice.
Phil, you disappear now.
The freaks are gonna jump in...
...and we discover the whole scene's
a horrible nightmare.
Wait. Look, Cher,
if you break this contract...
...they'll blackball the both of us.
You'll be finished.
I don't give a goat's bobo
what it says on that thing.
I knew we shouldn't have trusted
that bastard Morty.
Maybe he didn't know
what the movie was about.
He was the executive producer!
Yeah.
Doesn't that contract say
I can choose my own co-star?
Yeah. So what?
I just found my leading man.
Men.
What are you, frigging nuts?
Siamese twins!
-The network'll never go for that.
-Exactly.
That way they'll break the contract
and not me.
Don't--
Cher, please, don't do this.
Hey, guys! Guys?
I just want to say that I am really sorry
for being a bitch back there...
...but I was in the middle of being
balled out by my creepy manager...
...and I guess I took it out
on the wrong people.
Hi, Bob.
Hi, May.
Walt, what happened to your foot?
I fell off my unicycle.
-Easy.
-I sprained it pretty bad.
This is our friend April.
-Hi, May.
-Nice to meet you.
-God, you're a doll. Good going.
-Thanks.
So we're all here.
What's the big news?
-Yeah, what's going on?
-Okay, well, as of tomorrow...
...my brother, Walter L. Tenor,
the thespian...
...will be co-starring in his very own
major network television series!
-That's incredible.
-It's called Honey and the Beaze.
Cher plays Honey,
I have the role of Mack Beasley.
-Cher Cher?
-One of the nicest women.
-As classy as they come.
-You must've done a great audition!
-He didn't even have to!
-Nothing.
We bumped into Cher on the studio lot,
and she invited us out for coffee.
Actually, yerba mats,
which is this very soothing tea drink--
-Six bucks, though.
-Yeah.
She starts telling us all this personal
stuff like, she's been in a relationship...
...for the last three years
with a very high-profile actor...
-...but they've kept it out of the press.
-Who?
How would we know?
That's way too personal.
-You didn't ask her?
-No, I asked a lot.
And she said,
"That's way too personal."
We had it going on!
And I was going:
Mikey! I haven't seen you, man.
To Bob, my best friend,
who I'm just getting to know.
-Hello, May.
-Wes!
Oh, aren't you gonna introduce me
to your best friend?
-Hi, name's Bob Tenor.
-Yeah, I know who you are.
-You're HoldthePickle@hotmail.com.
-I came up with that.
-It's a double-entendre.
-I'm sorry, Bob.
He hacked into my computer at work
and read my mail.
Don't be pissed there,
lover boy, okay?
I think I had a right
to check up on my girl.
-I am not your girl!
-Not my girlfriend, huh?
Then what was that about
up at Mulholland when you sucked--
Hey, hey, hey!
I think we've heard enough, okay?
Bob, let him finish.
When you sucked down a six-pack
with me and said you cared for me.
-You--
-I said I cared for you as a co-worker.
You have good business sense.
That's all.
Hey, Wes, why don't you go drown
your sorrows somewhere else, okay?
I have a better idea.
You and me, why don't we step outside?
Let's go. Come on.
No, no, no, you stay out of this.
This is between him and me.
Come on, burger boy, stand up.
What the hell's wrong with you two?
-You can't fight fair?
-No, Bob, do not fight him.
He's a black belt.
Just like I thought.
You're a pussy.
Let's not let that--
--ruin our night.
-Come on, let's dance.
-Oh, no, I'm a terrible dancer. I--
Come on.
Walt, should you be dancing
on a sprained ankle?
Gonna take more than a sprain
to keep me off this dance floor.
You were right
about your brother Walt.
He really doesn't give you
much rope, does he?
She's not talking to you.
The weather's been
just unbelievable, isn't it?
It's just, like, incredible.
Because I bet back home
that it's snowing still.
Well, snow is beautiful too.
Oh, no, no, no, snow's my favorite.
I love snow. It's awesome.
Hey, and we don't
have earthquakes there, either.
-Earthquakes scare me.
-Oh, me too. They, like, freak me out.
Hey, what's with all these maniacs who
live on the cliffs, like on stilts out here?
-These people are out of their minds.
-I couldn't do that.
My dream house
would have to have a yard.
No, you definitely have to have a yard.
That way, that way we could have dogs.
I meant, me and my wife
could have dogs.
Not you.
Not that I have anything against you.
Hey, May, let's go to the bathroom.
-We'll be right back.
-See you.
How'd my right-hand man make out?
Look, man, I don't want any trouble.
Holy shit!
She's cheating on you
with a circus freak!
Hey, Walt, Walt, Walt...