Stop!
Stop the bus!
The story of my life is not
for the faint of heart.
Thanks.
But, like any story
worth telling,
it's all about a girl.
Not that girl.
- Hey. Hi.
- I don't think that is a girl.
No, it's about this girl...
Jill Johnson.
Ever since I can remember
I've been in love with her,
but she barely knows
I exist.
Yo, Rick!
Yo, come here, man!
I got you a seat
down here. What's...
I'll call y'all back.
Everybody, bye.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, Trey.
Dude, I'm so psyched
for this class trip.
We about to see some real
serious cutting-edge shit.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm. Mmm.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Yo, you got any C batteries on you?
AAs?
Got that new sandwich
from Sony in my backpack.
Wi-Fi... mmm!
Yo! You got to forget
about her, dawg.
Look look.
Let me show you something.
She not even
looking at you.
If I could just
tell her how I feel.
Look, Rick, I already told you...
you never gonna get
with Jill, all right?
Seriously, she hangs out
with the popular crew,
and nobody messes around
outside their group, man.
Come on, that crew stuff
isn't real.
The hell it ain't.
Look around, Rick.
- Look, you got your jocks...
- Get the ball, man.
...nerds, emos,
Frodos,
the Scarface society...
...the sexual predators.
- Yeah.
- Of course you got the Rick punchers.
- The who?
- Oh!
- Yeah, they new.
Mm-hmm. But you know what?
Who cares?
'Cause we got our own crew...
me and you.
Thanks, Trey.
You're the best, man.
- Am I in?
- No.
Come on.
Hey, it's me and you, baby.
The two of us against the world.
You hear me?
You look good today.
I like your hair.
I'm gonna show you
something nasty I downloaded.
Don't tell nobody.
Welcome to Amalgamated.
I'm Dr. Strom,
head of the research department...
- Come on, man.
...where we create the future today.
And now I'd like
to show you our crown jewel.
The Amalgamated
animal genetics lab.
Whoa.
Go ahead, explore.
Yo yo. Come on, Rick.
Man, check this out.
All of our animals are
genetically engineered
and each of them has...
Oh, you're so pretty.
Hi, birdie.
Hi. Hi.
- She's beautiful, isn't she?
- Yes, she is.
Uh, I'm gonna take
a picture of her
for the school newspaper.
Our only rules: Don't feed the animals
and please,
no flash photography.
Some of our genetically-
engineered animals
are a little sensitive
to light.
It flew away.
Uh... whoo-hoo.
What the F, loser?
Get him, Lance.
- Come on, Lance.
- Leave him alone.
- I don't think so.
Is there
a problem, Lance?
No. No problem,
Uncle Lou.
Mr. Landers!
Students,
this is Lou Landers,
visionary scientist
and C.E.O. of Amalgamated.
Well, I'm just
a businessman now.
The future of science
belongs to all of you.
Please, enjoy the tour.
Are you okay?
Yes, this is
healthy-cough blood.
Rick Riker. You're not Blaine and Julia
Riker's son, are you?
- I am.
- Ah. Good people.
- How are they?
- They died violently nine years ago.
But otherwise okay?
Yes, thank you.
I live with my aunt and uncle now.
Well, you seem
like a real chip off the old block.
Let's hope you're not
violently murdered too.
That's for making me look stupid.
Next time
I hurt you.
Yeah.
You the man, Lance.
Our work with these animals
has helped us develop
new antibiotics,
advanced pesticides
and a powerful new pheromone
which drives animals to mate
called compound H2O0.
It's a strong
sexual attractant.
A single drop is enough
to arouse any animal.
We plan on using it to breed
endangered species.
A special and indeed
often overlooked...
Our most-promising research
is with these dragonflies.
For example,
this dragonfly's skin
has a hard,
armor-like exoskeleton
to defend against...
And this species
of dragonfly
has enormous strength
for its size.
It can lift vast amounts.
More than it's body weight.
And here we've injected the DNA
from all three species
into seven
new genetically-enhanced
super dragonflies.
But there's
only six in there.
Well, one missing dragonfly
is the least of my concerns.
I lost six tigers alone
last month.
Ah!
This area is where
we keep our livestock.
Ohh.
Aren't you going
to do something?
Soon as I get
this up on YouTube.
I see. Ye... well,
yes, I understand.
Thank you
for the call.
That was
the principal.
Rick walked off
a class trip.
After all the parenting
you've done,
he's still so troubled.
Why do you think
that is, Albert?
I have no idea,
Lucille.
I have taught him everything I know
about being a man.
And a good man you are
after all these years
of marriage.
It's like we first met.
Sure, you're
a little older.
Your hair's grey.
You have crow's feet.
It takes you
an hour to pee.
Your thighs look
like cottage cheese
someone threw up
on a hot sidewalk.
And you've always had
a tiny penis.
Well... what does it matter
when you're in love?
Oh, Rick.
We were wondering
where you were.
It's so late.
About time you got home.
Your aunt was getting worried.
You can sleep late
in the morning,
but don't forget
to feed the fish.
Attaboy.
I don't know.
Something just doesn't seem
quite right with him today.
Teenagers.
I'll talk to him.
Rough day, huh?
Well, I won't lie to you.
Puberty is
a difficult time
in a young man's life.
Now this book may explain
what's happening.
Let's see.
There are mood swings, fluid retention,
and once a month you'll bleed
from your vagina.
This may be
the wrong book.
What's important is that you're on
the verge of adulthood.
Here...
take a drink.
Ah, the rituals
of manhood.
Today you have
your first beer,
and tomorrow
we'll circumcise you.
I'm losing patience,
Dr. Strom.
Please, sir, if you could just
wait a few minutes...
I've waited long enough
for this egomaniac.
We're the board of directors.
Our time is valuable.
Not as valuable
as mine, Mr. Carlson.
You see, I have
a terminal illness.
I've been
fighting it for years,
but the disease has
ravaged my organs.
As of this moment,
I have one hour left to live.
It was on sale.
Gentlemen, if you're ready,
allow me
to show you the future.
Strom.
From the... lift it ov...
lift it over!
What the hell
is that?
An innovation...
thank you...
that will not only
save my life
but the life
of this company.
For too long we've scraped out profits
from pills and injections.
The real prize is
the total cure.
A device
that can alter DNA
and restore the body
to perfect health.
- You're crazy.
- No.
Crazy is hearing voices,
talking to cats,
dating Paula Abdul.
I'm not crazy.
I'm a visionary!
Sir.
Sir, the machine's
never been fully tested.
If something should go wrong...
- Start the machine!
- Yes, sir.
Plasma level
is steady.
Genetic modification's
at optimum levels!
Sir, the core is overheating.
- Ah!
- We have to abort!
Did it work?
I'm so sorry.
Well, well, well.
I want you to know
what a joy it will be
running this company
without you in the way.
Let go.
Let me go.
Gentlemen, I think it's time we made
some personnel changes.
No, stay away!
Oh. How long
was I asleep?
Five days.
Huh.
Wait.
Wha...
Oh, Dad.
I thought
you'd live forever.
Oh.
Breakfast, Rick!
I'll be right down!
Oh!
If I can have your attention.
We are delighted to have
as guest judge
the foremost scientist
in the world.
He's a visiting professor
at Empire City University
where he's working
with the rare element cerillium.
I am so proud to welcome
Dr. Stephen Hawking.
Thank you for that warm welcome.
I have a disease
that has paralyzed me.
I cannot walk and I use
this computer to speak.
But I am not depressed,
because I have the gift of knowledge.
That's a lie.
I think about suicide every day.
But you should all be happy
with your lives.
You can walk, talk,
wipe your own asses
and then there's
all the sex.
I haven't had sex in years.
My nurse is a lesbian,
and not the hot kind.
Hey, anyone want
to get high?
- I've got some hash with me.
- No way.
White guy
in the dreads,
you know
what I'm talking about.
Can I get a what what?
Holla.
I've got a stiff pole
for your sweet hole.
Anyone? Anyone?
Pussies.
Dr. Hawking,
I am such a fan.
I'd love to show you
my project on supernovas.
You have an incredible ass...
...stromony career
ahead of you.
Wait, where's Saturn?
I'd hate to lose
my father's bowling ball.
There it is.
Great reflexes.
You have
very manly hands.
So do you.
I'm gonna go find a spot
for my project.
Yeah, okay.
Watch where you're going
in slo-mo, dipshit.
- Pfft.
- Yeah.
Go to her, stupid.
Tell her how you feel.
Yow.
Any day.
Uh... he did it.
Ow!
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Get him, Lance!
- Lance, stop it.
- Kick his ass, Lance!
Fight fight fight!
- Let's see what you got.
- Fucking break him!
Whoa!
Oh!
Damn!
Ooh!
Get off!
Get... get off me!
Yah!
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Shit shit shit shit.
# Oh no, you didn't, didn't #
- # Oh no, you didn't #
- # Oh yes, we did #
# Oh no, you didn't, didn't,
Oh no, you didn't #
- # Oh yeah, we did #
- # Oh no, you didn't, didn't #
- # Oh no, you didn't #
- # Oh yes, we did. #
Stop! Stop! Hey!
Get out of the way!
No brakes!
Ma'am, look out!
Are you okay?
- How did you...
- I can't believe it.
- You just saved that old lady's life.
- Amazing.
l... I guess.
If I hadn't pushed her out of the way,
she would've die... ah!
You should be really proud of yourself.
You're some kind of hero.
If you could excuse me.
There we go. Awfully nice of you
to help me out here, Trey.
Oh, no problem.
I'm waiting on Rick, anyway, so...
Ooh.
My God.
How did you do that?
Uh, it's easier
than it looks.
No, I don't think so.
Why don't you tell me
what's going on?
All right. Well,
there is something, okay?
But you have to
keep it a secret.
I think I have...
superpowers.
I find that
hard to believe.
All right, all right,
how about this?
Go ahead and throw
as many punches as you want.
I bet you 100 bucks
you don't land one.
Easy money.
What else can you do?
I don't know.
l... I was bitten by a dragonfly.
Well, some dragonflies
have armored skin.
I wonder if my skin is...
Well, good thing
that worked.
So you do have
superpowers.
We could be a team!
We gonna
get fame, money...
- Don't forget the bitches.
- There's not gonna be fame
and there's not
gonna be bitches, okay?
I didn't ask for any of this.
I just wanna be like everybody else.
That isn't what
your parents wanted for you.
You're not my father.
But I love you
like your father did.
I believe in you
I had sex with your mother just
like your father did.
Huh. You'll never
understand me.
Never.
That isn't what
your parents wanted for you.
What a great performance.
Well, Rick,
did you enjoy the opera?
Son, is something
troubling you?
It's so unfair.
They have nothing.
Why do we have $2 billion?
Well, your grandfather
left us $3 billion
and I made some
bad investments.
But that's nothing for you
to worry about.
But I want
to change things.
And you will.
Five generations of Rikers
have worked hard to make
this city great.
One day, Rick, people will look
to you to be a hero.
When that day comes,
will you be ready?
Give me your wallet.
That too.
People will look to you to be a hero.
When that day comes,
will you be ready?
Rick!
Ah!
Ow!
Huh? Ah!
Rick, please!
Ah!
- Dad!
- Oh, Rick, I'm dying.
- No!
- Don't worry.
My brother Albert
will take you in.
Rick, the money,
it's all yours now.
Sell all shares of a small company
called Google.
It's worthless.
Invest heavily in Enron.
Rick, I have
something for you.
Reach into
my coat pocket.
The other coat pocket.
God!
That ring
was my father's
and his father's
before him.
Earn it, Rick.
Be a hero.
Claim your...
- destiny.
Dad!
I'm no superhero.
I'm nobody!
Ah!
Shut up back there! I'm gonna kill you!
- Are you okay?
- What, you heard that?
You're nothing but an ugly,
ungrateful little whore!
Just like your mother!
- Who was that?
- My mother.
Listen, about what happened
at school this morning, l...
You really freaked us out.
I'm really going through
a tough time right now.
Me too. My parents,
they want me to go to college,
but I want
to be a dancer.
I believe in you.
You really do,
don't you?
I wish I could say
the same for Lance.
I don't know.
Is he the right one
or am I just dating him
to rebel against my father?
He doesn't want any boy near me.
That's why he installed
the electrified fence.
Well, we'll see.
You can't run from your destiny.
- Right?
- Right.
- Jill, let's go!
- Nice car.
Maybe one day you could take me
for a ride in your car.
Uh...
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh. Lovebirds.
Rick, this is
Professor Xavier.
Your powers are growing,
but you can't control it.
It's important that you...
become a hero...
train yourself to fly...
...in your ass because...
...squatting
on a glass table...
...two girls...
one cup...
You know what to do.
- This shouldn't take long.
- Well, I'll be waiting right here.
Hello, Mr. Bailey.
I've reviewed your request
for a loan, Mr. Riker,
but with no job,
no credit history,
I'm afraid
I have to say no.
But what about this?
That was last month.
This new promotion's
proving quite popular.
Look, I need
to buy a car.
Frankly, Mr. Riker, you're the worst
applicant we've ever had.
Thanks for the loan, Mr. Thompson.
This is a good boy.
There must be something I could do.
Ma'am...
rubbing my crotch under the desk
won't change my mind.
I'm not rubbing
your crotch.
I really need that car.
I don't see
how that's my problem.
This is a robbery! Nobody move!
Everybody stay down!
Stay down!
- Get down.
- Come on, Lady! Hurry it up!
- Oh.
- Come on, move it!
Oh, hey, I made the same mistake
before when I came in.
Thanks.
You idiot! You let him get away
with our money!
I don't see
how that's my problem.
- Oh, man!
- Wow.
Come over here!
You've got to see this.
Let me through.
Oh, thank God. I thought something
terrible had happened.
Well, an old guy did
get shot over there.
Uncle Albert! Just try to breathe.
I can't.
You're kneeling on my balls.
Oh, sorry.
Rick, listen.
With great power comes...
Great responsibility?
I was gonna stick
with bitches,
but if you want to be a virgin
for the rest of your life...
Uncle Albert!
My balls!
Very good.
Oh, God.
Mr. Landers!
Oh no.
Okay.
Hide the body.
Hide the body. Yeah.
Get in!
Yah! Yah!
Okay, I come back.
Jill?
I came as soon
as I heard.
- Where's Aunt Lucille?
- She's at home under heavy sedation.
They made her watch three hours
of women's basketball.
- This is all my fault.
- Rick, it was an armed robbery.
There was nothing
you could've done.
I could've stopped that guy
before he shot my uncle.
Then there is blood
on your hands.
But that's not important. All that matters
is that you're here for him now.
- Rick Riker?
- Yes?
Dr. Whitby.
I've run some tests.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
What is it?
I have an impacted colon.
Whew.
What a night.
Now what brought you
here today?
- My uncle.
- Your uncle brought you?
- No, he's gravely injured.
- Well, then he shouldn't be driving.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to perform a breast exam.
Doctor, please.
Is my uncle gonna survive?
Well, I don't know.
We should probably have a look.
Hard to say.
Yup, pretty deep coma.
Is he gonna be okay?
Well, I'm not a betting man,
but if you want to put some money on it,
- I'll take "dead in a week."
- Oh my God!
No, it's all right.
It's a normal emotional reaction,
but this should take
the edge off of it.
Here we go.
Nice and easy.
- That's your vein.
- Yes, I know.
First my parents and now this?
I'm nothing
but a screw-up.
Yes, your life has been
a testament to that.
But your uncle believed
in you and so do I.
It's never too late to become the person
you're meant to be.
Rick.
Hello, Rick.
Who are you and how
do you know my name?
- I'm a psychic.
- Prove it.
Think of any number
between one and a million
and I'll tell you
what it is.
- Nine.
- Not out loud, dumbass!
Follow me...
you dumb son of a bitch.
My name is
Professor Xavier,
and this is my school.
I started it
to help people
with special talents
like yours.
Our students here learn to harness
their incredible talents.
and use them to advance
the common good.
Ah! Ow.
Here we have children
who can walk through walls.
We have children who think they can
walk through walls.
Some faces may be familiar,
like Wolverine.
Other mutants you probably
didn't know existed,
like Sneezo.
Most of our students
are born with their powers.
Some, like you,
gain them later in life.
- Oh, is that...
- Yes, it is.
When he came to this school,
he weighed 130 lbs.
Take enough roids,
you could do anything.
Back up off those pills, Barry!
- Why have you brought me here?
- Because you have the potential
- to be the best.
- But I can't even fly.
Once you understand
the true nature of heroism,
you will fly.
But first I must teach you
the secret
to becoming a superhero.
Hey, Storm! You look
like you putting on a little weight.
Ah! Oh!
So, Professor,
about this secret...
- Well, you see...
- Xavier!
- Aw, shit.
- Well?
You wanna explain
why I found her hiding in your closet?
But, pumpkin,
I don't see nobody.
- Oh, you don't?
- Ow!
Invisible Girl?
Apparently not
invisible enough.
If you knew how to take care of your man,
maybe this wouldn't have happened.
- No, she didn't.
- Oh, this bitch is crazy.
I'm gonna have to
whip your ass.
- You don't say no disrespectful...
- What are you gonna do, baldy?
I'm everywhere,
sweet cheeks.
- Whoa!
- Ow!
- That all you got?
- Yeah!
Now what?
Now how about that, Invisi-bitch?
Yeah, whatever.
I'm out of here.
I'm sure gonna miss her.
She was crazy in the sack.
Biting, scratching, panting,
tongue all over the place.
Wasn't me, asshole.
Come on, Spanky.
I didn't even know
she had a dog.
Still some of the best
sex I ever had.
How could you do this
to me? To your kids?
To your newborn baby?
How do I know
that baby's even mine?
Because he can do this.
Shit!
Ah!
Aw, man.
Now I'm never gonna know the secret
to becoming a superhero.
You wanna know the secret?
Come close.
Make a costume,
shithead!
I swear to God. They get dumber
and dumber every year.
A costume.
Rick, you, uh...
Oh my God.
Damn!
Dude, you're like
a real superhero, man!
I love the mask.
How you breathe
in it though?
What's that sound?
You put some kind
of air intake in the mask.
Boy, you better...
now I'm assuming
that the material is
see-through, right?
Yeah, dude, I'ma tell you something.
Rick, this is good.
I'm impressed.
Like really impressed.
Hey, that's my spot.
You're sitting on my gargoyle.
Move it.
- Excuse me?
- What are you even doing here?
I'm looking seriously
out over the city
in a squatting position.
Well, that's what I do here.
So if you're not moving,
I guess we're gonna
have to share.
Uh, okay, fine.
I actually usually
perch in the front.
Oh, all right.
Well, here, you've got to go around.
- Okay, wait.
- Just turn this way. Here we go.
- Dude!
- You're right, I'm sorry. Relax.
- Okay okay.
- Uh, I can't perch like this.
- God, me neither.
- What's your name?
- John Storm.
Dragonfly.
So what's your power?
What's my power?
Stand back.
- Flame on!
- Whoa!
Huh?
I'm on fire!
Get a blanket or something!
Holy shit!
It's not working!
Get the fire extinguisher!
Ah! No! Ah!
God! You idiot, stop!
What's wrong with you?
Sorry, my bad.
Rick, once you understand
the true nature of heroism,
you will fly.
Shit.
This Dragonfly,
he's not even a hero.
He's not... I have... I have...
I have just a... I have...
He can't...
he can't even fly.
The Dragonfly
can't even fly!
I can fly, okay?
I can fly.
This just in:
Tom Cruise is dead.
World's most powerful man.
I have a feeling you might
disagree with that.
Strom, do you have
my test results?
Yes, sir.
Whatever you're doing
to your... victims,
rejuvenates you.
But only for 24 hours.
Hmmm.
What if I killed 28 people
in one session?
Would that give me
a month to live?
If it were February, yes.
But only if your cells
could absorb
that much energy at once,
and they can't.
I'm afraid
you have to kill each day
to live each day.
Still a slave
to the tyranny of time.
There must be some answer.
There isn't.
Unless...
unless you had
some cerillium.
Then you could create
a device powerful enough
to draw the life-force out
of thousands of people
and enhance your own
cellular capacity.
Strom, you're a genius.
Wikipedia.
But that's not important.
What is important is that you
don't have any cerillium.
Besides, it's immoral.
We don't do that sort of thing.
We're a pharmaceutical
company.
Wait a minute.
Take a look.
Hawking's lab is
in the physics building.
I could just
walk right in.
You're going
to steal cerillium?
No, not me.
I'm a law abiding citizen.
But perhaps there's
someone inside me.
Someone unfettered
by the rule of law.
Someone who will,
at any cost, survive!
Ow!
Oh, glass in my eye.
Glass in my eye!
- Does it hurt?
- Uh, yeah, it hurts.
Well, if you could spread...
spread them with your fingers.
Push your lids
with your fingers.
- Two... two... two fingers.
- Are your fingers clean?
That's it. And roll
your eyeball around.
- And push it.
- I'm rolling it!
Dig it out with
another piece of glass.
Are you fricking insane?
I'll get the tweezers.
Read about the Dragonfly,
world's greatest hero.
- Right here?
- Right here, yup.
Read all about it.
No, you listen to me!
I want that story
on my desk or you're fired!
Who the hell are you?
I was wondering if you've
got a job opening for...
Job?! How dare you come in here
and ask me for a job?
I'm the editor in chief!
I know the mayor of Venus!
Hamburgers can see
the future!
- Rosie O'Donnell...
- Sorry about this.
We share the building
with a mental hospital.
Bad news, boss. We're nowhere on
those Dragonfly photos.
Damn. Those were
tomorrow's lead.
What about these?
Wow! it's almost like
you're the Dragonfly.
Uh, no no no.
See?
Look.
Now that's photography.
Just heard on the scanner, some kind
of police standoff at Empire University.
We'll need photos.
Kid, I want you to...
Where'd he go?
Come on, let's go!
This is the chief of police.
We have the building surrounded.
Come out with your hands up.
What the hell is that?
I am the Hourglass.
And your time is up.
Get him, Dragonfly.
It's over, Hourglass.
No, Dragonfly.
It's just begun!
It's useless to resist.
I'll fight you
to my last breath.
Like the sands of time
I am unceasing and relentless.
Evil never triumphs,
Hourglass.
You'll pay for your crimes
and justice will...
stop!
Stop!
Are you okay?
No.
Titanium blades.
They cut through diamonds.
I'm not wearing any diamonds.
Ooh, ow!
Ow!
I wish I could stay longer,
Dragonfly.
But I just don't
have the time.
Whoever this Dragonfly is,
he's in over his head.
We don't need so-called
superheroes.
What Empire City needs
is more cops.
And a Hooters.
Titanium blades. Looks like someone
found your weakness.
It's not my weakness.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
Your weakness is you can't fly.
Maybe if you had a partner.
I don't need help.
I'm fine all by myself.
She means a lot to you,
doesn't she?
What?
Oh, no.
I mean, she's with
someone else.
Well, maybe
that's for the best.
After all,
it could be dangerous,
you know, being the girlfriend
of the Dragonfly.
I don't know what
to do, Aunt Lucille.
- I love her.
- So be it.
But remember,
to get to you
your enemies will attack
the people you care for the most.
Be careful not to hurt
the ones you love.
And shave your pubes.
No one wants to go down
on a tumbleweed.
Jill!
Rick?
I heard you were auditioning
for a part so...
Oh, they're beautiful.
God, you are so supportive.
Why can't Lance
be more like you?
There's something you're not
telling me, isn't there?
Something secret.
Something locked away
deep inside.
It was summer camp.
We had to share a shower.
You trip and fall with your mouth
open on one guys...
No!
I mean, in here.
Well, there is...
Keep your identity a secret, Rick.
Dude, you're like a real superhero, man!
Once a month
you'll bleed from you vagina.
I...
nothing.
Nothing?
Well, I should go.
You're a good friend.
Hey, check this out.
Oh, shit.
- Let's go.
- Get her.
Oh God, it hurts.
It hurts.
Please stop!
I'm begging you!
Wait!
- Where are you?
- Behind you.
You saved my life.
Do I get to thank you?
Go.
Be a hero.
Yeah.
It looks like you're planning
a mass murder.
Would you like help?
Paper clip guy.
I'm so happy that you
and your boyfriend
are spending Thanksgiving
with us.
Of course, Lucille.
You need support
at a time like this.
Yes, I miss seeing
my Albert each morning.
You know, 50 years
of marriage
creates quite a bond.
I wish I knew love
like that.
Oh, you will, dear.
You just have to
follow your heart.
That's the thing.
I don't know if I can.
Oh, Jill.
If you can't trust yourself
who can you trust?
I know.
But what if my heart
is telling me to be with someone
I can't be with?
It's not just any guy.
It's the...
forget it.
You'll think I'm crazy.
No, of course not.
You can tell me anything.
I'm very good
at keeping secrets.
You'll think it's
ridiculous, but...
it's the Drag...
- I'll get it.
- Thank you.
Hey, babe.
Oh, I forgot to tell you
I kinda invited my uncle.
- Your uncle?
- What? Set another plate.
Well, okay.
I guess.
Miss Johnson. Please,
excuse my nephew's poor manners.
- Thank you.
- Mrs. Adams, I'm Lou Landers.
I hope this isn't
too much of an imposition.
Oh, of course not.
There's always room for one more.
Thank you.
It's just Thanksgiving
is for family.
Lance is the only family
I have.
- I never married.
- Fruitcake?
Nope, just never met
the right woman.
Ah, yes, Lance told me
Rick Riker was your neighbor.
Where is Rick?
That's odd.
I thought he was out.
I'll go check on him.
Please, you're busy.
Allow me.
Thank you.
Upstairs, second door to the right.
Rick?
Hmmm.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, Mr. Landers.
Rick.
No, you're just on time.
Everybody,
take your seat.
Ohhh.
Ah ah ah!
Not till we say grace.
Jesus!
Amen.
Please start,
everyone.
This all looks
so delicious, Lucille.
We have Rick
to thank for it.
Ever since Albert...
Rick has been supporting me
with his new job.
New job?
You didn't tell me.
Oh well, I'm sort of the Dragonfly's
unofficial photographer.
What happened to your arm?
Uh...
a bike messenger
knocked me down.
I see
your wrist is bandaged.
Yes, I burned it
on some hot coffee.
And you have a cut on your lip.
Uh...
my crackpipe broke.
You have a scratch
on your neck.
Yes, I...
met a girl
on Craigslist.
And you have a bruise
on your neck.
I...
met a guy
on Craigslist.
I'm sorry, Lance.
We have to go.
- Why?
- I...
shat my pants.
I'll drive.
- Thanks for helping clean up.
- Of course.
Poor thing's so tired.
Yeah, well, you know
old folks after a big meal.
So... you know the Dragonfly?
Uh...
yeah, I guess.
You could sorta say
we're close.
Has he...
has he ever asked about me?
Um, yeah.
- Yeah, once.
- What did you tell him?
Well, I said...
I told him...
I told him, "The thing
about Jill is...
when you look in her eyes
and she looks back in yours...
- you know that
you'd do anything
anything to be a better person
than you are.
So that...
- if you were ever
lucky enough to be with her,
you could earn every second
of her perfect...
- grace,
and her limitless beauty...
- and her unending love.
- Don't cry.
- I'm not.
My eyes are burning.
Rick, I want you to know
that was the most
beautiful thing
anyone's ever said to me.
- Scented candle?
- Thank you.
Rick, I'm so confused, and yet...
- I know exactly
what I want.
Sorry to drop in uninvited.
It's okay. We were hoping someone
would open a window.
It was getting stuffy
in here.
So this is the lair
of the Dragonfly.
- How did you...
- No no no,
I'm not here to fight you. I've got
thousands of other people I plan to kill.
This little visit
is just to show you
who'll get hurt
if you get in my way.
Never!
Time to go.
The woman, Lucille Adams
of East Empire City,
- was badly injured.
- How was she injured?
- Badly.
- What about the Dragonfly?
All I can tell you is this:
he didn't save
anyone tonight.
Doctor, how is she?
I'm afraid your aunt's
taken a turn for the worse.
She can't speak, she can't walk,
she had no control over her bowels.
That's... that's awful.
I know. I went ahead and set up
a MySpace page for her
under "crazy shit machine."
She already has 40 friends.
Wait a minute.
That's somebody else's aunt.
Your aunt has no problem
with her bowels...
- Oh, thank God.
...because she's dead.
I'm truly sorry, Rick,
but there is a silver lining.
Your uncle came out
of his coma this morning.
He did?
Yes, but you mustn't tell him about
your aunt just yet.
He's in a delicate mental state.
The slightest bit of bad news
could send him spiraling
right back into a coma.
I understand.
Mr. Adams,
you have a visitor.
- Is it Lucille?
- No, sir, it's not your dead wife.
It's your nephew Rick.
Remember, no bad news.
Now, sir, here you go.
This is my bill.
- You did surgery on me?
- Yes, sir, we confused you
with one of our
sex-change patients,
but don't worry,
we didn't remove your penis.
We did cut your testicles off, but, well,
since your wife's dead,
you won't be
needing them anyway.
You just want
to keep his spirits up.
He'll land on his feet
in no time.
We are gathered today to say goodbye
- to Lucille Adams.
- Goodbye!
And now the eulogy.
It's tragic to think this is the last time
that I can look
upon my wife's face.
God, Lucille!
How could you take her from me?
I can't live without her!
Ahhh!
Lucille!
Snookie lumps!
I'm sorry, there's been
a terrible mistake.
- This is your wife.
- Ah!
She is this man's wife.
Give me five minutes.
- Uncle Albert!
- I'm not finished.
You're one lucky guy.
Now...
where's Lucille?
Ah, Lucille!
I do have this coupon
for a cremation.
Rick?
I am so sorry
for your loss.
What is it?
I know I said some things,
but now more than ever,
I realize...
we can never be together.
I don't believe you.
You love me, Rick.
I know you do.
Jill, trust me.
I'm telling you this for your own good.
I don't love you.
You're no longer
in my five.
How could you?
# When I was young #
# I never needed anyone #
# Makin' love
was just for fun #
# Those days are gone #
# All by myself #
# Don't wanna be #
# Anymore #
# All by myself #
# Don't wanna be #
# All by myself. #
# Anymore #
# All by myself #
# Don't want to be #
# Anymore #
# All by myself. #
You can't keep
getting lucky, man.
You only beat me
by two strokes this time.
And the back nine
is what killed.
Oh my God!
- Look at this place.
- Yo, what are you doing, man?
You gotta pull
yourself together, dude.
What's the point?
Look at you...
eating junk food,
wearing fake beards,
and we found your costume
in the garbage outside.
Yeah, well, I'm not
the Dragonfly anymore.
But you said the Hourglass
was going to kill thousands of people.
I told you I'm no hero.
All right? Aunt Lucille's dead,
I've rejected the only girl
I've ever loved
and I can't even fly.
I wish I'd never been bitten
by that stupid dragonfly.
And maybe your father
shouldn't have given you this after all.
Look at the words
your ancestors inscribed in that ring.
"Honor, valor, sacrifice,
duty, commitment,
bravery, justice,
integrity, brotherhood,
self-esteem, low prices,
affordable housing,
loose-fitting pants,
cheap internet porn."
The rest is in Latin.
Rick, the hero's path
is dangerous.
You may fail or you may fly.
All that matters
is that you do it
for the best of reasons.
Helping others, Rick,
that's what makes you
a real hero.
Maybe you're right,
but even if I wanted to stop
the Hourglass,
I wouldn't know
where to start.
I mean, where's he gonna
find thousands of people in one place?
Look.
Reporting here live from the
Empire City convention center
where thousands of people
are in one place,
but none of them
more important
than the attendees
of the World Humanity Awards.
I'll drive.
Well, that shortcut through the playground
sure saved us some time.
You go ahead,
I'll find
a place to park.
Mister, please stop!
Each year
the World Humanity Awards
are held to honor
the greatest achievements
on behalf of all humanity.
This gala event
is expected to draw
the world's most prestigious
leaders to Empire City.
- Excuse us, excuse us!
- "Empire City Times."
Damn! Look,
there go Prince Charles.
And Nelson Mandela.
Nelson!
Hey, I was
in jail too, man.
One of the guests here
is the Hourglass.
But which one?
Thank you so much
for inviting us, Mr. Landers.
Well, when you're being
honored by the world,
you want
your family with you.
Perhaps one day, you could
be part of our family too.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our first award
is for the medical
breakthrough of the year.
For his company's
pioneering work
in the field
of feminine hygiene
I award Lou Landers
douchebag of the year.
# Douchebag #
# He's the douchebag
of the year #
# Now ain't
he great, folks? #
# Ain't he grand?
The douchebag of the year. #
# Douchebag #
# He's Mr. Douchebag
of the year #
# Look at him smile,
look at him shine #
# He's the douchebag of,
the douchebag of the year. #
Hold up the douchebag!
Hold up the douchebag, sir.
Stop right there, Landers.
Mr. Riker.
So...
you know.
You're damn right I do.
Someone in this auditorium
is the Hourglass.
I need your help
to figure out who it is.
Now the Hourglass
could be anyone...
a guest of honor...
maybe even
a stagehand.
This may be nothing,
but I did see a man
with what looked like
a canister of
cerillium.
Who?
- This year's lifetime achievement award...
- Him.
...goes to one of the world's
greatest souls,
His Holiness,
the Dalai Lama.
This man isn't who you think
he is, he's the Hourglass.
No no,
I'm a man of peace.
Shut up! You're plotting
to kill all these people
and I can prove it.
Show the world
the armor you're hiding
under these robes.
You can't fool me,
Hourglass.
You're packing 10 lbs
of Cerillium under there.
- What?
- Ahh!
Take him down.
Tutu.
Peace!
Pea...
Shit shit shit shit shit.
You!
You're the Hourglass.
It's a pity you saw that,
my dear.
Perhaps this will help
you forget.
What are you doing?
Take me.
Hourglass!
- Hero con?
- It's a convention for people
who like to dress up
as their favorite heroes and villains.
- By the way, your costume sucks.
- Out of my way!
Excuse me,
there is a line.
No, you're killing him
all wrong.
It's like this.
Better.
Oh, shit.
Hourglass, you'll never
get away with this!
Forget it, Dragonfly.
You're too late.
Run!
Yeah.
Goodbye...
little fly.
Dragonfly!
- No!
- Ahhh!
My eye!
So, are you gonna
keep the body, or...
Eh.
Dragonfly, you must
stop the Hourglass.
I can't.
I can't fly.
If there is one lesson
my life can teach,
it is that the spirit
is stronger than the body.
The hero comes from within.
Those are
Celine Dion lyrics.
Whatever.
It's still true.
You're right.
It's working.
Sorry.
Watch, Dragonfly,
as your city dies.
Where... am I?
You're with me,
your lover.
Dragonfly!
No.
- No.
- Only now do you understand.
Oh, come...
Aha!
I need you to jerk this off.
Yeah.
There's not enough time.
Oh fuck.
- It's over.
- Dragonfly!
Jill!
Gotcha.
- Rick?
- You didn't think I'd let anything happen
to the girl I love, did you?
Well, we're still
falling.
Damn it!
If only I could fly.
Maybe I wasn't cut out
to be a hero.
You know, maybe I was meant
to have a normal job... an accountant,
a gym teacher.
- This is a really tall building.
- Rick!
I don't care
what happens anymore.
If I die, I die happily
in your arms.
You're my hero, Rick Riker,
and I love you.
Yes!
Oh, thank God!
We only have
50 stories left.
Hang on.
Thank you, Dragonfly.
Because of you, our city
is safe at last.
- You said it, Dr. Hawking.
- Shit!
It's a happy ending
for us all.
Let's go get some dinner. I'm buying.
Who am I?
I'm Rick Riker.
I'm the Dragonfly.
And as long as there's crime and injustice
I will forever be
a superhero...
I am the Hourglass!
# Darkness has found you,
evil surrounds you #
# No one to save you,
we're almost out of time #
# What do you do when
nothing can be done? #
# Where do you go
with nowhere left to run? #
# Where is the one
who stands up and tells you #
# I'm here to save you?
We're almost out of time #
# Nobody knows just who
he's trying to be #
# Behind this mask, his wings
and suit of green #
# Just in time to reach up
for the sky #
# And fly away #
# Don't worry you're safe #
# In my arms,
'cause it takes your love #
# To lift me up,
it's safe to say #
# Jill and I were always
meant to be #
# So I will show you why
I'm here to stay #
# Don't they know that
I'll protect you? #
# Don't they know
they'll have to get through #
# Me #
# Don't worry yourself... #
Your time is up!
# Watch out behind you #
# This is designed to #
# Quickly remind you #
# We're almost out of time #
# Somebody tell me what
he's trying to be #
# Behind his mask, his wings,
his suit of green #
# Just in time to reach up
for the sky #
# And fly away #
# Don't worry you're safe #
# In my arms,
'cause it takes your love #
# To lift me up,
it's safe to say #
# Jill and I were
always meant to be #
# So I will show you why
I'm here to stay #
# Don't you worry,
I'm the one #
# Who let's them know
that I'll protect you #
# Don't they know they'll
have to get through me? #
# Don't worry you're safe... #
# In my arms so green #
# It's easy. #
#I need a hero #
# I'm calling out,
I want you here #
# This is my 011 #
# I'm sinking down
into the fear #
# That I just can't outrun #
# To save myself
all I can see #
# Is that I've got
no choice #
# I cry for help
and pray you'll be #
# The one who hears
my voice #
# I need a hero #
# Someone to rescue me
when I'm in a mess #
# Whenever I'm falling,
someone to be my safety net #
# I need a hero
watching over me #
in my time of need #
# To fix it when
it's going wrong #
# To be big and strong,
you know that I need a hero #
# Waited my whole life #
# For someone like you #
# And I think it's time #
# For my dreams
to come true #
# If only you could hear me #
# I know you'd
be near me #
# You'll never let me go #
#Oh, I need a hero #
# I need a hero #
# Someone to rescue me
when I'm in a mess #
# Whenever I'm falling,
someone to be my safety net #
# I need a hero
watching over me #
in my time of need #
# To fix it when
it's going wrong #
# To be big and strong,
you know that I need a hero. #
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.moviesubtitles.org