Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[pen scratching]
[Man, narrating]
My wife likes to say
there are two kinds
of people.
Those chasing pleasure...
and those
running from pain.
[shallow breathing]
Lorelei Cranston is running.
Running from all kinds
of everything.
Probably has been
her whole life.
If you ask me, nobody
gets to escape their pain.
It's there when you
brush your teeth at night.
It's there before breakfast.
It'll come up,
fierce and sharp.
It'll lay on you,
blunt and heavy.
[bell dinging]
[horn blares]
The most you can hope for
is one good day.
'Cause on a good day,
you get to tell yourself
"I can fix this.
Today can be different."
"Today something
might change."
[ball game on TV]
[latch clicks]
Yeah?
Gary?
[squeaking]
[dog barking in distance]
[barking continues]
And then Mrs. Rodell
yelled at Anna and said
she'd had enough of her
last year in her class.
And Anna was like,
"Hello, I wasn't
in your class last year."
Well, it's a good thing
I didn't know any of this,
or...
What?
I got you a little treat
for doing so well
in trigonometry.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Trig's easy.
It's just memory.
God, I hope you don't
remember everything
when you get older.
It's not just because
you did so well in math.
I've got some news.
Come on honey,
sit down. [pats bed]
And how you take it
is important to me.
I've asked Gary
to move in with us.
For real.
Not just a couple nights
a week or whatever.
I-- I know it's only
been a little while,
but it just feels so different
this time, you know?
Yeah, it is different
this time.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Some people live
for their pain.
It's all they've got.
[clock ticking]
They stay up with it.
Afraid it might slip away.
People like me.
I would love to dream.
[alarm clock ringing]
But one way or another--
[ringing continues]
[ringing stops]
...I'm always awake.
[Man on TV]
Get back! Get back!
Oh, Dotty. Mmm.
[Man chuckles]
She won't let you go.
[both laughing]
[cooing]
[water sloshing]
[laughter]
[Woman]
You like that? Yes!
[Man] Look at that.
Look at that.
Whoo!
[clapping]
[dolphin barks]
[man, woman laughing]
Whoo!
Oh!
Aw, look at her.
She's really amazing.
[dolphin barking]
[gasps]
[woman laughs]
[dolphin barks]
[Woman]
Oh, Dotty.
That's a good girl.
[laughs]
My stars are
really nice this week.
They said, "Financial woes
through midweek
give way to--"
Oh. What's that word?
It means horns of plenty.
Eh, they're kind of
bullshit anyway.
Horoscopes.
No offense,
but kind of bullshit.
[scrubbing vigorously]
[water running]
[clicks tongue]
[scrubbing continues]
[Reporter on TV]
...confirming today the teen
will be tried as an adult
for the brutal murder
of his parents.
His case will be heard
in Buffalo City Court,
commencing later this month.
By contrast, Eric Komenko
committed the same crime at 15,
but prosecutors
chose not to try him
as an adult in this case,
citing high levels
of the antidepressant Zoloxia
found in his bloodstream
as a mitigating factor.
Komenko's sentence,
juvenile detention.
He is expected
to be released
this coming Friday
on his 18th birthday,
his record expunged.
Public questions about
Komenko's case remain, however.
Victims' rights groups
are protesting his release,
while members of Komenko's
Baptist congregation
are supporting it.
[girls laughing outside]
[bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter on walkie-talkie]
Komenko!
Lieutenant's here.
I can follow him,
be close by.
It's going to pay off
for us later on.
But I'm going
to need your help.
Anything you need.
All right, Brian.
Thank you.
[keys rattling]
[latch unlocks]
Mexico.
Cool.
I wanted to take Spanish,
but the teacher here
got laid off.
Spanish?
That could be helpful.
What's happening
on the college front?
I didn't want
to send applications
postmarked from here.
That makes sense.
So, you're going
to live with your aunt?
Yeah.
You don't think
that might be hard?
She said
she wants me there.
Antidepressants
messed with my chemistry.
The state even
testified to that.
I know. I was there.
Look, I did this evil thing.
But I know I can
put it behind me.
That's what
expunged means.
What do you want from me?
You're a psychopath, Eric.
You're going to kill again.
You know it,
and I know it.
And I want to prevent that
from happening.
And when I do,
I want you to know
it's going to make me
very happy.
It's the best thing
for you.
When you walk
out of here,
know I will be
waiting for you.
I got nothing else to do.
Thanks.
[bell rings]
I hope your wife
gets better.
[Man]
Let's go, guys!
Back to class.
Let's go!
I could get you
a magazine, John.
Sorry.
How about some pie?
Not tonight, Debbie.
[Debbie] Hi. Would you like
some more coffee?
[Man]
Yeah, a cup will do.
[thunder rumbling]
[chatter on walkie-talkie]
[bell ringing]
Come on. Let's move it.
[Man] We got five minutes
to clean this place up.
[muffled chatter]
[chatter on walkie-talkie]
Hey!
Get her out of there.
[Man] I got her,
I got her, I got her.
Open up!
[gasping]
[Man]
Psst! Komenko.
Shh, shh.
[chatter]
[muffled shouting]
[shouting continues]
[Man] Komenko!
[Man #2] Right here!
Here you go, Eric.
Good luck.
[reporters shouting]
[Man] Hey, Komenko!
Komenko!
[Man #2]
Eric! Eric!
[sighs]
You going home?
Not exactly.
Morning.
Good morning.
We're two early risers.
Yeah.
Come and sit.
Have some breakfast.
[clears throat]
Eric, you don't
have to pray.
Or only if you want to.
In this house, your spirituality
is your own.
I-- I do want to.
Okay.
[door bell tinkles]
This isn't a library.
Fuck off, Paul.
[humming]
A note from Lori
there for you.
Read it to me, sugar?
She's going to go stay
at Kim's for the weekend.
One of the girls from the store
is going to drive her.
In the quiet of a shadow
In the corner of a room
Darkness moves upon you
Excuse me.
Like a cloud
across the moon
You're aware
of all the silence
Of a constant
that will turn
[kissing]
Like the windmill
left deserted
Or the sun forever burn
It's okay.
[crying]
I'm sorry.
It was nice of you
to use a mint.
[crying continues]
And all the suffering
that you've witnessed
And the handprints
on the wall
They remind you
how it's endless
How endlessly you fall
So don't forget
to breathe
Don't forget to breathe
Just breathe
Wow. You look like
a real college kid.
You mind me
saying "kid"?
No.
Should I try that?
Sure.
- Here.
- Thanks.
So, the money
for the house came to--
Well, it's quite a lot.
I'll work for my money.
College
is a full-time job.
Just don't forget
who you are.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry, too.
Where's Battenville?
[Maria]
North of Albany.
Some random town.
That's cool.
I was-- I was going
to go to Albany
to look at colleges.
Maybe I could stop by.
[crowd chattering]
Um, where should we meet?
There's a place out here
called FunLand.
Please!
Let's go. Go, go, go.
[Man]
Can we get an umbrella?
[engine starts]
- A what?
- A ladies' choice.
They still have a cotillion.
Is that what
they're called?
Can you be here on Sunday?
Yeah, I think so.
FunLand. Sunday.
FunLand.
How about 5:00?
[dog barking in distance]
Hey, Maria...
What do you like?
[groans]
Fu--
What the--
[tires screeching] [honking]
Shit!
[tires screeching]
[honking]
I'm sorry.
I was just going to wait
until you stopped and then sneak out.
I needed a place that was dry.
I was going to go home,
but then there was this dog barking,
so I came in here.
Did someone
put you up to this?
No, of course not.
You were with the reporters.
No, I wasn't.
How old are you?
I'm 16.
[sirens blaring]
[gasps]
How old are you really?
- I'm 16.
- Get in front.
Your belt.
I'm so sorry.
This isn't how I thought
it would be.
[click]
I just wanted to--
Just stay quiet.
[police radio chatter]
Hey.
License and registration.
Was there a problem?
No, sir.
Just, um...
need to get
some sleep, I guess.
[clears throat]
Yeah, he had to work all night.
It's illegal
in the state of New York
for your girlfriend
to ride back there.
Yes, sir.
[sneezes]
Gesundheit.
Thanks.
Get home safe.
I don't think I've ever seen
a Chinese cop before.
[laughs]
No, I don't think I have.
I'm Lori.
Lori Cranston.
My real name's Lorelei,
actually.
But I hate that name.
I don't even know
where my mom got it from.
Have you ever seen
a Chinese cop?
I don't think
it's racist to ask that.
Do you want me to get out?
And then what?
You'll call the papers?
No. I guess my mom
will come get me.
But I'd rather stay.
Are you one of the ones
who wrote?
What? No.
Please. I--
I just thought
after all that time,
maybe you'd like
a girl around.
Just a friend.
We've met before.
You were outside
my aunt's house.
I don't mean then.
Look at me and think.
I don't know.
In a facility?
No. No.
I mean, I'm not all
Suzy Creamcheese or whatever.
[turn signal ticking]
But no.
[turns off engine]
Think you can find
your way home?
Take it.
You really don't
remember me?
No.
I didn't look like this.
Get home safe.
It was right before
your parents.
By the river.
I guess nothing ever happens
the way you think it will.
[locks]
[unlocks, locks]
[giggling]
[laughing]
I'm going to be gone
for a couple of days.
I got to look after
that Komenko kid.
Now this is where
you tell me
to keep my hat on.
And I tell you
I don't have one.
You'd laugh,
wouldn't you, baby?
Same old dumb joke.
Hey, can you think
of a nastier word
than "sneeze guard"?
I mean, it's this close to, like,
"snot window" or something.
Hey, what's this?
Um, I think it's curry.
Oh, cool!
I've never had it before.
Amen.
[coughs]
[sipping loudly]
God.
Geminis are indecisive.
About most things.
Not about
important stuff, though.
About important stuff,
once I make up my mind--
Do Leos ever do that?
Just, like,
go after something?
You still have
to tell me where we met.
Picture a river.
A girl wearing glasses.
[humming
"Do Your Ears Hang Low?"]
Can you tie them
in a knot?
in a bow?
Can you throw them
over your shoulder
Like a Continental
soldier?
Do your ears hang low?
Do your ears
stand high?
Do they point up
to the sky?
Do they droop
when they're wet--
- Hey.
- Hi.
You lost?
What are you doing
out here?
Just exploring around.
Do your ears hang high?
Do they point
up to the sky?
Do they droop
when they're wet?
Do they stiffen
when they're dry?
Can you semaphore
your neighbor
With a minimum
of labor?
Do your ears
stand high?
Anything?
You were just
exploring around.
You remember me?
Oh, my God.
Here you go.
Yeah, of course
I remember you.
You were the detective
on the case.
I was concerned when I
saw you at my door.
I apologize. I didn't think.
Why are you here?
Eric doesn't have
a parole officer, right?
No. No, he doesn't.
And I'm pretty much
retired, actually.
You know, actually,
I just had the weekend off,
so I thought I'd--
So you came down
to Lakewood?
I just thought
I would come down
and make sure his transition
was a healthy one, that's all.
Should I be asking
if your agenda
is a healthy one?
Yes, it is.
And I appreciate you
asking me that question.
I'm-- I'm sure it wasn't easy.
Can I ask you how, uh--
how you are with him here?
It's hard, you know.
When I was in the courtroom,
all I kept thinking was, uh,
thank God they haven't
called me to testify
because I'd have
to tell the truth...
about how our family
is damaged, so damaged.
We never talked
about anything,
and Eric just sat there
in the middle of it,
and my sister's, uh,
I don't know.
She was terrified
of the world.
This one and the next.
I'm not a believer
in medicating adolescents,
but my sister
had a teenage boy.
She had no clue
how to deal with him,
so she drugged
the feelings out of him.
Still, he killed his mom.
He said
he was going to Albany
to look at campuses.
I've been a teacher
for 14 years.
I have a pretty good sense
when a kid's lying.
Well, uh...
I might take a run up there
to see that he
checked in okay.
Thank you.
You have a very nice house.
You want to see something?
I got a lucky star tattoo.
Uh-huh.
This way,
if they ever superimpose
someone else's face on my body,
like, on the internet,
I'll know,
and I can really sue them.
You're a freak.
It's just ball point.
I got bored last night
and drew it on.
I'm pretty vanilla, really.
No tats, no piercings.
Did they let you listen
to music in there?
No.
I can teach you.
I know all the new music.
Here.
[Man]
He's gonna establish his kingdom.
He's gonna set up his--
[switching stations]
[rock]
There's a train station
in this next town,
so, uh--
...reach for you--
[radio shuts off]
So I'll give you some cash
for the train back to Buffalo.
But I just thought I'd
take one back from Albany.
Look, you're cool,
Lori, really,
but I-- I need to be
alone, okay? I--
I need to make
a fresh start.
Well,
aren't I a fresh start?
It doesn't get much
fresher than old Lori.
I'm basically a virgin.
That has nothing
to do with it.
I just need to stay
focused, all right?
When I find a college,
I'll send you my email.
We can write. Okay?
I wouldn't tell her.
I mean, really,
there's nothing to tell.
But if there were,
it would just be
what happens, right?
What are you
talking about?
Your girlfriend.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You were saying her name.
I what?
When I was in the back,
I wasn't--
I wasn't eavesdropping
or anything.
He just
kept saying her name,
like "Maria, Maria.
Hey, Maria."
Maria, Maria, Maria, Maria.
Maria, Maria, Maria--
Just stop.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to poke fun at you.
I guess I'm just jealous.
I don't know
what you think you heard.
There's no girlfriend.
Really?
Yeah.
That's cool.
I need to take a leak.
[braking]
I wish I smoked.
I kept saying somebody's name?
Maria.
Yeah.
You sure?
I was right there.
That's pretty weird.
Mmm.
Ahem.
[grunt]
Uhh!
[screaming]
Oh, God!
[screaming, coughing]
[screaming]
Hey, guys?
Eric?
[arrow is shot]
[choking]
No!
[thump]
[glass breaks]
[gagging]
[coughing, retching]
[door closes, distant]
[toilet stall door
closes, distant]
[toilet flushes]
It's a 1992
red Volvo 740.
740.
0319 Larry John Robert.
[Woman]
Do you want us to pick him up?
No, no. Don't--
Don't pick him up.
Just, uh,
just tell me
where he is.
Okay.
We're here.
Okay? If someone
spots him, let me know.
Okay,
we'll call you.
You have a nice day
now, John.
Okay, Hazel, I will.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Goodbye.
[car motor starts]
[Lori]
Eric!
Somebody
had to do number 2.
Let's go.
Those
are probably dirty.
You wouldn't say that
if you had one.
They're so fucking good.
Mm. Mmm.
We should get on the road.
[clatter]
[distant chatter]
Wouldn't you love
to go out on a boat?
I've never been on one.
I can't swim.
[laughter]
[deep inhale, exhale]
Why can't you swim?
Aren't parents supposed to
teach you stuff like that?
My mom can't swim,
either.
I lied before.
When I said
I was a virgin.
Maybe I am. I don't know.
Mom has always just--
been kind of a pervert magnet.
I guess she still is.
Gary just seems nice
because he's quiet
and he doesn't drink, and...
he acts pretty dad-like.
Mostly.
He took me
on this camping trip.
Just the two of us.
The bonding weekend.
He said since I got wet,
that was a sign I wanted it.
Friends,
to me it's spring
The windows show the same
Without you here
The seasons pass me by
I know you were not, no
It looked like May
in June
All the same, I miss you
Today has been okay
[humming]
Lori, you can't just knock
on someone's door
and ask for the bathroom.
Emergency! Hello!
Lori.
Hello!
Wow. This is so cool.
I wonder why they left.
We shouldn't be here.
Look.
They took seven photos.
[clicking film advance]
We should get them developed
and see what happened to them.
Here.
[shutter clicks]
What if these people
are, like, serial killers
and there are seven photos
of seven bodies in here
and then us?
So we get them developed,
and the cops arrest us
and we seem totally guilty
because of your record and all.
That would be freaky.
Let's get one together.
[shutter clicks]
Come on. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
No. One sec.
I got to freshen up.
Holy shit.
There's paper.
[sigh]
[twig snaps]
[ball hits pins]
Yeah-ha-ha-ha!
Yes!
Yeah.
You want to roll one?
No, thanks.
Bowling isn't gay.
I didn't say it was.
I'm just trying
to show you a good time.
I'm fun to have around.
Think of me as a dry run
for a real girlfriend,
somebody important.
Why do you say
things like that?
Like what?
Like you want pity.
I don't want pity.
[gutter ball]
Fuck!
Shit.
Okay. It's 11:30
in the morning.
You can watch your language,
or you can leave.
Hey! Can we get
a couple of beers?
So did you have
a lot of friends?
So no one visited?
No.
This cop.
He was a do-gooder.
What do you mean?
He was just too easy.
- Easy?
- Yeah.
Easy like most people
are easy.
Once he told me
about his sick wife.
From then on, all I had to do
was bring her up, and he'd go quiet.
This one time,
I called him a...
a small beans cop
with a vegetable wife.
His eyes got all watery.
But aren't most people
like that, though?
What?
Uh...
not easy, but soft?
It's gross.
What is?
That stuff.
It's gross.
What, people?
Isn't she soft?
Who?
The girl you never mention
because she doesn't
really exist
or we're not going
anywhere near her
because she doesn't
really exist.
The one
who's not named Maria.
Don't!
Eric!
Eric, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to freak you out.
I just--
Eric, wait!
I saw you kiss that girl.
That day by the river.
She was so--
so beautiful.
What girl, Lori?
The one you were with.
I wasn't spying.
What are you talking about?
Don't you even remember her?
[man's voice on TV]
[shower spray]
[Woman]
Oiga, no toque esto.
I thought you were shy.
You're not shy.
[operator] I have a collect call
from a Lori Cranston. Will you accept?
[Gary]
Her mom's not here.
I can talk to her,
but her mom's not here.
Look, we should just
get out of here,
keep moving.
Thank you.
[siren]
[siren stops]
Okay, we have a positive ID
on those plates?
Well, we'll check them
if not.
Are you the guy
from Buffalo?
Yeah.
Is that
a new flashlight?
Yeah. Oh.
Sorry, Lieutenant.
[motor stops]
You should check in
for us.
In the mind of this kid,
there's no violence,
no other will,
just a desire to take a life.
Pleasure of feeling
a body expire.
Feel its last beautiful
sigh in his hands.
He's addicted to
the intimacy of the kill--
the tenderness.
So that's the kid
they let out.
Yeah.
Not the Buffalo
I used to know.
[officers chuckling]
And they sent you?
Well, no, not exactly.
I'm pretty much retired.
They just give me
the easy cases.
You chasing
after this kid?
Kind of.
Alone?
Well, I got no family.
He's my hobby.
[officers chuckle]
Is it because I'm a freak?
You're not a freak.
You've said it before.
[scoffs]
You listen too closely
to every little thing
people say.
You remember stuff
you should forget.
You could do things to me--
things you want...
things you can't say.
Doesn't work
like that, Lori.
That day by the river...
there was something...
so...
perfect in that kiss.
Lori,
I never kissed anybody.
Yes, you did.
Not really.
Not like you think.
Let's go inside, Lori.
[gasps]
Just stay quiet.
Use your hands.
It's what I want.
[shuddering breaths]
Do it.
Dissolve me.
I love you.
[door closes]
[sigh]
[Man on P.A.]
Welcome to FunLand.
That's right.
Hey, kids, what's crazier
than a barrel of monkeys?
It's the Crazy Submarine ride.
Now open.
But you must be this tall to get on the
Crazy Submarine ride.
[continues, indistinct]
Balloons!
Come on, kids!
2 bucks!
Tell Mommy you want a balloon!
Folks, there's no line
at the Sky Sweep right now.
[people on ride screaming]
[chattering]
[Woman]
By the Ferris wheel.
Good afternoon, everybody.
Welcome to FunLand.
Please enjoy yourselves today
and tell all your friends.
Hey!
Hey. Hey, Maria.
Sorry I'm late.
I had to sneak away
from my mom.
It's pretty lame here.
No, it's cool.
I didn't come here
for the rides.
Should we walk around?
Yeah. Great.
[people chattering]
Now boarding,
the Dragon Coach.
So do you want
to go on a ride?
Yeah, I guess.
I like
the kiddie ones.
[chuckles]
Yeah, me, too.
[people screaming, whooping]
[Man]
Hey, wait up, bro!
Hi.
Are you from in town?
No.
I-- I should
keep you company.
You know?
So guys don't hit on you.
I'm 15.
So did you grow up
around here?
Kind of.
I mean--
It's a long story.
Tell me.
We move a lot--
my folks and me.
Uh-huh.
[Woman]
Whoo!
[bell ringing]
That was fun.
[Man]
All right. Everybody off.
That's it.
Off to your right.
Follow the railing.
Right there.
[Man on P.A.]
You must stay on the other
side of the yellow line.
Please don't put yourself
or anybody else in danger.
So do you-- do you want
to go on another ride?
We don't have to.
What do you want to do?
Be alone.
I know a place.
Follow the railing around.
Whoo!
[chattering]
Keep your hands
inside the ride at all times.
Thanks for coming.
[laughter]
[people whooping]
How about over there?
I like it here.
[Man]
Stop spacing out.
Oh, man!
[whooping]
Crazy!
[people screaming, distant]
That's really pretty.
[whispers]
Yeah.
[Man]
Here we go, bro. Hands up.
[Woman]
Whoo!
[Man]
Here we go! Here we go!
[Man #2]
Oh, my God.
[shudders]
Eric!
[Woman]
God! Oh, my God!
Eric!
[screaming]
[shouting]
Stop! Let me off!
Eric!
[riders screaming]
Get me the fuck
out of this thing!
Eric!
Is she
your girlfriend?
Get away from him!
She's a liar!
Get the fuck away from him!
She's lying to you!
She's a liar!
- It's a trap!
- Lori, you're crazy!
- Get the fuck away from him!
- Lori! Lori!
Get away from me!
Why would you come here?
Why would you follow me here?
We can see you!
- Why would you come here?
- Come out, you fuckers!
-Lori!
- Look! Look!
Cristofuoro?
No? Come on.
Let's go.
Stay where you are, Eric.
Stay where you are.
Step away from each other.
Step away!
No, you cannot
do this to me!
Shut up!
Put your hands on your head.
You cannot detain me!
You can't do this--
Put your hands on your head!
Kneel down now! Both of you!
Kneel.
Who the fuck are you?
Lorelei Jane Cranston.
- How old are you?
-16.
I have my parents' permission
to be here.
Eric, with your left hand,
empty your pockets.
Slowly.
Both pockets.
You can't detain me.
No, you're right.
I can't.
But I can detain her.
Nothing was going to happen.
Yeah?
What were you doing?
I know what you were doing.
You were trying to entrap me!
You were trying
to entrap me.
Stand.
Drop your hands.
From you, I'm going to need
a phone number. Come with me.
Stand up, pal.
[Cristofuoro] Well, can you get
her mother to call me?
When she can.
You do that.
[Officer] Get a statement from Eric
before we let him go.
[Officer #2]
Great. Wait up.
You get Gary?
[sighs]
Yeah.
[pen scratching]
Surprise, surprise.
Do you know
who this kid is?
Do you have any idea
what he's done?
He is not someone you can trust.
You understand?
Eric says you're a liar.
[car door closes]
I have to let you go.
But when I do,
if you stay with him,
there is nothing I can do
to protect you.
I can't even
have you followed.
So before that happens,
you're going
to hear me out.
That kid is a killer.
I know that.
Everyone knows
about his parents.
I'm with him
because I want to be.
Not just his parents.
He only killed them, because
they'd found out what he'd done.
I could show you
photographs of a girl--
Alicia Vargas.
A girl just like you.
She was breathing
and laughing and watching TV
and thinking she might like a boyfriend,
and now she's dead--
in the ground,
cold and dead.
And there was another girl.
She went missing
around the same time.
Sophia Tersa.
My guess is when
we find her body,
we'll find she went
just the same way.
Lorelei, Eric liked
Alicia and Sophia.
Just the same way
I'm sure he likes you.
He doesn't like me like me.
[sigh]
We're just friends.
If you're just friends, what did he tell you
he was doing with Maria?
What? Did he say he wasn't
going to hurt her?
Just hook up with her?
I know that bothers you.
It's my choice.
And I'm just trying
to help you make a good one.
He told me about you.
Told me all about you
and your sick wife.
You're just a small beans cop
with a vegetable wife.
[Officer]
Here you go, Mac.
[Officer #2] He's done, fellas.
He's going home.
Good work tonight.
When do I get to go home?
Just a couple more minutes,
and I'll give you a ride home.
What do you want
to do now, John?
I'm going home.
[engine starts]
[police radio chatter]
[thunder rumbling]
Lori.
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
You don't
owe me anything.
I was wrong.
You do owe me something.
[clanging]
It's cooler out here
than I thought it would be.
Mmm. Pretty much dead.
[bird cawing, distant]
You know what I smell now?
Lake.
Tell me I'm pretty,
Eric.
You are pretty.
Yeah.
[quietly]
But I'm breathing.
My mom has this tape.
And basically,
it's just this guy screaming
over and over,
"You have to want change,
you have to want change."
Nothing changes.
Nothing changes!
[water sloshing]
What are you doing?
Lori!
Stop!
Stop.
Lori, stop!
Aah! Fuck you!
No!
Lori! Lori,
give me your hand!
Give me your hand! Come here,
come here! Give me your hand!
Lori!
[coughing]
Take it!
Come on.
Please, grab it!
Grab it, please!
[gasping]
Lori!
[gasps]
[no audible dialogue]
[birds cawing, distant]
[crying]
[crying continues]
[bell ringing]
[door sliding]
[Eric]
That's it.
She just fell in.
And I tried to save her.
I didn't kill her,
Lieutenant.
No, I know you didn't.
I should get off this bus
and talk to the D.A.
on your behalf.
Here's the thing.
You do belong here, Eric.
I say we take this
any way it comes.
[knocking]
My wife wanted to say hi.
She wanted me to tell you
she's not paralyzed.
She might be fucked,
but she ain't no vegetable.
[door opens, closes]
[chuckling on TV]
[chuckling]
[Cristofuoro, narrating]
My wife likes to say
there are two kinds
of people.
Those chasing pleasure...
and those running from pain.
Maybe she's right.
I don't know.
What I do know is this.
Pleasure helps you forget.
But pain--
pain forces you to hope.
You tell yourself
"This can't last."
"Today could be different."
"Today...
something just might change."
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org