Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Synch by ShooCat
Good night t'ee
Good night Sir John
Begging your pardon, sir.
We met on this so same road to the day
and I said goodnight and you replied
"good night Sir john"
I may have
Did so again today.
So I did
Now, why call me Sir John
when I be plain Jack Durbeyfield,
the haggler?
Just a whim of mind.
I'm Parson Tringham,
by the way.
I've made a discovery about you.
I was tracing some family trees
for our new county history.
I'm an antiquarian, you know.
You Durbeyfield are directly
descended from the
knightly house of the d'Urbervilles.
Did you really not know that?
Really really... falsely
There's your head a little
so I can see your face from the side
Yes... that's the D'Urberville
nose and chin
trifle crosser and bold but still
in case my eyes
According to the Battle Abbey Rolls,
your line goes back to
Sir Pagan who came from
Normandy with William the Conqueror.
Living away in rough all these year?
Well I thought that you might
already know something about it
But t'is true
I've got myself an old
silver spoon at home and
graven seal which
i don't take much heed.
where do we D'Urbervilles live today?
You don't live anywhere
you lie buried in your family
vaults of Kingsbere-
sub-Greenhill, laid out in lead
coffins, with you effigies
under marble canopies.
do we have any family mansions?
Oh, you haven't any
no land neither?
none at all?
you had an abundance
of land in the old days
what can i do about it sir?
Well, as to that.....
can I do nothing?
nothing whatever
except possibly chasten
yourself by thinking
'how are the mighty fallen'.
Good night, Sir John.
what do you say to
a quart of beer with me sir?
There's a grand brew
in at The Pure Drop.
though not so good
as in Rolliver's.
Sir John D'Urberville.
that's who I am.
What is this?
T'is our club dance, sir.
But where are your partners?
They've not finished work, yet.
They'll be here by and by.
Will you join us till then sir?
with pleasure. But one partner
won't go far amongst so many.
One is better than none
it's sad working here when there's
noone to give you a squeeze.
what are you doing?
I've a mind to enjoy myself
Come on you two
what if someone sees us?
All rightyou go on.
I'll catch you up in five minutes
The nobliest in the county!
Oh lord... if it isn't your father
riding home in a carriage?
Hey! hey! The grandiest man
in the whole of Wessex!
Father's tired, that's all.
he only sent for the cart
because our horse died.
You know that very well.
Ah! I'm glad you've come.
Where are you off to?
I thought I'd change and help you.
We want to tell you what happened.
We've been found to be the
greatest gentle folk in the county
Rooting back long before
Oliver Grumble's time
Back to the days of Pagen Turks
With monuments and vaults
and crests and coated arms
and lord knows what all!
Is that why father made a
mommet of himself on that cart?
Our true name is D'Urberville
that's why he came home in style
not because he's been drinking.
where is he now?
T' was a Parson who told him
the pedigree of the matter.
Well where is he now?
Well to tell you the truth
he was that upset. He's gone off
to the Rolliver's to get up his strength.
not much strength he'll find
in the bottom of a pint pot.
Well, I'll go and get him
We'll be back before you know it.
now look be a good girl and
put the little ones to bed for me.
Now there's!
That?
The spoon may be small
but my family was great.
Jack, they've got a project.
We have a carriage, state,
mansions routing on...
Listen, listen to me.
Is there any money in it?
T'is well to be kin to a coach
even if we don't ride in one.
I've been a-thinking since
you brought me the news.
I've got a project.
Which reminds me, woman,
you better find that
damn seal of ours
or i'll do you a mischief
Listen, there's a great lady
by the name of D'Urberville,
living out by Trantridge
Yeah, at least nothing
compares with us.
younger branch of our family no doubt.
I'll wager that they don't go
back to king Norman's day.
That as may be but she's rich.
not a lot of good money will do us.
It could do. We must send
up our Tess to claim kin.
Claim kin?
Why should two branches
of the same family be
unvisiting too?
Certainly put her in the
way of grand marriage.
sure to go there tomorrow morning.
Let's drink to that.
Mrs. Rolliver!
Ah there you are my poppet.
We was just on our way.
You are asking me
to go up begging.
Begging? what are you saying?
T'is all in the family
If they was in need, I should
take them in, we all would.
WE all have to take the
ups with the downs, Tess.
now you must go and see her
and ask her for some help in our trouble.
If the lady were to receive me at all.
It would be enough if she were friendly.
you must not expect for her to help us.
oh come come my dear
your pretty face, you could
coax her into anything!
I'd rather try to get work.
Durbeyfield!
You decide. Now if you
say she must go, she'll go.
Now girl, do you want to go to visit kins?
Grandkins, Women-rows?
I'd much sooner not father.
There! she don't want to.
I don't like my children making
themselves spineless kids.
I am the head of the nobliest branch.
And I've got my pride to think of.
All this grobbling about your ancestors.
It isn't them who'll buy us a new horse.
It's all new
WEll my beauty?
What can I do for you?
I... I came to see Mrs. D'Urberville.
I'm afraid that'snot possible.
She's an invalid.
what was your business with her?
I'm her son.
It wasn't business, it was...
I can hardly say what...
not business, sir, no.
Pleasure, then?
No, sir.
T'is all foolish. I...
I fear I can't tell you.
no, no. I like foolish things.
Try again my dear.
I came sir, to tell you that... we
are of the same family as you.
Ah... poor relations?
Stokes?
No... D'Urbervilles, sir.
Now tell me. Do you like strawberries?
Yes, sir. They are in season?
Here they already are.
Our name has become
Durbeyfield but we have several
proofs that we are D'Urbervilles.
That's what the
antiquarians hold that we are.
So our mother said that we should
make ourselves be known to you
say we've lost our horse and
we are the oldest branch of the family.
I see... so
you've gone to pay me a courtesy
call, really, as one relation to another?
Yes, I have.
Yes, well. There's no harm in that.
I would rather take it from my own hand.
Don't be so coy, my pretty cousin.
Look up.
This one too.
It's the perfect place.
Believe me.
You'll look a regular bosie.
what's this?
A thorn.
Ah... is it? Beauty has its price...
I'm not very hungry
truly I'm not.
Nonsense.
You must eat
something before you go.
It's no near ride from
here to your village.
I shall see what i can do for you.
But listen, Tess, no more of
this D'Urberville nonsense.
Plain Durbeyfield. Understand?
It's quite a different name.
I wish for no better, sir.
In reference to your daughter,
and further to a visit,
we write to inform you of
our willingness to considering
engaging her services in
the managing of a poultry farm
of a modern character.
If after a certain suitable
period your daughter proves
satisfactory we should guarantee
you suitable accomodation and
a good wage. Your earliest reply
would be greatly appreciated.
So, you charmed them
after all, did you?
Let me see, the letter.
Who wrote it?
Who? Mrs. D'Urberville, of course.
below the signature.
Me? Manage a poultry farm?
I truly don't think I shall go.
Poultry.
T'is just her own way of
getting you there without
getting your hopes up too much.
She's going to own you as kin.
Ah! You see? This is it!
It's the same as ours.
Look at it lad.
A ramping great big lion
with a castle on top.
There's no denying it girl.
Mrs. D'Urberville recognised
her own flesh and blood.
she never even saw me.
Well you couldn't expect her
to throw her arms around your neck,
her being an invalid.
But her son made you welcome?
He called you cousin, didn't he?
I'd rather stay here with you.
Bye, father.
You are off then?
Yes. Goodbye, father.
Goodbye girl.
You are a comely site.
This young cousin of yours.
Tell him, being so come down in the world.
I would sell him the title.
Yes, I'll sell it. At a fair price.
Not less than a thousand pounds.
That's right tell him that
I'll take the thousand pounds.
WEll now I come to think of it,
He can have it for a hundred.
I won't stand on trifles.
Fifty. Twenty pounds, tell him
and not a penny less.
Family honour.It's family honour.
Now it's time to go.
I want to walk a little way with Tess.
So do i, now she's leaving
to marry our gentlemen cousin.
I'll hear no more of that.
Mother.How could you have put
such nonsense into their heads?
she's going to work for
a rich relation, my dears.
And help us earn enough
money to get us a new horse.
Oh mother.
I wish our Tess isn't going to be a lady.
Don't hold my arm.
Grab me around the waist.
Ungrateful little minx.
Why abandon me as
soon as you feel safe?
The danger came
from your foolishness.
I say what a temper.
When people are on top of the hill,
they have to get down somehow.
But never a gallop, surely.
Fancy being asked that by
a brave little beauty like you.
I always go downhill at a gallop.
You can't beat it for stirring the blood.
But perhaps you needn't feel so, again.
Perhaps not.
All depends. One little kiss
on those ruby lips
or even on that satin cheek
and I'd drive at a snail's pace.
Either one.
But they don't want to be kissed, sir.
Stop, stop.
Wait. I beg you.
Very well. Do as you wish.I don't mind.
But I thought you'd protect me being a kinsman.
Kinsman be hanged.
You are mighty sensitive for a village lass.
Oh my hat.
You look even prettier without it.
Come along now. Up you go.
No sir.
You mind my driving?
No sir. I shall walk.
But it's four miles to Trantridge, at least.
Well I wouldn't care if it were twenty.
You watch out for Dollop, the bailiff.
He's a devil.Not Mr Alec.
Spends half the time on horseback and
rest of it chasing the nights with us.
Heard his mother's a queer
old soul but no real trouble.
T'is mercy for us she's blind.
Mrs. D'Urberville's blind?
Stone blind.
Their real name is Stokes.
Who's that?
Mr Alec's father had the notion.
He bought the name of
an old extinguished family
to make himself look important.
Whatever are you doing?
Missus is waiting for her birds?
Oh quick, quick,
it's slipped my mind entirely.
Now you catch the Phena there.
And that one!
It's that one there and the white one.
So you are the new young woman?
Well? How are my birds?
This is Strut.
Doesn't seem so
lively today, does he?
He's alarmed being handled
by strangers I suppose.
And Phena? Ah... yes yes...
They are a little too frightened,
aren't you, my poor dears?
Never mind.They'll soon get used to you.
Can you whistle?
Whistle Ma'am?
Yes. Whistle tunes!
A little.
Then you will have
to practice every day.
I think a lot of my fowls but there are also
my bullfinches which you have to consider.
I had a young lad who whistled
to them very well but he left.
They've been neglected for days.
Master Alec whistled to
them this morning Ma'am.
Oh... him...
No art, no nature ever created
a lovelier thing than you, cousin Tess.
To see that pretty mouth
pouting and puffing away without
producing a single note.
T'is all a part of my work, sir.
Well, never mind. I'll teach you.
I won't lay a finger on you.
See? I'll stay exactly where I am.
Now you watch me.
Don't scrap your lips too tight.
Do it like this.
Blow gently.... gently.
Try.
No... no... try again.
Again.
There . You'll manage
splendidly now I've started you off.
Tell me Tess. Didn't you
find my mother a little... odd?
Why. I hardly know her sir.
WEll I'm not in her good
books at the moment.
But you should find her favour
if you treat her livestocks well.
So... if you meet to any difficulties...
don't go to Dollop, come to me.
Au revoir.
Don't you fancy a dance then?
I'm all tired. When are
you all going home?
Soon enough, soon enough.
WEll, my beauty. What are you doing
here at this time of the night?
I'm waiting for the others sir.
Not being acquainted with the road home.
I only have a saddle horse, I'm afraid.
Come along to the inn with me.
I'll hire a trap for us both.
Thank you but I promised to wait for them.
Very well. Ca m'est egal. Please yourself.
What's that creeping down your back?
WEll I declare... it's treacle.
You dare laugh at me, you hussie.
I can't help it.No more than the others.
Oh, you think you are the
queen of Trantridge, dont' you?
Just because your first favourite with him.
She never said anything.
Leave her.
I've worked two years
for your heirs and graces.
If I'd known what sort you were,
I never would have lowered
myself by sticking to your company.
I'll show you.
Hey there, work-folk.
What's all the row about?
Quickly, jump up beside me.
Out of the frying pan, into the fire!
Where are we?
Passing through the chase.
Chase? T'is out of our way surely?
This forest is one the oldest
and the loveliest in England, Tess.
Don't you think it is asked
to be seen on a glorious,
god-given night like this?
Yes ... but
No buts.
There's a good girl.
I'll be honest with you. I'm happy.
I'm trying to prolong the moment.
You were shivering a while back.
Now I can feel your warmth against me.
Are you still cold?
No. Not now.
I'll let my animal walk in a bit further.
He'll make better progress once he's rested.
Tell me. What feels of your parent's horse?
They have no horse.
They have. Since... monday last.
Did you?
Forgive me for having mentioned it.
I thought that they would have written to you.
I don't know what to say.
It's nothing. I knew how
important it was for your
father to have a new horse.
Really. It's you, he should thank.
I'm grateful to you, truly I am. But...
I almost wish you hadn't done this.
Yes, I almost do.
Is that a reproach?
Oh no.
T'is very kind of you, I'm sure.
I've been in torment since you came to us.
Then I'll leave tomorrow sir.
That is absurd. I don't want you to leave.
That's the last thing I want.
Is there no hope for me? None at all?
Oh, Tess. I'm dying for you. Can't you see?
Forgive me. Oh please, forgive me.
Are you hurt?
No. It's nothing.
You are bleeding!
Oh my god...
how could I have done such a thing?
It's me...
Don't be so foolish... open the door.
You'll force me to make a noise, Tess.
My mother has sharp ears. She'll hear!
Enough of this nonsense, darling.
Open up!
Why sneak away? Like a thief?
And at this hour in the morning?
nobody would have prevented you from leaving.
At least let me drive you home.
Unless you'd care to come back.
I shan't come back.
What are you crying for?
I was only thinking.
I was born over there.
Well, we all have to be born somewhere.
I... I wish I'd never been born. There or anywhere else.
You are absurdly melancoly, Tess. You can hold your
own for beauty against anyone. Queen or common.
I tell you that as a practical man who wishes you well.
If you are wise, you'll let the world get a clearer site
of that beauty. Before it fades. Why not make the most
of life? WE didn't fare so badly together, did we?
I was blinded for a while, that's all.
That's what all women say.
How dare you talk like that?
Has it never struck you that what all women say,
some women may feel?
All right, all right. I was wrong.I admit it.
Please, please, stop.
I should like to get down here.
I'm a bad lot I suppose. A damn bad lot.
I was born bad and I'll warrant that I'll die bad.
Listen, Tess. If circumstances should arise,
you understand, if you are ever in the least trouble,
least difficulty, just send me one line and you
shall have whatever you need, by return.
You really won't come back?
Goodbye my four months cousin, goodbye.
Tess!
T'is no use of her pretending she hates it.
And wishes it in the churchyard and herself besides it.
She loves that child of hers.
Poor little mite. He don't look right for this world.
Good evening, Durbeyfield.
What's your business?
My business? Whatelse but the child?
I've to baptise it before lord gathers it to his bosom.
What child are you speaking of?
All my children are baptised. You all know.
Durbeyfield. Don't play games with your mighty.
I don't play sir. I work! I work! Like a beast of a field.
You can tell the almighty that for me!
The baby's dying!
You ought to have been more careful.
Like it or not Jack that
child was born this year!
Not true.
Come to your senses!
For pities sake, let the vicar in!
He shan't set foot in this house!
Not over my dead body!
There's enough disgrace
on my name as it is!
The works of god have pity.
Have pity on him.
Send all your anger on me and
put all your mercy on my child.
My child!
I should like to ask you something sir.
Well speak girl, I'm listening.
Each of us share in your sad affliction, my child.
We are all members of the suffering body of christ.
My son was baptised.
Baptised? By whom?
By me... last night.
What procedure did you follow?
I woke my little brothers and sisters.
Made them kneel down to
pray. Lazaru, hold a prayer
book open, I lit a candle.
And then?
And I hold my child like this, over the basin.
Yes?
Poured some water over
his forehead. And I said,
Ibaptise thee, in the name of the Father,
the Son and Holy Ghost.
Did you make the sign of the cross?
Yes, I did that too.
It was allthe just the same
as if you'd baptised him.
In the sight of god, I mean.
Yes, my dear girl. It will be the same.
Can you give him a christian burial?
That's another matter.
Another matter? Why?
That would concern
village as a home,
not just the two of us,
you understand.
Would you do it sir?
Just this once?
I'm sorry.
I beg you! Please.
I told you. It's out of question.
Then I don't like you.
I shall never come
to your church again
Never! Never!
Mr Crick!
You here already?
We didn't expect you
till before tomorrow.
Just a step away from
here to Weatherbury.
Marlott sir. I come from Marlott.
That's even further.
Quite sure that you can stand it here?
T'is comfortable enough for rough folks.
But we don't live in a co-cumber frame.
I'm accustomed to that.
I used to know your part of
the country when I were a lad.
Good... right char...
Well you'll want a rest and a muscle of food.
I'd rather begin now. To get my hand in.
Ohh... come on... you must be famished.
No, Thank you. A little milk will suffice.
Oh well. If you prefer that... so be it.
Just what I hate. Haven't touched it for years.
Lies in my inwards like lead.
My thinking, we aren't getting all we should.
That's because there's
a new hand come among us.
I know it's happened before.
They do say that the milk, goes
up into their horns at such times.
Anyone would think we
were back in the Middle Ages.
I don't think we are making any progress.
Keep it gentle. keep it gentle, sir.
It's the skill that does it, not your strength.
So my aching fingers tell me...
Mrs. Crick is far too proud to
come a-milking with us and that's a fact.
Still, there's little enough worried
about.WE eat like game carts.
Know you'll like it here.
Mr Crick, he's a very kindly man.
Just fancy. he has his
own family pew in church.
Dairyman on the deck all the weeks
and on Sundays - Mr Richard Crick.
Who's that playing?
Mr. Clare?
Mr Clare.
Him that's learning to milk.
Angel Clare, he's called. Angel, t'is no common name.
He never says much to us. For is the pity.
Why? Does he scorn on common folk?
Quite the opposite.
He often makes mock of the old families.
It's quite simple.
He's a parson's son with a mind to be a farmer.
He's already tried his hand at the sheep-farming
and now he's learning dairy work with Mr Crick.
What does he hold against the old families?
He says that they are... they are war....
war mutants.
It's half of your soul trying to escape.
it's bread that's all.
No! Helping you sneeze, you are like the role you
throw away.
As I see it, no soul can be
mortally shared before he dies.
What if a man falls down in a faint.?
Well that's a different matter.
The spirit lives on there inside
you but you can not feel it.
We can sometimes make
our souls leave our bodies.
How's that then Mickey?
Only have to lie by some grass at night and
stare up at some great stars.
And stare at it with all your might.
And by and by you feel you are falling into the sky.
Miles and miles from your body which
you con't seem to need at all.
Tess! Why run away like that?
Are you afraid?
No sir.
Not of outdoor things. No.
But you have your indoor fears. Aye?
But I couldn't really say.
But the milk turning sour?
No
Fear of life in general.
Yes,
So have I. Very often. Life's a puzzle. Don't you think?
Perhaps. now you put it that way.
It takes no use.
It won't take it.
Visit the I shall have to
call on conjuror Trentle.
I don't say I believe in my
but if nothing else works I shall have to try at chance.
Somebody here's in love, i'll be bound.
That can cause its white curd.
Conjuror Paul.
He didn't have the knack of it when I was a lad.
It's a pity. He must be
feeding the worms by now.
My grandpa used to go
to Conjuror Minturm
Hunted owls for him.There's
no folk like him these days.
Somebody's in love I tell you.
What's the matter?
The blasted butter won't come.
Why's that?
To my mind...
How warm it is today.
I think... I better be out of doors.
Don't push.
He looks so sad.
What can he be thinking of?
Not of us. You can rely on that.
You are fine one to talk, lzz.
I saw you.
What did you see?
Just the other day.I saw
you kissing his shadow.
O... Here he comes again.
Dear eyes.Dear his face.
Dear Mr Clare.
It's terrible that he doesn't
want to wed any one of us.
Or likely that he'll ask us to milk
his cows for so much in years.
What are we going to do?
We shall have to take the Stonebridge road.
WE'll be late.
Do he go to church?
No no... never.
Wish he would.
You look like cats afraid of water.
Only on account of
our Sunday bests sir.
Very well. I'll carry you just as you are.
No, no, I'm far too heavy.
Nonsense, I could carry
all four of you at once.
Hold on to me. That's it.
I should put my arms around
his neck and look into his eyes.
There's nothing in that.
There's time for everything under heaven.
Time to kiss and a time to cuddle.
Shame on you lzz.It's a scripture!
I always read the prettiest verses in church.
If you help me, perhaps I could climb along the bank.
Oh Tess. I've gone to three courses
of this trouble Only for your sake alone.
She's angry.
She doesn't understand and
she'll kick away her bucket.
Forgive me my darling Tess.
I don't know what came over me.
There's only one excuse for it.
I love you.
Angel!
Hello Mercy!
Forgive me I didn't see you.
Forgive me.
Welcome home.
How are you?
Very well.God be praised.
You look radiant with health I see.
The open air probably.
Have you come to spend
the holidays with your brothers?
Are they here? I had no idea.
No. I'm only paying my parents
a brief visit to settle some urgent business.
Oh. Then I won't detain you.
I have my bible class
to take in any case.
Au revoir Angel.
Au revoir.
Angel! My boy.
I'm apologise father.
I had no time to warn you of my arrival.
Actually forgotten how to write?
With a pen. Remember?
I brought you some
common house delicadies.
Black Puddings and
a bottle of mead.
Black Pudding...
It's true. Your mother and
I have regretted hearing so little
of your news.
Why fare with him father?
If anyone wants time
with sheep and cattle,
if we are closer to nature...
Father, notsworth.
I'd like to remind you, Felix,
that university education
means nothing. Unless it
goes down to the glory of god.
It could also go down to the glory of land.
It can be in the second place.
Howfar have you got
with your apprenticeship?
It's drawing to a close.
What counts is spiritual cleaness.
Isn't that true, Father?
Too good together, my boy.
Father tell us that you intend
setting up your own account.
In what part of the world?
I don't know yet. In the colonnist perhaps?
Heaven preserve us.
It could suit the type
of forming I have in mind.
what colony?
The choice is wide.
Or I may settle in a foreign country.
Some places offer lands
to immigrants on very
favourable terms. Brazil for example.
One knows you will never see us.
Nothings settled yet.
I came here to discuss it.
That among the other things.
Shall we take a drop of good
Mrs Crick's delicious mead?
Oh forgive me . I forgot.
Strong drink is the root of all evil.
Take us into your confidence.
Is it something serious?
Not serious, but something
important. The truth is
son't you think it's time
i considered marrying?
Yes indeed my boy, yes indeed.
Your mother and I have sometimes
debated the same question.
Really?
And what sort of wife would you favour
for a budding farmer like myself?
Truly christian, god-fearing woman.
One who will be of help and
a comfort to you in all things.
The rest matters little.
You musn't hesitate, dear son.
Why hesitate?
To marry your heart's desire.
Mercy Chant.
She may be fond of over-
decorating the church and
flipparies and flowers,
scraps of lacys and so forth but
It's merely a girl's fancies. It will pass.
Mercy's a pure and virtuous girl.
Oh yes I know she's pure and virtuous.
But honesty compels me to
inform you that I have other plans.
Other plans?
Very much sir.
Mercy Chant appeals more
to you than she does to me.
I'm not disputing her merits
I'm only speaking of my own inclinations.
My dearest boy.
Angel.Please remember that
you are addressing your parents.
I'm aware of that.
I already know the woman I intend to marry.
Her name is Teresa Durbeyfield.
Father, Mother. I respect you both.
I also respect Mercy Chant.
And have no doubt
she'll find worthier husband with or
without your help. As for me,
my mind is made up.
Oh it's you...
Tess, I want to ask you this now.
Will you be my wife?
I love you with all my heart and soul.
I can not be your wife.
Don't you love me?
Oh yes yes...
I'd rather belong to you
than anyone in the world.
Forgive me. I can't marry you.
It was the good lord who put
this nice young person's in your way.
You must believe that.
But with respects to your question,
I tell you quite private but
very strong. On no accounts,
say a word about your bygone trouble.
Never a word, my girl. Least of all to him.
Tess. Why does the idea of
becoming my wife displease you?
I never said that. It would please me so much.
It's simply that I can not.
Why? Is there someone else?
Don't i deserve to know the truth?
Well?
Not now
When then?
Later.
But why?
I'll tell you when we get home.
You'll stop loving
me when you know.
Let me wait till then.
Londoners will drink it at
their breakfast tomorrow, won't they?
Yes but watered down,
in case it goes to their heads.
Strangers that we have never seen.
You saw me once before.
you know that?
I did?
You wouldn't dance with me.
It was at Marlott.
Of course!
That's incredible!
You remember now?
Tessy!Tessy!
Now my girl.
Yes. I may never again be
brave enough to tell my story.
Then get on with your precious story.
I was born at such and such place
and in such and such a year...
I was born at Marlott and i grew up there.
I was in the Sixth Form when I left school.
They said that I would make a geed teacher.
But there was trouble in my family.
Father was no great worker.
He drank. Anyway, my parents, they...
it was then that something happened.
Something which changed my life like.
They discovered
that we were not Durbeyfields
but D'Urbervilles.
WEll, go on.
WEll, that's it.
WEll the D'Urbervilles are an old family.
I know
On account of being of that
name my mother thought that...
I was sent...
-I had a...
-A what?
I was told that you hated old families.
Is that all the trouble?
None of that matters, Tess. Say you'll be my wife.
Say it, Tess. SAy it, my dear love!
Yes yes yes...
my health, my simplicity.
I'm a strangeness of my situation.
I perhaps lessen my fault.
But since I've committed it I am guilty.
I must be guilty.
Because the lord sawfit to take my child.
If what I have just written,
failed to pass my lips,
in your presence, then I have
repeated it a thousand times
in my heart. For it was the
fear of losing you forever.
For love of you,
Is hall conquer that fear
and bring you this letter
Once you are savoured Angel
you'll hold the rest
of my life in your hands.
I hope and I tremble. I love you.
Oh darling!
I've been assumed to put
an edge on my appetite.
I'm starving.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org