Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My name is David Kruipen.
"What is sacrifice?
What does it mean
to make a real difference?
Throughout my life and career,
I have straddled two worlds.
Increasingly I have become...
...respected.
Increasingly my books and
articles are published and read.
Increasingly I have been
embraced by policymakers...
...and referenced by bureaucrats...
...but today I realized...
...that I have...
...misguided myself.
Today I rediscovered...
...what I knew
when I was..
Young.
- Is that one on her forehead?
- I can't look.
Jesus Christ!
I know.
You said it was a tick.
- Um, I don't know if it was a tick.
- It's not a tick.
- It was a bug.
- It hurts.
I know, sweetheart,
but I need you to stay still.
Okay, it's just about there.
Hold on, hold on.Hold on.
Okay okay.
Okay, there, Doug,
do you see that?
- Jesus.
- What?
- See those hairs?
- Get the tweezers, the tweezers.
I want you to grab it. Honey,
keep your head still, please.
- Get back in so I can see it.
- What?
Get... Just...
Shit.
What do I do?
We have to do something
about the population.
- And what is wrong with the population?
- We have too many people.
There's way too many people
using way too much stuff.
That's why we have
global warming.
They will tell you
that we are on the verge...
...of imminent destruction.
The carbon dioxide in the air...
...is gonna turn our atmosphere
into a microwave...
...and we're all gonna burn and die.
What a load of crap.
I don't care what they say.
It's not a glacial meltdown
or anything like that.
For decades
we've been warned.
Global warming is definitely real
and it's potentially catastrophic.
I believe it's prophecy
being fulfilled...
...hard times that's spoken
about in the Bible.
Global warming is
becoming a religion...
...for some of these...
for some of these loonies.
Of course there's global warming
and of course it's man-made.
It's a hoax.
The melting Arctic will
reveal a frightening truth.
I don't think that people are
going to do enough in time.
We're on the brink of Armageddon.
Most of us will die.
The few of us who survive will be...
...living in a world like Somalia.
And what can we do about it?
make small sacrifices,
but the real ones that really matter...
- The world will change, I don't think.
- Ever.
What does it mean to make
a real difference?
...radical environmentalists are
clearly a legitimate terrorist threat.
When non-violent
methods fail to...
...change people's minds
quickly enough...
...well, we have to consider
other options.
- The time is now.
- We have a breaking story.
It's spreading quickly
and hospitals cannot keep up.
Thousands are violently ill,
hundreds dead.
There is complete chaos
in the streets.
400 people have died.
At least 10,000 are infected.
State troopers and the National Guard
were ordered to seal off all borders...
...as people
are trying to flee.
-When nature is the terrorist...
We're gonna... we're gonna die.
It's too late to do anything.
I'm gonna die,
I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna... Help me!
-One...
of the Horrors...
-The worst bioterrorism
we've ever known.-
Oh my God!
Help me!
Banks island Canada arctic
Late spring.
David!
A hundred pounds
underweight.
He must have traveled far.
The teeth... only two years old.
He probably tried to swim...
...off island, had to come back.
Not enough ice.
What's he saying?
He's saying get
the fuck over here.
What did you find, man?
What is it?
Manalu.
Pine beetle is
just one example...
...of the profound impact
global warming is having on the planet.
Truth is our way of life
is leaving the door open...
...to an infinite number of threats...
...equally as pernicious
as the tiny pine beetle.
We're not going to see an end
to this sort of horror...
...unless sacrifices are made.
And that's all for now.
Now as you know, a few
of you will have the honor...
...of joining the renown
Dr. Kruipen and his team...
...studying the impact
of global warming...
...on polar bears.
Adam Galen...
Frederico Fulce...
...and Ling Chen.
- Yes, Adam?
- I thought there were four
students going on to the trip.
So did I. Unfortunately
that is no longer the case.
Jesus Christ!
You know, we probably would
have been there by now...
...if you guys didn't have to, like,
put on four different bathing suits.
I asked you
to please not call me.
Evelyn, don't hang up.
It's important.
We discovered something.
I want you to come up.
I told you I'm not ready
to see you.
Can we please
just leave it at that?
Ev, I just...
I want you to understand.
You want me to understand.
That you couldn't even
make it to her funeral.
Evelyn, this is important.
It's important to our cause.
Look, Dad, it's not my cause.
It's your cause.
You're the one who chose...
Okay, so apparently people just get out
of vehicles when they're moving.
Everybody knows about
global warming,Congratulations.
It just really too bad
nobody really gives a shit.
Ev, I'll...
...give you all
of your Mother's money.
- No more monthly payments?
- That's right.
There are some students
coming up from Dawson...
I'll save you a seat.
Hey, Evy, get in the car!
Uh, I'll... I don't know.
I'll think about it.
- Get in the car!
- Dad, look, I have to go.
I'll think about it.
Could you hold on a minute?
- We're moving.
Calm down.
How can I communicate
with the world...
...when I can't even communicate
with my own daughter?
She's just angry right now.
She'll come around.
What?
Eight hours from bottle
to throttle, buddy.
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Someone named Ling called.
- Said she was running late.
- Thanks.
Sounded cute.
Hello?
Bart, I need your help.
Dr. Kruipen?
I can't reach Evy.
She can't come up.
Why?
Is everything okay?
Yes, everything's fine,Just...
make sure she
doesn't come up.
Okay.
Tell her that i'll send the
paperwork back with you.
Sure,Listen...
Did you reach Bart?
David, did you
tell them not to come?
To call for help?
- Yes, I did.
- Thank God.
Nuti is...
...he's much worse.
And I'm...
I'm not much better.
- Hey, nice chopper.
- Hey,Thanks.
- Where are you from?
- Dawson City.
- Where are you from originally?
One of you gentlemen want
to help her with her bags there?
Yeah. Here, let me
take that for you.
No thanks.
- Oh, hey, let me get that.
- Oh, thank you.
Thanks.
- Can I ride in the front?
- Yeah.
There you go.
Hop in.
Thanks.
Oh, shit.
Uh, just put your stuff
in the back there, guys.
- Evy.
- Hey, Bart.
Well... shoot.
You weren't supposed
to come up.
- What?
- That's what he said.
I was supposed to give you some
sort of paperwork when I got back.
So he doesn't even
want me to come up there?
I'm sure he's got his reasons.
You know what? I don't really
care what he says. I'm coming.
Uh... Uh... Evy?
Listen...
...that's going to put me
in a really tight spot, see- 'cause...
Sorry, Bart.
Yeah, you see, I kinda...
I promised him...
Okay.
Ground Control, this is Major Tom.
We're outta here, man.
This is Ground Control.
You're cleared for takeoff.
Did I hear that you're
David Kruipen's daughter?
Yeah.
No way. That...
it must be so cool.
Yeah, he's my hero.
Is it true that
when he was younger...
...he sabotaged a pipeline
that was blocking...
- Migratory caribou?
- I guess so, yeah.
Huh, sure has changed.
It's okay, buddy.
It's okay.
I'll wrap him in plastic...
...just in case.
Make sure it's sealed.
We need to protect ourselves...
...until we're ready.
Are you okay?
No.
Ready for what?
Edward, ready for what?
Look at that ice.
Yeah, she's breaking up
more and more every year.
It's terrible.
When are we gonna wake up?
It's not that easy, buddy, not when
people's lifestyles are at stake.
What are you
implying, Frederico?
I'm just saying that we can't ignore
the reality of what we're up against.
Somebody's got
to take responsibility.
Okay, sure, but what are we
really doing to stop it?
I mean really stop it?
Look at Kruipen. He's attacking
the problem from the inside out...
- Changing how people think.
- What if we don't have that much time?
Maybe the best way to change
how people think is to...
...blow something up,
you know?
Look at that ice down there.
That's melting fast.
What do you think?
Oh... You don't want to know
what I think.
Sure we do.
Honestly, I think that people
are incapable of change...
...and our days are numbered. Might as well
enjoy the place while we can.
See? That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Nobody's willing to make
any sacrifices.
There she blows.
There's no power.
What is that smell?
Smells like something
died in here.
Hello!
Dr. Kruipen?
Edward?
Why is there no heat?
Yeah, wouldn't the pipes
freeze at night?
They must be
out in the field.
There's no running water either.
The genny must be off.
I'm gonna go check it out,
okay? All right.
Hey, where you going?
The restroom.
Is that okay with you?
Well, now we know why
one of us got bumped.
Yeah, and she doesn't even
sound like she wants to be here.
Shoot.
Did you want a water?
No thanks.
I'm gonna go look around.
Ling...
...look, I know I can never
expect you to trust me again.
I made a huge mistake.
You are so full of shit.
What, a little makeup sex
in the Arctic?
Something to tell
your buddies about.
You know it's not like that.
Oh, really?Well, then...
why tell me this now?
I don't know.
You were so angry.
And I was scared.
Evelyn?
I'm looking for something
that belongs to me.
You don't really believe what
you said in the helicopter, do you?
What did I say?
About just giving up.
Bet your dad
doesn't think that.
You'd probably know what
he thinks better than I do.
My dad's in the oil business.
A few years ago,
one of his rigs hit sour gas...
...and the well blew out.
The gas blew downwind
and killed nine people.
I asked him how he could live
with himself and you know what he said?
"Plenty more
where they came from. "
Just part of the risk.
So now you know why
I'm willing to blow shit up.
You don't really think that
ecoterrorism is the answer.
I don't know.
But I want to do what needs to be done,
be there when the ball starts rolling.
There's a flashlight in the lab. We'll
need it if the genny doesn't start.
GunShot.
Pheeww.
- Man.
- Ugh.
Oh, that is brutal.
God, it stinks.
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
Hold on.
Don't get so close.
Oh my God!
Oh, shit, are you okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
Hello?
Yeah, we're in here.
Oh, Jeez Louise!
Not exactly my choice
of words, but...
...yeah.
Why do they have this
rotting bear in here?
- Oh.
- I don't know, but I need a picture.
Something just bit me.
What?
I think it's just a flea bite.
You're gonna make it.
Let's get out of here.
The stink is getting to me.
Evelyn, hold up.
I heard a gunshot.
What?
From out in the field
when I was filling up the genny.
Look, I'm sure it's nothing.
I just thought
you should know.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
My name is David Kruipen.
"What is sacrifice?"
Base station
to field station, come in.
Base station to field station.
Dad?
Dad, are you out there?
Evelyn?
Jane, could you please
put my dad on?
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here.
I don't want to discuss this with you.
Could you please put my dad on.
Evelyn, are the students
with you?
Yes, of course they're here.
Why wouldn't they be?
Jane, could you please
put my father on.
David!
They're here!
The students are here.
David! Evelyn's here.
She's on the radio.
She's at the base station.
What's going on, David?
Evelyn, what are you
doing here?
- So now you don't even want to see me?
- I do.
It's just... it's very important
that you stay where you are.
Where are you?
Everybody's waiting.
Please do what I'm saying,
just this once.
- What's going on?
- Just do what I'm asking you do this one time.
Okay?
Please.
Okay. Fine.
Good.
Why are they here?
- I don't know.
- What did you do?
You should lay down.
I'll be there in a minute.
The students are here.
Evelyn too.
What did you tell Jane?
Nothing.
I don't think she's...
...got the strength
to go through with it.
- I'll take care of it.
- I know.
- We're doing the right thing.
Jane?
Edward, no!
Any luck?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, they're on their way.
Good.
Everything okay?
I don't know. Why did he
tell you not to bring me?
- He didn't say.
- God, he's such an asshole.
It tears him up, Evy.
It really does.
Look, I know you're probably
still mad about the funeral.
But he did everything
he could to get there.
- I mean, we were snowed in.
- Yeah, I know.
You hear that?
Yeah, what is that?
It sounds like...
...homo sapiens mating.
I missed you so much.
I know you did.
A bug!
- Jesus.
- What?
It's a bug.
- It's just a bug.
- You don't understand.
It's something I've had since
I was a kid. It's a phobia, okay?
It's... it's a...
I can't handle it.
You never told me that.
It's not exactly
something I'm proud of.
All right?
Now come on, let's go.
Where are you going?
I'm not going to go sleep out there.
Okay, come on, you don't understand.
I can't stay here.
- Please come with me.
- It's okay, Freddy.
- I'll look after you.
- I can't stay here.
Okay? I'll be
in the other room.
What are you doing?
Somebody's here.
Bart!
- You guys!
- God.
I feel like ass.
Dude, your arm is bleeding.
Jeez Louise,
this ain't no flea bite.
- Ow!
- Stop scratching it.
It's flipping itchy, man.
Hello?
Dad?
Jane? Oh my God.
Help!
Somebody help!
What was that?
What's going on?
Ling?
No no, Ling...
Ling, honey, it's okay.
Ling, you'll be fine, baby.
- Who the hell is this?
- My dad's assistant.
Evelyn found her
in the helicopter.
Jesus Christ.
I... I thought
there was a bug.
- Uh-huh.
- It was just my zipper.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna try my dad again.
- Okay.
Oh, uh...
...sorry.
Base station
to field station, come in.
Base station to
field station, come in.
Dad, it's me.
Come in.
Dad, are you there?
Ahem.
Is she contagious?
I don't know.
She's burning up.
Might be pneumonia.
We gotta get her out of here.
She needs medical attention.
That's the best idea
I've heard in a long time.
This place is infested with bugs.
Ling's got bites all over her face.
We gotta get out of here.
I got this... it's a medical condition.
It's a phobia.
It's like a panic attack!
All right, all right.
As soon as light breaks,
we'll fly out to Sachs Harbour.
What about my dad?
Nobody's answering at the field station.
Something's obviously
happened out there... something bad.
We don't even know where
"out there" is, do we?
What?
Look, the ATV she came
in on has a GPS unit.
We'll get the coordinates for
the field station. We'll fly out there...
...and we'll see what's going on.
If there's an emergency,
we'll call for a second chopper.
Okay, sounds reasonable.
Guys, I'm sorry.
It's all right. Let's load everything
into the helicopter.
We'll come back
and we'll get Jane.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Where did you get
my dad's camera?
It was in Jane's jacket.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
There's no tape.
Okay, guys, come on,
let's get packing. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
- What time is it?
- About 3:00 a. M.
Jesus.
Holy shit.
What is it?
Oh, man.
- What?
- Take a look.
Jesus H Christ.
- What the heck was she thinking?
- That's a really good question.
What?
- Sabotage.
- Jane.
It'll take me a couple
hours to fix this.
You gotta be kidding me?
Can't we call another helicopter?
It won't take me that long.
Oh, whoa whoa.
What's that for?
Relax, it's just a precaution.
- I have to go.
- Evy!
- Where are you going?
- The field station.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
No kidding. What if this thing's
fixed and you're not back?
Honestly, what do we do?
Hey, that woman's really sick.
I don't think she can breathe.
Come on.
Oh my God,
oh my God.
Oh, Jane!
Jane, it's me. It's Evelyn.
Oh no.
We have to do something!
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry for what?
It's okay.
- Don't let them leave.
- Let who leave?
No.
Holy shit.
- She can't breathe!
- What can I do? Tell me what to do!
No, stay with me, please.
Please!
Jane, stay with me.
It's okay.
No no.
- No!
- No no no no! I wouldn't do that, no.
Better seal off the room.
Who knows what she's got?
Yeah, it's a good call.
There... there's some plastic...
...around back by the genny.
Yeah.
Come on, everybody out.
Now.
Just give me a minute.
I knew her!
Evy.
Oh, God damn it.
Hey, where the hell is she going?
I thought we agreed to stick together?
Adam!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?
That woman just died in there-
man.You Think about it.
That's her dad out there, man.
As soon as that helicopter gets fixed,
we're getting out of here.
Get the duct tape.
Let's seal up this door.
Evelyn!
- Wait for me.
- What are you doing?
I'm coming with you.
Why'd you stop?
Shoot.
- How is it going?
- It's worse than I thought.
Why didn't you say something?
We should be calling for help.
- I'm doing everything I can, okay?
- This is so fucked.
Dad?
Holy crap.
Is that a wooly mammoth?
Jesus, it's pristine.
What is it?
It looks like eggs of some kind.
Yeah, it looks like they're
thawing with the mammoth.
Oh my God,
did you see that?
That's impossible.
Isn't there that
species of frog?
Yeah, the-the... Um...
...the wood frog, its liver glycogen
converts to glucose...
...but, you know,
that happens over a winter.
This thing's gotta be what?
20,000 years old?
Yeah.
Dad?
Oh... oh my God.
- Who is that?
- It's Edward.
He works for my dad.
Dad!
No no no.
- No no no...
- Evelyn.
No, God, no!
- Don't don't, Evelyn!
- No, please.
- Let go of me!
- You don't want to see him like this.
- No no!
- Don't remember him like this.
It's okay,It's okay.
What am I supposed to do now!
It's not fair!
He's gone and I still hate him.
Ow, ohh.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I just had the most
painful piss of my life.
- Any idea why?
- What are you saying?
- Oh, little Miss Innocent?
- Oh God.
Who have you been seeing
for the past couple months?
Jesus, baby, I'm sorry.
I just...
Oh, I guess I'm just...
I'm scared, okay.
There's something
wrong with us.
Some kind of infection.
It's inside of me
down there.
What happened?
They're all dead.
Shot.
Jane shot them all.
Kruipen too?
Why would she do that?
I don't know.
Look, man, I don't know
what a "20" is...
I just know that we're
in trouble and we need help now.
I just need to know
where you are.
What are your coordinates?
I don't know where I am, man.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
- David Kruipen's research center.
- Okay, stand by.
Ling, are you all right?
Get out. Get out!
- Evy, what are you doing?
- I need to see her.
- This room is quarantined, Evelyn.
- Please!
Please, you have to trust me.
We need to see her, please.
Please trust me.
Please.
Oh God.
What is it?
- Eggs.
- What do you mean eggs?
Like the ones
from the mammoth?
What?
- Oh my God, did you see that?
- What?
- What happened?
- The bugs that bit Ling...
...they must be some kind of parasite.
I just saw one. They're inside of Jane.
- We gotta move her.
- We have to get her to the lab.
It's a separate structure.
Come on, use the sheet
to wrap her up.
What is it, Evy?
The bear's infected too.
There's more eggs over here.
I wonder how long they stay
in their larval state.
I radioed for a rescue helicopter.
We're getting out of here.
- How long?
- A few hours if the weather holds.
Oh, thank God.
What, Evy?
We have to call them back
and tell them not to come.
- Excuse me?
- They won't be prepared.
We have to contact disease control.
They'll have time to study this thing...
- And decide what to do.
- What?
- Evelyn, we have to get out of here.
- We have to be quarantined.
Quarantined?
Are you out of your mind?
Ling is sick in there. She's been
throwing up. We have to get out of here.
- Frederico, you don't understand.
- Hold on, hold on.
Maybe we're jumping
to conclusions.
I mean, we're just
students here.
She's not even a student.
They died out there
because they couldn't stop it!
They're dead?
Jane was trying to stop us
from getting home.
She said don't let them leave...
she was talking about the bugs.
- What do you mean?What bugs?
- Look, you don't know that.
We don't know what
happened out there.
- You saw the eggs in the mammoth, Adam.
- Mammoth?
Jesus Christ, would somebody please
tell me what's going on here?
There's a wooly mammoth
in a glacier melting out there.
It's full of eggs.
The same ones that are in this bear...
...the same ones that are in Jane, and very
likely, the same ones that are in Ling.
And me.
And Ling?
Fred...
...we think that the insects
that bit Ling...
- They're laying eggs inside.
- What?
They're some sort
of prehistoric parasite...
...that thawed in the ice
inside the mammoth.
This is so sick.
You guys are sick. Where would you
come up with something like this?
We have to contact disease control.
They'll know what to do better than us.
No no.
No no... Hey!
Where are you going?
Hey hey!
We could die here.
Hey, stay away
from the radio!
Don't. Don't!
- Put the gun down!
- I didn't have a choice.
I'm in charge now. Until the helicopter
arrives, I'm in charge!
What was that noise?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, it's just a scratch.
Oh, Jesus.
- Hey, baby.
- When are we going home?
Soon, baby, soon.
Jesus.
It's the same color as...
- As what?
- Maybe you'd be comfortable lying down.
- That's a good idea.
- Same color as what?
All right, put her
in the spare bedroom.
It's okay, baby.
You'll be fine.
You just need to lie down for a minute.
- Where's Freddy?
- I'm right here, babe.
- When are we going home?
- Soon.
Really soon.
It won't be long now.
Wait.
We need to seal off the room.
- What about me?
- Good question.
You guys need to see this.
What is that?
What do you think it is?
Oh my God.
Ohh.
Do you think they can get out?
No. But we need
to seal that door.
Okay.
I need to do
something about this.
Right now.
Bart, wait.
What are you going to do?
I doubt there's a chopper between
here and Dawson City this time of year.
They're not gonna
be here for a while...
...and I ain't got that kind of time.
If these things hatch,
they'll spread.
If that happens, I'm done.
If I can just kind
of get underneath...
...some of them.
If I can just...
It's starting to come off a little bit.
- Oh shit.
- Oh, Jesus!
No.
No no no,
don't look at me.
Bart, no, you'll lose
too much blood.
Okay, then...
...we'll burn them out then.
I don't see why not.
We'll just douse
the arm in gasoline.
How do you know if you'll get them all?
You'll have to burn it to the bone.
If you don't do it...
I will.
We have to be
more prepared.
Are you sure about this?
I don't even know if this is morphine.
The worst that can
happen is that I OD.
There are worse ways to go.
Go on, man, jab it in.
Jeez Louise.
There we go.
Oooh, a guy could
get used to that.
All right, man, do it.
Something's happening
in there.
They're hatching.
Okay,Okay,
here we go.
Adam, hurry!
This isn't right.
You can't just chop off body parts.
This isn't the way.
- Adam.
- Do it.
Adam!
- Adam, do it again!
- Oooh.
Adam!
- Evelyn.
- Oh my God.
Bart.
Get the bugs.
- With what?
- Try the bug spray.
- It's not working.
- There's a lighter... try it.
God, I can't stop it.
It's working.
I need something else to stop
the bleeding. This is not working.
I saw in the...
ATV kit.
Is he okay?
- The bleeding's starting to slow.
- Aw, he could go into shock.
Get his arm up.
We gotta put him on the couch.
Lie him on his back.
Okay?
Come on, come on.
There we go.
- Get some gauze and some tape.
- Okay.
Lie him on his back. Okay, wait...
put his feet up, okay?
- Put his feet up.
- Oh, fuck.
There we go.
There we go, buddy.
Got the tape.
We need some gauze.
Shit.
What the hell?
It looks like they knew
what they were dealing with.
Who?
Dr. Kruipen.
It's a vertebrate.
It's not a bug.
- So we're related to this thing?
- Yeah.
It says that the males are harmless,
except for they create the sores...
...that the females bore into
and then they lay their eggs...
...and multiply.
What are you saying?
If you're bit by a male...
...you might not necessarily
be infected?
Yeah, the eggs
are the only threat.
These tapes, they only
date up to yesterday.
We have to see what's on them.
We need to know exactly...
.. what we're
dealing with right now.
This tape's the most recent.
Where's my dad's camera?
It's with Jane's jacket.
But we put all that stuff in the lab.
- What the hell are you doing?
- We have to get in there.
You're not going back in there.
It's completely sealed.
You're just going to bring
those bugs back in here with you.
We need to get the information
before the helicopter gets here.
There might be something
in there that can help Ling.
Maybe save us all.
You get any bugs on you,
you're not coming back in here.
Evelyn!
Behind you!
Shit.
There's no fucking way she's getting
in here. She's covered in bugs.
- Back off!
- Let me out! Let me out!
No no!
There's... There's...
there's bugs on her!
Adam, step away from her.
Adam, step away.
There's one under my shirt!
God!
- What the fuck is that?
- Get it out.
Get it!
- It's fine.
- What if it laid eggs in her? Huh?
I got it. She's fine.
All right. Um...
...the rest now.
She's clean, Fred.
Drop it.
Take the rest
of your clothes off.
- Now.
- It's okay.
He's right.
Adam, I need you
to check me.
She's clean.
Okay.
I had to be sure.
Are you sure you
want to see this?
Of course.
I'm really sorry,
you know?
Whatever happened between you
and your dad, I know it must be hard.
The weather's cleaning up.
They should be here soon.
What exactly are you guys
trying to find on that tape?
I mean, they're bugs and they
eat people... it's that simple.
We need to know what's gonna
happen if the bugs get off the island.
What kind of habitat
can they survive in?
What are the odds
of this turning into a pandemic?
My dad would have
thought this through.
We have to get that
information back.
"Today I rediscovered...
...what I knew when
I was young.
Whoa!
One got out.
Somebody kill it.
Oh my God.
It's time to get out of here.
We have to get
to the helicopter.
It's the only safe place.
Everything else should be burned.
- Help me! Help me!
- Oh my God.
Shit, they're coming
through the vents.
- We've got to get her out of there.
- No, we can't.
- There's too many. It's too dangerous.
- We gotta do something.
- What's going on?
- The vertebrates... they're with Ling.
We gotta sedate her.
Get me some drugs, man.
Get me something to wear...
something protective.
Jeez, you almost fell.
You gotta loosen this.
It's too tight.
I can't.
Freddy!
Freddy, open this door, Freddy.
- Almost got it.
- Agh.
Help me, Freddy.
Oh, please,
you have them too.
Freddy, what are you doing?
She was suffering.
She asked me to.
She's still alive.
You son of a bitch.
I gotta sedate her.
Bart, wait.
It's okay, Evy.
- I got nothing to lose.
- No.
Evelyn, come on.
Come on, we've gotta go.
We need to make sure
everyone's clean before we leave.
I'm going straight
to the helicopter.
Anybody who wants to leave
can come with me.
It's just a precaution.
We're not accusing you of anything.
We just want to be sure.
Fuck that.
Frederico, wait!
You can't go in there.
I know why you shot Ling.
You're gonna fuck
this up, aren't you!
- Fred...
- Shut the fuck up, Adam.
Soon as the helicopter gets here,
she's gonna blow the whistle on me.
And that means I'm gonna
die with these fucking bugs in my dick.
I can't let that happen.
Please don't.
I'm sorry.
Dad?
- Dad!
- Kruipen.
Oh my God,
you're alive!
I'm sorry.
Me too.
I'm so sorry.
- Are you infected?
- No.
- You're shot.
- I'm okay.
Jane...
Jane died.
She sabotaged
the helicopter.
It's okay though.
We already called for help.
The whole place...
it's almost entirely infested.
Now the only safe place
is the helicopter.
We're gonna burn it down.
There's some gasoline
around the back.
- You should wait in the helicopter.
- I'll be okay. Go on.
Go ahead.
Bet you wish you didn't
get on that helicopter now, huh?
What?
He knew.
"These parasites were
discovered in a thawing glacier.
They are just one...
...of the horrors that will
come from global warming.
And so today I...
...prepare this statement...
...as I prepare myself...
...for the ultimate sacrifice,
the only sacrifice.
Though thousands will die...
...the threat will surely
be contained.
This video, too,
will surely be contained.
But the impact of both...
...will survive...
...spread through the veins
of the internet...
...onto the screens
of the youth...
...into your souls...
...into your spirit.
You will know the need
to sacrifice.
You will know
the time is now.
You were right, Evy.
No one cares.
May I have the tape, please?
Dad, please. Please don't do this.
There has to be another way.
Please.
People listen to you.
- You didn't.
- I only said that to hurt you.
You were right.
You've always been right.
We can change people's minds, but, Dad,
this is not the way to do it, please.
I'm getting on the helicopter.
Alone.
When the fear...
when it spreads...
...the people will know.
- You can't go.
- Maybe he's right.
How could he
possibly be right?
Dad, you were going to save me.
What about everybody else?
What about
other people's children?
How do you know how quickly
they'll be able to isolate it?
How many people
are going to die? Thousands.
Maybe hundreds of thousands.
Plenty more where they came from, right?
Please. Please don't.
I'm sorry...I'm sorry.
Dad!
No!
- No.
- The window... gotta go to the window.
Oh my God.
That's Dr. Kruipen.
He looks hurt.
Are you okay?
- I should take a look at that.
- No, let's go.
Hey, is there
somebody else in there?
Quarantine.
They're contaminated.
- Are you contaminated?
- No. Let's go.
Aw, shit!
Stop, he's infected!
Stop, this whole area's
quarantined!
- He's on the skid.
- If he gets in, we die.
- He's infected.
- What did he say?
This whole area's quarantined.
Something about the quarantine.
We've got to put him down.
We can't.
He's infected.
He's rocking us.
I can't stabilize it.
- Jesus Christ. Is he okay?
- He's not moving.
- We need to go now.
- What about her?
- She'll be okay.
- No.
No.
Hey, she's got a gun!
Get up, get up!
Aw, fuck!
Fuck!
Come on!
Oh my God, no, we need
to get you to the helicopter.
No, it's too late.
- No.
- It's too late.
You have to... you have to get your
father's notes. You have to warn them.
I can't.
No, I can't leave you here.
I can't do this.
Yes, you can, Evy.
This is it.
The ball is rolling.
This is the beginning.
No. No.
What is sacrifice?
We keep saying
we want change...
...but we just keep doing the same
shitty things every day.
And that's no justification
for what my father did.
Or what he tried to do.
A body! There's a body
over here!
But I want people to know that he
really did believe he was helping us...
...and he sacrificed everything...
including himself.
I have a pulse!
Come on, let's get
her out of there!
I used to believe that
people couldn't change...
...that all we could do was just...
...have as much fun as we could
before it all came to an end.
But now...
...now I don't want it to end.
All right, we're back and today...
...we're talking
about Evelyn Kruipen...
...daughter of infamous ecologist,
Dr. David Kruipen.
- Max!
- Now she's being hailed as a hero.
- Max, come on.
- She's on the front of every newspaper...
- And website around the globe.
- Come on, boy, let's go.
The Center for Disease Control
said this young woman...
...saved us from total annihilation.
Well, I don't know, Mike.
You're a bit of a conspiracy nut.
What do you think?
Well, callers, what do you think?
What is going to end
the human race?
A giant meteor out of the sky?
Are we all going
to starve to death?
Or is a tiny little bug going
to come and wipe us all out?
First caller, you're on the air.
I honestly think it's just more
global warming propaganda.
I... I think the whole thing's
just a marketing scam.
It's just another example...
...of how vulnerable
we are, you know?
You've got SARS, bird flu, AIDS.
It's just a matter of time
before the big one comes.
The End.
j2009
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org