Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
No emotion other than a golf may long
His own individual shape
I have always wondered if a butterfly
The security of its cocoon leaves ...
He realizes how beautiful
He become?
Of  sees himself still
As a caterpillar?
When I was a child, I knew the secret
Of a happy life.
Play according to the rules, work hard at school.
And if you work hard at school,
It is your reward ... More school.
And even more after school,
Then they give you the best ...
What life has to offer.
A job and money in a future ...
Filled with an endless hunt for more.
This is where I lived for ...
My happy life.
I benijdde those who never
At doubted. I ...
I had a way out.
The usual.
-- Certainly.
I have signed something which I hoped
That you can perhaps even to watch.
Is there anything on?
-- No.
Your reputation perfect.
And your shares ...
We can, you can, perhaps
You must invest more.
No, small amounts.
Keep it simply simple.
How do you do it?
Sometimes everything is risking the only choice
You use.
But it seems that you all
No any chance Ventures.
I was not talking about myself.
I am sorry, you are right.
They are all my things.
Do not worry that I meerij
On one of your shares, which I would never do.
I am not sure. I know
Sure that you never would.
So where does one change
Come ...
And how we recognize it as it happens.
She cried a question, she said: 'No, please
That hurts. "
I owed you one.
Back to that girl.
How is it with my nephew? They
By evening, so listen carefully.
This case is a real good trade.
Achterkamers and everything, so over
Kloten not around, we go inside ...
We do our bets, collect the money
And make us away.
The kontrolno is already within, he has the name
Of the winning horse.
And understand this well bastards,
The chances are eight to one.
That is certain. We meet
Down to seven hours.
And keep your heads close, certainly you dick.
Do not worry, it works out.
What is the name of the winning horse?
Butterfly.
Do you want something?
I want some money bets on Butterfly.
At the next race.
Can I use it?
-- Sure.
How much?
Ten, ten thousand dollars.
Wait, twenty.
What would you think of fifty?
Have you so much money for you?
Because if you do not, you can always
Borrow something from the house.
I have to see your driving licence.
Look even after this.
Vijftigduizend on Butterfly.
The horses at the fence.
And they are gone. Yello has a head start.
Alpha and Santana right behind him.
Followed by Shooting Star, Perpetrater,
Butterfly and Silking Accrow .
On the inside Alpha takes the initiative.
He is neck to neck with Yello .
Wait, there is Butterfly.
This is unexpected.
He passes  Alpha. Passeert Yello.
Butterfly goes to the leadership.
They go into the curve, it's Butterfly
Followed by Alpha and Yello .
My God, he is .
Butterfly goes down, and Alpha,
Also. What a terrible accident.
And  Yello is about the finish.
Yello wins.
How have you found here?
How did you ... I will talk to you.
It is a damned simple question.
Jobs you for the police?
-- No.
I tried just gambling,
That's all.
You wanted to gambling?
Nobody comes here because
They are a bit like gambling.
I am sorry, I did not want to run away.
I wanted ...
You have to gewed Butterfly.
-- Yes, that is what I have done.
You knew that kontrolno.
-- No, I ...
Lieg not against me. How?
Come on, you knew how,
Kontrolno that?
I hear my colleagues talk, and ...
I love butterflies.
What do you love about?
-- Butterflies.
I love butterflies.
He loves butterflies, the name
Butterfly is of the horse, so ...
He comes here and bets on
Kontrolno one.
Do you know why I want 'Fingers' call?
Hr. Park knows why they call me Fingers.
He came two weeks ago even though along,
Because he also wanted to gambling.
I did not want to run away, I came the money
Get for my sister. I was getting.
Lost, and instead of me to pay what
I think he is guilty ...
What does he?
He tries away.
-- I tried not to come away.
I swear it.
What is it with you? You come here,
A dumb mistake, what's next?
Should I now the bad guy,
Is that my job?
I can not for that damned opera, I must
To come here and the bad guy?
Do you think I like it?
-- I do not know.
Well, I think this is not fun, it
Guys like you ...
And you Hr. Park ...
You let me simply no choice.
You have a choice.
My sister has the money.
You have two weeks to give me the money.
Every day that you are too late, cutting
I need a finger.
Go somewhere you go?
You are in the pack.
No, I am not.
-- Sit down.
You walk away for Fingers, or not?
You have a nice house, a good job ...
Where you are good at, and you throw
It all away. Why?
Please, I do not know.
-- Why are you doing this?
I do not know. I was dumb,
I thought not after.
Why are you doing this?
-- I do not know.
Yes, you know.
-- No, I do not know.
Do you know.
-- I do not know.
Tell me.
Take it.
Toe but.
That is all I can give you.
What should I do with it?
I do not know anymore.
Sometimes it cut its total
A liberating experience.
Today, I see things in a new light.
I see the money to come here as
That every day.
I see the cameras that each movement
From me in the eye.
I see paniekknop which kasbediende
Press to the police to warn .
And when that button is pressed,
I know that ...
That the police no earlier than
About four minutes will arrive .
That gives me enough time, provided
Ontsnappingsroute that I already have planned.
That I have already, and eventually I
Tied a bag with money propvol ...
No one else will see it. But I
Know that there is .
Everybody stand.
Dude, that was stupid.
Is all well with you?
This is the police.
You are surrounded .
Will be shot if you
Suddenly moves.
Let your weapon, do
Your hands up ...
Course to the south and
Then to the roof.
Put your gun down there.
This is the last warning, get your gun
, Or is there on you shot .
Sir, can you tell me what's
You done?
I do not know.
-- Can you remember what happened?
I do not know. Tell me it.
As far as I could remember I have
I have never lost a battle.
Race.
-- I can no longer do so.
I fought not as big or I
Fast or in common was ...
I  moisture well because I future
Could see .
The problem with the future is that
Only in a piecemeal comes ...
As a reflection in a broken mirror.
After a while it was just like
A video game playing in your head.
Play it often enough, and you know
All the movements.
And therefore what the future
Written ...
I can not change.
And sometimes the things that you do not
Change can ...
Ending there that they get to you.
Fingers, he listens to you.
Talk to him, please.
I have seen what's going to happen with you.
Nothing can change that.
It is done.
-- Well, I want you pick up someone ...
At the airport.
-- I know it.
My father, the home affairs
Good for each other, but I want the world to see.
My uncle Fingers, wild
The family. The wealth sharing, you know.
You know how he is to that nickname Fingers
? People do something for him ...
He just put on his fingers
To be cut, that's all.
Great nickname.
Just with his fingers cut.
My uncle is cool, but I am here
Only one thing.
Kutjes.
You know what I say?
I want to fuck tonight.
I heard that my favorite uncle
Here.
How are you?
-- How is it Tony? Good to see you.
That is the nephew of the boss.
That is damned big.
What kind of person is he?
-- Can express themselves well.
Did my men ensured good for you?
-- Yes, we are going to the city.
A young man must refresh its oil.
Listen to me ...
Your father wants you your virginity that I
Let lose, you show how it works.
There is enough time to use your dick
To wave, but we must make time for ...
Affairs.
-- Exactly.
No running joke, okay.
Would you take Tony tonight on your rounds?
The city show, show what we do?
Beginning with his training.
Him company.
Sure.
-- Good then.
Stay out of trouble.
Think of the last time.
Adrea No more, I swear it.
-- It is now funny.
Do you get away. Go out,
I have things to discuss.
I can see you later.
He is a damn problem.
Make sure he is not in trouble.
Perhaps he still learns something.
But now it's time for business.
You can listen to.
What do you think?
-- It is good.
Sorry? It is damned amazing.
What are you talking about?
I do not know a lot of music.
A customer of mine, which are debt
Paid to me ...
A portion of the deal
Was its management's contract.
This is her first CD. The sale,
Increases through the roof. Many promising.
I am sorry, I can still
Not follow.
How long do we do this already?
Too long. I am tired of order behind
The money to hunt.
I am tired of lessons to nietsnutten
Learning, which do not want to pay.
I have always hoped for more.
For us both.
This girl is our way up.
I am sure that it is evil, if they
Discovered that I am her new manager, but ...
Count because I do it.
Let you but her.
What is it? What do you see?
Nothing.
You see something.
-- I see nothing.
What do you mean?
Did they have no future?
It does have a future,
But I can not see.
You do not talk much, huh?
Too busy to think of the future
I would bet.
My uncle has told me that you
The future can see, and so forth.
He says, the money, the casinos
The stock market. You know everything.
Do you know where that reminds me?
Have you ever seen that movie, Krull?
Since that plays Cyclop in ...
And it is so, because he is an eye
Had exchange for the future.
But a long story short ...
Came the evil warlord
Deceived that bastard ...
And the only future that he could see
Was his own death.
Man, that was zanie.
What's the plan tonight?
Are we getting something to drink first,
Or is it immediately ...
To the pussies.
-- Tonight we work.
He's not.
Come back next week but.
He is in the hospital.
There is a mole removed by him.
Come back next week.
Do you like that, baby?
I have told you, next week.
No, you will now pay old tart.
Otherwise we go into the bunch
Still a little verkloten.
Dude.
Why you helped me, I
There was sewn by Moby Dick.
What do you think, we go back?
Shall we die together trut rams?
Where did they damn well?
I am not.
Are you at the bleeding?
-- I do not know.
Sta.
Let me give you even more time.
I come back next week.
I want to see the money you have.
Or make sure the Fingers.
Because if he does not get,
He takes one of these.
You do not want to.
I see you next week,
I am sorry of the message.
Let's go.
I have never seen such thing.
Verdomde cold ruthless junk.
You knew that there was trut.
How's that? What do you see?
Enjoy you?
People so to beat each other?
Sometimes hear that work.
-- Yes, but you enjoy it?
I think you do.
I think you do in life.
Yes, it is done. Otherwise you do foreplay
The lottery, and that makes you here.
I can not.
How come, that you can not? You are
As a man who does what he is like.
I can not do that because it is not
Shown to me.
At the time that I see,
I go by.
So you can ...
You can launch any girl fuck, and you know
Sure you are not sewn.
Safe sex is something great,
I have heard that at least.
That is my dream there.
Let me exactly where something like this.
Music, chicks that fuck each other, while
Another brill to my balls sucks.
Why are we not first
Go afterwards?
It has a lot with him,
As an old man.
Hello, boys.
It is fine for you to see.
As always.
This is Tony, nephew of Fingers.
-- Hello, how are you?
I love you uncle, he is a lovely man.
Have you had anything to drink?
I have a bit of a program ...
Got a flat?
-- Enough time to stay.
That can always say, but I know
It is not true.
Whatever you want, ask for
Just about.
Follow us but.
-- Tony is not so easy.
Let us clothes off.
Where is the room?
That old man there ...
-- He and his men were regular customers.
They do not share their pistols.
Has he a gun?
-- He alone, nobody else.
You pay for the protection
Of Fingers.
That is worth every cent.
You know that you are always welcome
To stay.
I am not a hostess more,
Just as I do that themselves prefer.
Can you do something for me?
-- Everything.
Say that I am against Tony after my rounds
Come back.
Sure.
If you can see the future,
So you think that you can change.
But you are only a witness
Of the moments that are going ...
Not in a position to help, even though
Would you want to.
And maybe you do not.
Sometimes you think that you assumed
Is something to learn.
About  patience or remote storage.
But at the end, it all
About discipline.
Things  see that you do not always want.
And  through.
After a while, the things easier.
Routine ensures that you do not
Wanders into your head.
You start to accept things
As they are.
Every man has his fate.
You can not escape,
Even if you see it coming.
Come on, baby.
Come on, rot.
You are in the wrong room.
Touch me not to damn.
Come on, that you should not do.
-- Tell me what I should do.
We had just as a fun time ...
So go away.
Quietly.
Give that damned pistol.
You are wrong, this is not my fault.
Let that damned pistol.
It is not my fault that gun
Just went off.
Then there is nothing for you to worry about it.
-- Do not closer.
I use this damn ga
Backwards.
Do you shoot all of us?
I have done nothing.
What should we do, you have the gun.
-- No, no massacre today.
What did you damn plan.
After a while, there is that effort
When you know that it's going to happen.
We look at people
Moving slightly intention .
Or is it like to watch a movie,
When you know how it ends?
And then something happens that I
Will never forget.
I am wrong.
For the first time, the confidence
A detour.
And I see a glimpse of something strange
And new.
A future where everything
Can happen.
It is something good.
And the feeling that it gives me ...
Comes closest to what
I have ever felt ...
With pleasure.
Sir, can you tell me what
There with you happened.
I do not know. Tell me
It.
That's my boy.
I appreciate what you Tony
Already.
How is it that you do not
Have to see.
Do not worry about it but.
Make sure you just better.
You have to go back.
I need you.
The boys who have done this with you,
I shall account checkout.
Nobody treats my boy Sun,
Nobody.
Chaos, rubbish, panic on the streets.
Your work here is done.
Thanks.
Do not worry. The pussies will
Surely in the row for you.
Girls like scars.
Just as a road map
For the soul.
It is a new day, and I have no idea
What I should expect.
I can change someone's life
If I do sense in it. The worse.
Of  better.
That, I know.
A girl with a future that I do not
Can see, my life.
On the same day that my visions me
For the first time in the lurch left.
There are people who believe in coincidences.
But I am not one of them.
This is old cake, he.
Every ten minutes there will be another boy
Like me, you the same questions.
That belongs to my work.
I promise you that I will try
To make it interesting.
For me it is a question to ask,
That nobody else.
Nobody? -- Nobody.
-- You must trust me. It seems to be good.
You are loved.
-- Forty seconds. -- Included.
Frank is here.
-- Where?
What does he.
-- It must be your agenda.
Trista, thank you here today
Wanted to come with me.
I do everything for you.
Your first album, which gives you weather
As a great new talent.
Is there pressure? Try you to the excessive
Media attention to compensation.
It is not excessive media attention,
I am not just a pretty face.
I have something to say, and I am so
Excited that my fans want to hear.
Okay, but what difference you and with all those
Other songs beyond?
I think it is my musical influence.
If you go back ...
What I mean is, you are young,
You are beautiful. I see you dancing ...
Why should we care that something can?
I mean, what's yours
That is so special?
What makes me special?
-- Yes.
Nothing.
-- Nothing?
Bedoel you, what makes me better
Than all the others?
No, not better, but ...
Why you earn that?
Why do I do that?
What do you say here?
-- What does he?
She is doing well.
-- I call it K.P.A.B.
Almost nobody has that.
That is the gift of God.
That, and I sing and dance well enough,
Millions of fans with them.
It is something of hundred thousand more.
What else.
That makes not much difference.
I have fans who call my name
I also Ga.
Come on, Trista. They do not call
Even your real name.
Right?
-- What?
I mean, can you at least we
Not even your real name?
That I will never tell.
-- What do you think of my name?
We have each other now met three times.
Three different interviews, you say ...
Everything you do for me.
What is I?
We are ready.
Quietly, what is the problem?
What do I do? -- You.
That bastard will be on Thursday,
By the time I am finished with him.
Bring me home.
-- We have that, we have a meeting.
Take me in your leg?
Do not worry, it's studio at ten.
It will be soon.
Well, let dad on his wonderful Fingers
Blue eyes.
That man has nothing against you, child.
Fingers, what do you think.
Lives a dream, or not?
You have destroyed my broadcast, Frank.
It is a pleasure working with you
To meet.
Fingers, that's cute. Should I now
If you ask why they call it?
I think that if I use talk
I already have my hands a lot.
You are Trista, right?
-- Yes.
Now we are friends,
We are down to business.
Of course, Trista things go great ...
Be rotated singles, albums
Start to sell ...
The video is often broadcast, but there is
A big difference between a video on MTV ...
And between an artist whose headlines
Say that they are nice.
As Frank says, is that someone you need,
You to the next level.
Someone who opens doors.
Someone who is strong.
You resigns.
-- No, I do not resign.
I would step aside. A person
Its influence can be a superstar yours.
He asks for things, and people give
To him. Please.
I love to work with you.
I am totally committed to me your success.
And the only thing I ask is,
You can bet for me.
That is our appointment, that is our promise
We make each other.
When someone our way ...
Then I rule that.
-- I believe this damn not.
Line a car for me. -- Trista, baby.
Fuck you, Frank.
That was not so good.
-- That went very well.
Tomorrow we enjoy shopping.
You are still under contract.
-- Rot with contracts.
I think I go.
Can you continue with her?
I am back tomorrow.
I am tired.
-- Yes.
Do you love me, Danny?
-- Of course I do that.
I also love you.
Remove the light at?
I do not like the dark.
The girl is not nervous, do you?
Do not worry. After school
I am here to wait on you, okay?
Your friends will not help
You know that?
No one will help you.
Nobody, but I do.
Your manager has all your accounts
Leeggehaald for me to pay back.
And that little piece of paper, which is
That you are the property are ...
Is the only thing that prevents
That he remains alive.
And what does that mean? That means
You have nothing.
And you are nothing, until I say.
And you are on tour ...
And you still travel,
Until I see profits.
And if I should ever come back,
We have a totally different conversation.
Understand you me?
Proost.
Do you not think you have had enough?
No, I think it is hardly enough.
It may not be as bad as you think.
You must be tired from it, to name
To have no idea of what you talk.
Where was you actually, when Frank
Me at the sewing?
Did you?
Hielp you him?
No, of course not.
I am your girlfriend.
Remind you your ...
How much it pays again
For my girlfriend to be?
Alison, wait.
Who will pay for the drinks?
-- I referred to it not the case, come on.
Alison, wait damn. Come on.
Are you Trista? -- What?
Are you Trista? -- No.
Yes, you do.
-- No.
Can I get a signature.
-- Sure.
For Jake 'the hotty. "
Trista, my sister loves you.
-- I love your sister.
You were great last.
-- Thank you.
That hurts, damn.
-- Another photo.
Take a picture.
So I can leave?
-- Sure.
What are you going to do?
Where will you go?
There will be something to overcome.
You are now Fingers his possession.
He will do you edit you are exhausted.
Jou throw away, which is what he does.
What imagine that I must do.
Fingers If you know that the legs,
He will come after you hunt.
The only place where he will not come
Search, is here.
I can see some money together to get ...
And then you can go far enough away with it,
Fingers can even order not to deal with them.
Why you help me?
I do not know.
That let me just disappear.
As long as I can remember ...
I myself have never let something ...
Want.
Stay away from windows, and ...
Suit but all you need
From the kitchen.
Tap nothing else.
Is all well with you?
-- Yes.
I am doing fine, it's just work.
What have you done today?
I have searched for you.
I like what you here
Already.
For us, as we here for a while.
Who's that, in this picture
Together with you?
Sparky.
Were you well with each other?
-- Yes.
That we went, it is ...
He died.
What happened?
I saw it coming, and ...
I could do nothing to halt.
I know how that feels.
It feels as if you never
Will be something like ...
Feel.
Therefore, I have more scars.
You know that the road map scars
To the soul.
It's been a few weeks ago, I thought
Perhaps we could make a ride?
Tomorrow?
You go away?
-- Yes.
What do you have in your hand?
-- Nothing.
Something that I think that I have seen.
It's not what you think.
-- What should you do?
Do not worry about it.
It is for a friend.
With whom I speak?
Piece shit.
Three weeks, we are already looking
To that slut. Three weeks.
Rondvragen, heads together,
You at my side ...
And all that time she was here with you.
You would think that for you to death
Abandoned impaired idiot ...
That you had shown some mercy to those
Poor bastard, and had told me the truth ...
But no, you stood there and looked.
You are a cold my friend,
A damned cold.
What is this? Do you have something to put aside
Your little lady to take along on vacation?
Is that yours?
I thought it not?
Leave me alone.
What's going on with you?
In the past you had seen it coming.
You lose the feeling.
Say you anything against me?
Are you trying to say something to me?
You put me in this situation.
Do you think I am a bad guy.
I will talk to you.
I am not a bad guy.
I want what everyone wants.
I try everything.
What happens? What do you benefit?
That was not enough for you.
That was not enough, you wanted more.
You have all the love of the world,
But that's not enough for you.
So you took my friend, and put him
Against me. And then?
You self piece of shit.
I think ...
That you do not know what's for you
To be about.
Tell me ...
What should I tell you?
Your real name.
The case is closed, you must skirt.
-- You must let me inside.
You do not understand.
I am a doctor.
You have to the front.
-- There is somebody dead. I must Trista.
I must Trista.
Come on man, I am a doctor.
If she dies, it is your fault.
Everyone has a purpose.
Sometimes someone lives his entire life without
To know what his own.
I do not. I knew it when I was ten.
My goal is to the right person
To keep sacred and accurate.
When I was ten, was one
Heidi Fontell .
But when Heidi's father with his family
Was moving ...
Knew I sure am back of someone
Went. And fast.
I was wrong.
I met Gina when I
Studied medicine.
We were best friends.
My roommate Henry said,
That the kind of girl she was,
You waited to get married.
But, I waited too long.
She married Henry immediately after school.
And I was the witness.
And all these years later, I think
That I still am.
Where were we stayed.
Henry tried a clear position
It.
About that you would go with him
The plastic? -- What else?
Bob is rich.
That is not true.
Derrick studied almost impossible.
And Derrick is strontrijk.
It is not all about money.
You stop it in time, you are doing the work.
Since you want to be compensated.
It goes well with me.
-- It goes well with a lot of people.
It goes well with her, that's where
She is the waitress.
Anyone else I know, strontrijk.
-- I do not.
You argue ingenious research. What a day
Leads to a great discovery.
And that leads to patents, and then
We talk about very rich.
There is nothing wrong, if they live
Of people trying to do better.
No, it's great. Therefore I also love
Hers. I make people's lives better.
That I do. Okay, I admit it.
Work on tits and botox
That pays for my great car.
Consider this view. A girl is born
With a nose on the ground that you can finish.
There is no date for the eindfeest
For this girl. None shy first kiss.
She comes into action, and of course
You lapt her fine.
Eventually this girl wrote a farewell -
Letter to her cat, and jumps from one roof.
The same girl comes to me ...
I use a little magic, and my friend
That letter will never be written.
I have saved her life.
I have saved a life today.
Maybe I have also known,
You know it but never.
But anyway, I sleep tonight
In a damn big house.
I must urination.
My husband.
-- Your husband.
How is it with the snakes?
-- They are great.
The times demolish me very much.
-- Feel you yourself?
Exhausted. I fight against a cold.
-- I wish you came to me tomorrow.
I would not bother you.
-- That is impossible.
That lets you know right?
Make good for yourself.
Think about what I said.
Ga you in that direction?
-- I parked at the back.
Is it well with you?
-- Yes, I am used to them.
I love you.
-- I also love you.
Bring me the dossier.
You will cure haemophilia, small boy.
This is not ratelslang.
Want tool?
Do not worry.
What we have to do?
-- A slangenbeet.
They gave us the wrong antidote
. They must now have a transfusion.
Gina, can you hear me?
Now awake. What?
What did they?
-- I am not sure.
Something about her blood. See what
Blood for it.
Well, tell me about that snake.
-- You do not understand.
It's been in her heart, she
Has a transfusion.
Send me now that blood.
-- It has twenty-four hours.
Here is the blood.
What is this on?
-- The lab says it is extremely rare.
Do we have this in stock?
-- I have never seen here.
Check again.
Do it simply.
Has Gina something of her own blood
In stock?
Listen, it is bitten.
Look again, it's very rare.
She is too weak, it is too late.
We have not, I
The checked into the computer.
We have her blood.
What do you mean?
-- Wait, you understand not.
You need to let me go.
You understand it is not, it goes dead.
It is good. Let me go.
It is fine with me.
I am here directly from the studio
Palm Hills ...
Where Trista began with the recognition
Half of its music.
We may not bring within,
In the actual recording ...
But while we wait, watch
We still agree to a recent interview ...
Which everyone wondered, pop superstar,
Or pop collapse?
What makes me special?
-- Yes.
Nothing.
-- Nothing?
You mean what makes me better,
Than everyone else? -- No.
Not better, just why you deserve that?
-- Why that I earn?
I have a special blood.
What do you think of them?
A blood?
-- Yes, it is called K.P.A.B.
Almost nobody has that.
That's my gift from God.
I have spoken with the director, and said
No more than two pictures for that song.
Is it good?
Do you need some air?
I think you need some air.
Can anyone please go backwards,
She has some air.
I believe it. Reverse.
Do this about.
-- What is going on?
Your plane ticket and passport are
In the pocket.
The gate is closed, you have to the front.
-- You need me admitted.
Wait.
Call nobody.
Keep your gedeisd a while. Give me some time,
I make sure that someone you can achieve.
I am a doctor.
It goes damn death, and
It is your fault.
It goes damn dead.
Trista, wait.
-- No, step.
I have shifted your performances,
And your video recordings will be cancelled.
I am not angry with you, even though I know ...
That you tried away.
But I am not angry with you.
If you wanted to tell me?
What should I tell you?
-- About the Baby.
Am I pregnant?
-- Three weeks.
Did you not?
It seems to be good, I know
What you were trying to do.
Do you think the whole world you love?
It is a damn dangerous life.
You can not only do, I go for
You. I make sure it happens.
All your dreams will come true.
For that to be put aside, it would mean
That he died for nothing.
That would mean that you him
Have killed for nothing.
No, we have an appointment.
He stood in the way, I have done my part.
Now it's time to do your part.
We have a special someone
Lost. Now is the time to proceed.
I hate you.
Until the day that I will be dead,
I will hate you.
You can not keep the baby.
-- What?
You have concerts and TV appearances,
You can not keep the baby.
It is my baby.
-- Nobody is our way. Nobody.
You have about two weeks a concert.
Enough time to be here with handler.
I will make arrangements.
Wait.
You need me EUR.
I need you.
You have saved a life today.
-- You are the.
It's funny ...
If only that one little part,
And all the rest ...
I am glad that it goes well with your baby.
Me too.
Thanks that I could borrow.
I bring you back as soon as
As I can. -- Does not matter.
Is all well with you?
Yes, it will be good.
It's hard, a fresh start.
You are good.
You too.
Thank you.
I am sorry Sir, you can
Not inside.
Sir, you do not have permission.
That was stupid.
Is all well with you?
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org