Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
There's a personal file.
Do you mind if I open it?
No, sure. Go ahead.
Ti amo.
So you'd better ask that kind,
nice husband of yours to translate.
He's got very delicate little ears.
He's dreaming
about his favorite things.
He's dreaming about...
a world without any weeds.
Justin Quayle,
it's time to get up.
Go away.
You're very annoying.
Time to get up, Justin.
Get up.
This is really just not fair.
It's time to get up.
Tessa, just let me sleep.
There's gardening to be done.
Weeds to be pulled out.
Good morning.
Come back to bed.
Oh, sweetheart.
Moral dilemma, Ham.
And the person that I most
want to tell can't be told.
I had a creepy love letter today.
It's not your fault.
From a five-star creep.
You've got to move on, huh?
I've cold-bloodedly led on.
I stole something from him.
And worse,
I made him a vile promise...
that I have absolutely
no intention ofkeeping.
Oh, do come in.
Yeah, please. Of course.
Thank you.
You lead the way.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Take a left.
I really hate to think how
it would hurtJustin ifhe knew.
I've violated his code, Ham,
in the most cynical way.
And the end
thatjustifies my means?
I need this creep to help me
blackmail Her Majesty's government.
Please tell me I'm not a ruthless bitch.
Please tell me thatJustin
would understand ifhe knew.
If you give me the wrong answer,
then I will push you into the Tiber...
like I did when we were 16.
Ciao, my darling.
Thank you.
For what?
For this wonderful gift.
How very generous of me.
No,I..
Here, Justin, put this on.
I like it here.
This is where you work from?
Mm.
Amnesty.
Won't make any difference.
That's the official line
of the Foreign Office.
I thought you were like that.
I thought you were one of those
privileged revolutionaries.
- My lady.
- Am I?
These plants, If they were children,
you'd be prosecuted.
I do water them.
When I remember.
You say you're all into saving lives
around the world,
but you let your poor plants die.
I say put people first.
Why don't you water them?
You're being cruel.
I feel safe with you.
I can imagine when you were six.
You leading the revolution.
Ham? Hi. It's Justin.
Listen.
Do you still represent that
dodgy client in Amsterdam?
Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry. I only just got it.
Directions for use.
No air travel, no credit cards.
Never say your name on the phone,
or the computers will kick in.
Dodgy client adds,
"Welcome to my world."
Well, I don't want his world.
No choice, old chum.
Actually, I'm getting
a bit paranoid myself.
Look, suppose I posited
that all this was just coincidence-
Tess killed by bandits,
pure and simple...
and that you're being
as paranoid as she was.
Ham.
Thanks for trying, Ham.
I have to finish what she started.
Well, look, look. I've got the address
of Aunt Claudia, the old bat in Rome.
If you need to contact me,
you'd better do it through her.
She adored Tess.
I failed her, Ham.
I lost my faith in her.
No, she forgives you.
She loved you rotten too,
you know.
You think?
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
It seems our erstwhile colleague
has disappeared.
Four days ago he lunched
in London with Pellegrin,
who describes him as overwrought,
after which he visited his wife's lawyer...
before going off our radar.
The poor man seems
to have convinced himself...
there was a conspiracy against Tessa
in which we are all complicit.
Lfhe has left the U.K.,
he did so without a passport.
Therefore, any contact from Justin
must be reported to me immediately.
In his own best interest.
No point asking if you've
heard from him, I suppose?
No, no, Tim, none at all.
Birgit, why are ThreeBees spending
$70 million testing Dypraxa for KDH?
I mean, is the African market
worth that much?
Tessa, you have to understand
the scale of this.
There is a T.B. Epidemic coming.
It will affect the entire world.
Or, put into the language that stock
exchanges all over the world understand,
if the T.B. Market performs as forecast,
billions and billions of dollars
are waiting to be earned.
And the boy to earn them is Dypraxa.
Lf, of course,
the preliminary trials in Africa...
have not thrown up
any disturbing side effects.
Ich suche Birgit.
Ich bin Justin Quayle,
Tessa Quayle's Ehemann.
Michael Adams.
Okay, Herr Adams.
She collects Karl at 3:00
from the kindergarten at Bahnhofstrasse.
¶¶
Karl, here.
Birgit.
You sent this to my wife.
Justin.
I need to talk to you.
Our computers
were stolen last night.
Yes, I know.
They have never gone
this far before.
I can't be seen with you.
Sorry. I've Karl to think of.
Is there some safe place
we could talk?
Nowhere. Nowhere safe.
Nowhere?
Please. Just... a few questions.
Okay, let's talk here.
With these people.
All right.
Okay. My bike's across the street.
Ask your questions before we get to it.
Is it a scam?
Scam?
Dypraxa.
Does it cure T.B.
Yes, it cures.
But it can also kill, you know,
because they haven't got
the formula right.
Right. So why don't they work on that?
It's cheaper to fix the trials.
Exclude the patients that
have side effects, you know.
To go back to the lab would
cost them time- two years-
millions of dollars, and other companies
would have time to produce their own cures.
Okay, next question.
You said to Tessa in your e-mails
that the Kenyan government
had approved the trials.
Somebody bribed them.
Who?
ThreeBees, Lorbeer.
We don't know.
But $50,000 in the right hands,
and you can test battery acid
as skin lotion.
My bike's there.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Who is Lorbeer?
Birgit, is it a company?
A white coat.
He invented Dypraxa.
When patients started to die,
Lorbeerjumped clear.
Is that why Tessa went to Lokichogio?
Is that where Lorbeer is?
Disappeared.
Murdered?
We've gotta go. I'm sorry.
Where can I find him?
Birgit? Where?
Go back to Africa.
Lorbeer's still there.
Singing In German]
¶¶
Tessa, why didn't you tell me?
I could have helped you.
It is my sad duty to inform you
that Dr. Bluhm has been found.
I'll spare you the details.
Suffice to say, the poor fellow...
seems to have been tortured to death
on the same day Tessa was killed.
Which would seem to exonerate him.
Seem? So what's the new theory?
That he tortured himself to death?
That'd save you looking
for anyone else, wouldn't it?
Moving on.
What is the purpose of your visit?
I'm seeing a friend.
Welcome to Kenya, Mr. Black.
Thank you.
Has anyone seen
ThreeBees' share price lately?
Does that mean he won't be able
to contribute to tombola?
Hardly Kenny's fault if someone
put the word out on him.
Wish I'd know that's all it took.
I'd have done it sooner.
I expect he'll land on his feet.
Give him a life peerage.
Henceforth you shall be known as
Lord fucking Curtiss of fucking Kenya.
Whoever you are, I don't
take kindly to being blackmailed.
Christ. How did you get here?
Safari tour. Via Paris.
Hunting me now, Justin?
You're the one on the run.
I loved her.
I'm not ashamed of it.
Nor should you be...
if it were true.
It's not for you to tell me
how I felt.
If you've read that, you'll see
that I let her read something
she shouldn't.
Yeah. A letter from Pellegrin.
She trusted you.
What do you want for that?
I want to know why Pellegrin
suppressed Tessa's report.
It was him, wasn't it?
Don't try and play detective.
ThreeBees, KDH, Dypraxa.
What's the story on that axis of evil?
KDH is Swiss-Canadian.
So why are we involved?
Curtiss is one of us.
He's British.
Christ, Justin, stop bleeding
for bloody Africa
and show some loyalty.
That plant KDH built in Wales
could have gone to France.
Fifteen hundred jobs
in a depressed region.
We owed them.
They needed help
with the Dypraxa trials.
KDH needed
an investment partner here.
Curtiss and ThreeBees
served us both.
And Tessa wanted what?
Pressure on Kenny...
to stop the tests,
redesign the bloody drug.
Three years' delay,
millions of dollars.
Or?
We're not paid
to be bleeding hearts.
You know that, Justin.
We're not killing people
who wouldn't be dead otherwise.
Look at the death rate.
Not that anybody's counting.
But you were
a bleeding heart, Sandy.
Tessa was your salvation,
wasn't she, from all this?
You loved her. Remember?
Pellegrin said the report
was too damaging...
and she had to be stopped.
Oh, yes. She was stopped.
I betrayed her.
We all did.
You did it by... growing flowers.
How did you betray her, Sandy?
They wanted to know
what she was up to.
I'm the one who told them
she was going to Loki.
- Who did you tell?
- Pellegrin.
But God knows who he told.
Ghita, get in the car.
Get in the car!
Go!
Get in.
Listen, fuckhead,
if I wanted you dead,
I would've brought Crick with me.
I wanna show you something.
Show me from there.
Don't mess me about.
I'm doing you a favor.
How did you know where I'd be?
I've still got a friend or two, you know?
We're marked men, Quayle.
They've called in my fucking bank loans.
I'm finished.
They want you silenced.
And they want another country's flag
flying over my pharma division.
So, you've been asking
about Wanza Kilulu.
She's under there,
covered in quicklime.
Her and 62 others
who never officially existed.
Dypraxa?
Yeah.
Is that where I'm going?
Not on my agenda.
Then why are you
showing me this?
Let's just say
if I'm going to the wall,
I want a trophy.
That's what you lot do,
isn't it? Heads on walls.
I think I'll have Pellegrin's
fucking head on mine.
So, now you know where it is.
I'm not taking any fucking questions.
What about Lorbeer?
That Bible-thumping bullshitter,
he's doing his penance in the Sudan.
Jesus the healer.
You don't know where I'm going?
You get one guess.
I'm gonna surprise you, Tess.
- I love this man.
- Hello.
I wish you had shared
just a few things.
I love you.
I love you too.
Who did you think it was?
Fuck you, Donohue.
This is bandit country.
Did you tell Curtiss where I'd be?
Ghita's car?
Well, Ghita's
my only friend here, Tim.
I wouldn't want her
to get into trouble.
She won't.
You do have another friend,
believe it or not.
You won't find what
you're looking for in Loki.
Let's be honest
with each other, shall we?
That's a- a late career change
for you, Tim.
There's something else
we have in common, you and I.
We'll both be dead by Christmas.
There's a contract out on you.
Same people who did for Tessa,
I shouldn't wonder.
Mine's cancer.
My pain is controllable.
I knew that you were ill.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize.
Yeah. Sandy tell you?
He fingered Tessa.
He said he'd made a phone call.
He didn't know they'd kill her.
Silly sod was besotted with her.
But that's the way it works
with corporate murder.
Boss gets wind of something,
calls in his head of security,
who talks to someone,
who talks to a friend of someone.
Finishes up with an answering machine
in a rented office,
a couple of sensitive gentlemen
in a blue pickup truck.
They will never know
who ordered the hit.
I can get you out of Kenya.
It's one of the few things
we still do well.
Drop it now, and it's over.
I'll make sure word
gets to the right people.
Go home... and live.
But I don't have a home, Tim.
Tessa was my home.
Know about Bluhm?
What about Bluhm?
Let me tell you
what you're facing.
They dragged him into the desert,
cut out his tongue,
chopped offhis manly apparatus
and stuffed them where his tongue had been.
Then they crucified the poor bugger.
Pathologist's opinion is
he was still alive when they nailed him up.
Of course, you might be lucky.
It might be in their interest
to make yours look like suicide.
Which it is.
Balance of mind disturbed.
No fuss, no inquiry.
Nothing.
Right.
Well, thank you for the warning.
You've been very kind.
I was afraid you'd say that.
In case you meet any bandits.
I, uh- I wondered
if you could help me.
Yes, sir?
Thank you for agreeing
to take me, Mr.
Please. I can't hear you.
Please put these on.
I said thank you
for taking me, Mr. Andika.
Jonah. No formalities up here.
Do you know about
Southern Sudan, Mr. Black?
The place we're going to
is a food camp,
but on the way we must drop
to some villages.
We'rejust about to do a live run.
Take a look.
His name is Brandt,
this man you want to see.
He works at the clinic up there.
He's a good man,
but he pushes God with the pills.
Don't get him started.
Better strap yourself in.
We're landing on the surface of the moon.
¶¶
Hi. Uh, Robert Black,
freelance journalist.
I'm looking for Dr. Brandt.
Dr. Brandt? Yeah, he's just here.
He's traveling over from the village.
Thank you.
- Dr. Brandt?
- I'll see you over by the tent.
My name is Robert Black.
I'm a freelancejournalist.
Uh-huh.
I'm told that you're the man to talk to.
I don't know
about that, Mr. Black.
But I can tell you what's
happening around here, yeah?
Good.
Meet my self-appointed
assistant, Abuk.
Abuk.
Hello. How are you?
I'm very well.
Follow me. Come this way.
Youse need to go
all to the medical center,
quickly as possible.
¶¶
I only give the food
to the women, Mr. Black.
The women make the homes.
The men make the wars... and hooch.
Adam was God's first draft.
He got it right with Eve.
You tell that
to your readers, Mr. Black.
It's a philosophy
that I learned from my wife.
Cherish her, man. Cherish her.
One of God's finest creations.
Now I'll show you
what the devil's up to.
¶¶
Our treatment center.
Pretty crude, isn't it?
Well, I've seen hospitals
little better. In Nairobi.
So have I. Gharan, what surprises
have they got in store for us this month?
Have you checked those things?
Ja? Should be 40 boxes.
Free medicines, Mr. Black.
Most of them well beyond
their sell-by date.
The drug companies donate them.
It's a tax break for them.
Disposable drugs
for disposable patients.
Out here they have
absolutely no shelf life.
Safest thing to do
is incinerate them.
Big pharmaceuticals are right up there
with the arms dealers.
This is how the world
fucks Africa, Mr. Black.
Blood on their hands?
It's how they expiate their guilt.
Pharmaceuticals,
the aid agencies, everybody.
This whole machine
is driven by guilt.
Is it?
And now you will sample
my goat stew. Come with me.
So tell me, Robert,
do you believe an individual
can redeem himselfby good acts?
Abuk.
I do, yes.
Maybe the redemption
is in the struggle, huh?
God has your head.
The devil has your balls.
So which particular devil had yours?
Oh, you don't want to know
about that, Robert.
What's your paper
really interested in?
In the big
pharmaceutical companies.
African guinea pigs.
Cheap trials for unsound drugs.
Uninformed consent extorted
with threats against children.
Who are you?
Christ!
Payoffs, cover-ups.
You were in Nairobi.
At the hospital.
Unmarked graves.
I knew I'd seen you
somewhere before.
Murder.
You're the husband.
That's right, Dr. Lorbeer.
Markus! Markus!
Something's going on out there.
Why did my wife come here?
She-They had written this report.
Sixteen pages of inspired guesswork.
I was supposed to provide
the missing clinical data.
Testify on tape.
And did you?
This could be a raid.
Tribesman. Nasty.
They steal cattle, food, children.
- I think maybe we should leave.
- Did you testify on tape?
She was a very persuasive woman,
your wife, Mr. Quayle.
And, no, I do not have the tape.
They took the tape.
But you kept a copy
of the report, yes?
Yes, I did. You're welcome to it.
Level four alert!
They're leaving in five minutes.
If you don't want to die, my friend,
you'd better come with me to the airstrip.
Hurry.
- We can still make it.
- What were Tessa and Bluhm
doing at Lake Turkana?
Are you crazy?
We've got to get out of here, man.
I mean, these people,
they kill anybody. Sorry.
Have you lost your senses?
- There was something else!
There was a letter!
Look, you're a lunatic.
Do you know what you're doing?
You're killing us both.
We'll take our chances with them.
No!
Get down!
Abuk!
Abuk! You okay?
Come with us, quick. Run.
Run.
Wait. Wait!
Be careful!
Abuk, be careful!
Here!
Hurry on up!
Where have you guys been?
Sorry about that, Jonah.
- I'm sorry. I can't take the girl.
- I'm not leaving her.
- We're only allowed to evacuate aid workers.
- Well, to hell with what's allowed.
I'll- How much do you want for her?
- Look, there's $800.
- Don't embarrass me.
You can't buy this. The rules
are made for good reason, please.
This is a child's life!
There are no rules to cover that!
Look, there are thousands
of them out there.
I can't make an exception
for this one child.
Yes, but this is one we can help! Here.
Abuk! Abuk! Abuk!
Listen, that's the way it is here.
Keep your money.
Strap yourself in, and let's go.
¶¶
What- What'll happen to her?
She might make it to a refugee camp...
if she's lucky.
¶¶
This is what you came for,
I believe.
Your wife would have made that tape public,
Mr. Quayle, with my voice on it.
That letter was my insurance policy.
But how did they know
where to find her?
They were on their way to Marsabit,
taking the whole rotten package
to Grace Makanga.
Makanga would have put it
in front of the U.N.
But someone knew exactly
where Tessa and Arnold would be.
That was me.
I radioed Nairobi.
KDH security man name of Crick.
God, Christ, man.
I didn't know they
were gonna be murdered.
My oath to God.
Crick's going to know
that you were up here.
Going to be very interested
to know where you're headed.
What do I tell him?
He'll know.
He's been there before.
Mr. A ndika?
Yeah?
I'd like to apologize
if I embarrassed you earlier.
It's all right.
Do you think that it would be possible
to land the plane here?
Lake Turkana? It's possible,
but you don't wanna go there.
It's-There's nothing there
but crocodiles.
Let me take you back to Loki.
Well, l- I wouldn't be alone for long.
Please. I'd be, um- I'd be grateful.
I have one more favor
to ask you, I'm sorry.
Do you think you could post
that envelope for me?
It's quite urgent.
Ah, Rome.
If we have lost in Justin and Tessa...
two valued friends,
the diplomatic community
has lost a true gentleman-
courteous, self-effacing,
large ofheart.
That he chose to take his own life
in the same remote spot...
where Tessa met her tragic death...
is a sad reflection
ofhis tormented state of mind...
but also typical ofhis discretion.
He would not have had us troubled.
He would not have had us inconvenienced.
Nothing in his life became him...
like the leaving it.
I have, uh, chosen a text I know
Justin and Tessa would approve.
It's an epistle.
Noncanonical.
"My Dear Sandy:
Your naiveté is beyond belief.
"Knowing our arrangements
with KDH and ThreeBees,
"you send me
this half-baked report...
"by some bleeding heart
diplomatic wife and her black lover...
"and ask me to take action.
"The only action required,
apart from shredding the thing,
"is to keep a tighter rein
on your resident harlot.
"I want to know what she does,
where she goes, whom she meets.
"The issue here is deniability.
"If nobody told us
Dypraxa was causing deaths,
"we can't be held responsible.
"But, my dear Sandy,
should it ever become known...
"that we've closed our eyes to the deaths,
"none of us would survive the scandal.
"I still have great hopes of you.
My love to Gloria.
Yours Sincerely, Bernard."
This way, sir.
What do you have to say, sir?
It was a bizarre sort of suicide.
His body bore no fewer
than eight bullet wounds...
from three different guns,
none of which was the one
found in his hand.
So who has got away with murder?
Not, of course, the British government.
They merely covered up,
as one does, the offensive corpses.
Though not literally. That was done
by person or persons unknown.
So who has committed murder?
Not, of course, the highly respectable firm
of KDH Pharmaceutical,
which has enjoyed
record profits this quarter...
and has now licensed ZimbaMed of Harare...
to continue testing Dypraxa in Africa.
No, there are no murders in Africa.
Only regrettable deaths.
And from those deaths
we derive the benefits of civilization,
benefits we can afford so easily...
because those lives
were bought so cheaply.
I know all your secrets, Tess.
I think I understand you now.
You want me to come home.
But I am home.
Mr. Quayle.
Tess.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org