Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[STUDENTS CHEERING]
- Hey, man, let's get out of here!
- School is out.
What's up, little brother?
I gotta catch up with the twins.
Hi, Will.
Hi, Gwen. Come on, let's go.
PAUL:
Hey, Will.
Any thoughts on your first semester
as an American overseas?
WILL: Guys, stop it.
PAUL: Just answer.
ROBIN [IN ENGLISH ACCENT]:
In an English place.
PAUL [IN ENGLISH ACCENT]:
At an English school.
The people wanna know
if you made any friends.
That's their question to you.
Any, uh, lady friends, maybe?
ROBIN: Looks like a pretty lady there.
- Okay, guys? Guys, back off.
- Shut up.
- Talk to her.
- Why don't you talk to her?
ROBIN: Because I see you want to.
Hey, that's the new girl, right?
Will, why don't you go talk to her?
I mean, why not?
WILL:
Wait, you forgot your scarf!
JAMES:
Are we gonna go to any soccer games?
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Good afternoon, Stantons.
Miss Greythorne wishes to extend
an invitation to the whole family...
...to attend a Christmas Eve party
at the manor. Mince pies, mulled wine.
- Can we count on you?
- Yeah.
What about you, Will?
- Oh, yes, Mr. Lyon. We'll be... I'll be...
- It's Merriman, please.
- Okay.
- Look forward to your company.
We'll be there.
JAMES: If you refuse, I'm afraid we'll be
forced to ridicule you behind your backs.
GWEN: What's a mince?
ROBIN: I hope it's a fruit.
Would it kill them to put, like,
a cherry or apples in their pies?
- Lf it has meat in it...
WILL: Guys, wait up.
...I don't think
it should be called a pie.
MARY:
Hey, guys, look who's home.
JAMES: Whoa! Look at this stranger.
GWEN: Max!
MAX: Hello, fellas.
ROBIN: Oh, my God, Max.
PAUL:
What are you doing here?
MAX:
Hey. Family Christmas.
Family Christmas?
Didn't stop you missing last year.
- Or the year before.
MAX: Hey.
Hey, Gwen, sweetie, you don't
let these guys corrupt you, all right?
JAMES: So, Max, how's college?
- Uh, it's pretty good.
Hey, Max.
You still doing that tae kwon do?
- Come on.
ROBIN: Here it comes.
MAX:
Challenge me.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Don't kill him. He just got home.
Guys.
WILL:
Hey, Mom.
- How was school?
WILL: It was good.
Yeah?
MAX:
Will.
I got your room.
MAX:
Hey, Will.
How long are you staying?
I don't know. A week, maybe two.
- All this for a week or two?
- Come on, Will, do me this one favor.
People to see,
I got phone calls to make.
I can't do that
if I'm sleeping in the attic, can I?
[SCOFFS]
- But I can?
- Yeah, well, you're young. Versatile.
Hey. We gonna go all out
for your birthday?
- Special day. I didn't forget.
- Don't change the subject.
Thirteen.
They grow up so fast.
Fourteen, actually.
ROBIN:
Hey, man. Lame about Max. Come on in.
- Glad to have you here.
- Hey...
- ...this will be your designated area.
PAUL: Yes. Smile.
ROBIN: It's tape. What?
That's funny. Come on.
[WIND BLOWING]
Boys, turn the TV off. James.
MARY:
Come on. Everything's getting cold.
ROBIN: Ketchup.
JOHN: Where have you been, honey?
[DOGS GROWL]
None of your business.
Maybe, uh... Maybe next year we'll get
Stephen home, make up the full crew.
- Would you like to see Stephen?
- Yeah, that'd be awesome.
Well, we'll try to get him home.
Depends where the Navy sends him.
JAMES: The Bermuda Triangle.
- To Stephen.
ALL:
To Stephen.
JAMES:
How come yours is in a can?
JOHN: So, Max,
how did the semester finish off?
Oh, it was, uh,
it was good, you know.
- Any more thoughts on grad school?
MAX: Nope.
Just still, you know,
weighing my options.
- Weighing your options.
- And what about you, Dad?
JOHN:
Things are pretty good.
Good, so then you're coping?
I mean, it's a lot, you know.
New place, new job.
It's been a long time
since you've felt able, right?
Max, drop it.
No, it's all right. It's all right.
- It's turning out to be a good year.
- Yeah.
- The move here has been good for us.
- It has.
All of us.
[DOGS GROWL]
PAUL:
Will. Will!
What are you staring at?
- The dogs.
ROBIN: Hey, man, I know that look.
PAUL: Yeah, it's the look that girl
gave you on the bus.
- You met a girl on the bus today?
- No, he looked at a girl on the bus today.
ROBIN: Wasn't his type.
PAUL: She looked at me.
MARY: All right. Leave him be.
PAUL: I'm good-Iooking. Can't help it.
Isn't this nice?
[DOGS GROWLING]
[BELLS RINGING]
GEORGE: I told you
we should have trimmed it first.
MARY:
Hey, guys, the tree's here.
[GEORGE AND DAWSON GRUNTING]
DAWSON: Come on, George, push.
GEORGE: There we go.
Come on. It's gorgeous. Just bring it
on through. Be careful of the boots.
Boys, come and help.
Isn't that gorgeous?
Just lean it up against that wall
and my boys will take care of it.
Will, this is Mr. Dawson
from Court Farm, and George.
GEORGE:
I got it.
DAWSON:
So...
...this is Will Stanton, eh?
- A pleasure to meet you.
- And you, sir.
Hey, George, look here. It's Will.
So it be. And with a birthday today
as well.
- Yeah.
MARY: That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
Can I get you gentlemen something,
coffee or tea?
No, we're only stopping.
Too much to do before the storm sets in.
- The storm?
DAWSON: Yes.
Bad weather on the way.
Tomorrow will be a bad night.
The nights after...
- ...beyond imagining.
- Really?
Excuse me.
Well, you have a good day, huh?
- Come on, George.
MARY: Thank you so much.
DAWSON: Missis.
- Will.
- You gonna come open your presents?
- Oh, yeah.
MAX:
Hey, heads up.
Happy birthday, big guy.
Sorry, I made a little mistake with
the age. I'll fix that right up for you.
No, no, that's okay.
ROBIN: Here you go. Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Second one comes on Christmas.
There's two.
Yeah, happy birthday, man.
ROBIN:
Is this all the milk we have?
MARY:
I'm gonna make some eggs, all right?
Boys, come on.
Give me a hand here.
Gwen.
- You shouldn't have.
- I knew everyone else would forget.
- Thanks.
- Here, let me help you.
- So what's your wish?
- What?
It's your birthday.
You're allowed to have a wish, anything.
Snow. You know,
like we used to get back at home.
- Yeah.
- I want lots of snow.
GWEN: You guys, I got him. He's here.
- Hey, can you hear me?
- Stephen!
- Hey, son.
Hey, Mom and Dad.
Bros! Gwen, look at you.
- You're becoming a heartbreaker.
MARY: Isn't she?
Sorry I can 't be there. As you can see,
I'm busy defending the free world.
JOHN: We miss you, son.
ROBIN: Very tropical.
All the gifts sort of have
a Hawaiian theme.
JAMES:
Yeah, perfect for winter in England.
Hey, Will, listen, yours is different.
I was walking the street market,
and...
For some reason,
I knew it was for you.
- Cool. Thanks, Stephen.
- How cute. Oh, these are fantastic.
Anyway, enjoy the day,
and I wish I was there.
JOHN: You too.
We wish you were home too, Stephen.
Take care of Mom and Dad, guys.
Merry Christmas.
JOHN:
Merry Christmas!
[WIND HOWLING]
[WILL GRUNTS]
[CAWING]
[AIR HISSES]
["JINGLE BELLS" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
SANTA:
You want all those things, do you?
Can I help you?
Hello? Are you going to buy that?
Sorry. Um, it's for my sister.
It's 5 pounds.
Thank you.
- There you go. Thank you.
- Thanks.
Excuse me, sir.
I wonder if you wouldn't mind
coming back with us.
We think you left the store
without paying for an item.
What? No, I don't think so. I'm sorry.
It might just be a simple mistake, sir...
...but perhaps you would
accompany us to our office...
...rather than dealing with it
here in public.
- This way.
- Please.
- You all right, then?
WILL: Mm-hm.
Nicked something, didn't you?
- "Nicked"?
- You stole something.
We've been watching you
from the moment you came in.
SECURITY GUARD 1:
He looks like trouble.
SECURITY GUARD 2:
Looks like a thief.
SECURITY GUARD 1:
Wandering hands have deep pockets.
Children are always the worst.
SECURITY GUARD 1: You won't mind
if we search you, then? Mm?
- What?
- Or you'd rather we call your parents?
Tell them you're being investigated
for shoplifting...
...which is a criminal offense
in this country.
- That's right.
- Don't waste our time, Will.
[IN DISTORTED VOICE]
Just give us the Sign.
How do you know my name?
- Give us the Sign, Will.
- Just give us the Sign.
- Give us the Sign.
The Sign. Give us the Sign.
Give us... Give us the Sign.
Give us the Sign!
WILL:
Get off!
[GRUNTING]
[CROW CAWING]
["WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[BALL BOUNCING]
PAUL:
Will, get out of the way.
JOHN:
Hey, guys.
ROBIN: Hi, Dad.
PAUL: Hey, Dad.
Robin. Paul. How many times
we have to tell you? Not in the house.
PAUL: Sorry.
ROBIN: Sorry, Dad.
Dad... Dad, can we talk?
[TELEVISION SQUEALING]
Can we do it later, Will? I have to
grade all this before the holidays.
Since nobody wants to stress about
physics over Christmas...
- ...I have to do it myself. Later, I promise.
- Just for a sec, please.
Look, something is going on with me.
I'm... I don't...
It's mixed up.
Will, you're 14.
These changes are normal.
Uh, you talk to your brothers about it.
ROBIN: Your body starting to feel
all funny and different?
[DOGS GROWL]
[WILL GRUNTS]
Oh. Sorry.
[CHATTERING]
["DECK THE HALLS" PLAYING
ON GRAMOPHONE]
MAN:
It's lovely.
MERRIMAN:
Go inside, sir. Have a marvelous time.
Thank you, sir.
- Stantons.
MARY: Hello.
Merry Christmas.
Give me your coats.
Thank you very much.
Coat, darling.
MARY: Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas to you. Coat.
Go on in and have a wonderful time.
Coats, please.
MARY:
Oh, look at this.
Merry Christmas.
Do take something to eat.
- Hope you're hungry.
PAUL: I am.
- They're always hungry.
JOHN: Yes, they are.
Merry Christmas, Miss Greythorne.
- We need to talk to him.
- Discretion, Merriman.
There is a right way to do things.
And a way of getting them done.
A drink for the vicar, please.
VICAR: Thank you very much, Merriman.
- Less haste, Merriman.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
No way.
WILL:
Ha, ha.
[ZAPS]
It's fruit. Mince pie is fruit.
- Oh, thank God.
PAUL: It's fruit?
GEORGE:
All right?
- Something to eat?
- No. No, I'm fine.
- Drink?
- I'm cool.
Nice to see you again.
Out of your league, buddy.
Watch and learn.
- Hey, how you doing?
MAGGIE: Hi there.
Thank you.
JAMES: Want some food or something?
MAGGIE: Sure.
MERRIMAN: He slipped away.
- He had his reasons.
We ought to go after him.
This may not be the best moment.
The boy is troubled.
I'm used to dealing
with warriors, not boys.
This warrior is a boy.
We can't afford to wait.
You know what's out there.
[GRUNTS]
[HOOFBEATS]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[DOGS BARKING]
[WILL GRUNTING]
RIDER: Why do you run, boy?
- Who are you? What do you want?
- The Sign.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
Are you frightened of me?
You should be, Will. I'm very angry.
All this time it was you.
- Give me the Sign.
- What Sign?
- Give it to me!
- I don't know what you're talking about.
You escaped me once before,
a mistake I won't repeat.
- Now, give me the Sign.
DAWSON: Leave him be.
Leave the boy alone, Rider.
You can't fight us all.
- You're not strong enough.
- Not yet, but I will be.
My power rises now.
Five days are all I need, then you...
...and all your kind will be destroyed.
Merry Christmas, Will.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
Walk with us, Will.
- Where?
- Through time.
- Where am I?
MERRIMAN: This is the Great Hall...
...where we are strongest.
You're safe here, Will.
No one may enter here
without our invitation.
WILL:
Who are you?
We are the Old Ones.
Well, to tell the truth...
...we're neither young nor old,
being outside time.
You're the last of us to be born.
You are the Sign Seeker.
Everybody keeps
talking about these Signs.
Sorry. Honestly, I don't know
what that is.
GREYTHORNE:
Will...
...you are part of something that
has been waiting for you all your life.
We, the Old Ones, we serve the Light.
The Rider, he serves the Dark.
The Dark is rising, Will.
It is you who must restore
the power of the Light.
Um, I'm sorry, Miss Greythorne,
but maybe you've got the wrong guy.
MERRIMAN: A thousand years ago,
a great battle was fought here...
...between the Light and the Dark.
The Light won, but only just...
...and the Earth was saved.
The Dark was defeated
but not destroyed.
GREYTHORNE:
To protect the power of the Light...
...it was divided and hidden
in the form of six Signs.
And the Seeker...
...will find the Signs.
WILL:
And you think I'm this Seeker?
MERRIMAN:
On your 14th birthday...
...when you were
first able to sense a Sign...
...the Dark sensed you.
In five days' time, it'll reach its peak.
Unless you have all the Signs,
you won't be able to fight it.
I don't know how to sense a Sign.
The book will tell you
how the Signs are to be found.
Only the Seeker can read the book.
You are special, Will.
The seventh son of a seventh son.
You got it wrong. Sixth, actually.
I only have five brothers.
I guess you made a mistake.
I'm sorry. I'm not the one.
GREYTHORNE: You will not be able
to run from this, Will.
MERRIMAN:
Better open that now.
See what'll happen in five days' time
if the Dark prevails.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
Hey, Will. You're back late.
- Where you been?
- Went for a walk.
Why are you all dirty? Hey, man.
- Where were you?
- Tell us.
Leave me alone!
[BOTH GRUNT]
ROBIN:
You okay?
PAUL: Yeah. You?
- Yeah.
PAUL:
What was that?
ROBIN:
I don't know. Puberty?
Where did you get this?
Surfing. Seemed sort of cool...
...and I figured, physics problem,
I know the man to ask.
Since when did physics become cool?
I don't know.
You spend all your time on it.
I thought maybe
we could spend time on it together.
I always hoped you'd stick to
more fulfilling pursuits, like Xbox.
Dad. Really, I'm interested.
It's, like, some sort of equation
about light and darkness.
Almost like they're fighting
for the same space.
What I need to know is, can dark win?
That's not how it works. There are
no winners and losers in physics, Will.
But according to this, Dad,
maybe darkness isn't just dark.
But like... But like a thing.
So I mean...
...could darkness...?
Could it hurt someone?
"Hurt someone"?
That's not how it...
Look, Will, don't waste your time with
this stuff. It's theoretical. It's boring.
- I wanna know.
- Well, you can't.
Look, Will, you're a kid. Just enjoy it.
Just be happy you don't have to
deal with it. I have work to do.
You know, Dad, when I was little...
...you never told me
not to be afraid of the dark.
[WINDOW RATTLING]
[GRUNTS]
MARY:
Will, stay off that foot.
Mom, it's fine, okay? I just twisted it.
I called the doctor to see
if you should go to the hospital.
[KNOCKING]
- I do not want to go to the hospital.
- I know. We'll see what he says.
WILL: Mom, I do not want
to go to the hospital.
MARY: Hello, doctor.
RIDER: Good afternoon.
MARY: Come in.
RIDER: And I hope you don't have to.
Hello, Will.
Let's have a look, shall we?
MARY:
Come on, sweetheart.
- Come on.
WILL: Wait a minute, Mom. Mom.
- Honey, it's all right.
RIDER: Come along.
Don't worry, I don't bite.
Come on. There we go.
RIDER:
Here we are. Let me see, here.
Mm. I wonder, Mrs. Stanton...
...do you have a tape measure
so I can check the swelling?
- Yes, yes, I'll go look.
- No.
- Thank you.
- Mom, stay here.
Somebody doesn't want to
be separated from his mommy.
MARY: Come on, now.
You'll be fine. I'll be right back.
- Leave me alone.
- These old fools...
...would have you do work
that they can't...
...but they haven't told you
that you'll fail.
Now, give me the Signs, Will.
I don't forget those
who stand with me.
- Nor those who stand against.
- I don't have what you want.
Will, I'm the Dark on this earth.
I'm the end of everything
you see and know.
But I can help you.
Or I can make things
very much worse.
MARY:
Here we go.
Ah! Wonderful.
Actually, it's fine.
- The good news is he hasn't broken it.
- Yes.
But I do think he's damaged the
ligaments, so it's going to take time.
Now, my advice to you, William,
is take it easy.
And don't look so worried.
It's not the end of the world.
Not quite yet.
[MARY AND RIDER CHUCKLE]
- All right.
- All right?
Terrific. Thank you for coming by.
I so appreciate it.
RIDER: You have a lovely home.
MARY: Oh, thank you.
RIDER: Bye!
MARY: Bye-bye.
[DOOR CLOSES]
MARY:
It's your brother. Tom.
You two were born just minutes apart.
Another set of twins.
Huh. Can you imagine?
What...? What happened?
We... We don't know. We don't know.
What do you mean?
Mom, what do you mean?
When you were both...
...just 2 weeks old,
just new, just babies...
[BABIES CRYING]
...there was a storm one night.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
You were both crying
and I took you downstairs.
Your father was working in the study.
I asked him to check on your brother.
He was distracted for a few minutes.
And when he went in...
...Tom...
He was gone.
What, kidnapped?
They searched for months and we...
We hoped for years,
but they didn't...
They never found anything.
- Why didn't you ever tell me?
- We were devastated.
Especially your dad.
You know, he just blamed himself.
As the years went by...
...we just spoke of it less and less...
...until finally...
...just not at all.
So...
...was Tom born before me?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was.
Another big brother.
Seventh son.
WILL: "Six Signs were created
to contain the power of the Light...
...from stone, bronze, iron,
wood and water.
But the sixth was to be carried
in the essence of a..."
The essence of a human soul?
"The Signs were hidden
and scattered throughout time.
The Seeker will find them."
Okay.
Look at this.
This pattern, it's a fractal.
It's physics.
My dad teaches this stuff.
Like a hiding place
that goes on and on forever.
Like a clue hidden in plain sight
that declares the presence of a Sign.
WILL: George, can you
pass me your hammer, please?
GEORGE:
Here you go.
Thank you.
Gwen, I'm sorry.
[WILL GRUNTS]
The Sign of Stone.
Five more to go.
You are the seventh son
of a seventh son, Will Stanton.
You step through time.
One by one, the Signs will call to you.
You will gather them...
...and gain the power of the Light.
You are the Seeker.
MERRIMAN:
Not all the Signs will be so easy.
And the Rider wants them too.
He may try to trick or threaten you.
- Well, then how do I face the darkness?
- You'll learn to face it as you are.
You have powers, Will.
You'll be able to
command light or fire...
...move objects,
summon great strength...
...and, of course, step through time.
- Can I fly?
- What?
You know. Zoom. Fly.
No. No, I don't think you can.
MERRIMAN:
Merry Christmas.
RIDER: Mrs. Stanton.
- Yes.
May I introduce you to my mother?
Mother, this is Mrs. Stanton.
She lives in the village.
Hello.
And this is the young boy
I was telling you about.
VICAR:
A very happy Christmas to you all.
If we can now stand...
...we'll sing hymn number one from
the hymn book, "Joy to the World."
[ALL SINGING "JO Y TO THE WORLD"]
Where is everybody?
Exactly when they were.
It's we that have moved.
They can't see it, of course.
You've sensed a Sign, Will.
You've moved us through time.
It's late 13th or early 14th century.
I see.
The crypt has not been bricked up,
so that means we're before the plague.
About 1290, I'd say.
Be quick, Will. The Rider was present
and he will hunt you through time.
I don't know where it is exactly,
just that it's here.
[CROW CAWS]
[GROWLING]
I suggest we prepare.
Merriman, guard the Seeker.
What do you reckon?
Dragon.
GEORGE: He wouldn't
send a dragon against us, Mr. Dawson.
Knows better than that.
- It could be a shapeless beast, I suppose.
- No. Dragon.
GEORGE:
I don't think so.
Flagon of ale says it is.
[FOOTSTEPS POUNDING]
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org