Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
1964, a crucial moment
in American history...
Lyndon Johnson is re-elected to
the presidency by a landslide,
The New York Worlïs Fair
introduces a bright new future.
And after five scintillating
years on the air...
Presto!
The Rocky and Bullwinkle Show
is abruptly cancelled.
- Cancelled?!
Uh, sorry about that, boys.
A lothas changed
in 35 years.
Velcro has replaced
the zipper.
Sneakers have
lights on them.
The Cold War is over.
And The Rocky and
Bullwinkle Show...
is still cancelled.
Frostbite Falls, Minnesota,
once the beloved home
of Rocky and Bullwinkle,
had been a thriving
cartoon town.
Nowit was crippled
by years of reruns.
The beautiful
Frostbite Falls Forest...
decimated.
The once majestic falls
above Veronica Lake...
...devastated.
While the narrator...
thas me...
down on his luck
and out of a job,
was forced to move in
with his mother
where he was reduced
to narrating
the events
of his own life.
"With the speed and dexterity
astonishing in a woman
of her advancing years,
Mother bastes the chicken,
tosses the salad,
and mashes the potatoes."
Oh, sonny,
shut up!
Ow!
And in a little house
at the top of a stump forest,
Rocky and Bullwinkle
themselves,
were forced to subsist
on ever-diminishing
residual checks
from reruns of their oldshow.
World famous television stars
whose adventures once
took them all over the globe,
now their exploits
were just a memory.
Yes, it was a
melancholy time indeed.
Rocky the flying squirrel
hadn't flown in years.
Whas the point?
I guess the world just doesn't
need us anymore, Bullwinkle.
Say, where are
you going?
All this exposition
is wearing me out.
I'm going for a walk
in the woods.
But, Bullwinkle,
there aren't any
woods anymore.
You don't have
to tell me.
I'm the chairman of
the Frostbite Falls Society
for Wildlife Conversation.
You mean
wildlife conservation.
What did I say?
You said,
"wildlife conversation."
Somebody's going to start
talking about these things.
Yes, even their wordplay
had become hackneyed and cheap.
No, it was always
like this.
But times were just as tough
half way across the drawing
in the former Soviet satellite
of Pottsylvania.
Where Rocky and Bullwinkle's
archrivals,
Boris and Natasha,
and their fearless leader...
Fearless Leader...
were cooking up
their latest scheme
for taking over the world,
when their plans
were crushed
by the fall
of the Iron Curtain.
Whas going on?
But, while the citizens
of Pottsylvania
rejoiced in their
new found freedom...
Yay!
...Fearless Leaderand
his cohorts went underground,
where upon they embarked
upona terrifying plan,
a plan that would take them
to a strange new land
where the line between cartoon
and reality is so thin,
thas is hard to tell
one from the other.
A place where with
the right special effects,
it might just be possible
to break through...
to the otherside!
It was a beautiful and smoggy
day at Phony Pictures Studio,
where an ambitious junior
executive named Minnie Mogul
was busy searching
for a hot new script.
Too intelligent.
Hello, Minnie.
Holy mackerel!
Who areyou?
Three ofthe most
terrifying villains
in the history of
children's television.
How do you do?
Nice to meetyou.
What do you want?
We were wondering,
how would you like
toproduce the Rocky
andBullwinkle movie?
I'd love to.
I love it.
What is it?
Is classic American cartoon
from early '60s.
Mm-hmm.
Listen, Minnie...
we're stuck in reruns.
You're looking for a project.
Maybe we can help
each other out.
This contractgives
youallrights
to The Rockyand
Bullwinkle Show.
All you have to do
is sign right here
andyour fiirst
producing endeavor
is as goodas gold.
Whas the matter?
I can't sign a contract
that will help three ruthless
villains take over the world.
I just can't.
Why not!?
My pen's out ofink.
Use mine.
Okay.
And then through the miracle
of computer-generated
digital technology...
Minnie reached
into the televisionset
and signedthe contract.
But when she tried
to pull the contractout...
the expensive animated
characters
were instantly converted
into evenmore expensive
motionpicture stars.
Hey...
how did that happen?
We're attached
to the project.
But even though thepun
was weak,
the contract was ironclad.
And the three villains
walked out of the studio
and into the real world,
while Minnie marched
straight into the offiice
of Phony Pictures' C.E.O.,
P. G. Biggershot.
But unfortunately for her,
when she pitched her project
to the powerful executive,
she ran into
an unexpected snag.
I don't like
moose pictures.
So while Minnie's motion
picture plans were stymied,
back in Frostbite Falls,
Bullwinkle got a rare flash
of inspiration.
It is kinda hot in here.
I've been inspiring
for hours.
- Hey, where areyou going?
- I'm going to the White House,
to talk to the president
about the trees.
So Rocky and Bullwinkle set off
on the road to Washington.
I don't know, Bullwinkle,
it looks a little jammed.
Horsefeathers!
How bad could it be?
Rocky:
Look at all the red tape!
Don't worry,
little buddy.
I'm sure the president
will send for us
after all the letters
I wrote him.
Why, I bet
any second now...
or two...
or three... or four...
There the matter seemed
destined to rest...
until six months later,
in Washington, D. C.,
when idealistic,
warm hearted,
and beautiful FBI agent,
Karen Sympathy,
was summoned to the office
of hard-boiled FBI director,
"Cappy" Von Trappment.
Agent Sympathy,
given all your bungled
assignments in the past,
I suppose
you were wondering
why I picked you
for this mission.
Yes, sir.
Sympathy,
allow me to be frank.
Thisjob requires
the ideal FBI agent...
someone tough,
someone
hard-bitten,
emotionless.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir. Tough!
Hard-boiled! Unemotional!
Good.
Are you familiar with
The Rocky and Bullwinkle Show?
Oh-hh!
I mean... ahem...
I've heard of it.
171/2 short minutes later...
Cappy:
Mr. President,
this is a regular
networkTV station.
Announcer:
PresidentSignoff,
standing firm lyin
the middle of the road.
But lookwhat happens
when we switch to cable...
For the last six months,
a cartoon villain from the old
Rocky and Bullwinkle Show
named Fearless Leader
has been buying up
every single hour of cable
programming in this country,
forming asingle
gigantic network
called RBTV,
or "Really Bad Television."
According to our sources,
three days from now
Fearless Leader plans
to broadcast TV shows
so terrible,
they'll turn anyone
who watches them
into a mindless zombie,
incapable of independent
thought.
Totally different
than regular TV.
The RBTV broadcast
starts at noon on Saturday.
By 8:00 that night,
Fearless Leaderwill have
hypnotized enough viewers
that he can go on the air
and make the whole country
vote for him as president.
Well...
thas no good...
No.
No, I mean...
I want to be president again.
Yes.
We all know that, sir.
Can't the Pentagon
do something about this?
Any recommendations?
General Foods?
General Store?
General Admission?
We can't think ofanything,
Mr. President.
Can't the FBI
do anything, Cappy?
We've already sent three
crack agents to infii ltrate
RBTV...
They've disappeared.
Is almost as if there were
a mole in the White House.
Thas just ridiculous.
Yes, sir.
Mr. President,
our only chance is to call on
those two gallant heroes...
who successfully foiled
Fearless Leader's schemes
forworld conquest...
backwhen he posed
a threat in the 1960s.
If anyone can stop him,
they can.
Rocky and Bullwinkle!
Rocky and Bullwinkle, sir.
Sympathy, you've got
exactly 46 hours...
to get Rocky and Bullwinkle
to New York
and shut down
Fearless Leader's
broadcast.
Thank you, sir.
I won't fail.
Just be careful.
We've already lost three
ofour best agents.
So good luck.
Oh, sir,
just one thing...
How do I get Rocky and
Bullwinkle out ofreruns?
I don't know.
Fearless Leader
and those other two
got out somehow,
didn't they?
Figure it out!
And, Sympathy,
remember,
we only care
about results.
Within the hour, Karen
was enroute to LosAngeles.
She was determined to give
the Rocky and Bullwinkle movie
the green light.
Rocky:
Whas happening?
Cobs and shuckins, Rock!
The president must be
beaming us to Washington!
Thas not the president,
Bullwinkle.
Thas agreenlight
from Hollywood.
Those TV people
musve changed their minds.
Whoa!
Goodbye, sonny!
Narrator:
I'llbeback forhiatus, Ma!
Bullwinkle:
Hang on, Rocky!
Narrator:
Mama!
Oof!
Hokey smoke!
Areyou all right?
Yeah, but I think
we're on the wrong show.
Look how well
they drew that girl!
Is you.
Is really you!
Rocky...
and Bull...
Bull...
- Bull...
- I believe the word...
you're searching for
is "winkle."
Bullwinkle.
Hey, what network
areyou from?
I'm not from any network.
Agent Karen Sympathy, FBI.
Listen, you guys.
I've been sent here because...
Somebody's coming.
We gotta get out ofhere fast.
Quick!
Les go to a commercial!
What is this,
PBS?
Come on!
Les go!
- Hold it right there, lady!
- Just a second!
Er...
this way!
Hey, wait for me!
Ow!
Bullwinkle, I don't think
we're on television anymore.
Bullwinkle, can you rappel?
Sure! I've been repelling
viewers foryears!
Never mind.
Get on my back.
I'll carry you down.
What about Rocky?
He's a flying squirrel.
He'll manage.
Er...
Bullwinkle:
Aah!
Ooh!
Hurry up, Rocky!
Fly down!
Just like old times.
Aaah!
Oh, my God!
Are you all right?
Rocky! You okay?
Sure, just out ofpractice.
Moments later...
Agent Sympathy, can I ask you
something personal?
Didyou watch ourshow?
Did I watch your show?
I lovedyour show!
- You did?
- Sure!
Ever since I was a kid
I wanted to have adventures
like you guys.
Thas why
I joined the Bureau.
Rocky and Bullwinkle:
Really?
But that little girl
doesn't exist anymore, Rocky.
They don't want her kind
in the FBI.
I do exist! I do exist!
Let me out!
- There's something in your eye.
- No, there's not.
Ow!
All right, we need
to get to New York
and stop Fearless Leader's
broadcast within 40 hours.
Rocky:
Waitaminute!
Why don't we take an airplane?
Because then it wouldn't be
a road movie. Whee-ee!
Karen:
We don'tknow how, but Fearless
Leader, Boris and Natasha
escaped from the cartoon world
into the real world.
- So the president sent me to...
- Ofcourse!
The president got my letters
about the trees!
What trees?
The Frostbite Falls Forest.
I knew he would respond.
- Look, we don't have time...
- Bullwinkle,
this lady isn't here
about the trees.
- She's from the FBI.
- FBI?
Didn't they take
our show off the air?
- You mean the FCC.
- Didn't they like it either?
Look...
Can you believe we used
to get paid for this routine?
Would you listen
to me, please?
Finally, in a crisis
of conscience,
Karen decided
to tell...
an untruth.
Okay, you're right.
The president sent me
because he wants you to head...
the... er...
Committee for Animated
Wildlife Preservation.
Ooh!
Okay?
Thas not
whatyou said before!
I was building up to it.
Gee, what kind
ofmusic is that?
- Hip-hop.
- Okay...
but I'd still like to know
what kind ofmusic it is.
Thas funny,
the radio's off.
Oh, thas just Bullwinkle.
His antlers pick up everything.
Bullwinkle,
cover up your nose!
Okay. I was just
gettin' jiggy with it.
They sure don't have music
like that in Frostbite Falls.
Agent Sympathy,
have things changed a lot
in the last 35 years?
Karen:
Just you waitandsee.
As dawn broke over
the City ofAngels,
our valiant protagonists
boldly rocketed
toward the beckoning horizon
of a strange new
three-dimensional world,
and the unimaginable perils
that lay on the road ahead.
While on the otherside
of the country,
at Fearless Leader's
headquarters,
Really Bad Television...
Fearless Leader:
My fellow Pottsylvanians,
this is the quality control.
It will enhance
or degrade the quality
of what ever you run
through it.
If the input show
is bad enough,
the quality control will
exaggerate its mind-numbing
properties...
until the audience is
completely hypnotized.
So, Badenov,
these shows had better
be terrible!
Don't worry,
Fearless Leader.
We are ready
to test the machine.
Ready to test machine!
Put on your protective glasses!
Put on protective glasses!
Fearless Leader:
Badenov, proceed with the test!
Badenov, proceed
with test!
Sometimes, is not so easy
being Fearless Leader.
Announcer:
Coming toyour TV,
brand new exciting shows
of the highest fun!
So, if adventure is
your best ingredient,
try the action with...
Clever Spies Crush
the Enemy On Monday!
And the laughter never
gets away...
with Three Funny and Wacky
Spies & Their Horse,
Who Will Also Be a Spy.
It works!
Yeah!
Silence!
Is a message from my mole
at the White House!
Moose and squirrel!
Moose and squirrel.
How many times in the past
have they stood between me...
and my dreams ofglory?
How many times have they
foiled my plans...
with their bungling
interference?
Er... 28?
Quiet, idiot!
They must never reach
New York alive.
I want you to destroy them
personally.
After 30 years of waiting,
one more chance to crush
moose and squirrel!
Oh, Fearless Leader,
you are so good to us!
There has never been
a way to actually destroy
a cartoon character...
until now!
What about in that movie,
RogerRabbit?
Shut up!
This is totally different!
There has never been
a way to actually destroy
a cartoon character...
untilnow!
This is the computer
degenerating imagery.
Show them, Sydney.
The "computer
degenerating imagery"
or C.D.I.,
as I like to call it,
is totally user-friendly.
Just index
the binary codes
of the animated image
you're gonna degenerate
and the C.D.I. 'll dismantle
the digital image
on your film stock. 'Kay?
Bring in
the test subject!
No, no!
Oh, this is what
I was afraid of.
I've been tricked!
Please, don't send me there.
Please don'tsendme there!
Now I know what happened
to my friend Freddy the Ferret
and those cute
little bunnies...
Okay, now all you gotta do
is type in an address
and send him where all
worthless cyberjunk ends up...
the Internet!
Let go of my paw.
You broke my nail!
Aah!
So, thas all
there is to it.
Here's the manual
and she's all yours.
I assumeyou're both
computer literate?
We don't need computerweapon
to kill moose and squirrel!
We've been trying to kill
moose and squirrel for 35 years.
And we've never
even come close.
Exactly.
Andso, armed
with the C.D.I.,
and a truck load full of
really silly cartoon weaponry,
Boris and Natasha set off
to blast Rocky and Bullwinkle
from the face of the Earth,
and immediately
got stuck in traffic.
While back at RBTV...
Dear Diary,
soon the presidency
will be mine.
As for this FBI agent,
Karen Sympathy,
I will deal with her
the same way I dealt...
with the three agents
before her.
At the moment oftruth,
she'll be plugged directly
into the quality
control current
and turned into a helpless...
mindless...
vegetable.
Vegetable.
...A barrel ofmoney
Maybe we're ragged
and funny
Bullwinkle:
But we'll travel along
Rocky:
Singing a song...
Karen:
Youknow, lusedtobe
justlikeyouguys.
Cheerful, optimistic.
But if there's one thing
I learned in the FBI,
is that life
is not a cartoon.
Whoa!
Look out!
Aah!
Out ofthe car!
Whas the rush?
All right, I'm going,
I'm going!
Are you all right?
Ofcourse.
Guess I should have figured.
Boris:
Butnotforlong!
Hey, Rock.
They look kind offamiliar.
Yeah! Haven't we seen
those two somewheres before?
Whas with the cannon?
Is traditional!
Run!
Karen:
Boris Badenov!
I've seen you on TV.
You're a crooked, creepy,
no-good rotten worm.
Oh, thank you.
You're slimy,
sneaky, sleazy...
Please! You'll turn
my pretty head.
You're asadisticspy
anda...
and a...
really, really
bad person!
Stop!
You're embarrassing me.
Where is boom?
Boris, darling,
maybe is time
to update our technique.
Fearless Leader!
We're so happy you called!
Haveyou liquidated
moose and squirrel?
Did you use the C.D. I?
Yes?
Are you talking to me?
Er...
Then who else
are you talking to?
Are you talking to me?
Well, I'm the only one here...
soyou must be
talking to me...
and you are lying!
Now catch moose and squirrel
and next time
use the C.D.I. On them!
Rocky:
ButKaren, we can'tride to
therescuein astolen truck.
Yeah!
Why couldn'tyou steal
something with bucket seats?
Bullwinkle!
Just kidding, Rock.
Isjust not right.
Is not right?
What are you talking about?
They wrecked our car!
They were trying to kill us!
But we're supposed
to be the heroes.
Rocky,
is not 1964 anymore.
You're in the real world now.
Rocky's right, Karen.
And two rights
don't make a wrong.
Bullwinkle, thas not
what you mean.
You mean two rights
do make a wrong?
No!
I always thought two rights
made a U-turn.
I don't know how much more
ofthis I can take.
Well, les fii nd out.
Two U-turns make a circle,
two circles make
a figure eight,
two figure eights
make a butterfly...
Look, all I want from
you guys are results. Okay?
It was their first fight.
Andso, racked with
internal conflicts,
they made their way
across the Great Divide
and onto the great plains.
Bullwinkle:
Hey, look at that, Rock!
What a strange looking town!
Andwhile Bullwinkle
ponderedthemodern world,
severalstates back,
Boris andNatasha...
were still tramping
along theroad.
Ifonlywe had
a helicopter.
Butsince they were
in themiddle ofthe desert,
there was obviously
no chance whatsoever
of finding
a helicopter.
Boris...
Look!
Oh, damn!
Nevermind.
Natasha, quick.
Natasha:
Whatluck!
Great googly moogly!
Holy cow!
What the?
Hey, listen,
gol-darn it!
Thas the third time
this month.
I'm sick and tired
of shopping for helicopters.
Boy, ifl had a missile,
I'd blow your buns
right out ofthe sky!
Yes, Boris and Natasha
were back in business,
but they had no way
of discovering the route
our heroes had taken...
Hey!
You can'tdo that!
Interstate 1,
just outside Red Bait,
Oklahoma, darling.
- Cheaters.
- Thankyou!
And high above
our unsuspecting heroes...
Natasha:
- Statepolice?
- Yes, ma'am?
This is FBI Agent
KarenSympathy...
All right,
I'm sorry I yelled.
Butyou don't
understand.
I can't mess up
this time.
"This time"?
Was there a last time?
Tell us about
yourself, Karen.
Lesjust say
I've made...
mistakes.
Look, I can't blow this one.
The whole world depends on it,
and I can't do it
withoutyour help.
Agent Sympathy,
you can count on
Bullwinkle and me.
- We won't letyou down.
- No.
Thanks, you guys.
You know,
I'm glad Cappy picked me
for this mission.
I think we're gonna make
a great team.
- Huh?
- Oh, no.
And just as
this sentimental moment
had mercifully
come to a close,
our heroes were pulled over
by two state troopers
and a cameraman
from the hit TV show,
Made Up Stories From
the Real Highway Patrol.
Step out of the vehicle
with your hands up, please!
Is okay, Officers,
I'm with the FBl...
Step out of the vehicle now!
Hey, Rock,
your face is all blurry.
So's yours.
This truck matches
the description...
ofa vehicle reported stolen
outside Red Bait, Oklahoma,
just a couple ofhours ago.
You are under arrest
for grand theft auto
and for impersonating
FBI agent, Karen Sympathy.
I am FBI Agent
Karen Sympathy!
Like fun you are.
We both know Agent
Karen Sympathy...
has a heavy
Pottsylvanian accent.
We heard her on the radio.
But she really is
with the FBI!
Yeah, and I'm really
john Goodman.
Les get in the car.
Just one minute, Officer!
Wherever she goes,
we go.
Yeah, thas right.
We're a team!
Well, she's going off
to the federal pen...
to break rocks for
the next fiiveyears.
Okay, well,
don't forget to write.
I guess we could always
appear atyour trial...
as animated character
witnesses!
No!
Rocky, Bullwinkle...
is your duty to get
to New York by 8:00 PM tomorrow.
Rocky:
Karen, we can't
leaveyounow.
Hey, I'm an FBI agent,
remember?
I'll straighten this out,
and catch up with you later.
But we've never been
in the real world before!
Oh, you'll do great.
I know it.
Hey!
What about our faces?
Oh...
sorry.
Wait, you can't just leave them
on the side ofthe road
like that.
They don't even know
where they are.
Don't worry, ma'am.
They're animals.
They'll forage.
Bullwinkle:
C'mon, Rock,
time's a-wastin'!
We owe it to Karen
to see the president
about the trees!
Trees?
Bullwinkle, we have
to go to New York.
We don't have time
to get to Washington!
This is no time to worry
about getting the washing done.
Not "washing done."
Washing-ton!
A ton?!
Well, that is
a lot oflaundry.
Bullwinkle, that joke
just won't wash!
Well, you can't
blame me for drying!
I think I'll fly ahead.
Butit was just no use.
Faced with
the utter hopelessness
of their predicament,
the razor-sharp mind
of Bullwinkle
quickly formulated
a daring plan.
Help! Help!
Somebody please help!
Help!
So on they walked,
two lone figures...
making their way
through a foreign and hostile
live-action landscape.
I thought you said
we were in Oklahoma.
Would you like to
narrate this movie?
No.
And so on they walked,
two lone figures...
making their way
through a foreign and hostile
live-action landscape.
They walked until
their thumbs ached,
but no one wanted
to take a chance...
ona 6'7"
talking moose
and a flying squirrel
who couldn't fly.
I could f-fly if I had to!
Whoa!
Ow!
Kinda makes you
feel discouraged.
Maybe we should be a little
more aggressive.
Stop!
This movie's gettin'
kind of...
Don't say it!
Two-dimensional.
Yes, things were beginning
to look mighty dark...
for our intrepid heroes...
It is gettin'
kinda hard to see.
Bullwinkle, he means
our situation.
Oh!
Wait a minute, boys,
there's a couple of headlights.
I think is...
Yes! Yes!
It was a couple of fresh-faced
college students...
named Martin and Lewis.
Come on, Rock!
Is a convertible!
All right,
buckle up now, fellas.
Yeah, safety fii rst!
So where doyou boys
go to school?
We're undergrads
at Wossamotta U.
Rocky and Bullwinkle:
Wossamotta U!
My old alma mater!
Bullwinkle was a big football
star at Wossamotta U.
- Quarter-buck!
- I thoughtyou looked familiar.
Where are you fellows
coming from, anyway?
Thankyou!
We've been on the road,
looking for America.
Lewis:
We've been looking
forAmerica all day.
Martin:
We just can't find it.
Lewis:
Man, we're exhausted.
Bullwinkle:
Gee, fellas, perhaps
you've been looking too hard.
Maybe America is
all around you...
in a thousand different
beautiful manifestations.
Wouldn't you say so,
young people?
Yeah, right.
Rocky, haven't we passed
this town before?
Following ominously above them
in the Midwestern sky,
Boris conceived
a sinister plan.
Flying ahead
to Wossamotta U...
the two villains made
asizable donation
to the college...
in Bullwinkle's name...
prompting the college president
to bestow upon Bullwinkle...
an honorary moosters degree.
And when moose is at podium
for acceptance speech,
I'll be on water tower
with C.D.I.
There was only one problem...
Wossamotta U. Had
no watertower.
Can't even find
water fountain.
Their entire scheme seemed
to be on the verge ofcollapse,
until they hit upon an
incredibly ingenious plan...
Together:
What?!
Dawn brokeat 6... 00AM.
The day of Fearless Leader's
deadly broadcast...
had finally arrived.
And there was Karen,
toiling away
under the watchful eyes
ofa tall, blond,
incredibly handsome,
Swedish-American prison guard
named Ole.
Several states away,
our hitchhiking heroes
were doggedly making
their way to New York,
but little did theyknow
they were driving...
straight into Boris Badenov's
sinister snare.
Heavens to Betsy!
The car is sticking
its tongue out at me!
No, is not.
Isjust a fax.
- A what?
- A fax!
Don't you guys know
about faxes?
Yeah, don'tyou know
about E-mail?
Sure. A fax is
a little red critter...
that steals geese
and chickens.
Half of them are males and
the other half are e-males.
No, is a way of transmitting
computer-generated information
across great distances
in the blink of an eye.
Well, I was close.
Lewis:
Oh, hey! Is for you.
Hokeysmoke, Bullwinkle!
Wossamotta U. Wants to
give you an honorary degree.
And the ceremony is today!
Bullwinkle, we don't
have time to go.
We've gotta get
to New York!
Oh, woe is me!
I must have my degree!
I'll put it on the wall...
for everyone tosee.
I guess if is
in the name of education...
Oh, it was a happy day
at Wossamotta U.,
scene of Bullwinkle's
football triumphs years ago.
Gee, it looks so different.
Everything's in
the same place, but...
Well, Wossamotta U.'s been
a live-action university
since the show went
into reruns back in '64.
I thought the buildings
looked a lot more realistic.
Say, whereyou guys been
all this time, huh?
Reruns.
You know thas never gonna
happen to us, right?
Well, anyway,
there's still a lot...
ofanti-cartoon feeling
on campus these days.
Hokey smoke,
Bullwinkle!
Is some kind
of demonstration.
What are the kids
protesting these days?
Is it a civil rights march?
Not really...
Is it an anti-war rally?
No, not exactly.
Tell 'em, fellas.
Is a anti-moose march.
Yes, itseems that
araging controversy
had broken out among
the students that very morning
over the decision to give
Bullwinkle an honorary degree...
Gee, Bullwinkle,
I guess is true.
You can't
go home again.
Why, Rocky!
Whatever doyou mean?
Wossamotta U. Is home!
Rocky:
Oh, brother!
Look! There's
the animated freak now!
My fans!
Bullwinkle,
these aren't fans.
This is an angry mob.
Butin the face of danger,
our insipid hero...
bravely made his way
through the angry crowd.
You mean "intrepid hero,"
don'tyou?
No-oo...
Hundreds of miles away,
in RedBait, Oklahoma,
it was time for
the prisoners' daily helping
of disgusting slop.
ButKarenSympathy
hadsucceededin making Ole,
the simple-minded
but incredibly handsome
prison guard,
fall madly in love
with her.
Presently, Karen promisedto
let him take her to the movies
ifhe would help her
break out of jail.
Could we hold hands
in the movie theatre?
Of course we could, Ole.
But how would we
eat our popcorn?
Well, we could eat
our popcorn with one hand...
and hold hands
with the other.
But what ifl want a soda?
Look...
I'm sure we can
work this out.
Good morning, students.
Today Wossamotta U.
Honors one of our own...
As the students vented
their collective spleen
at Bullwinkle,
RocketJ. Squirrel anxiously
surveyed the raging crowd
for signs of danger.
And suddenly,
his sharp little eyes
picked out the terrifying
figure of Boris Badenov
near the top
of the watertower.
Hey! That guy's not
a college student!
...that we present
this honorary degree...
to Bullwinkle J. Moose.
Good morning, children!
Today's lecture
is about trees.
Bullwinkle, look out!
Is a trap!
ButRocky's voice
couldn'tcarry
overthestridentshouts
ofthestudentbody.
With no alternative in sight,
Rocky tried one more time
to summon up those faded
aeronautical skills
that had once made him
a household name.
But just then, Boris managed
to turn on the C.D.I.
Aha!
Yes, it looked like
curtains for Bullwinkle...
Got to...
save...
Bullwinkle!
Rocky:
Whoa!
"Bad command or fii le name.
Press any key to continue."
Which one is "any" key?
Rocky:
Look out!
Oh, no!
With asingle blow,
Rockysent the C.D.I.
Hurtling through thesky...
where upon Boris
single-mindedly
reached out to catch
the catapulted computer,
forgetting as he did,
one vitally important
piece of information...
I ain't a cartoon no more.
Aahh!
Darling!
Ow!
Rocky:
Mayday!
You like me!
You really like me!
I guess I've
lost the knack.
I'll never fly again.
Yes, without trees,
where would
the birdies live?
Forced to migrate
to the cities,
they would take jobs away
from local pigeons.
Bullwinkle,
they're listening!
Yes, Bullwinkle's speech
was soinane...
that thestudents
couldn'tunderstand
a wordhe was saying,
andconsequently found
nothing to object to.
So RockyandBullwinkle
bade a fondfarewell
to thehallowedwalls
ofWossamotta U.
Don't forget to write,
oldbuddy.
Bullwinkle,
who are you talking to?
I don't know,
but is like
talking to a wall.
I want to thank you fellas
for bringing unity back
to this troubled campus
with your ludicrous remarks.
Martin and I would like
to wish you guys
luck against
Fearless Leader.
Yeah, and we would come
help you guys, but...
we don't wanna
get hurt.
Yeah, man, we're not
going near him.
Yeah, until we metyou guys,
we almost totally lost
faith in America.
Lewis:
Youknow, andwe
lostfaith in our car.
I used to think
our carwas really cool,
but now isjust
always dirty.
And running low on gas.
Yeah, but since we met you guys,
we love it again.
Yeah, the car is totally back.
So, as a gesture of our
appreciation,
we want you guys
to have it.
Yeah, so,
take the car.
Really?
Is yours.
Whoa!
Rocky:
Gee, fellas, thanks.
Yeah, thanks!
You do know how
to drive, right?
Please!
What moose can't
drive a automobile?
Rocky:
Oh, brother!
Never said I could
drive it well.
Andjustas Rockyand
Bullwinkle got back
on the road,
Boris and Natasha emerged
from the student infiirmary,
ready foraction.
Meanwhile, in Cow Tip,
Oklahoma...
Ole,
why don't you go
get the tickets,
and I'll park the truck?
Gosh, Karen!
I've never had
so much fun
in my whole life.
Is like...
Is like there was always
a little boy trapped...
somewhere inside me,
and now that I've met you,
I can finally
let him out.
Please, two for
the love movie.
There you go.
Tack.
Now, thas not verynice.
Shut up.
As for Rocky and Bullwinkle,
they were gently motoring along
an Illinois interstate...
Hey, Rock,
there's that same town again!
Areyou sure we're
going the right way?
Bullwinkle, look out!
Whoa!
Rocky:
Sorry!
Bullwinkle, we're not
going to Chicago!
We are now.
As our heroes found themselves
racing toward Chicago,
little did they realize
that only a few miles behind...
And back in Cow Tip,
Oklahoma,
the only person in this movie
more clueless than Bullwinkle
faithfully waited for Karen
to get back
from parking his truck.
But our heroine was already
passing through Indiana...
where she was about tomake
an ominous discovery.
Announcer:
For watching miserable people
suffer in daytime,
is The Jenny Spy Show.
Are you sorry that
you called her fat?
Yes! Yes!
Oh, no!
Not already!
Yes, Fearless Leader's
hypnotic broadcast...
was already underway.
Announcer:
You are watching premiere
broadcast of RBTV.
Ah, I love my RBTV.
Fearless Leader!
The zombombidor shows
that 30% of despised,
decadent Americans
are already total zombies!
Good!
I'll address the nation
at exactly 8:00 PM
Eastern standard time.
Back at the RedBait
Prison Farm,
Karen's daring escape
had not gone unnoticed.
Meanwhile on the bustling
boulevards ofChicago,
Illinois,
Rocky and Bullwinkle
were about to discover
they had considerable
troubles of their own.
There they are!
Motorist #1:
Hello!
Motorist #2:
Look out!
Smush them!
Duck!
Well, mercy me!
Excuse us!
Bullwinkle!
Mamma mia!
Is Rocky and Bullwinkle!
And you thought
I couldn't drive.
Bullwinkle!
Look out!
Hold her steady, poopsie.
Is time to say goodbye...
to moose and squirrel.
- Ahh!
- Oh, no!
Hasta la vista, baby!
Boris:
Hey, poopsie...
whas happening?
I think you degenerated
wrong special effect.
And while Rocky and Bullwinkle
were making their getaway,
Boris and Natasha were still
high above the Chicago streets,
but with one small difference.
Boris and Natasha:
No helicopter.
And as luck would have it,
a travelling mattress salesman
just happened to be
passing bybelow.
Matresses for sale!
How do I do it?
Volume!
Ouch. Oy.
Now thas a soft mattress.
Temporarily outofdanger,
Rocky and Bullwinkle
breathed a sigh of relief.
At the same time,
Boris and Natasha
were forced to rent...
an econoclass Chevy Metro from
the Cheapo Rent-A-Car Company
in order to resume the chase.
This slight delay gave
our heroes the opportunity
to effect a not her beautiful,
if implausibly coincidental,
reunion.
Whoa!
Whoops.
Hey, you lunatic!
Why don'tyou watch
whereyou're...
Rocky!
Bullwinkle!
Karen!
Guys, I missed you so much.
I was so worried about you...
I didn't mean to...
I mean...
Good work,
Agents Rocky, Bullwinkle.
Lookit, we have six hours
to get to New York.
- The Big Apple!
- Bullwinkle, please!
RBTV is already turning
people into zombies.
But Karen,
why aren't you injail?
Oh...
er...
I was pardoned.
Freeze! Freeze!
Must be some kind
of clerical error.
Officer:
You're under arrest.
Keep your hands
high above your head!
Andjust to think...
Is the opening
of moose season.
Bailiff:
The states of California,
Arizona, NewMexico,
Colorado, Kansas, Oklahoma,
Missouri, Illinois,
Indiana and Ohio,
versus KarenSympathy,
Rocket J. Squirrel
and BullwinkleJ. Moose.
Judge Cameo presiding.
Who speaks for the defense?
BullwinkleJ. Moose,
attorney at law.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
The defendants
are charged with
grand theft auto:
One count;
breaking outofjail...
one count, .
Impugning the character
of a prison guard...
- Ooh!
- One count...
reckless driving:
Four counts;
talking to the audience...
- What?!
- Five counts, .
Criminally bad punning:
18 counts.
And three dukes
and seven earls!
Make that 19.
Hey! Hey!
Counselor,
call your first witness.
Yes, Your Honor.
As our first witness,
the defense calls...
Karen Sympathy!
Oh, please, no.
Doyou, Karen Sympathy,
swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth and
nothing but the truth,
so helpyou God?
I do.
Ha!
A little late!
Oh!
Ms. Sympathy,
isn't it true that when our
convertible
was destroyed
in Monument Valley...
the first thing you did
was to steal...
somebody else's truck?
Um...
That depends on how you
legally defii ne the word "steal,"
because I believe...
And didn't you escape
from prison...
by telling that poor
trusting prison guard
that you would let him
takeyou to the movies?
Well, I thought we might have
time ifwe went to a matinee...
Isn't it true you never
meant to see a film at all?!
Yes...
is true.
And didn't you tell
Rocky and me...
that you got out of prison
because you got a pardon?
Yes...
I did do that!
Isn't it true you have
no respect for the law
or anything else?
No!
I was just trying to
complete my mission!
I was only supposed
to care about results!
And how come Rocky and me
are still cartoons...
and Boris and
Natasha aren't?
I don't know!
I didn't write the movie!
I'm only one
ofthe characters!
Your witness, Counselor.
What are
the teams again?
Bullwinkle, you're supposed
to be the defense attorney.
You just proved
we're guilty.
Yes, but now our
consciences are clean,
and the healing
can begin.
Your Honor,
is time the court
showed the world
that no quarterwill be given
to celebrity defendants.
- Celebrity?
- Mm-hmm.
Did you say celebrity?
Where are myglasses?
Oh, my Gawd!
Is Rocky and Bullwinkle!
Oh, my God!
I love, I loveyour show!
Your Honor!
And you,
Mr. District Attorney,
I'd like to point something
out to you in the penal code,
section C, paragraph22.
"Celebrities
are above the law."
This case is dismissed.
Moments later, our heroes
were back on the road,
with a mere three hours
to get from Rabid Froth, Ohio
to New York.
Three hours!
If only we had
an airplane.
Hokey smoke!
Look!
Gosh!
Another wild coincidence.
Afternoon, folks.
Together:
Hi!
You got any planes left?
Well, lesjust kinda
give a look-see...
I thinkwe have one left.
They've got tobehere
somewhere, Boris, darling!
Keep the change!
Oh! This is gonna get
my stepson a new trial.
Boris:
Bingo!
Natasha:
Goody! Goody!
Hey! Hey!
Y'all can't get in there.
She won't hold the weight!
You'll never reach
the end ofthe runway.
The wings will come off.
Oh, God!
Oh, crap!
Boris pushed the little Metro
for all it was worth...
We've got them, Boris,
we've got them!
They've got us, Rocky,
they've got us!
But at that very moment,
Boris and Natasha's rental
agreement suddenly expired
and they were immediately
blockaded...
by the dedicated agents ofthe
Cheapo Rent-A-Car Company.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, you can do it!
You old bird!
Come on!
Although Boris and Natasha
tried feverishly to complete
the necessary paperwork...
Look!
It was too late.
- Stop! Stop!
- Stop!
Stop!
That certainly
was a close one.
Les just hope this thing
makes it all the way
to New York.
Where did we go wrong, Boris?
We tried
to blow them up.
to have them arrested.
We tried
to degenerate them.
We tried to smush them.
Yes, and we never
even came close.
Oh, Boris,
what are we
doing, darling?
We been trying to catch
moose and squirrel...
ever since
we first got drawn.
We tried to stab them,
shoot them, smash them,
smush them, crush them,
bash them, mash them
and they don't even
know our names.
I'm tired
ofall this, Boris.
I don't want to be
spy no more.
Les faceit, darling,
we suck.
We can never catch
moose and squirrel.
Boris...
don't you want to have
little Boris? Hmmm?
Little Natasha?
Wouldn't it be
wonderful?
We could rent cottage
by sea of Pottsylvania
and teach them how to lie,
and cheat and be rotten.
They would be worst
children in world!
They'd be monsters.
It would be awful!
We could be so happy.
Telephone.
Hoboy.
Saved by bell!
Well, Badenov,
did the C.D.I. Work?
Oh, it...
it works all right!
So moose and squirrel
are dead, then?
Well, is funny
you should ask...
Yes, Fearless Leader!
We killed moose
and squirrel!
Excellent!
Wait there for
my private jet.
I want you both beside
my side for the big broadcast.
- Natasha...
- Yes, darling?
Why did you
tell him that?!
Because, Boris!
Moose and squirrel
can't reach New York...
by 8:00 PM in
that little plane.
And what ifthey did?
So what?
How could they
stop us now?
Practicallywhole country
is zombifiied!
We've won, Boris!
We've won!
Just the way
I planned it!
On their way to New York,
our heroes were soon
to discover...
that old Jeb was right.
She won't pull up,
we're too heavy!
Rocky,
can you fly Bullwinkle down?
I don't think so,
Karen.
He's a huge moose!
I beg your pardon!
I'm as trim as a young fawn!
You weigh 400
imaginary pounds!
Yeah, but
is all "mooscle."
Bullwinkle, can you fly
an airplane?
What moose can't
fly a aeroplane?
Rocky, you'll have
to fly me down.
I can't do that, Karen.
I can't fly again!
I've lost the knack.
Bullwinkle,
take the controls.
Okay.
Listen to me, Rocky.
- You can do this.
- I can't!
- I knowyou can do this.
- I just can't!
This is everything you taught me
since I was a little kid.
All you have to do
is believe in...
Rocky:
Karen!
Look out for the sign!
Aaah!
Here goes n-nothing!
Gotyou!
Rocky!
Uh-oh!
Together:
Bullwinkle!
Never said
I could fly it well.
See you in New York!
Hang on, Karen!
Hang on!
If I couldjust...
Rocky!
You're flying!
- You're flying!
- Yes, I am!
I certainly am.
Look at me!
I'm flying!
New York City,
here we come!
Yahoo!
Yeah!
What a day, a year,
a life it is!
You know
Well, you know
you had it coming toyou
Now there's not
a lot I can do
Dreamer
A stupid little dreamer
So now you putyour head
in your hands, oh, no!
Whoo!
Boris, darling,
how can you be
so rotten?
When I stop
moose and squirrel
from saving country,
I don't kid around!
Karen looked upon
the brave little squirrel
with a new admiration.
However, she couldn't
help but wonder,
were they too late?
Soaringprecipitously
overRockefellerCenter,
Karen and Rocky found
the entire city of New York
completely zombifiied.
Rocky,
whatever you do,
don't look at the screen!
Touching down
outside RBTV,
the daring duo was soon
to discover
that something else
was terribly wrong.
Where's Bullwinkle?
The speech starts any minute!
I knew we shouldn't
have lefthim.
Bullwinkle and I have never
been apart in 35 years!
Quick, Rock, follow me.
Come, Natasha.
Follow me
to Fearless Leader.
Go! Go!
Oh, Fearless Leader!
We're back!
You are so-oo
happy to see us!
Well, Fearless Leader,
he did it!
Boris Badenov is now
offiicial number one killer...
ofmoose and squirrel.
Excellent, my faithful minions!
Excellent!
Hail, Pottsylvania!
Hail to the black
and the blue!
Hail, Pottsylvania!
Sneaky and crooked,
Through and through...
Down with the good guys,
Up with the boss,
Under the sign of
the triple cross! Hey!
Hail, Pottsylvania!
Hail, hail, hail!
Thankyou, Fearless Leader!
Well, no one can stop
my broadcast now!
FBI! Freeze!
No one but these
chocolate-chewing idiots!
All right, I want anyone
in this room...
who's a Pottsylvanian spy
to putyour hands up now!
That means you, too,
Fearless Leader!
Let me see your hands!
All right,
Agent Sympathy.
We don't want anybody
to be hurt, now do we?
And whatever you're holding,
drop it!
Gladly.
Don't look, Rocky,
is a trick.
Ill turn you into a...
Rocky!
Rocky?
Oh-hh!
Peek-a-boopsie!
Fearless Leader:
Well, Agent Sympathy,
I have waited manyyears
to face an enemy
I could respect...
and I'm still waiting!
No, that was just
a little joke.
But I'm afraid that you
and this flying rodent
have reached the end
of the road.
Now get ready for a taste of
Pottsylvanian hospitability.
Thas ability to put you
in hospital, darling.
Andso, Rocky and Karen's
onlyhope
in the whole wide world
was BullwinkleJ. Moose.
In other words,
they didn'thave aprayer.
For Bullwinkle hadmanaged
to miss New York altogether
and had flown instead
to Washington, D. C.
Gee, New York sure has
changed a lot since my day.
They even moved
the White House here.
Couldn't fii nd the brakes.
Well, as long as I'm here,
I might as well talk to
the president about the trees!
Anybody home?
With onlymoments left
before thebroadcast,
Fearless Leader
hadreleasedRocky...
from thegrip ofzombifiication
sohe could...
share.
As foryou, my friends,
we have planned...
something quite special.
We are hooking you directly
into the quality control.
As soon as we g olive,
the current will pass
throughyourbrain
and you will be turned
intoahelpless,
mindless vegetable.
But don't worry...
it won'thurt.
At least, I never
heard a complaint
from the other vegetables.
I think your ecognize
your three missing colleagues
from the FBI?
Help us! Help!
I'm sorry, Rocky,
I've really done it this time.
Don't worry, Karen,
you need the most faith
when things look
the most hopeless.
Thanks, Rocky.
And, Karen...
this is pretty hopeless.
Look,
we don't care
what you do to us...
just leave America alone!
Ah, America...
I'm proud of you, Karen.
Listen,
Fearless Leader:
If there's one thing
this plucky squirrel
has shown me,
is that you have
to be who you are,
no matter how much pressure
there is to change!
Yay!
Anddespite
this inspiring vindication
ofKaren's innerchild,
Fearless Leader
was unimpressed.
So Karen, Rocky,
andthe entire nation...
werepoisedon thebrink
ofunimaginableperil.
And there is no one...
I said no one...
who can stop me now!
Or, in fact,
was there?
Soyou see,
Mr. President,
all the trees in
Frostbite Falls are gone.
The birds have no place
to put their things.
The children have no place
to build their tree house.
I built them a stump house,
but they say is just
not the same.
Please help
when you have time.
But Gorka,
the horse has swallowed
the transmitter!
Not again!
They certainly enjoy theirTV
at the White House.
Bullwinkle!
Don't watch!
Oh, no!
Notyou, too!
Not a bad show,
eh, Mr. President?
Yes, cheap as itmayseem...
anditcertainly
does seem cheap...
Bullwinkle's head
was so thick
that Fearless Leader's
mind-numbing programming
had absolutely no effect
on him whatsoever.
Come here!
At least one thing
hasn't changed!
TV's as good as ever!
Bullwinkle,
allow me to be frank.
Okay, Frank,
allow me to be
Bullwinkle.
I'm Cappy
Von Trappment, FBI.
I thoughtyou said
your name was Frank.
- Shut up, Bullwinkle!
- Okay, Frank.
As we speak,
99% ofthe country is slobbering
in front ofthe television.
- Whas so strange about that?
- Listen to me!
We haven't heard from Karen,
I think she and Rocky...
are in terrible danger.
You've got to get
to New York!
I thought this was New York.
No, Bullwinkle,
thas Washington out there!
Thas Washington!
Really?
Where's that
little white wig
he always wears?
Is no use.
Fearless Leader's speech starts
in less than two minutes.
There's no way anyone
could get there in time now.
Oh, butterballs!
If only there were
some way of transmitting
computer-generated
animated characters
across great distances
in the blink of an eye.
Bullwinkle!
Thas it!
It is?
Yes, is our
only chance!
We're gonna E-mail you
to Karen in New York.
Well, okay,
but don'tyou think...
she'd rather get flowers?
Just shut up
and hold on!
- Okay!
- One... two...
three!
And squeezing into
the scanner drive...
Bullwinkle found himself inside
the presidential computer.
Butback atRBTV,
Fearless Leader's deadly
countdown hadjustbegun.
15, 14...
12...
And thas when Bullwinkle
snapped into action.
Look, Frank,
solitaire.
I'm sorry, Bullwinkle,
we don't have time
for that!
With the coolagility
ofajungle cat,
our heroic moose grabbed the
corners of the E-mail envelope
and hung on for
the ride ofhis life.
Eight, seven,
si-i...
While time stood virtually
still at RBTV,
Bullwinkle surfed
the information super highway
onhis way tosave the day.
Look, I'm hangin' four!
S-S-Surf's up, dude!
Hang on, Rocky!
I'm coming!
Bullwinkle found himself
inside the RBTV computer...
Five...
Computer:
You've gotmail!
...with only seconds left
to spare and no idea
how to get out.
Four!
Bullwinkle, hurry up!
Click on something!
- "Mine sweeper"?
- Three...
Print! Print!
Andusing his brain,
Bullwinkle activated
the 'print"icon...
but was hein time?
One...
Fearless Leader!
My fellow Americans.
Say hello
to Fearless Leader!
Hello-oo!
You are tired, America.
You are getting verysleepy.
Your mind is mush.
You need help.
Yes, America,
you need me
to run your country.
Youreallyneedme!
So vote forme
asyourleader!
Vote for Fearless Leader!
We will vote
for Fearless Leader.
I will vote
Yes, America, I will bring
order to the government.
This country will finally have
a president you can respect.
Look, is moose!
And no sooner had Bullwinkle
emerged from the printer
than his might yantlers
momentarily jammed
the quality control signal,
reversing the vegetation
process
and bringing Karen and Rocky
miraculously back to life.
Fearless Leader:
Yes, eversince I was
a little sketch
growing up in Pottsylvania,
I dreamed of
ruling the world.
Fearless Leader,
moose is loose!
Get them!
Go! Go!
Now, where were we?
Yes. I always knew
I would rule the world someday.
Thas exactly
whatl'm going to do.
Ouch!
So vote for Fearless Leader
and make a little boy's
dream come true.
We will vote
for Fearless Leader.
Once I am elected,
there will be an end to chaos.
There will be discipline.
Because I'm going to run
this country...
like a well-oiled machine...
I guess you could
call me a neat freak,
but we all have
our little foibles...
That tingles!
...l'll be the president.
And with a single voice,
America will say...
Aaah!
Come on, Rock!
Wrap it all up!
Okay, Karen!
Bullwinkle,
finish the speech!
Ahem...
Good evening, America.
Bullwinkle Moose here,
saying...
Forgot my line.
Just tell 'em
to turn off the TV
and vote for
whoever they want.
Turn off yourTV and vote
for whoever you want!
And whoever wins
the election,
replant the forest
in Frostbite Falls!
And sure enough,
all across America,
RBTV viewers
turned off their sets
and faced
the diffiicult question
of who they actually
wanted to vote for.
And the moment the machine
had been destroyed,
the three vegetables
from the FBI
immediately resumed
their human form.
Thanks, Agent Sympathy.
Freed at last from
Fearless Leader's evil grasp,
even the Pottsylvanian
spies rejoiced.
Well, we won't be
needing this anymore.
Yeah!
Oh, that reminds me!
I should E-mail
that nice Frank
an dthank him for his help.
Bullwinkle, no!
Ooh!
Aaah!
Andso the three villains
were launchedup into
the Internet,
where they wouldbe
heardfrom nomore.
Aaaaaugh!
And so it came to pass
that the election
took place as planned.
Yes, Rocky and Bullwinkle
were stars once again.
RBTV changed its name
from "Really Bad Television"
to "Rocky and Bullwinkle
Television."
Whas the difference?
Sir, there's one thing
I still don't understand.
Why did you pick me
for this mission?
I mean, I'm clearly
not FBI material.
FBI material is what gets
thejob done, Ms. Sympathy.
If you needed an agent
to work with a cartoon
moose and squirrel,
who would you send?
Someone tough,
hard-boiled and cynical?
Or one ofthose
soft, squishy,
lovey-dovey,
idealistic types?
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir...
I think.
Affirmative.
Oh, by the way,
good work.
Well, I really want
to thank you guys
for everything.
And I really...
Well, I really...
I'd really like to say
that I thinkwe made
a great team.
I'd really like to say...
that I think we made
a great team.
And if it hadn't been fo ryou,
I never would have learned...
And if it hadn't been for you,
That what you believe in
when you're young,
can still be true
when you grow up.
Please don't
make me say that.
You gotta say it!
Who is she talking to?
You got me, Rock.
That whatyou believe in
when you'reyoung,
can still be true
when you grow up.
Anyway...
thanks for the adventure.
So long.
Where areyou going?
Um... the movies.
Ofcourse!
The movies!
Hi. Um...
sorry I'm late.
Oh...
thas okay.
And as Karen and Ole finally
went to the movies,
back in Frostbite Falls
the president carried out
the post-hypnotic suggestion
to replant the animated trees.
Mama!
Sonny boy!
Meanwhile, all was well
with our heroes.
Rocky was his oldself again...
Aw, I'll never forget
our trip to New York
to visit
President Washington!
Andso was Bullwinkle.
Yes, glad to be homein their
revitalized little town,
Rocky the flying squirrel
took a well-deserved joyride
through the sunny skies
of Frostbite Falls!
- Bye!
- Bye-bye!
When you're feeling
like you're...
Out of touch
All alone and lost
And drifting
through the night
Just think back
toyounger times
And you'll fii nd
the light
See the world
for a while
Through the eyes
ofa child
You will see
so much wonder
In your days
All thatyou believed
When you were small
Are still the dreams
That guide us all
The mirror shows
you've grown
But reflects
the child in you
If you're lookin' out
On stormy skies
And empty fiields
Afraid to give it
one more try
See yourself
above the clouds
Spread your wings and fly
See the world
for a while
Through the eyes
of a child
You will see
so much wonder
In your days
All that you believed
When you were small
Are still the dreams
you carry on
lmagine what could be
If you just believed in you
When you were young
Who did you wanna be?
What is stopping you
From that dream?
This is whoyou are
Don't be afraid
The child in you
will never fail
The power to believe
is yours alone
No one can ever take
that child away
See the world
for a while
Through the eyes
ofa child
You will see
so much wonder
In your days
All that you believed
When you were small
Are still the dreams
That guide us all
The mirror shows
you've grown
But reflects
the child in you
lfthere's
one thing I could
Say toyou
It would be to try
To makeyour dream
come true
You can do
almost anything
If youjust believe...
If only, only, only
You believe...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org