Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
It stopped.
What's that, Dave?
Nothing.
How we doing?
Oh, we're ready.
You feeling the magic?
Oh, I'm feeling the magic,
all right.
Let's hit 'em.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
Let's hit 'em.
Let's go make $30 million.
Good morning.
Before I begin, let me...
David?
I'll go get help.
Jesus. Jesus, David.
Phone 9-1-1. Phone 9-1-1!
David?
Nick?
Vicky?!
Vicky!
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Everybody else off the bus.
Sound waves.
So, if we know that sound waves
gain wavelength
and lose frequency
as they travel
through more dense materials...
...then the anomalies
in these waves
are the means by which
we can surmise
the fundamental architecture
of our planet.
How are the nails coming,
Christine?
Good.
All right,
let's have a demonstration.
Mr. Acker, Veronica.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Mrs. Limestone,
being a big softie, you know,
loves walks in the park,
bedtime stories,
big romantic.
Loves Chet.
I can't play Chet,
but I'll see what I can do.
Watch the oscilloscope,
all right?
Here we go.
Dr. Joshua Keyes?
Maybe.
Yes or no, sir?
The first one.
Please come with us, sir.
Guys, wh-what's going on?
We don't know, sir.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Your security clearance
is higher than ours.
I have security clearance?
We're just here to
bring you to your jet.
I have a jet?
Hey, Serge.
Ah!
Serge.
Damn!
It's about time.
You're always late.
Let's keep moving, gentlemen.
What am I doing here?
They wouldn't brief me
until you got here.
You know, there are biochemists
everywhere, military.
I hate them.
When are you going to meet
a nice girl
and bring her for dinner?
I'm married to my work.
So am I.
Which makes my wife
my mistress...
that's why I'm still
in love with her.
You were always a romantic.
I love my wife.
Yeah, I know.
I love your wife, too.
I know.
But I don't love your wife.
You know what I mean.
You don't love her
the same way, you know.
It's the French.
I think it's the cheese.
Ah, the cheese.
You're...
you're teasing me, right?
Oh, my...!
Whoa. Wait, these are bodies.
I think we're
in the wrong place here.
Yeah, we're in the wrong place.
No. If you were
in the wrong place,
you would've already been shot.
That's a hell of a greeting.
Serge.
Serge. Yes.
Always a pleasure.
Same here, Thomas.
Dr. Keyes.
- I know.
- Tom Purcell.
Gentlemen, you do realize
that everything here
is totally classified, okay?
At 10:30 a.m. Local time,
32 civilians,
all within a 10-block radius...
died.
They didn't get sick first.
They simply hit the ground dead.
Nerve agent?
Our first guess. No.
They all died
at the same time?
As far as we can tell,
to the second.
This hits CNN in one hour.
I need a reason.
Is there a variation
in sex, age, body type?
They all had pacemakers.
Under a minute.
Your reputation is
well deserved.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- How did you guess?
Without any clues
from the victims?
No, that's...
Serge and I are the clues.
I mean, he specializes
in high energy weapons.
I do geomagnetics.
So calling us means you suspect
an electromagnetic
pulse weapon.
If these are
the only fatalities,
they must be people
susceptible to...
electronic interference.
QED pacemakers.
You're spooky sometimes, eh?
Now I need to know,
did some sort of weapon
kill these people?
The power that you would need
to create an EM pulse
strong enough...
I mean, that's...
that's not a weapon that
- I've ever heard of.
- No.
Okay, we're done.
We're not done, sir.
There's nothing on the other
side of the equal sign.
I agree with Joshua...
Thank you.
Our greatest concern was this
may have been an act of war,
but since it's not,
I think we can all breathe
a little easier, can't we?
Look at my hat.
What is it, sweetheart?
It's okay, son.
These things happen
all the time and...
Let's, go, let's go!
Come on!
Justin!
Watch out, you bloody idiot!
Hurry! Run!
Daddy!
The skies are empty
over Nelson's Column now,
but a few hours ago,
it was a different story.
Eyewitnesses claimed that
the frenzied swarms of birds
were not in fact attacking
people deliberately...
And it's not just this time.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
But seemed to be confused
and flying blind.
The FOrtean Times reported
violent bird swarms
twice last month in
Australia and Japan.
Five people are confirmed dead
and dozens injured
in the panic that followed the
bizarre and terrifying incident
in London's historic
Trafalgar Square.
- Weird.
- Mm-hmm.
Quite strange, also.
Mm. Strange, indeed.
Mm!
How do birds navigate?
By sight?
No, no, no,
the long range stuff.
Magnetic fields.
Little ions in their brains
align with the magnetic field
of the Earth.
- Yeah, what she said.
- Right?
Acker.
Hit the 'Net, do a search for...
oh, two years ought to do it.
Any and all, like, "weird news",
you know...
bizarre animal migrations,
specifically birds.
Whale and dolphin beachings.
Unusual atmospheric phenomenon,
unexplained plane crashes,
you know,
just use your imagination.
That is a huge search.
You can use our T-1 line
to look up Sailor Moon crap.
You're up to this.
Danni, Danni,
get me the brightest kids
from the Field Theory Class,
and design a computer model
of an electromagnetic field.
What are we doing?
I need a 3-D computer model
of the Earth
to lay the field over.
Whoa-ho-ho, the planet Earth?
Yeah, the planet Earth.
You know, the pretty blue one.
Map out the anomalies
that Acker finds
and grunt out the equations.
And, uh...
grab those smelly kids
from the Non-Linear
Diff class, too.
Listen, Josh, do we even
have time for this?
Do this and I'll sign
your doctorates blindfolded.
- Blindfolded?
- Blindfolded.
Do not pass Go.
Go directly to PhD.
Be wrong. Be wrong.
Tim, I'm coming in a little hot.
Give me some drag, will you?
Roger that.
We are in attitude and ready
for an entry interface.
Nice work, Major.
I have the controls
now for E.I.
I could take us in.
You could...
but you won't.
I'm ready for this, Bob.
Oh, no, you're not, Beck.
You're trained,
and you're certified...
doesn't make you the commander.
And the commander
lands the bird.
You got to be the youngest
person ever in space.
You should say,
thank you, be happy.
Now.
EndeavOur, Houston,
at this time
we show you go for reentry.
Houston, EndeavOur descending
through 400,000 feet
coming upon entry interface.
EndeavOur, this is Flight.
Weren't able to annoy
the commander
into letting you
bring her in this time?
That's a negative, Stick.
I'll have to be
more annoying next time.
Is that even possible?
EndeavOur,
we see you in
good entry config.
Roger, Houston.
Advise.
I'm seeing those
plasma trails now.
All right, mark 241/2.
So, a minute to air.
I don't believe in belts.
Just get me through the Earth's
atmosphere in this spaceship.
Com dropout.
Start the I Com.
Let's wait till the...
Com restored.
Quiet!
We are out of position here.
Guidance shows us
on energy and on course.
Well, I've made this approach
213 times in the simulator.
We're not where we should be.
Where the hell are we?
EndeavOur, guidance is bad.
You are now
1-2-niner miles off course.
Roger, Houston.
We sort of noticed.
Is that...?
Los Angeles. That is confirmed.
We are 1-5 thousand feet.
We got maybe two minutes
of glide time left.
Doesn't make sense.
The guidance,
the beacons are all wrong?
We're heading straight
for downtown.
We're not going to crash
into Los Angeles.
They're going to hit
downtown L.A.
At 300 knots.
Bob, you know L.A.?
Because I have an idea.
Houston, those buildings
are getting mighty big.
Can you clear a freeway?
Okay, thank you.
Come on. Come on.
It's rush hour, Commander,
and it's bumper-to-bumper.
Sir, I have an alternate.
If you turn to heading 1-7-5...
It's Houston's call. Houston?
Computers are still plotting.
Come on.
Houston, we are running
out of time here.
Sir, I have an alternate.
All right, Beck,
what do you got?
Houston, I have coordinates
for an alternate landing site.
Can you confirm?
EndeavOur, give them to me.
I show possible touchdown...
at 33.55 north, 118.10 west.
Bill?
It's theoretically possible.
EndeavOur,
that is confirmed.
Turn right, heading 1-7-5.
Expect visual contact
with Los Angeles River
in five seconds.
No, that will not work, Houston.
We got bridges
every few hundred yards.
Our wingspan alone
is going to fold us up.
I've figured the "L"
over "D" max.
We can make it
if you can bring us straight in.
We're coming in high and hot.
290 feet, 320.
- 270, 3-0-5...
- Arm the gear.
You're armed.
Gear down. Now.
Gear in transition.
240 feet, 290.
Hang on.
This isn't going to be subtle.
210 feet, 265.
Get out of the way! Move!
Derotate.
Inward.
230... 210...
Speed brakes!
100%.
Oh, we're way too fast.
Deploy the chute.
No. We'd snag the bridge.
We'll tear the tail off.
Banking right.
Commander, that next bridge!
Watch it!
We're way too high
for that one!
Suck up the gear!
Not yet.
We'll lose all steering.
We hit, it's over!
And... gear up now!
Lock your harnesses.
This is out of my hands.
Let's get out of here!
Run! Let's get out!
Dr. Zimsky?!
Will you make sure
my assistant has
your number, darling?
Sure.
- Dr. Zimsky!
- Hello.
I'll call security.
No, it's all right.
It's all right. Hello.
Thank you, sir.
- Dr. Zimsky.
- Yes. What's your name?
- Josh Keyes.
- Josh.
No, sir, I don't need you
to sign it.
I need you to read that.
I'm sorry, I don't have time.
- I'm late for the White House.
- Sir, please.
I need you to confirm
my results, sir.
Young man, do you have any idea
who I am?
Yes, I do, sir.
Please read this.
What's it about?
It's the end of the world.
No, I... this is impossible.
I'm sorry.
L-l-I can't have missed this.
You-You have to be wrong.
I mean, look, I'm sure
with careful comparison
to my own work,
we'll find that
you are mistaken.
No offense, but...
Well, I mean,
we'll know soon enough.
The bigger effects will start up
any day now.
Rebecca?
Only you and Dad
ever call me that.
Well, Beck.
So, what brings you
to sunny D.C.?
The Board of Review
is next week.
Just trying to get a sense
of the mood upstairs.
How bad is it?
Your crew crashed
the space shuttle.
Now, how good do you
think it could be?
Sir, this is my life.
Well...
I was studying for the academy
when I was 13.
It still is and has always been
my life.
It's over.
It's over, Rebecca.
I'm sorry.
It's right down here.
Really?
It's like the 4th of July.
What the hell's the hurry here?
Rebecca, would you excuse me,
please?
Excuse me.
Purcell.
Thomas, um, look...
it seems that destiny
may have caught up with us.
Did Zimsky really try
to give you his autograph?
Ah, Monsieur Zimsky.
Conrad Zimsky.
Herr Zimsky.
Superstar.
Oh...
I think I skipped drunk.
Went right to hangover.
Weren't you the one?
I spoke with the kids.
They don't sleep at night.
They look at the sky, and...
and they think it's pretty.
Is there any chance
you're wrong?
No. The sky, man.
The sky... I mean,
that's just the beginning.
That's high-altitude
static discharge.
I know.
Dr. Keyes...
...your presence is
required at the Pentagon.
Ah... it's my best buddies.
Hey!
Why don't you join
us for a drink?
We'd be grateful if you could
join us for a ride, sir.
And if I were to say no?
- Just asking.
- Yeah.
Well, we have
no sense of humor.
That's true.
Oh...
And we're armed.
Thank you.
Dr. Keyes, welcome.
Dr. Zimsky informs us
that you made a
useful contribution
to his investigations,
so he wanted you
to assist him
in the briefing.
That's very generous of you,
Dr. Zimsky.
Science is a selfless business,
dear boy.
Now, why don't you begin,
and I'll fill in
all the difficult bits.
All right, I'll put this
as simply as I can.
Everybody on Earth
is dead in a year.
And let me explain why.
Wrapped around the Earth
is an invisible field of energy.
It's made up of...
electricity and magnetism,
so it's called...
creatively enough...
the electromagnetic field.
It's where we get our magnetic
North Pole and South Pole,
and it protects us
from cosmic radiation.
So this EM field is our friend.
But now...?
But now,
that field is falling apart.
Why?
This here.
Does somebody have a can
of air freshener?
Quick and dirty.
The thin skin,
that's the Earth's crust.
That's what we live on.
It's 30 miles thick.
The meat here,
call it the mantle.
And forgetting
all the-the funky transitions,
it's 2,000 miles thick.
The core,
the peach pit in the center...
that's a tricky one.
There's two parts...
the inner core
and the outer core.
Are you following me?
The inner core
is, uh...
well, it's a big, solid chunk
of iron,
we think.
And that's surrounded
by the outer core,
and that is liquid.
Yes, but,
most importantly, this liquid
is constantly spinning
in one direction.
So a trillion trillion tons
of hot metal
spinning at
a thousand miles an hour, so...
Right, so Physics 101...
hot metal moving fast
makes an electromagnetic field.
This spinning liquid outer core
is the engine
that drives the EM Field.
And that's where
we have our problem.
This engine has stalled.
The core of the Earth
has stopped spinning.
How could this have happened?
We don't know.
What's the timeline here?
As the EM Field
becomes more and more unstable,
we'll start seeing
isolated incidents.
One plane
will fall from the sky,
and then two, and then...
in a few months, anything...
everything electronic
will be fried.
Static discharges
in the atmosphere
will create "super-storms"
with hundreds
of lightening strikes
per square mile.
After that, it gets bad.
The Earth's EM Field
shields us from the solar winds,
which are a lethal blend
of radioactive particles
and microwaves.
When that shield collapses,
microwave radiation
will literally
cook our planet.
Dr. Zimsky.
This is the Sun.
This is the Earth...
without the EM Field.
Would you?
Mm-hmm.
Three months, gentlemen,
and we're back in the Stone Age.
A full year,
the field collapses...
and that.
May I?
Feel free to throw up.
I know I did.
So, how do we fix it?
We can't.
Not in my vocabulary.
Then you might want
to get one of those
Word-A-Day calendars,
General, because
it's impossible.
The core is the size
of Mars.
You're talking about
jump-starting a planet.
This is a superheated
hyper-fluid
of molten iron and nickel
at 9,000 degrees Fahrenheit,
2,000 miles down,
1,000 miles thick.
And the deepest we've ever been
is... seven miles
with a two-inch drill bit.
If we can go into space,
we certainly...
Well, space is easy.
It's empty.
We're talking
about millions of pounds
of pressure
per square inch.
Even if we somehow
came up with a brilliant plan
to fix the core,
we just can't get there.
Yes, but...
...what if we could?
Hello, Braz.
Why the hell
aren't you dead yet?
Okay, this way.
Well, that went better
than I expected.
Dr. Brazzleton,
I see you know Dr. Zimsky.
Yeah.
20 years ago,
he stole my research.
After that,
we-we kind of lost touch.
Research that
was equally mine.
That's funny,
I don't remember a check
from any of the patents.
All right, Braz.
20 years in the desert makes
you a prophet and a martyr.
Look, we're here
about your legendary ship.
Okay, I'm combining
high-frequency pulse lasers
with resonance tube ultrasonics.
If you've ever seen
ultrasonic waves
break up a kidney stone
on the Discovery Channel,
it's the same deal here.
You can...
put your helmets on now.
Firing.
Woo-ooh!
Woo-hoo!
Yeah. Oh.
Okay, I'm officially impressed.
So, all right.
So you've made some progress
with the engine,
we'll grant you.
Have you begun to think
about a shell?
Okay, this is Alex.
Okay, Alex. Good.
Okay, here we have
a concrete block,
and in back of that,
we have a two-inch steel plate.
Okay. We're ready.
And we are... firing.
Voila!
That's...
That's impossible.
I combined the crystals
in a tungsten-titanium matrix
at supercool temperatures,
and that's what did the trick.
The applications
for this are just...
What do you call this material?
Well, its real name
has 37 syllables.
I call it Unobtainium.
Unobtainium?
Mm-hmm.
The Unobtainium will take
the heat and the pressure
and transform it to energy,
which in turn, reinforces
the shell of the ship, you see.
So the hotter
and the deeper she gets,
the stronger she gets...
theoretically.
Theoretically?
Theoretically, yes.
This... is Johnson,
don't mind him.
This is the prototype
for the cockpit here.
Excuse me,
Dr. Brazzleton,
when do you think
the ship will be operational?
When I get my fabrication
methods perfected...
12... ten years, ten years.
What would it take to get
it done in three months?
$15 billion. I...
Will you take a check?
Why don't you use a credit card?
You get miles.
Mm.
Shit!
Mr. Finch, this is the FBI.
We have a warrant.
Purge!
Come on, purge!
FBI! Freeze!
Okay.
I know these
look like computers.
Totally not.
Theodore Donald Finch.
Carnegie-Mellon University.
M.I.T.
Worked at the Sun,
Lucent, Rand Corp.
My handle's "Rat."
Call me Rat.
63 computer fraud indictments.
64.
Two convictions.
This is strike three, Mr. Finch.
Wait a second.
You guys aren't here
to whack me, are you?
Because I was really,
really hoping to have sex
before that happened.
Yeah. I've been told
by the FBl...
whose database you crippled
last year...
that you are
the best in the business.
So you're about
to be given a choice.
What if I say no?
Excuse me, but is this really
the best we could do?
I mean...
How many languages do you speak?
Five, actually.
Well, I speak one.
One, zero, one, zero, zero.
With that, I could steal
your money, your secrets,
your sexual fantasies,
your whole life,
any country, any place,
anytime I want.
We multitask
like you breathe.
I couldn't think
as slow as you if I tried.
Do you have any idea...?
Okay, hey. Hey!
Let's just, let's give
the kid a break.
Okay, it's a phone.
It's just a phone.
Rat, we got a big problem.
A lot of people
are going to die.
We need your help.
What kind of help?
Information control.
We need you to control the flow
of information on the Internet.
You're dreaming.
Nobody controls the 'Net.
Could you...
with unlimited resources?
You want me to hack the planet?
He wants me to hack the planet.
You've got free long distance
on that phone... forever.
Okay.
If I decide to do this...
I'm going to need
an unlimited supply
of Xena tapes and Hot Pockets.
Hot Pockets?
They help me concentrate.
Sounds fair.
Major Childs,
they're ready for you.
a clarification:
You and you alone
were responsible
for proposing
the descent vectors
for the shuttle, correct?
Yes, General.
We have determined that
the Class "A" landing mishap
experienced by
the Shuttle EndeavOur
was caused by biased
navigational data
from the ground due to a brief
geomagnetic disturbance.
Major Childs,
the resourcefulness you showed
in determining
the descent vectors proved
that you have exceptional
navigation skills.
You've brought much credit
upon yourself,
the space program
and the United States Air Force.
Congratulations, Major.
You are reassigned
with Commander Iverson
and Flight Director Stickley
to a new mission
effective immediately.
Transportation
is waiting outside.
Good luck and Godspeed, Major.
Are you sure you want
to wear this tie?
Why?
I don't know.
I mean, you look so
nervous about it.
You look so...
So, how are you holding up?
Oh, hi. I'm good, I'm good.
I'm about to tell
a couple hundred people
the world is going to end.
Well...
I've had better days.
You look good.
Well, no, you don't look good.
Why did he touch his tie
like that?
Thomas, let me speak
with you for a moment.
Listen, wouldn't you
rather I did this?
I mean, given my reputation,
I think that...
No. No, Keyes is in
the lead here, Zimsky.
Yes. Thomas, this is
the most important
scientific operation
in history.
And given my status, I feel that
it's my job to present...
Project Destiny
was your job, Zimsky.
And you went way beyond
authorized limits.
And let me tell...
And let me tell you,
I still, I want to know
if Destiny caused this problem.
It's highly unlikely,
but it may be the solution.
Now, I have not
finished checking...
Excuse me.
Rebecca...
I'm so glad I was wrong.
Right over left...
No, the other left,
the other left.
- Gentlemen.
- And then you...
Gentlemen.
Commander Iverson,
Major Childs,
this is your crew:
Dr. Brazzleton knows the ship;
Hello.
Dr. Zimsky knows the planet;
Doctor.
Dr. Leveque knows
the weapons system;
Excuse me, ladies first.
Hi.
And Dr. Keyes...
Dr. Keyes built
the navigation system, so...
Hi. Rebecca Childs.
Bob Iverson.
These are your fellow...
fellow... what?
Terranauts?
Hello.
All this brain power over here
is starting to smell
like burning batteries.
Y'all better come and join in.
Yeah.
It's the simplest things
that are the hardest, huh?
Yeah. It's official.
I'm the least-qualified person
on this base.
Dr. Keyes,
I'm sure the people in charge
have every confidence in you.
Well, the problem is that
I'm in charge.
Yeah, I know.
Can I help you?
Yes, please.
You're an astronaut,
and you can tie a Windsor?
Mm-hmm.
Is there anything you can't do?
Not that I'm aware of.
I find that
incredibly intimidating.
Yep. Most people do.
Here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let me introduce our project
leader, Dr. Joshua Keyes.
Thank you, thank you.
Good evening. Good evening.
Wow. This looks like a meeting
for Nobel Prize Winners
Anonymous.
I know you are all
the finest in your fields
and have come a long way
to be here.
So, I'll outline our program
over the next three months.
Dr. Brazzleton will supervise
the building of a ship
which is capable of reaching
the center of our planet.
Once there, it will deliver
an explosive charge
large enough
to restart its core.
Dr. Zimsky will calculate
the scale
of the explosion needed.
This is a program I designed
to simulate the effect
of nuclear detonations
on the core.
If my calculations are correct,
a tiny nudge in any direction
will force the core back
into its normal flow.
What's a "tiny nudge"
in planetary terms?
A thousand megatons,
give or take?
Tops. Because any more than that
would create
a core instability.
We made a few monster warheads
in the 200-megaton range.
Braz, do you think the ship
can handle five of these babies?
Yeah. I can enlarge
the ejection pod...
Forgive me,
but, you know, I know
I'm not the expert here,
but what if the core
is thicker or thinner?
I mean, what if it's not
what you think it is?
Isn't that going to affect
the way the explosions are...?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And what if the core
is made of cheese?
This is all best
guess, Commander.
That's all science is,
is best guess.
So my best guess is
you don't know.
With luck, irony will break
for the good guys for once,
and the world's biggest weapons
of mass destruction
will help save the world.
The ship will be powered
by a small experimental
nuclear reactor.
It will be divided
into six compartments
like cars on a train:
The locomotive unit,
navigation compartment,
living quarters, engineering,
bomb compartment
and finally
the weapons-control module.
Up to a 45 degree angle, every
compartment will be held level
by these gyro control gimbals.
But if we do breach a section,
bulkhead doors engage
automatically,
seal off the section in red,
and eject.
Is ejection really
the best option?
Only option.
Each damaged compartment
degrades the entire hull.
The objective is simple.
The obstacles are gigantic.
We're going to need
all the help in the world,
but if we are to avoid
panic and chaos,
the world at large can never
know what's happening here.
Which is where our friend
Mr. Rat comes in.
It's called Virus-bot.
It's a computer virus
that will seek out files
anywhere on the Web that contain
keywords that we designate
and wipes them out.
This is my Kung-Fu,
and it is strong.
Meanwhile, there are
a million puzzles ahead of us,
and we have three months
to solve them.
We have a committed
and ingenious team.
We have every resource available
to us,
and we have the best
of the world's scientific and
technical talents on our side.
With your help we can,
we must... succeed.
Feedback in the resonance tube.
Talk to me, gentlemen.
We are losing
structural integrity.
No, it's not feedback.
It's an impeller malfunction,
I believe.
No, it's not, no. If it were
an impeller malfunction...
For God's sakes, Braz,
make the call!
No, I'll make the call.
I should make the call.
65 knots.
Depth, 8-5 thousand feet.
Look, guys...
It's a disaster!
What part of "talk to me"
don't you guys understand?
For the 22nd time in a row,
everyone on Earth is dead.
Let's take a little quiet time,
and you all are going
to try this again.
Hi.
What is this?
Well, it's...
I invented it.
It's how you're going to...
going to steer underground.
It's, um...
not very good reception.
Well, you're looking
through three feet of lead
at 50 yards away, so...
it ain't bad.
It's like a CAT scan
at a hospital,
but it's-it's souped-up.
I invented it
for Deep Earth surveying.
And then the government came in,
bought my research,
paid off my student loan guys
and made me a consultant.
I'm sorry,
this is really delicate.
And I have it
just the way I want it.
So... excuse me.
Uh, yeah.
Then they brought me in
when the pacemakers quit,
and... boom...
you know, I'm Apocalypse Boy.
Apocalypse Boy?
Yeah. I'm having T-shirts
made up.
Well, hats sell better.
You know, it's funny,
because that is...
right where it should be.
Well...
I'm sorry. I'm a little
ragged around the edges.
I'm just trying to get
this thing to focus correctly.
This is really cool,
but can I just...?
Well... mm-hmm.
It's better.
It's better. Uh...
God, I hate this sky.
Crashing one ship
isn't enough for you?
Hey. Practice makes perfect.
You can practice all you like.
It doesn't mean you're ready
to sit in that seat.
So you keep reminding me, sir.
You know, I doubt
you're even going
to listen to this,
but I'm going to give it a shot.
Being a leader
isn't about ability.
It's about responsibility.
Got it, sir.
No, you don't, Beck.
I mean,
you're not just responsible
for making good decisions.
You have to be responsible
for the bad ones.
You got to be ready
to make the shitty call.
What makes you think
I'm not?
Because you're so good.
You haven't hit anything
you couldn't beat.
I mean, hell,
you were the one who figured out
how to save the shuttle.
You made me, you made the rest
of NASA just look like an ass.
It's just that
you're used to winning...
...and you're not really
a leader until you've lost.
$20 billion has been spent
developing this system...
Oh, come on, guys,
the chefs at NASA...
I want wine!
I need wine!
It's about nutrition.
In five days, I think...
Whoa!
That's high-level
static discharge.
I think we should
check this out.
This doesn't look so good.
It's a lightning superstorm.
Popping up all over the world.
Got 'em. Tracking.
Uh-oh. Rome does not look good.
This planet is decaying faster
than we thought.
It's just the start.
Soon they'll be EM spikes
and microwaves will break
through the weak spots and...
All right. Get this ship
in the ground. Now.
Ah! Summer in the Pacific.
Yeah, the world is inside out.
I was saving this for later,
but...
this is the time for...
Josh, do you mind?
No, not at all. Yeah.
We should have a name
for this baby.
Oh, she's called virgil,
actually.
Virgil... the poet that led
our man into the depths of hell?
That's it.
That's appropriate, I guess.
Well, here's to virgil.
To the planet.
- To virgil.
No flashbulbs, no press,
nobody cheering.
It's... weird.
Let's go.
Cabin pressure, TSI, 3.5.
Check.
ECS cabin repress open.
And repress VLV closed.
Check.
Fluid dump valve.
We are about to begin
our journey
into the heart of the cosmos,
into the very core
of our own planet.
Close.
- Where we find therein...
- Check.
The secrets of the universe...
...3.5 PSI.
...the mysteries of time...
LM circuit lockup.
- Check.
...hope for the future.
And signal.
Deep Earth Control,
this is virgil.
Signal check.
This is Deep Earth Control.
I have thumbs-up
across the board.
You are clear
to initiate power-up.
Reactor power confirmed.
At 1,000 rpm, we will countdown
to launch. On your mark.
Pad leader, stand by for launch.
All right, virgil.
Mark.
Gantry count. Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one...
launch.
500 feet.
Leveling out.
Okay, guys,
let's swing forward.
800 feet.
Light 'em up, Beck.
Gyro leveling operational.
Hull integrity holding.
I'm going to keep her nose
down about 15 degrees and...
Oh, my goodness.
They're singing to us.
Virgil's resonance tubes
are powered up,
so they're vibrating
sub sonically.
Actually, we're singing to them.
What's our depth?
1,600 feet,
plenty of room on both sides.
Hull integrity is good.
You sure?
Let's increase impeller speed.
I think we'll be needing
additional control.
Stick, I'm getting
a seismic reading.
What's happening?
T-phase.
Underwater earthquake.
Still think the water-launch
was a good idea?
Yes, yes, I chose this location
because the crust is thin here.
The downside is... there's lots
of seismic activity.
4,000 feet.
You see that rock?
That is not good.
We're losing steering here.
There's some kind
of crosscurrent.
14,000 feet.
Okay, guys, fasten
your seat belts.
We're turning into the skid.
18,000.
18,500.
They're going way too fast.
21,000 feet.
We hit the wall,
we're rabbits on the highway.
Pressure, pressure,
pressure, pressure.
What do you mean, pressure?
I thought you said this
thing was indestructible!
I said the pressure
makes us stronger.
We just don't have
enough of it yet.
We're at 25,000 feet.
Pull out, sir.
Can't.
- What?
- We're locked in.
Go to full throttle.
Standby to engage front
and lateral lasers, please.
But what if we hit bottom
in ten seconds here?
Just give it
a couple more seconds.
The lasers will fire.
No, there's not enough time
for power-up.
27,000 feet.
The lasers will deploy.
29,000 feet.
- Do it!
- And...
Do it! Now.
And we've got a signal.
- All right.
- Yeah!
All right.
Switching on electron spin burst
transmitters.
Plotting through
lowest density material,
reconfiguring
every five minutes.
Hull integrity 100%.
Reactor power 100%.
All green
on the bomb compartment.
Speed is 60 knots.
Hot damn.
All right, we'll be through
the crust in 15 minutes
and into the mantle.
24 hours to the core, and
then assuming we survive...
Assuming?
Yes, assuming.
Another 15 hours to the
inner core-outer core border.
They're doing well.
The crust is just rock.
Now it gets interesting.
Virgil, can we get
a status check?
We're about to make
the transition into the mantle.
Come on, come on.
Well, exterior pressure
is 800,000 pounds
per square inch.
And hull integrity is 100%.
It is as if we we're diving
through the memories
of the planet.
But we are about to pass
from memory
into madness.
Are you going to be doing
that Carl Sagan narration
all the way to the core?
- I beg your pardon?
- I said...
l-I have an obligation to
my students, to my readers...
An obligation to make
a book deal perhaps?
Two book deals,
if you'd like to know the truth.
I read that last book.
It wasn't very good.
Oh, really? Really?
When did you learn how to read?
People.
Drs. Zimsky and Keyes?
You guys are
our resident geophysicists.
What do you make of this?
The mantle
is a chemical hodgepodge
of... a variety of elements...
Say it with me:
"I don't know."
Well, Commander,
wise men say, "When in doubt,
you should go around."
No. It's too big.
We turn too slow.
Anything that
we can't go through
displays as black.
So what's... what's static?
It's nothing.
What do you mean?
It's empty space.
I...
I never taught the computer
how to read empty space.
And I never taught virgil
how to fly.
Oh, God!
Oh, no, man!
Oh, dear God.
Serge, you all right?
Yeah.
Anybody hurt?
No. You okay?
Yeah.
What's that?
What is that?
From the cooling system.
Shut that down.
Shut it down.
I told you to go around her.
Nobody listens to me.
Where in God's name are we?
Whatever has us jammed up
is inside our lasers.
Shut 'em down.
We're not going anywhere.
Powering down.
Josh, is there any other image
you can pull up?
Nope.
Whatever it is, it's also inside
our MRI cameras.
We have to go outside.
What?
Believe me,
I hate to admit it,
but I think he's right.
I'm coming.
I want to collect samples.
Wait, hang on, hang on.
Wait, wait,
the first problem is,
the only way out of the ship...
is the way we came in,
which is through
the impeller outlet...
Which is still
at 5,000 degrees.
Exactly, I mean...
I'll just flush it
with liquid nitrogen
from the cooling system.
Wait. The cooling system
that's keeping us from
roasting to death in this ship?
Well, just a small part of it.
Alternatives?
Anybody.
Whoa, whoa, that's it.
It's like a giant...
giant crystal.
Where the hell are we?
Well, the good news is,
it looks like the suits
can take the pressure.
It's completely jammed
the laser assembly.
We just...
we got to hope,
if we can cut it loose,
- they're still functional.
- Careful!
Okay.
Got it.
Beck, try the lights, will you?
Lighting up.
Oh, it's magnificent.
Oh, my God.
Aladdin's cave.
It's like
a crystal Grand Canyon.
I think it's a geode.
But I don't understand
how it could have survived
down here.
Cobalt shell, maybe?
No. L-I mean,
in a magma environment
of 5,000 degrees.
Something would have
to protect it.
Unbelievable.
Zimsky.
Yeah?
We're inside
a giant gem bubble,
wrapped in a cobalt cocoon
700 miles below the surface
of the Earth.
Hell of a day.
Yes, it is.
I'll start cutting.
Okay, Braz.
I'm going to check the hull.
Call me if you need me.
Okay.
Oh, no.
- Zimsky!
- Yeah?
Zimsky, look!
It's an amethyst.
Oh, God,
we've breached the shell.
Guys, you don't have to be here!
I want you back inside!
Well, I think that means me.
Orders are orders.
Wait, Josh.
The problem is
I'm losing oxygen.
Braz, what can I do?
Check the feeds for me.
Check the feeds for me, Josh.
Quick!
I'm coming. I'm coming
as fast as I can.
Hey, guys, at this rate
we have three minutes
before the lava gets to us.
Come on, guys.
Come on.
It's not going to work
without oxygen!
We're losing oxygen!
I fixed it. Now cut!
That's good. It's working now.
It's working well now!
That's good, Josh!
Josh's vital signs are dropping.
What?
Serge!
You're almost there.
You're almost there, Josh.
Josh!
Joshua!
Okay, guys,
connect the oxygen.
Braz, you got that?
Yes. Connected!
Good. I got to check
these lasers.
Okay, Beck, turn 'em over.
Pre-lasers only,
if you don't mind.
Initiating.
This better work.
The tide's really coming in.
Yes!
We got lucky...
I think we're going
to swim right out of this one.
Bob?
Huh?
Bob...
Braz, come on, it's over.
Okay. Okay.
Beck! Beck!
We're coming in.
Initiate start sequence.
Beck!
- Beck, do you hear me?
- Careful.
Start the impellers!
The door, open the door.
Activate bulkhead doors!
Now, Beck!
You okay?
You're going to be weak.
You're okay.
Good job, good job.
Good man.
Well done, well done.
I'm fine. Thank you.
So, um...
we have some good news,
and, uh...
and we have some bad news.
Uh, good news.
I'll take good news.
All right.
Well, we're alive
and we're moving.
That's g... that's good news.
Oh, it is hot in here.
Yeah, that nitro we flushed out
of the cooling system,
it-it's causing things
just to heat up a little.
I'm going to go back
and just make
some adjustments.
I'll lend you a hand.
All right.
I'm fine.
I'm going to check
your heartbeat, okay?
Thanks, Braz. Appreciate it.
So, that's the bad news?
That's not too bad.
No.
Commander lverson died.
But...
we're living,
and he would want to...
he'd want us to complete
our mission,
so I think that it's important
that we all...
It's all right.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Let's give him a second, okay?
He deserves that.
Oh, God, this all just seems
too big, doesn't it?
I think you were attempting
the impossible.
You were trying
to save the world, and...
it's overwhelming.
I came here to save my wife
and my two children
and... six billion lives...
it's too much.
I just hope
I'm-I'm smart enough
and brave enough to save three.
You did a nice job, Joshua.
Very nice. Great.
You'd have done the same thing.
Well, maybe, maybe.
Hey... who's steering
the ship?
Video screen autopilot.
I hope he knows the way.
You and me both.
So... you're really
a college professor?
You're not from the CIA,
or the NSA or any
of those three-letter places?
No. I am a boring
college professor.
Wrong place, wrong place.
That was the bravest thing
I've ever seen.
Well, I just, I just...
Listen, the lack of oxygen
kept me from weeping
like a little girl
as is my custom
in dangerous situations.
Hey, guys, we're close
to the mantle core interface.
Where are you?
Key's in, Dr. Brazzleton.
Ready.
We are in the...
Okay, the code...
0-1-3-1-9-9-5.
...luxurious, beautiful
weapons control...
checking the controls
on the nukes.
This is the birthday
of my daughter.
0-1-3-1-9-9-5.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Three, two and one...
Thank you.
Green. All green.
Great. So we have
to synchronize
the babies now.
Just a second.
There.
All right,
now let's put them to bed.
Zimsky, could you please
come up here for a second?
Yes?
We're not supposed to go through
anything black.
Yes, so please don't.
What is this?
They're scattered everywhere.
Oh, my God!
They're diamonds!
Great.
You might want to sit down
and buckle up.
We're on a collision course
here.
All rightie. Careful.
Guys, we're dodging diamonds
the size of Cape Cod,
so bear with me.
Not exactly nimble here.
Diamonds? I want some.
Can I help?
Ooh!
Okay.
It's okay.
Okay, it looks like
we're in the clear.
Breach!
Guys! Weapons control, get out!
Get out now!
Serge!
Serge! What the hell
are you doing?
Come on!
My notebook!
Now!
Serge!
Take the time reg, Joshua!
Come on Serge! Come on!
My notes!
You'll need them!
No!
God, no, Serge!
It's okay.
Serge, come on! No!
Serge!
Come on, man!
- Leave the box!
- We need the box!
We can get him!
We can get him out!
Hold on, Serge!
Beck! Beck!
Override the ejection system!
Beck, no!
One damaged compartment
threatens the whole ship!
Beck! Beck!
Override the ejection system!
Serge, we're right here.
We're not going
to forget about you, man.
- Josh, can you hear me?
- Serge! Serge...
Hey, buddy,
look in your monitor right now.
Serge, look in your monitor.
I'm right here. Serge...
Josh, I can't see you.
Braz is going to override
the doors manually, okay?
We're working on it right now.
Braz, how long?
Going as fast as I can,
Fast as I can.
- Okay, I'm scared.
- We're going right now.
Shouldn't be two seconds,
all right?
Josh!
Beck, override
the ejection systems, okay?
Damn. I don't think
Beck can hear me.
Serge, look at me now. Serge!
Serge, we're right here, okay?
We're not going
to forget about you, man.
I'm going to get you
out of here.
We're working on it, all right?
Stay with me here.
Okay?
I don't know what to do.
Can you hear me now?
All right, here I am.
I'm not going
to let you go, man.
I'm not going to let you go,
all right?
Stay with me here, okay?
I'm going to come to Paris
and we'll go out, all right?
After this.
After this is all
said and done, all right?
- Josh!
- Serge!
Serge! Serge!
Serge!
Did you reset the overrides?
I never pushed them.
You let him die.
Actually,
you really want to know?
I killed him twice.
First when I hit the diamond,
and then when I didn't hit
the override.
Do you want me to feel any worse
about that than I already do?
It's not possible.
Why are you being
so smug about that?
Could you have made
the decision?
- Yes.
- Could you?
Yes, I could've.
If you would've hit
that switch,
I could've got him outta there!
I was yelling for you!
Take it and look at it!
I was two inches from him!
I was two inches,
and I told you
to put the door up
and you didn't!
I was screaming for you!
Why didn't you do it?!
Because I had to make
that decision.
Fate or God...
No!
Damn it!
You leave God out of this!
Serge died so that we could
complete our job.
Oh, that's right,
the job of saving the world.
Not the whole world, Josh!
Just three of them.
Virgil, you are approaching
core interface.
Are you good to go?
Josh?
Josh, can you hear me?
Ready as we'll ever be, Stick.
Dr. Keyes.
Right here.
Deep Earth,
we are green and good to go.
We just got a huge speed jump.
We're at 95 knots.
110.
130... 140.
Our speed's jumped
because the density of the core
is different than our estimates.
It's lighter
than we thought.
So much for best guesses.
I'm fine with this.
At this rate, we'll, what...
hit the inner core
in a little over five hours.
I think we finally
bought some luck.
Braz.
- Yeah.
- Would you please
punch the new core density
into the equations
for the nuclear detonation?
Please tell me this is enough.
Okay.
You're telling me
the 1,000 megatons
of nuclear warheads
we hauled down here
isn't going to cut it?
No. This core material
is too thin.
- What?
- The energy waves from
the explosion
won't spread far enough.
They'll just bleed
away into nothing.
That's it.
We go home.
- Home?
- What?
Our Commander is dead.
Our weapons specialist is dead.
Our weapons control systems
are gone.
We don't know whether
we can arm the nuclear devices,
and our plan to fix the core
no longer works. So...
we have failed.
We have not failed.
We have failed, and we go home,
and we go to the alternative.
What alternative?
What are you talking about?
General,
this is Dr. Conrad Zimsky.
Destiny is a go.
Repeat.
Damn.
I need to know everything
to do my job.
You don't have to know this.
General, it is my job
to ensure the safety
of this mission.
Anything that affects
it is my business.
Now what the hell is Destiny?
It's a device.
Deep Earth Seismic Trigger
Initiative, DEST-INI. Destiny.
We had reason to believe
that our enemies were
building a weapon
that could generate
targeted seismic events.
They would be able
to create massive earthquakes
under our territory.
No way of telling who did it.
So?
So... we built one, too.
M.A.D.
Mutually Assured Destruction.
A perfect acronym
if ever there was one.
Beautiful.
They built it first.
I built it better.
I beamed high-powered
electromagnetic
energy waves down Deep Earth
fault lines, and, you know.
Zimsky, what makes you think
that Destiny
would even touch the core?
'Cause it already did.
This isn't a fluke.
We killed the planet.
You keep saying
that the core is too big
to be affected by anything
short of nukes.
- So...
- The core is an engine.
Throw a small wrench
into a big engine,
you can still stall it.
Deep Earth, this is Virgil.
We require clarification on
the status of Project Destiny.
Why weren't
we notified of this, sir?
Because you didn't need to know,
Major.
Now you may not like this.
I may not like it either.
But it's my job,
and I do it for my country,
and if we don't develop these
devices, someone worse will
and they will
use them against us.
But you have my word.
No one in this
administration... no one,
had any idea
that this could happen.
So the device that killed the
planet is your backup plan?
An electric shock
can stop a heart.
It can certainly restart one.
Destiny will work.
It has to.
No, it won't work.
If you fire that thing again
with the core already stalled,
it'll terminally destabilize it.
Yes, granted... there is
a marginal risk involved,
but given the circumstances,
I hardly see that there's
an alternative.
No, Zimsky, listen to me.
Every volcano
on the planet will blow.
There'll be earthquakes big
enough to rip us to pieces.
- Dr. Keyes.
- What?
I'm afraid it's all we've got.
Now, I have orders
from the president.
Come home, Virgil.
We go to plan B.
Well, what about plan C?
What? What?
Well, plan C.
We continue on.
We restart the core...
somehow.
We don't do it,
you fire Destiny.
I can't wait for you
to get out of there.
Then don't.
We fail, fire Destiny.
Oh, come on! That's ridiculous!
What choice do we have,
- Zimsky?
- Are you kidding me?
If they set that thing off,
the shock waves
will wipe us out!
We'll be lucky to get back
if we turn back right now!
Virgil, I'm telling you
right now, we will fire Destiny,
and we need to do so
as quickly as possible,
and if you're still there,
you will be destroyed.
Rebecca?
Please don't make me
have to do this.
Plan C.
It's your call, Commander.
Majority decision.
We're going in.
I'm sorry, sir.
Oh, come on, you're
a bunch of suicidal morons!
What are you, crazy?
Plan C?
Restart the core "somehow"?
Oh, that's a great idea!
That's a brilliant idea!
I can't believe I'm stuck
in this floating septic tank
with you lunatics!
You may have nothing to lose.
You may have nothing to lose!
You may have nothing to lose
but I have my life to lose,
thank you very much
while you're up!
Now turn it around!
He told us to go back
and we're going back!
Why? You want to be a hero?
You want to be a martyr?
What do you want to be?
You're out of your mind!
Thank you!
Turn it around!
- No!
- Zimsky.
You, shut up!
It's not a stupid ship.
I had to.
It had to happen sometime.
Yeah.
Oh...
Status! What is that?
It's the EM
monitoring station.
It's the one that
tracks EM pulses.
God, no.
Just talk, Mr. Rat.
No.
That's a good boy.
Remember those
invisible microwaves
that Josh was talking about?
Well, they just found a hole.
No, it's a parking lot
out here...
Oh, my God.
And now with this
horrific breaking news,
we go live to San Francisco,
where Leo Jacks has the story.
Yes, Claire,
it's hard to believe
that half of San Francisco
is in ruins today
following the most devastating
and the most baffling
event in our nation's history.
It's-it's
a horrific situation here.
Thousands are dead.
Many are missing.
It's-it's hotels, hospitals.
Bring up the power grid.
The whole West Coast is out.
That means we're going to have
to suck up just about every drop
of juice east of the Rockies
to fire Destiny.
Another EM spike, we're not
going to have enough power.
General, you have got
to give them more time.
There is no more time.
Colonel, call Destiny.
I am launching
a formal complaint
against you
with the Department of Defense.
Rat to Josh.
Go, Rat.
Hey, um...
here's the EM Field data
that you're primed for.
Digging that, Rat.
Primed for.
Prime numbers...
one, two, three, five,
seven, 11, 13, 17...
Here we go.
James.
Yes, sir.
Here we go, folks.
Okay, this time
it's going to work.
Here you go... beautiful.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
Come on, baby.
Come on, Daddy wants to see
the sky again.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's try again.
Your torque is R,
cross F...
No, your R is too small, Josh.
Right.
Wait, hold on.
What are you laughing at?
No, I mean, it took me and 400
of the world's smartest people
to come up with the first plan.
You want to help?
No. I want to turn around
and go home.
It's not going to happen.
Well, then we're going to die.
True.
All right, look,
- let's start from square one.
- Okay.
Let's start from square one.
The bulk modules...
depends on density.
Your torque is R cross F,
but you have
to integrate volume...
But here, here...
just consider this.
Now, we got this...
Okay, now, R cross F,
we're putting in pi.
What's V?
Oh, for God's sake!
All right.
I'm hitting him again.
No, no, no!
Braz, no, look, I have a theory.
Are you interested?
Yes. We're interested.
Then let me smoke a cigarette,
and I'll tell you.
Oh, thank God.
Hmm? All right, fine, look.
Look, we have to use
wave interference, okay?
Because one explosion
won't do it.
Think about stones in a pond.
You drop a large stone
into a pond,
you get a big splash,
and then that's it, it's over.
But drop a smaller stone,
wait until the ripples weaken
and drop another and another,
and another,
and fluid dynamics 101.
The ripples reinforce each other
in geometric progression.
Hm, the whole bigger than
the sum of the parts.
Then we'll have five
200 megaton explosions...
Instead of one big bang.
So, we hot-wire the nukes.
Yes.
And as one does,
we seed them
through the core...
at locations that have
to be accurate to the inch.
We detonate them in a sequence
that has to be accurate
to the millisecond...
then we outrun the biggest
nuclear shock wave in history.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, that should be
fairly simple.
Destiny now should be
diverting to the central.
Final calibration
on both transmission systems...
Come on.
Cut the...
cut the rouge.
The red wire above the circuit.
Okay. Okay.
No, no, wait, hold it!
I'm sorry, cut it below.
Please...
Extensions A, B.
- Here we go.
- F, check.
Increase power to reactors
ten through 15
We're almost there, folks.
Okay, guys we're closing
on the inner core.
The nukes are ready.
Timers are on.
Great.
Let's start dropping them.
No. The bombs are not built
for these pressures.
That's why they were
in that pod.
If you send them out now...
out of that casing,
they'll be crushed instantly.
I'm assuming we have a Plan D.
Plan D is
Virgil's compartments.
We put a nuke in
each section of Virgil,
and then eject the individual
sections one at a time.
They should stay intact long
enough for the nuke to go off.
Oh...
What?
Virgil's not designed to eject
undamaged compartments.
Okay, these are
the ejection mechanisms
holding each compartment
in place.
They're all connected
by one master hydraulic gear.
Kind of like keys
on a key ring.
What we have to do, we have
to unlock the piston.
That will release
the compartments
so the bombs can be jettisoned.
Where's the master gear?
In the crawl space
we used to get out earlier.
Well, what the hell
is it doing there?
I built the ship
in three damn months.
I didn't think I'd be
intentionally sabotaging it.
I'm sorry!
So one of us has to go in there.
Correct.
Into the crawl space that has
core fluid at 9,000 degrees.
Yes.
Can you flush it
with liquid nitrogen?
We don't have enough
at this point.
9,000 degrees.
And our suits are built
to withstand...?
Half that, probably.
Right. Half that.
So what you're saying is
whoever goes into that crawl
space, is not coming back.
Hmm.
Together.
Yes, thank you.
Wait.
- On three.
- Okay.
One... two... three.
Huh.
Well, I better go on,
get myself ready.
No, Braz, wait.
No, Braz, no wait.
Excuse me.
Just a moment, may I see that?
- No.
- May I?
May I?
Yes.
Thank you.
Magic.
I mean, Braz, three straws
of equal length.
I mean, this is childish.
Let's do it again.
No, we will not do it again.
I thought you'd be happy.
No. Not at the expense
of you making us
look like fools.
He's right. Why do you get dibs
on being the hero?
Because it's my damn ship.
Oh, that makes perfect sense.
Look, for 20 years, I've done
nothing but Virgil. 20 years.
Virgil belongs to me,
and I will not let her fail.
I will not.
Now if you want to know
what's worth dying for...
this ship.
Building it
instead of imagining it.
If Virgil needs more blood,
it will be my blood.
Now I am going to go
and get ready.
Good to go.
Beck.
Josh.
It's a hell of a boat
you built, Braz.
I am really proud to
have known you guys.
Thank you.
Braz.
Edward.
Yes, Conrad?
You're right.
It is your ship.
But I wish to God
it had been ours.
The chamber's sealed, Beck.
Ready.
Open the hatch.
Hang on, Braz.
Come on, hang on.
Manual override is complete!
Braz, we can still
get you out of there.
No... start...
start the impeller.
No.
We got a job to do.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Magnetic shielding systems
are up.
Power level's 85%.
Increase power to Reactor 10.
All personnel should be clear.
Oh, God!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay, she's down.
Approaching the first
drop-off point.
We got to be accurate
to the second here, boys.
And drop in three-five seconds.
And... timer on.
Pull it.
Clear... and...
ejecting.
All right.
Initiate firing sequence.
Sir...
It's our last shot, Stick.
Damn you.
Damn me? Too late.
Ten, nine, eight...
What's that?
Gotcha!
...four, three, two...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Someone's diverted our energy.
Where the hell's it gone?!
It looks like...
Coney Island.
Your Kung Fu is not strong.
Well, how long will it take
to get it back online?
Well, then get to it!
Oh, hey, General.
Is there something
I can do for you?
Timer on.
Clear...
ejecting.
Ejecting.
Pull it.
All right.
Let's go throw our last little
200 megaton stone in the pond.
I always wanted to make a splash
in nuclear physics.
You know, that energy
propagation stuff
you were talking about...
Oh, that was
high school physics.
Yeah, it's not exactly...
I just took the wavelengths
from the core fluid
off the MRI readings.
Yeah, and multiplied by 800...
600.
Surely you compensated
for the MRI bias.
We got to reset the timers!
Reset the timers!
No! It just won't work.
It's not the timers!
This is not enough!
What's not enough?
The last bomb is
not enough.
To complete the wave form.
Yeah. No. The last bomb
has to be 30% larger.
That's six or seven pounds
of plutonium.
Where are we going to get six
or seven pounds of plutonium?
Guys, we got hit
by an energy flare.
I can't keep us on course.
Ejecting compartment
in 50 seconds.
No, Beck! No, wait!
No! Push it!
You push it!
Come on, guys, I can't hear you.
It's got my shoulder!
Push!
Guys!
Clear!
Clear the compartment!
What are you doing?
I think the flare
has knocked the Coms out.
I can't get it, Josh.
I can't get it.
Go...
I can't.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can you hear me?
I'm correcting course. Now!
Zimsky!
No!
Push it!
Ejecting compartment
in ten seconds.
Can you hear me?
Josh, go! Go! Go!
Get out! Get out!
Now! Get out!
Now! Get out! Go!
Josh.
For the last bomb,
to make it larger...
use the fuel rods
from the react...
Ejecting.
I got to get...
I got to...
Beck.
Beck, can you hear me?
Beck, if you have any better
ideas, you tell me now.
We've only got three minutes
to eject this one.
Beck!
Come on, guys.
I can't hear you.
Beck.
Josh, come on.
Are you okay?
Will you take my gloves off?
Oh, my God.
Please.
I had to build the blast.
I'm sorry.
Hold on, let me get...
No. Stay here for one second.
I was trying to call you.
I know the Coms were down.
Right.
I know what you did.
We don't have enough energy...
I know.
...to get back.
You did good.
I would've done the same thing.
Where's Zimsky?
Come here.
You did good.
One minute
to the first detonation.
And 12 until the blast hits us.
I was hoping we'd suffocate
to death first.
Beck.
Beck, Beck.
What could you do
if I got you enough power
to fire the impeller?
Maybe not the laser
but the impeller.
What? From where?
The heat of the core.
It's 9,000 degrees.
Unobtainium converts heat
to energy.
So this whole damn ship is like
a big, old solar panel.
Come on, I need your help.
Number two's going!
Come on, come on.
For here in the great infinite
unknowable...
man can come to know the
most important thing of all:
Himself.
He can understand...
What the fuck am I doing?
We've got full rotation!
It's turning!
All right!
Come on, Beck, where is it?
Come on.
Come on, hurry up.
Is that the last one?
Yeah.
Give it a couple seconds.
It worked!
Get ready to pull a few G's.
420 knots.
Now, this is more like it.
440.
So, Rat, what's the center
of this quake?
It's everywhere!
It's one giant shock wave!
The planet's healing itself.
At this speed,
we're going to be home
in a third of the time.
As long as we can surf
these magma flows,
we'll be okay.
Let's just pray we don't run
into any dead ends,
or we're going to miss
those lasers.
Okay, navigator, which way?
We've got greater
fluid density on the left.
Go with the flow.
Uh-huh.
Bill, where are they headed?
Looks like she found
a space between
some tectonic plates
somewhere near Hawaii.
Josh...
Yeah?
They're closing in
on us too fast.
I don't know if I can...
Hey, you got it.
Um... w-we lost them, Stick,
and I...
Where'd our power go?
Well, we're powered by the heat.
It's stone cold down here.
Well...
Look on the bright side.
At least we're not
going to boil to death.
You always look
on the bright side?
Always.
Okay, let's assess:
We've got no communications,
we're probably 800 feet down,
but we might as well
be 800 miles.
We're in an Unobtainium
cigar tube with the sonar
signature of a rock.
We've got just enough power
to make the ultrasonics burp,
but no one's listening
on those frequencies anyway,
and...
nobody even knows we're alive.
Okay.
Give me a minute on this one.
This is hopeless.
Come on, General,
we've got to be getting close.
We can't...
Mr. Rat, even if
they were still alive,
there's no way
they could contact us.
Bridge.
Skipper, Combat relays that our
sub has something on the sonar.
Where do they think?
Bill, put it up
on the hydrophone.
Whales, sir.
They're a long way off
their usual path,
but that's not uncommon
since that, uh...
what are they calling it?
Orbital wobble?
Yeah, that's what they call it.
Well, thank you
very much, Captain,
but I think we're done here.
General.
J.O., this is the captain.
Stand down from SAR Operations.
It's whales! It's whales!
Hey! General!
Stick!
It's whales!
The ultrasonics!
They're singing to them!
You gotta find the whales!
Alpha X Ray, this is
November Echo six one zero.
I'm changing...
Hold on, I'm seeing
those whales now.
Whoa!
Okay, ball's in the water.
This is neat. Those whales
are circling something.
Hold on, hold on.
We have a strong echo here.
Depth, 800 feet.
There-there's something
down there.
There's definitely
something down there.
I told you pulsing the
ultrasonics would work.
Do you ever get tired
of being right?
Yes.
So what's next for you?
A shower.
Then back to NASA, I guess.
You?
Deep-dish pepperoni pizza,
green peppers, onions,
extra mushrooms... then a shower
and then back to the classroom.
NASA could use
a few good men, you know.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, so could my
freshmen geophysics students.
You know what makes me
really, really angry?
Bob, Serge, Braz, Zimsky...
no one's going to ever know
what they did or why they died.
Unless...
it all got out somehow.
That's unthinkable.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
Sweet.
It is now emerging that
the world owes its survival
to the heroism of six
remarkable individuals...
Shuttle Commander
Robert lverson...
This extraordinary craft...
French Scientist, Dr. Serge...
was captained by NASA astronaut
Dr. Bob lverson.
Edward Brazzleton
is a name so...
Dr. Conrad Zimsky
will be best remembered...
On Capitol Hill today,
everyone's asking
the same question...
What is Project Destiny?
Destiny, meet world.
World, meet Destiny.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org