Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You're lost.
I'm not lost.
I just don't know exactly where we are.
Maybe I should steer for a while.
Whoa. I'm a little buzzed.
Man, you are so cute
when you're hammered.
- I'm not hammered.
- You sure are.
Hey, look.
I'm busy here.
Land.
You see? We're not lost, we're just
on some creepy island penal colony.
You know what?
I'm gonna go and find that bar.
- Ok.
- Woof!
Woof!
Hey, wait up!
I've just gotta finish tying up here.
Ow!
Hello?
Luke?
Jenny?
Jen?
There it is.
- What?
- There it is! You excited?
Three final exams, two biology labs
and a term paper due in four days
and I let you convince me to go
for a party weekend.
It's my duty
as the irresponsible brother.
To make sure I never get
into medical school?
The burden of the smart guy!
I got two words for you -
Communications Major.
I'm a fan of the five-year program.
This is why I had to study
in the library.
Noah has turned our dorm room
into prime happy-hour real estate.
Because I read the brochure that said
it's Ok to have fun in college.
- I have fun!
- You have fun, when?
Baby, you'll have the last laugh
when you're a doctor...
and they're stuck living off of ramen
noodles and unemployment cheques.
Oh!
- That's not a bad thing.
- Bill Gates never went to college!
Just fly the plane, Maverick.
Gosh, Mattie, this place is incredible.
I can't believe it's yours.
Ours. It's "ours."
God, it must really suck
being a trust-fund baby, huh?
When my uncle died,
I only got Sonics season tickets.
Our Uncle Frank wasn't rich.
This house was all he owned.
- Lived here for... what?
- 20 years.
...20 years, doing nothing but studying
birds, watching animals...
Talking to trees, guzzling whisky.
Yeah, he was a little eccentric.
Johnny and our uncle
never really got each other.
- No one ever gets me.
- I got you.
You got me so much,
you dropped my ass.
Hey...
- Come on.
- Oh. Sorry, man.
Overgrown chic! I love it.
Come on, let's get inside.
Man, I missed this place, Johnny.
Ah, the zip line.
I'm going on that.
Here we are.
Home sweet home, huh?
- I love it!
- Wow!
How long has it been
since you guys were here?
God, ten... How old were you when
you sunk Uncle Frank's car in the bay?
I was 12 and bored.
12. So... 13 years.
I'm surprised he left us the place.
He was afraid you'd burn it down.
- I still can.
- Poor house.
Check out the wine cellar.
Whoa!
- An M5 Medoc? God, this is fancy!
- Yes, yes!
In M5 I was still playing
with Rainbow Brite.
Yeah? And looking good doing it.
- We can't get into his wine, it's...
- What?
It's... I don't know.
It's disrespectful or something.
You know what? Let's all be quiet.
Lucky for you guys I came prepared.
- What you got?
- Anybody know what time it is?
- What time is it?
Margarita-30!
Where's the blender?
Come on, baby.
Chips, salsa...
hot dogs, beer...
Soy milk? Flaxseed oil? Kasha?
What the hell is kasha?
That's Nikki's. She's a health-food nut.
Her body looks like no vegetarian
I've ever seen.
Ooh!
Have a good time.
Don't be a little vagina this weekend.
Ok, that's offensive, A,
and B, I am gonna have a good time.
- You still remember how to do this?
- Yes. Go.
Ah, the memories.
The car that was once a submarine.
Give the nozzle a turn.
If you smell gas, run.
Thank you.
Hey, look. The keys are still in the car.
That thing hasn't been used for ages.
It's never gonna start.
Given your history,
it's probably a good thing.
German engineering at its finest.
Come on! Oh! Oh...
What's wrong?
The only thing separating me
from my immediate personal happiness
is John and Matt's skill
with a generator.
Then we'd better start drinking
these... before they go...
Yes! That's what I'm talking about!
That's what...
Why, blender?
- What happened?
- What do we do?
I saw the fuse box in the basement.
- You know how to fix a fuse?
- Hell, no. You?
- No!
- Well...
maybe we could figure it out together.
Ok, Ok...
a young, handsome brother...
...takes blonde little bad girl
into the dark, dusty basement with him.
- I got it.
- Ok, you go ahead.
Young... attractive... virgin...
pushes obnoxious
asshole in the basement!
Are you really a virgin?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Er... yes.
Ooh! Vintage.
Here's the fuse box.
- Look, there's the fuse.
- New one?
Yeah... Oh. You see?
That one's blown.
- This one?
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- Dude!
It was this thing! I'm sorry!
- You scared?
- No. Where is this?
- Oh! Got it! Got the fuse.
- Yeah.
- Should I put it in?
- Oh, God, yeah.
Eugh!
- Ok, here's the master switch.
- Ok, try it.
- Ready?
- Yeah... Yes!
- You weren't supposed to find that.
- Why?
It's just a secret attic
for make-out parties.
You were nine the last time
you came here, silly.
And?
I was a very early bloomer.
If everybody knew the Matt that I know,
it'd be so hard to keep you to myself.
No, it wouldn't.
Which room should we take?
The one farthest from my brother's?
Ideal.
Two years and it's still awkward.
I apologised to him a thousand times
about us, but he's still mad.
He's not mad, he's John.
Are you trying to fulfil
some adolescent fantasies?
I might be.
Uh-uh. There.
- A secret make-out party.
- Uh-oh.
It's on!
You know you're gonna kill
yourself.
You'll never believe what I found
in the attic.
Ah.
Ah, the house flag.
We were such dorks.
At least one of us has changed, huh?
- That rope's gotta be 20 years old.
- It feels Ok to me.
John, really.
Hemp like that deteriorates.
I brought climbing rope with me.
You can string it with a Dynaloc.
Whoo!
- Once a brute, always a brute.
- Whoo!
Sometimes it stuns me
that you two are related.
Usually people who live
on the edge like that die young.
Johnny wouldn't be caught dead dying.
It would make him look bad.
What? All work and no play.
You sound like Johnny.
Well, he wants you
to enjoy yourself too.
- Right.
- He does.
Remember when we were 13 and he
threw you your first boy-girl party?
- When your mum went out of town?
- I do.
And we played Truth or Dare
and watched, er... What was that called?
"Wild On lbiza"?
- And he dared you to kiss me.
- And I did.
Then I cried.
I don't think my male ego
ever recovered from that.
I think you're doing just fine.
- You think?
- Yeah...
Have fun, Ok?
- Did you ever...
- No.
We've been friends for a long time,
plus I got with too many of her girls.
- Too many! What's too many?
- For a chick, any is...
- Any is too many?
- Any is too many.
Hi!
- Ok...
Whoa!
Nice shot, Robin Hood.
That's so white of you.
- You wanna give it a shot?
- What?
- Do you wanna try?
- Er... no.
All right.
See? It's that easy.
You guys hear that?
Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
Where is it from?
- You better leave that thing alone.
- Can I see it?
He just peed on you.
It's a boy.
- It can't be more than 8 or 9 weeks old.
- You go, Dr. Ruth.
What kind of dog is that?
Well, it looks like a German Shepherd,
but he's big. Really big.
I thought we were the only ones
on the island.
He was probably abandoned
by some boaters.
Hey, guys, I have an idea. Hold on!
Ssh! I have an idea, a good idea.
- Let's eat him.
- You're such a dick.
I'm serious.
We'll put him on the target...
I got my iPod. Please, please.
Here's to that!
You like it here, huh?
Let's keep him with us tonight,
you guys.
You like it here?
Wait, wait. No TV,
no phone, no Maxim?
Some people like a break
from civilisation.
All right. Sure. I'm for the whole
kumbaya-granola thing,
as long as when it's over,
there's a fifth of Jager
and internet porn waiting for me.
Noah, sometimes it amazes
me that you're still single.
Here's to being single, seeing double,
sleeping triple...
- and to multiple orgasms.
- Yeah, by yourself.
Ooh!
Oh!
What's that in the cellar?
You hear that?
- Is that an M5 Medoc calling me?
- Yes.
You are gonna drink the cheap stuff
and you are gonna like it.
You are a cruel, cruel man.
But I still love you.
Uh-uh. That cute stuff's
not gonna work on me.
I'm a cat person.
Cheap enough?
That little sucker growled at me.
You piss on that rug, you're dead.
Hey!
He was just kidding! Come back!
Meanies.
That dog is weird. He just growled at me
for no good reason.
I said I liked cats.
I wasn't talking about the musical.
This little dog is harmless.
Chicken.
Don't worry, he'll come back.
He knows there's food here.
You wanna find him?
- I wanted to sleep with him.
- You were sleeping with me!
She was gonna make love to me
and then sleep in your bed.
That's Ok.
I see cancer patients every Thursday.
That's my charity work for the week.
Oh! Funny!
The folks got jokes tonight.
You all want some?
Here, pup. Where are you?
- You see him?
- Uh-uh.
This is bringing me back memories
from Ghost in the Graveyard.
Remember? When we were ten?
I don't remember that.
- Yeah, you were too cool back then.
- I'm still too cool.
- Right.
- Over there. There he is.
Hey, pup, there you are.
There you are! Come here.
Sara!
You Ok?
Here.
Ok?
It bit me.
All right, you're Ok.
You're Ok. Come on, let's go.
It just attacked you, unprovoked?
Yeah. Came out of nowhere.
It was probably just protecting
its young
but the rules say you gotta treat
any bite by an unknown animal
as a possible rabies infection.
But listen, you will not get rabies.
I know what I'm talking about.
There isn't a single case
of somebody who's gone through
a proper post-exposure treatment
who's then contracted the disease.
Isn't that where they gotta stick
a bunch of needles under your skin?
It's a little simpler than that.
- A little simpler?
- I think we should get the plane ready.
- You wanna leave?
- We should get Sara to a doctor.
Remember when I got that rabies shot
cos of that bat in the Bahamas?
You don't have to start right away.
- You really don't, if you're feeling Ok.
- Is that true?
As long as you have your first shot
within a week, yes.
But... there's no pressure.
Well, then I'm cool.
I'll be fine, you guys.
- She's fine.
- Sara?
Mattie, the point of this weekend
was for you to live a little,
so don't use this as an excuse.
That's bullshit.
Yeah, it's true, I'm fine. I mean, really.
It was scary!
Nothing that a little drinking can't cure.
Could someone give me a drink?
I need a drink.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. Sure I'm sure.
What are you thinking about?
There was this company
who leased some land
on the other side of the island,
a couple of miles away.
Anyway, they built a compound
for training dogs.
When I was little, my uncle
used to walk me over there
and we'd play with all
the little puppies.
I think that's when I decided
I wanted to be a vet.
About a year ago...
...one of the dogs got rabies.
It started spreading
and all the dogs got it,
and my uncle told me
they had to put them down.
- That's horrible.
- Mmm.
So I assumed
they had been killed, but...
...after seeing that dog today...
So you think some of them survived?
That's just it.
If they had rabies and escaped, they
would've been dead a long time ago.
In dogs, rabies is always fatal.
So, what are you saying?
I don't know.
Oh!
Sorry. I didn't see you.
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep.
- You?
- Me, neither.
You look like an angel.
Ow! Damn it!
Easy, tiger.
Go away.
So, how about doing
some swimming today?
Maybe hang out by the dock?
Maybe when your leg feels better?
I'm fine.
How did I wind up dating
an outdoorsy type?
I don't know. I think it's
a lot better than living in a library.
I'm outdoorsy as long as
beautiful women in thongs are involved.
Do you ever get tired
of making an ass of yourself?
Not really. I figure
it's a part of my charm.
Yo. Excuse me.
I'm still hungry.
- Knock yourself out.
- I'll make more.
No, that's cool.
- Morning, guys.
- Good morning.
Boys and their toys.
I thought I'd take a walk in the woods
and find something to shoot.
I hope you mean something inanimate.
- Gosh, no, I thought I'd hunt for Bambi.
- Just checking.
I'm gonna come with you. I haven't
been around the island for years.
- You guys wanna come?
- Noah, come on.
Yeah. Yeah, why not?
Enjoy your breakfast.
Actually, I think I'm gonna stay here.
I'm not keen on that dog running around.
- Ok. We'll be careful.
- Keep him away from Thumper, too.
Come on.
No deer. No droppings.
You hear anything?
No.
It makes you wonder
where all the animals are.
Are you guys trying
to freak me out or something?
Is this like a game you play?
What?
- No, I'm serious.
- He's referring to inanimate animals.
You think Sara is feeling Ok?
I hope so.
- She's looking pretty good these days.
- Don't.
- What?
- Don't go there.
Why not?
She's obviously into me, so why
shouldn't I just go for it?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Because I've seen
how you treat women.
Because you're good
at saving them
doesn't always mean I'm the one
that ruins them.
- Brother in love.
- It's all right, man.
- Are you feeling all right?
- Yeah.
Are you sure?
I made out with John.
- So that's what's bothering you?
- Kind of, yeah.
- Why?
- Nice.
I don't know. I guess I thought
the rabies was settling in.
Very funny.
No, actually, I feel fine.
I feel great. I've got like this
adrenaline inside.
From John kissing you?
- Maybe.
- Well, might as well.
- You've liked him since you were 14.
- How did you know?
Who doesn't know that?
Everybody knows.
Oh, really?
Ok, then I hate everybody
right now.
Any day, Mcknight!
Can a brother not get
some alone time?
Damn!
Nice doggy.
Good boy.
Oh!
Ok, Ok...
It's fine. It's fine.
John! Matt! Hey!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
- What happened?
- What are you doing?
The dogs on this island
are not friendly!
- You afraid of a dog?
- No, dogs, man. Plural.
- How many?
- Three, but it sounded like more.
You hear that?
You believe me now?
Oh!
They don't want you here.
The dogs, they don't want you here.
Help!
- Get back!
- We gotta help him!
What's up?
Nothing.
The house.
- Hey!
- Go to the house.
- What?
- Here they come.
What?
Run!
- Run to the house!
- Oh, my God! Run!
Run! Hurry up!
Come on, you guys!
Hurry up!
Hey!
Mattie, no!
This ought to be fun.
- Argh! Argh!
- Damn!
Damn it! Son of a bitch!
God, I'm so sorry, Nikki.
That's Ok.
For all I know,
you could've saved my life.
I don't know if I'm the life-saving kind.
I couldn't save that guy in the woods.
- I thought we were the only ones here.
- He came out of nowhere.
They ripped the shit out of him.
I know! Death by dog is brutal!
None of this makes sense!
There's no reason dogs could do this!
These have the characteristics
of a rabid dog.
- But if they had rabies, they'd be dead.
- Then what is it?
- You know that dog compound?
- The seeing-eye dog facility, yeah.
What if they were actually training
attack dogs, right?
A year ago they shut the compound
down because of a rabies outbreak.
So, attack dogs plus a weird strain
of rabies equals what?
Scary-ass Lassies, that's what!
- Relax.
- They don't want us here.
That's what the dude in the woods said.
Twice.
Who cares?
We need to be focusing
on getting the hell outta here!
I'm in serious need of some painkillers...
and there's something wrong with Sara.
You feel it, don't you?
- Is something wrong with you?
- It comes and goes.
We've gotta be smart here,
smarter than these dogs.
Everybody just shut up! You're all
driving me crazy right now! Wild dogs?
Nikki's right, we gotta get outta here!
Sara needs help
and we're gonna do that!
But first, we'll stay in here
where it's safe, let the dogs disperse,
then get in the plane
and get the hell out...
I don't wanna be here
any more.
What do we do?
We get outta here.
Ready?
The dogs are on the dock.
It's like they know we wanna leave.
You gotta be kidding me!
What?
- The plane's drifting away.
- It can't be. I tied it myself.
Look, then.
Shit. If it hits the channel,
it's lost.
The dogs are gone.
You guys, you guys...
- I don't wanna go out there.
- You're going.
You'll have to swim.
No one else can bring the plane back.
- I know.
- Just give me this.
For your brother being a screw-up,
he's stepping up and being a badass.
I can't believe this.
They chewed through it on purpose.
Listen, I don't know what the hell
is going on around here
but dogs can't think like that.
They can't plan.
If a dog chews through rope,
it's because dogs like chewing rope!
Come on, John.
He's almost there.
Shit!
- Come on, swim back, man!
- Swim!
- The dogs!
- Hurry!
- Stop looking back!
- Swim! Swim faster!
You're fine!
Bitch! Back to the house!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Go! Go! Hurry up! Go!
Run!
Go! Go! Get inside!
Come on, get up the stairs!
Shut the door! Shut the door!
But how did the dogs
even get on the plane?
I once saw a dog balance
a marshmallow on his nose.
Still no service.
- You're running a fever.
- I am?
Don't worry, it wouldn't be rabies yet.
It could be some other kind of infection.
Great.
All right, pros and cons.
What are the negatives?
Negatives? Well, everything.
It's dangerous just trying to get
to the garage.
We don't know if the car will start
or what we'll find across the island.
- Whatever got that guy here.
- With our luck, he parasailed in!
The compound has gotta have
some kind of communications system.
Hopefully it's not equipped
with some crazy Old Yellers.
Look, we can't stay here.
We gotta get off this island.
Ok. Ok?
Ok, damn!
All right, eeny...
Meeny...
Miney...
I'll go.
- lt'll lift right off.
- I don't want you to go.
- I don't want anyone to go.
- I'll be fine. I'll be really quiet.
How much do you weigh?
You know how much I weigh, baby.
You're not doing this.
Speed climbing champion three years
running. I weigh 120 pounds.
I could do this with my hands tied.
You were injured badly.
I know my limits.
This cable can't support you.
I know what I'm talking about.
Think about it.
I mean it. Think about it.
- You didn't get any on the handles?
- No, you'll be fine.
- Be careful.
- Yeah.
You gotta be kidding me.
They're here.
Hurry, Nikki.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Dogs! Dogs!
Dogs! Dogs, over here! Come on!
Come on!
Come on! Piece of shit!
- Hey! Are you Ok?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Just seems like it's gonna be dinnertime
over here soon.
Hang on.
We got something worked out.
Come on, guys!
- Let's go!
- Yep!
- Good?
- More slack! Watch yourself!
- You didn't hit her this time!
- I'm gonna tie the line to the rope.
- Pull it across.
- All right.
Here it is!
All right, pull it, pull it!
Hurry!
Come on.
Behind you! Jump!
Come on!
Nice shot. We got one, man!
Come on, pull!
Bring her in, bring her in.
Get off the harness!
Hey.
You have to talk to me.
I'm not in pain but...
I think I'm in trouble.
- I'm so sorry for this, Sara.
- Don't be. It's not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
- Matt!
It's Ok.
This is Ok?
None of this is Ok.
We should've left this morning.
We should never even have come here.
I didn't know this was supposed
to happen.
Of course you didn't. Because
you don't think, you just do,
only this time you dragged
all of us down with you.
Nikki, just let it happen.
Does this make you feel better?
Lay it all on me. I'm the fuck-up.
Mum knows it. Dad knew it.
It's never you. It's always me.
It is always you. I wasn't given
the room to make mistakes.
- That room was filled with yours.
- I just wanted you to have fun.
Bullshit. You wanted me to act like you
cos if there's two of us it would make
you seem less of a disappointment.
It must be nice to have your life
so together.
Dad would be proud.
What's up? You all right?
- How you doing?
- I'm all right.
You know, er...
when our Dad got sick...
...I knew Matt was pissed at me
for bailing,
but I just didn't know what to do.
After he died, I tried to make it up
to him. I tried to be around more.
I just didn't know
he hated me so much.
He doesn't hate you
as much as he thinks he does.
- All evidence to the contrary.
- He loves you, John.
He's here for you.
Mr Responsible skipped school,
a week away from his finals, just to
spend a weekend with his big brother.
- He can't say no to you.
- Yeah, look where it got him.
None of this is your fault.
You'll get through this.
Besides, you're a hard guy
to stay angry at.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Even I don't hate you
quite as much as I used to.
"Quite."
I really love him, you know.
I know.
I'm glad.
- Hey.
- Want a sip?
Uh-huh.
Your uncle had
very eclectic musical tastes.
That's putting it nicely.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Hey. You're gonna be fine.
I feel awful.
Why? You guys have been wanting
to do that for years.
You'll both recover.
I hope so.
- You ready to turn this mother out?
- Yes!
- Ready?
- Come on, Mr DJ.
The fuse?
- Yeah. I'll get it. I know where it is.
- I'll come with you.
- No, no. Relax, relax.
Each of you has your job.
You're the future doctor -
smart and calm under pressure.
You're the Eagle Scout
in black sheep's clothing -
quick with a weapon
and handy with a sea plane.
You're the perky, athletic one -
very randy to have around.
And you... you look incredibly sexy
in a bikini.
Now where does all that leave moi?
I'm the one who knows
where the fuse box is.
He's in need of psychiatric help.
Why have they always gotta put
the fuse box in the basement? Damn.
Ok.
Oh!
You're mine, baby.
Oh! You gotta be kidding me.
Almost, baby.
Stay with Sara.
No!
Matt, slide that over here!
They're coming
through the door, Nikki! Hurry!
Come on, come on!
Come on, hurry up!
Get Sara and get upstairs now!
Get upstairs!
Get to the attic!
Oh no!
Hurry up!
Matt!
Grab this!
- Ok?
- Let's go, let's go!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Get the rope!
- You Ok?
- My shoulder.
Oh, my God! You got bitten!
None of this seems real.
I can't believe that Noah is dead.
Ok, look, we'll get out of here.
We'll get you guys to a doctor,
Whatever it is,
they're gonna figure it out.
Go away!
- Hey, Sara, please...
- Get off me!
- I'm so sorry.
- That's Ok.
- You know I didn't mean that.
- That's Ok. Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- I promise.
- Ok.
I just don't feel right.
I know.
You'll be all right.
Johnny.
AMCS.
Army Mountain Combat School,
that's who leased the compound.
- So they were training attack dogs?
- Could be experiments that went wrong.
Why would Uncle Frank
have these papers?
Uncle Frank wouldn't be involved
with something like this.
- He was an animal rights activist.
- keep telling yourself that.
They probably told him what
he told me - that the dogs got rabies,
it spread, and that's why
they had to put them all down.
Well, they missed a few.
- Clear?
- Yeah, we're good.
You guys get in the room.
Stay there.
- Be careful.
- I will.
What's that smell?
They've marked their territory.
We're the ones trespassing now.
You ready for this?
No. You?
No.
Jesus, Matt. Matt!
What is he doing? Is he insane?
He's not afraid.
So sad.
I've waited ten years
for him to notice me.
What are you talking about?
It feels over.
It's not over. Don't talk like that.
Pop the clutch!
Shit!
Come on, Mattie.
Come on, Mattie!
- Give me the bow.
- Here.
Heads up, Mattie!
Come on, come on.
We need more speed.
Hold on!
Better work this time!
- Cool.
- Piece of cake.
They don't like the noise.
Let's go!
I don't think I'm gonna make
those finals, Johnny.
Shit!
Hold on to him!
Sara won't come down.
You've gotta help.
I got it, Mattie.
- I tried everything.
- Get in.
Sara!
- Sara.
- Go away.
- No.
- Get out!
- No!
- I won't make it.
I don't care! Get up! On your feet!
Get out of my house!
- John, out the window!
- I'm not leaving!
You understand?
If I break eye contact, it's over.
I will be right behind you.
- Gone?
- Yeah.
You Ok?
Sara!
- Sara!
- No, no.
- No!
- Come on!
That fence didn't used
to be here.
We'll break through it with the car.
What if the fence is the only thing
standing between us and those dogs?
That's true.
Ok... Ok,
but we'll leave the car running.
If we turn it off, we don't know
if it'll start again.
The car's not gonna
get us off this island.
Well, if we need to,
it'll get us the hell out of here.
Come on.
There's gotta be a radio here.
It's no good if there's no power.
- Look.
- Solar panel.
- We could hook onto that, right?
- Yeah.
- Were you ever here?
- No, not inside.
Looks like an attack-protection suit.
What the hell is all this stuff?
This was not a training facility.
Something else was going on here.
They weren't training anything.
They were genetically redesigning them.
They were playing God.
No!
Let's keep moving.
Here's a radio.
No power.
All right, how do we hook in
to the solar power?
The batteries have to be
around here somewhere.
Down here.
- Batteries.
- All right, good.
I'm gonna check the main first.
Hit the breaker.
These batteries
are never gonna charge.
They're too rusted. Look.
No, they're the old lead-acid kind.
They'll hold a charge forever.
Positive to positive.
Negative to negative. Just like a car.
You good?
- Nice.
- Right.
How do you know all this?
You'd be surprised what an irresponsible
fuck-up can pick up over the years.
Ok, here we go.
Does it Work?
- It's dead.
- Still no signal.
Give me that cell phone.
Open the back.
We can hook up this phone
to the radio tower.
It's a giant antenna. By itself,
a cell gives you two, three miles,
but a tower like that gives you
over 100. We attach the cell phone...
here to the radio antenna.
- Shit. No signal.
Wait a minute, guys. Look right there,
on the radio tower.
- There's a cable detached.
- I'll go.
- We gotta stick together.
You guys stay here. Once I connect
the cables, you're gonna see this signal.
When you see the signal, you wanna
turn on the antenna amplifier here.
All right.
Hey... Be careful.
We're gonna get outta here.
What's wrong?
Baby, calm down, sit down.
It's just...
What happened to Sara
is gonna happen to me.
Matt, don't talk like that.
You're gonna drive yourself crazy.
What's wrong?
What?
They're inside.
What are you talking about?
For the dogs to survive
being put down
they would've had
to find a way to escape.
If they found a way out
of the compound...
They found their way back in.
John.
Argh!
Oh, my God!
Give Cujo my best.
Nikki!
- Nikki!
- No!
Stop it! Listen! Listen to me!
There is a boat on the other side
of this fence!
It's our only way out!
We're not getting off this island, John!
Need a ride?
- I thought you were dead.
- Any ideas?
Hang on!
Come on!
- You Ok?
- Yeah.
Go!
John, get the boat started.
Jump on!
What do you think's gonna happen
to you guys?
Find a doctor that can cure it.
- What if he can't?
- He has to.
I need some sleep.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org