Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My name is Dale Kerrigan,
and this is my story.
Our family lives at 3 Highview Crescent,
Coolaroo.
Dad bought this place
15 years ago for a steal.
As the real estate agent
said, "Location, location, location."
And we're right next door
to the airport.
It will be very convenient
if we ever have to fly one day.
Dad still can't work out
how he got it so cheap.
It's worth almost as much today
as when we bought it.
Our street was going to be the heart
of a major housing development.
But it never got up.
They reckon the planes put people off.
Them and the power lines.
Not Dad. He reckons power lines
are a reminder...
of man's ability
to generate electricity.
He's always saying
great things like that.
That's why we love him so much.
Dad is the backbone
of the Kerrigan family.
He made our billiard table.
Shot, Dale.
In fact, he's built half this house.
He's always planning extensions.
I reckon we need a patio.
Oh, darl, how about we finish
the back room first?
No, I'm waiting
on some cheap siding.
I reckon we give
the patio another go.
Dad is a tow truck driver.
One of the best in the game.
He takes great pride
in his work.
And he comes home
with so many stories.
You see, the car was wrapped
around the pole,
so I said, " Why not hook the chain
on the back axle?"
See, no one
had thought of that.
If Dad is the backbone,
Mum is the other bones. All of them.
She keeps
the family together.
Dad adores Mum,
and Mum adores him.
They met at the greyhounds one night,
and it was love at first sight.
Mum just loves craft.
And she can pretty up
just about anything.
How did you do that?
- Spray can and stencil, darl.
That's all you need.
- You could sell that.
Dad always reckons
Mum could open a shop,
but she has a good part-time job
in the office at Sunbeam.
Dad reckons Mum is
the greatest cook on Earth.
- What do you call that, darl?
- Sponge cake.
Beautiful. And what's
that stuff on top?
- Icing sugar.
- How is it, kids?
And why would you want
to go out to a restaurant...
when this keeps coming up
night after night?
I have two brothers
and a sister, all older than me.
Steve is an apprentice mechanic,
but he spends most of his time
reading the Trading Post.
He just loves
buying and trading.
Dad, ergonomic chairs.
Four of them.
- What does he want?
- One-eighty.
He's dreaming.
Him and Dad
really know bargains.
Steve is also an ideas man.
That's why Dad calls him the ideas man.
He has lots of ideas.
It's a motorcycle helmet
with a built-in brake light.
You are an ideas man, Steve.
Dad thinks all of us
are tremendous,
but I guess it's no secret
that Tracey's his favorite.
How do I look, Dad?
Dad just loves her.
You look beautiful.
Thanks, Dad.
Tracey's the only girl in the family,
apart from Mum and Gran.
Tracey constantly
gave Dad proud moments.
Once she was
on "The Price Is Right".
It was such
an exciting afternoon for us.
Swap them around.
None of us could actually
believe it was Tracey up there
with Larry Emdier.
$45,000 worth of prizes.
The luggage needs to be more than 640.
It needs to be less
than 740.
She almost won the lot.
If only she'd known
the price of the luggage.
I'm so sorry about that.
But she still managed to come home
with a tumble dryer and drill set.
She is the only member of the Kerrigan
family who'd had a college education.
Dad reckons the day she graduated
as a fully-qualified hairdresser...
was about
the proudest day of his life.
I knew he thought
about that... a lot.
There were only two places
he did his thinking--
in the poolroom and out the back,
looking up at the power lines.
Yep, Dad's a real thinker.
But the proudest day
was the day she got married
to this nice guy called Con.
He is an accountant,
but also a fanatical kickboxer.
Now Tracey's
taken up kickboxing too.
Dad could not get
the smile off his face.
And he gave a speech
that brought the house down.
Now, as the bride's parents,
I don't mind paying for the wedding,
but could you please stop busting
all them plates?
That being
a Greek custom and all.
I suppose, as a father,
you'd like your daughter
to marry one of your own.
And let's not beat around the bush.
The Greeks have a reputation.
At first, the Petropoulouses
thought he was having a go at them.
But Dad was just saying
how much he thought of Con.
I never thought anyone
could love our Trace...
as much as me,
Sal and the boys.
But there is
another person. Con.
Smart, polite,
fit as a fiddle.
And anyone who loves our Trace
as much as us deserves our love.
So we love you, Con.
We love you.
Thank you, and, uh,
"Kalispera".
That's "Good evening."
We'd had many top nights,
but this was the most top.
Pity my oldest brother
couldn't be there.
His name's Wayne.
He's in jail.
Eight years
for armed robbery.
Many people call him the black sheep
of the family. But not Mum and Dad.
He got caught up with the wrong crowd.
He didn't mean to rob the gas station.
Now he's sorry. With good behavior,
he'll be out in a couple of years.
I visit him every Friday.
- How's Mum?
- Good.
- How's Dad?
- How's Trace?
- Good.
- How are you?
- How's Dave?
- He's all right.
Good.
Even though he's the oldest
and I'm the youngest, we get on great.
We can just chat for hours.
Thanks for coming down.
- You want some chewy?
- No.
So, as you can see,
our family is very close-knit.
We also have pets.
Four greyhounds.
Banshee,
Starflash,
Trailblazer and Coco.
Coco is the best,
most successful Dad has ever had.
She picked up two firsts
in the country and a third in town.
Dad feeds them every morning
in big bowls...
that Steve made out
of tractor hubcaps.
They are good dogs. Good to Dad.
And Dad is good to them.
All of them are descended
from his first dog, Red Rocket.
Dad never stops marveling
at the beauty of the greyhound.
In fact, he doesn't even
race them for the money.
He reckons they are noble animals.
Skinny and sleek...
and have a beautiful snout.
Another thing Dad loves
is his boat. Sea Lady.
He cleans it every Saturday
with something else Steve built.
It's a brush
with a hose in it.
Dad never stops marveling
at Steve's ideas.
He's a ideas man, Steve.
Steve gave it to Dad
for Father's Day.
That's something our family
prides itself on. Presents.
Even though none of us
have a real lot of money,
we love giving
each other presents.
- He got a rod and reel from Trace.
- A rod and reel.
- I gave him a new muzzle.
- A muzzle.
Wayne sent him an ashtray
he'd made in prison shop.
An ashtray?
But I don't smoke.
And Mum, well, Mum got him a big German
beer mug from Franklin Mint.
Dad couldn't believe his eyes. It was
too good to even drink beer out of.
I'd like
to do pottery.
Oh, you should.
You'd be good at it.
This is going straight
to the poolroom.
All Dad's most prized possessions
are in the poolroom.
All his mementos and things
that remind him of something special.
So by him saying it was going straight
to the poolroom...
meant he thought
it was special.
That is a collector's item.
This has been
the best Father's Day ever.
Of course there
were ups and downs.
Wayne being in jail
was an example of a down.
But, all in all,
3 Highview Crescent was a happy home.
Dad called it his castle.
But one day in June,
a knock at the door
was to change all that.
- Yeah?
- Mr. Darryl Kerrigan?
- John Clifton.
I'm from the local council.
- Is this about the dogs?
- No.
- The aerial? The extensions?
Look, if this is about
my truck on the nature strip,
I've had it out with you guys.
No, I'm a valuer
with the local council.
I'm here to do a land valuation.
- What for?
- Well, all properties
get valued from time to time.
So, you'd be able
to give me a value on this place?
- That's my job.
- That'd be good.
- Do you want me
to show you around?
- If you wouldn't mind.
Oh, not at all.
Be pleased to.
Because, between you and me,
I reckon the values around here are--
As you can see,
I've put a fair bit of work into it.
Would you like me to point out
the features as we go along?
- If you wouldn't mind.
- You see that lace up there?
- Yeah?
- Fake. Plastic.
Gives the place
a Victoriana feel.
The chimney? Fake too.
Why is it there?
Charm. Adds a bit of charm.
Look at the size of that aerial.
That's a big aerial.
What do you think? Add a bit of value?
- Hard to say. Yeah.
- Yeah.
You can overcapitalize,
can't you?
But it's a huge aerial.
And this is my backyard.
- Shuttle. From Melbourne to Sidney.
- How close are you
to the end of the runway?
- Ah, just over the fence.
- Is that the runway there?
- Yeah.
- There?
Beautiful machines.
Sometimes you think
they're gonna land right on top of you.
Freaks the dogs, though.
Greyhounds.
Large kennel.
Well, originally, it was a tree house
when the kids were growing up.
I was thinking of turning it
into another room.
- But the county said no.
- Ah.
Now, here back, all landfill.
Not allowed to build there.
- Has the soil been tested?
- Oh, yeah.
Nothing too serious
in there.
What do you know
about lead?
Oh, this is
beautiful, darl.
- What do you call these things again?
- Meat loaf.
Everybody cooks
meat loaf, darl.
Yeah, but it's
what you do with them.
Mum reckons the trick is you
don't use minced meat.
She gets topside and crushes it.
Is that right, darl?
Well, it shows.
She gets silverside
and she'll crush that too.
Dad, a guy's selling
a pair of jousting sticks.
Jousting sticks?
What does he want for them?
- Make us an offer.
- Darl, what do you want
with jousting sticks?
Oh, I don't know. But I reckon they
wouldn't come up all that often.
But they're jousting sticks.
What would anyone want
with jousting sticks?
Well, if you get them
for half price, it's a bargain.
- Give him a call?
- Yeah.
I'll be interested to see
this fella's valuation.
- Are you thinking
of selling, Dad?
- Oh, no, mate, no.
But it would be nice to know
what we're sitting on here.
Clay.
No, mate.
The value of the house.
You know, it's odd, because
Farouk reckoned he had
some bloke around as well.
Must've been doing
the whole street.
- Maybe the market's on the move.
- Here?
Dad? Four-fifty.
For jousting sticks?
Tell him he's dreaming.
How much is a jousting stick worth,
Dad?
Well, it couldn't be more
than 250.
- Depending on the condition.
- When do we find out?
Well, we should have the official notice
in a couple of weeks.
But just quietly,
I reckon we could be in
for a little surprise.
Compulsorily acquired.
You know what this means,
don't you?
- They're acquiring it compulsorily.
- It must be a mistake.
They're gonna take our place,
and we don't get a say in it.
- Well, how can they do that?
- I don't know. 70,000 bucks.
Who the hell
is Air Link?
- Dad, a guy's selling seven coolers.
- Hang on, Steve.
What's that?
Is this about Wayne?
No, no. Look.
What do you make
of that?
Jesus. This is
a kick-out notice.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
- Ah, good day, Farouk.
- Hello, Mr. Kerrigan.
Can you read to me something,
please, I get today?
Yeah, sure, mate,
but I'm a bit busy at the moment.
Can I-- Can I come--
- Shit. You got one too.
- Got what?
What the hell
is going on?
Jesus Christ.
Jack!
Jack, it's Darryl, mate.
Someone is going
to take me house, Darryl.
- Mr. Kerrigan.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Mr. Kerrigan--
Darryl, this is
a compulsory acquisition.
Yeah.
Mr. Kerrigan,
the airport is expanding.
They're setting up one of the largest
freight-handling facilities...
in the Southern Hemisphere,
and they need a great deal of space.
Yeah.
And your house...
is on that space.
Yeah. Yeah,my house.
That's right. Your house.
That's why
you'll be duly compensated.
No. No, you've missed the point.
I'm not interested in compensation.
I don't wanna go.
Under the laws
of compulsory acquisition--
and I don't necessarily
agree with those laws--
I can understand
the pain and trouble--
Would you stop pretending
to be on my side?
All right, Mr. Kerrigan,
I'll state this simply.
There is
an ironclad agreement...
between federal, state
and local governments
and the Airports Commission.
Yeah?
Well, where's the agreement
with Darryl Kerrigan,
3 Highview Crescent, Coolaroo?
Where'sthat agreement?
It's not gonna happen.
I don't know, Darryl.
This isn't my area.
What do you mean this is not your area?
This is law.
Darryl, the airport
wants to buy your place.
Airports come under federal law.
Federal? I just do small stuff.
Conveyancing, magistrates.
- You defended Wayne.
- Yeah, and he got eight years.
Yeah, but you did your best.
I mean, you can hold your head up high.
He was the one that
held up the service station.
- I don't know anything
about this sort of stuff.
- But they can't do this.
- I don't know. Maybe they can.
- They can't.
Look, I'll ring around
and I'll see what I can find out.
Good on you, Dennis. Eh.
How is Wayne?
Good. Yeah, good.
Behaving himself.
- Any word?
- Nah, nah.
They reckon he's still
a couple of years off.
I'll let you know.
But Dad was never one
to bring worries home.
Even in the down times he'd still
tell us funny stories about his day.
It's a head-on between
a Geo and a Volksy.
Dad also had a way
of making everyone feel important.
Come on, Dale.
Tell 'em.
Go on. Tell 'em.
Dale dug a hole.
- Like the time I dug a hole.
- Started the patio.
- Good on you, Dale.
- And he'd compliment Mum every
single night on her cooking.
Well, hello.
How's this, boys? Whoo-hoo!
- What do you call this?
- Chicken.
- Yeah, but it's got something
sprinkled on it.
- Seasoning.
Seasoning.
Looks like everybody's
kicked a goal.
How are our
backs feeling?
Steve did get them
ergonometric chairs.
And Mum had already
started prettying hers up.
Dad placed a great deal
of importance on mealtime.
He had
a very strict rule:
When the family starts to eat,
the television is definitely
turned down.
But as soon as we've finished eating,
it's a different story.
That was great.
Dad, 7:30.
All right,
time for some fun.
Dad reckons there's only one show better
than Funniest Home Videos,
and that's The Best
of Funniest Home Videos.
It made Dad laugh. And when Dad laughed,
his whole body joined in.
And then we would too.
Doggy breath!
It was funny how on the fun nights,
part of me got sad,
'cause I'd think about
my big brother in prison
and wonder what he was doing.
Wayne always reckoned
he was doing fine,
but I get the feeling
he was missing us more
than he was letting on.
It'll be great
when he comes home.
You're a ripper, Dennis.
I said you're
a bloody ripper!
Yeah, okay.
- That's it, Sal. All fixed.
- What did he say?
He said I have recourse
to the Administrative Appeals Tribunal.
All I gotta do is run
up there, put my case,
and they can go and get stuffed.
Good on you, darl.
- He still hasn't noticed, Mum.
- What?
- Oh, it's finished.
- Today.
How is that?
You should open a shop.
Dad, some guy's selling
an overhead projector.
Nah--
Nah, hang on, Steve.
What's he asking?
- One-fifty.
- Tell him he's dreaming.
- Yeah.
- So what else
did Dennis have to say?
- Nothing. It's fixed.
- Yeah, but when's the hearing?
Monday. And I know exactly
what I'm gonna say.
- Don't babble on, darl.
- I don't babble on.
When do I babble on?
- You do babble on.
- All right.
But I tell you
what we're gonna do.
Friday we're gonna
pick up Trace and Con,
and then we're going straight up
to Bonnie Doon for the weekend.
And we're not worrying about
those clowns for another second.
- Mum! Price is Right'son.
- All right, eh.
I'd better ring up Farouk and Jack
and Evonne and the others...
and tell 'em
what's going on.
Trace and Con had
a great honeymoon in Thailand.
We met them as they came off
the plane with a baggage cart,
which was lucky 'cause
they had heaps of stuff.
We couldn't wait to hear all
the stories about their trip,
and we didn't have
to wait all that long either.
'Cause one of the good things
about living next to the airport...
is that it doesn't
take long to walk home.
And they had these masks
which you put over your eyes
when you're sleeping...
so that you can't
see anything.
- And they were complimentary.
- Yeah, they were for free.
It was the first time
anyone in our family...
had traveled
outside the county.
And we just sat glued
listening to all the details.
Oh, Mum, we had a choice between fish
and Beef Wellington.
- Beef Wellington?
- What's that, darl?
It's beef
done in pastry.
And it was an absolute
credit to the airline.
- Did they show a film?
- Two.
- Two?
- Yeah.
- And they also had--
- What were they?
- We saw Twister. And they had--
- Was it on a screen or a telly?
Telly. And they had
easy listening, classic gold,
contemporary rock, world--
What was the other one,
the other film?
- Uh,Juman-- Jumanji, yeah.
-Jumanji.
- And with the headphones--
- Which one was first?
- Twister. You could
turn the sound all--
- How many on the way back?
- Dale! You can ask all this later.
- Sorry, Trace.
It was so dry in the plane
that your hair actually dehydrates.
- Doesn't it, Con?
- It loses its moisture.
- It's so interesting.
We could have
listened for hours,
but then it
was presents time.
For you, Dad. It's a samurai sword
letter opener.
That is handcrafted.
How's that, love?
That is just--
This is going straight
to the poolroom.
You should use it, Dad.
This I am not even taking
out of the wrapper.
They bought Mum a genuine Rolex
for 15 bucks off a guy at the beach.
He said he'd mail
the warranty later.
I got a necklace with a shark tooth.
They got a Walkman for Steve.
'Cause it was Friday,
I told Trace I'd take
Wayne's present to him.
It was an elephant,
'cause elephants bring good luck,
especially if the trunks are up,
and his trunk was up.
It really made Wayne's day.
- She's great, isn't she? Trace.
- Yeah.
It brings good luck.
She's coming in on Monday.
Great. And when's Dad going in
to do that hearing?
- On Monday.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. He reckons they can't do it.
- Dad would know.
- You going up to
Bonnie Doon tonight?
- Yeah. Maybe. I don't know.
I didn't want to tell Wayne
that we were going to Bonnie Doon,
just in case he'd feel bad
that we were going to Bonnie Doon.
He liked it there.
We all liked it there.
* We're going to Bonnie Doon *
We all left soon after,
except for Trace and Con.
As you can just imagine,
they were just married and
wanted some time to themselves.
So they drove up
in their own car.
Dad had a song he used to sing
about going to Bonnie Doon.
Only he sang it a lot,
and it was a bit repetitive.
Darl!
- Dad, radar!
- How much did that cost?
- Seventy bucks.
Just paid for itself.
Dale, why don't you
unload the boat, Mate?
Steve, don't forget
the dog food, pal.
Hey, boy. Hey!
- Bloody marvelous to be
up here, isn't it, Dale?
- Yeah.
- Bonnie Doon.
- Dad loved Bonnie Doon.
How do I describe it?
It is a little town
on a big lake.
It's a beautiful place,
especially this time of year
when the water levels are down.
Dad could not believe his luck
when he found this place.
It was a bargain,
and he couldn't work out why.
It was just a block of land
with a beautiful view.
It took him five years
to build this place.
He bought an unfinished kit home
out of the Trading Post,
built it in the backyard
and towed it up here with his truck.
He was the only bloke
he knew with a holiday home.
Not a mobile home,
a holiday home.
And he reckoned we were
the luckiest family in the world.
- Dale, I reckon we're the luckiest
family in the world. - Yeah.
He loved the serenity of the place.
How's the serenity?
I think he also just loved the word.
So much serenity.
Let's get to bed.
Tomorrow is going to be a great day.
Yeah.
If there's one thing
Dad loved more than serenity,
it was an outboard motor
on full throttle.
Listen to that!
Singing like a bird!
He just loved Bonnie Doon,
and he reckoned the faster you went,
the more you saw of it.
Look at that!
- What?
- Back there.
But eventually he found a place
he reckoned looked like a good spot.
I reckon this looks like a good spot.
Dad loved fishing. And he really
looked after his equipment.
He said they only made on good rod,
it's called the 'ugly stick'.
It's so strong, you can bend it
right around on itself.
Look at that.
Bends right around itself.
The lake had trout,
redfin and carp.
The carp was not a good eating fish,
but it was good catching.
They could grow
to quite a size.
Genuinely, that just hooked himself.
But occasionally Dad went crafty.
- Got a nibble.
Dad reckoned that fishing
was 10 percent brains
and 95 percent muscle...
and the rest
was just good luck.
We pulled off a few carp that day.
And each of us had a muscle ache.
- Where's Con?
- Down the shops.
You and Con talked about kids, yet?
Yeah, Con wants to start
straight away.
But, you know,
I've got a career.
Of course.
So, I said I'm not having kids
until I'm at least 23.
Times have changed.
- Gale had a boy.
- Was he a whopper?
10 pounds. They got to be
a big beefy family.
Tyler Jake. Even the birth notice
was beef. Stork and everything.
Shannon was 9 pounds.
Would you mind then?
Uh, I needed a pair of booties.
You always liked booties.
- I reckon you should make
faked flowers. - Uh, yeah.
- Jenny makes fake flowers.
- Jenny?
- Yeah.
- Jenny Jenny?
No, Malcoway Jenny. She reckons
the trick is to make 'em real
but not too real. Just real enough
to know that they're fake.
- I'd like to do pottery.
- Wow, on a wheel?
Yeah. I just love mugs.
Yeah, I'd like
to make my own mugs.
- Mum?
- Yeah?
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
- You worried about the house?
- No.
- Well, Dad said everything's
going to be okay.
- Of course it is, darl.
We ended up
with four carp and one redfin.
A reasonable day's fishing,
considering we had to get back
earlier when Coco got seasick.
Steve wasn't looking
all that good either.
Keep it still, Trace.
Disciplined,
isn't he, Sal?
Here are you and I relaxing,
having a beer, and he's still training.
Yeah, he just loves
that sport.
- Well, you gotta have
a passion for something.
- Yeah.
Ours is serenity.
Dad, where do you want me to put
the chicken coop?
Out the back, Steve.
Forty-five bucks. You couldn't buy
the materials for that.
Now, what do you want
with a chicken coop?
And what do we want
with a kit home?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Now, give me a kiss,
you big hunk of a man.
Marvellous, ain't it?
The lake, the kids.
Oh, look at the dogs.
Don't they love it?
Oh, smell that.
- Diesel.
- Yep.
Pity Wayne can't be here.
- Darl.
- No, no, I could've done better.
Well, let's start
cooking this feast.
- Who ordered medium rare?
- Me.
Good stuff.
Check that, Steve.
It could be a little underdone.
- I bet they don't have places
like this in Thailand, Con.
- No, Mr. Kerrigan.
Hey, hey, hey.
"Darryl" now, mate.
Sorry, Darryl.
- It's a good place, though.
- Yeah, yeah, I'm curious.
Now, I know it's unfair
to compare anyplace to Bonnie Doon,
but why would I want to go there
instead of here?
- It's for young people, Dad.
- I know that, Trace.
- It's the culture, Darryl.
The place is full of culture.
- Chockers.
- Oh, yeah.
- Something for everyone.
- What was that movie again, Con?
- Dale.
There were so many stories.
At the hotel
Trace and I were staying in,
they had this one channel:
kickboxing, 24 hours a day.
It was just so interesting
to hear about another county.
Meals were 5 dollars, mum.
The most beautiful sadeys(?).
What's that, darl?
It's meat on skew with
peanut sauce and wheat.
And the stories
went on and on all night.
The value for money is
absolutely second to none.
- One of the other Sony Walkmans.
- With presets?
Yeah, presets and megabytes.
$85 dollars Australian.
- Wow.
- Bargain?
But I reckon someone like you, Steve,
could have got it down even further.
I can't wait to get a beer and coffee.
- It's great to have you two back.
- It's great to be back.
Great to be up here.
They haven't got
a place like this in Bangkok.
How's the serenity?
Not a sound.
- Feeling good, Sal.
- Good on you, darl.
Steve, could you move
the Corolla?
I need to get to the Torana out
so I can get to the Commodore.
I'll have to get the keys
to the Cortina if I'm going
to move that Corolla.
- Watch the boat, mate.
- Yeah.
- Know why I'm feeling good, Sal?
- Why?
I'll tell you why.
Because this is an example
of the individual.
Of how the individual,
if he has the guts to stand up...
and shove it right up
those people who think
they can stand on top of you.
The people who think
they can do that, that's why.
What do you mean
what's my plea?
- What is the case you are putting?
- I told you.
I mean, you just can't walk in
and take a man's house.
Mr. Kerrigan, are you disputing
the amount of compensation?
I'm not interested in compensation.
I'm saying that you can't kick me out.
Very well.
- What is your argument?
- That's it.
That's my argument.
You can't kick me out.
And on what law do you base
that argument?
- The law
of bloody common sense!
- Mr. Kerrigan.
- I must ask you
to restrain yourself.
- Yeah, all right.
Mr. Kerrigan, this is
the Administrative Appeals Tribunal.
You are an applicant.
You need to show--
I need to show?
So it's up to me, is it?
Mr. Kerrigan, Air Link,
as a federal authority,
has the right to purchase property
compulsorily.
And, as far as I can see,
you have offered no evidence
to refute that right.
No evidence?
It's not a house. It's a home.
A man's home is his castle.
I mean, it's-- it's--
it's Jack's castle.
It's Farou-Farouk's castle.
You just can't walk in
and steal our homes.
- You will be compensated.
- I don't wanna be compensated.
You can't buy
what I've got.
Mr. Kerrigan, I am rapidly
running out of patience.
- You're running out of patience.
- What is your case in law?
Well, okay, um,
the law is supposed
to be about justice-- no, fairness.
And I know that sometimes
what is right and fair is
not clear-cut. It's a bit iffy.
But this is not iffy.
I mean, this is as clear as day.
It is right and fair
that a family be allowed
to live in its own house.
That is justice.
I rest my case.
Dad reckoned he'd nailed it.
Farouk agreed.
But Dad was wrong.
I can't believe I lost.
I've let you down.
No, no, Mr. Kerrigan.
You do good job.
- Please, Farouk, call me Darryl.
- Okay, Mr. Darryl.
But, you know, I never heard that one
you say before.
"A man's home is his castle."
Well, that's an old saying.
No, no. Other one. Other one.
"Is not house, is home."
Farouk, I lost.
I know, Mr. Darryl.
Farouk, how much
are they paying you?
- $65,000.
- For your place?
Yes. They say the plane,
they fly overhead, drop the value.
I don't care. In Beirut,
plane fly overhead, drop bomb.
- I like this plane.
- What are we going to do, Darryl?
I don't know, Jack.
This is the only place I can afford.
I don't wanna move.
You see what
they're doing, Sal?
Mm.
- How long you lived here, Jack?
- Three years.
Now, in the area.
How long have you lived around here?
Fifty-seven years.
And they're gonna
kick you out on your ass.
Well, bugger 'em.
I'm not giving up, Jack.
If they wanna play things by the law,
fine. We'll play by the law.
But they're not
the only big guns in town.
If it's gonna be lawyers, I'm gonna
hit them with the big artillery.
Hang on, Darryl.
Jesus, these fucking photocopiers.
What the fuck is that?
I cleared tray three.
Why don't you get your girl
to do that for you?
She's not here on Mondays.
She does Tuesday, Thursday, Friday.
F-3. What the fuck
is that?
- Dennis, how did it go?
- Not good.
I spoke to every barrister I know.
No one wants to touch it.
All right. You do it.
I told you, Darryl,
I'm not qualified.
You're not qualified?
Now I've heard everything.
What do you mean
you're not qualified?
I mean I'm not
in the big time.
You have lost faith
in yourself, Dennis.
- Darryl--
- You have lost faith.
Darryl, it's over my head.
It's over your head too.
Over my head? Dennis.
- Darryl, have you heard
of the Barlow Group?
-No.
It's basically a big investment company
controlled by three blokes...
worth about
a half a billion each.
Well, the Barlow Group
is Air Link.
I thought Air Link
was the government.
It's a government authority,
but all the money's coming from Barlow.
It's a way of privatizing
without privatizing.
Anyway, it's a big, big thing.
Every level of government.
Huge investment.
All right, fine.
So they're big.
But why do they
wantmy house?
Why don't they just fill in
the old quarry and build it there?
I don't know. Maybe it's just cheaper
to pull down more houses.
- So we fight 'em.
- Darryl, they want this thing to work.
- They're gonna get their way.
- And you know why people
like that get their way?
Because people like us
don't stand up to 'em.
Now, they've still
gotta play by the rules.
Darryl, they write the rules.
They own the game.
Fuck, Dennis. It's my fucking house.
You're not gonna run scared on me.
I can't do this by myself.
All right, mate.
Let me think about it.
- Con's working late tonight.
- He's just so busy.
I cannot believe
this postcard arrived today.
Thanks
for dropping in.
How's he treating
my princess?
Dad!
All right,
all right.
You saw
some amazing things.
Now, that is
a bloody big statue.
- Yeah, and it's all made of gold.
- Is that so?
This bloke's
gonna win the cars.
- How's the salon?
- Good.
And look at these models.
They've got ripper bodies,
but they let themselves down
in the hair department.
You ought to contact
Channel Nine, get
a contract with them.
Dad, it doesn't work
like that.
Well, look at them and look at you.
Now, that is a head of hair.
- Just beautiful.
- Thanks, Dad.
I'm only stating
the truth.
Dad, what's a pulpit?
Where the minister gives
his sermon from. How much?
- Eight hundred.
- Dreaming.
Actually, I know how
to get you on there.
- Send in a photo of you
for the home viewers.
- Dad, if you dare.
- Oh, I've got quite a few lying around.
- Dad!
Actually, I think I've got one taken
when you were two...
and you didn't have
any clothes on.
Dad! Don't you--
- Quite a few to choose from there.
- Don't-- No!
That night I thought of Wayne again.
I wondered what he was doing
and whether the elephant's
trunk was still up.
'Cause that
brings good luck.
So, in conclusion,
my client will be appealing the decision
to the federal court...
and, as an interim, will
be seeking an injunction...
to stop any further action
in this matter.
Sincerely, Dennis Denuto.
Hammersley and Laycock.
May I help you?
Yes, putting you through now.
I'm afraid he can't come
to the phone right now, Farouk.
He's up in the ceiling.
All right, I'll get him
to give you a call
as soon as he comes down.
Okay. Oh, give my love to Taboulah.
- Good-bye.
- Shit!
Steve!
- Yeah?
- The beams aren't supporting.
- I reckon we put a hold
on the mezzanine.
- Yeah, all right.
But I'll have to give that guy a
call about the spiral staircase
'cause he's holding it for us.
- Darl, can you give Farouk a ring?
- Yeah.
- Where's Dad?
- Up in the roof.
- Dad!
- Yeah, mate?
I dug another hole.
It's filling with water.
You are fucking kidding me.
I cleared that tray three fucking times!
- Mr. Denuto.
- Yeah?
Ron Graham, Hammersley and Laycock.
Got your note during the week.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Um, sit down.
Now, the Kerrigan matter.
Well, we're going
to be taking it further.
Yes, we totally understand,
and we're here on behalf
of our client to apologize.
- We made a mistake.
- You have?
Yes, it appears that the house
belonging to Mr. Kerrigan was
grossly undervalued by mistake,
and our client would like
to rectify the situation.
- Well, what are you offering?
- Another $25,000.
- Whoa.
- As a separate cash check.
You know, Darryl, my client,
is disputing
the compulsory purchase.
Yes, though with
the correct valuation,
we thought this may put
the dispute to rest.
What if it doesn't?
If I were you,
I would advise Mr. Kerrigan
against taking any further action.
This is
a multi-billion dollar project.
It's been in planning
for a long time.
If this action were to delay
or spoil the plans,
the understandable anger
could well spill into something else.
- Are you threatening?
- Hang on.
I just came in here,
apologized and increased
the offer by $25,000.
- I'm sorry.
- And that offer should
be put to Mr. Kerrigan...
with your strongest
possible recommendation.
Tell 'em to get stuffed.
- It's $25,000, Darryl.
- Don't you get this, Dennis?
Darryl, they're
offering 25 grand extra.
Dennis, this is not about money.
I am not leaving my house.
- Tell 'em I'm not moving.
- They're not gonna be happy.
- Who cares?
- I mean, they're
gonna be really unhappy.
- So what are you telling me, Dennis?
- Nothing, Darryl.
- Did they threaten you?
- Not me, really.
- They threatened me.
- Not exactly. They just said--
- They fucking well threatened me.
- They just said--
I want you to get on that phone
right now and tell 'em where
they can shove their 25 grand.
Darryl, " them"
is the Barlow Group,
people used
to getting their way.
Now, they want
to expand the airport,
and there's one bloke
who's a pain in the ass.
Tell 'em to get stuffed.
More, darling?
Oh, no. No, love. That was beautiful.
What do you call that?
lce cream.
Yeah, but what you've done with it.
What did you do to it?
Scooped it out of the tub.
Did I do the right thing?
Oh, yes, sweetheart,
you did the right thing.
- Twenty-five grand, Dad.
- Yeah, but not that way, Steve.
We're not gonna
take the money.
- I want to tell you a story.
- Oh, good.
- About how your father and I met.
- I know this one.
Not all of it, Dale.
You see, I used to go out
with a very handsome young man,
well-to-do,
called Bob Thompson.
Big Bob Thompson.
What's he doing now, eh?
Putting in fence posts
in the country.
- He runs a construction company.
- So he says.
Well, anyway, one night he took me
to the greyhounds.
- He put on a real show.
We ate at the carvery.
- What did you have?
Uh, pork.
Anyway, we had wine, champagne.
He put on all my bets,
and he was just sweeping me off my feet.
And I wouldn't have
been at all surprised
if he'd popped the question.
Well, anyway, later on--
I don't know what it was--
But out of the corner of my eye
I spotted this lanky bloke...
- struggling with one of his greyhounds.
- Red Rocket.
- That's you, Dad.
- Now, Bob, he went off to talk
to one of the stewards.
And this young fella,
he comes right up to me
and starts chatting to me...
and he asks me out.
And I said,
"Well, I'm on a date."
Well, he backed right off.
He said he wasn't cutting
anyone's lunch,
and he wished me good night.
And I thought,
"That man has principles."
And from that day on,
I've only had eyes for one man.
Hook, line and sinker.
And that's what I love about him:
his principles.
So we're not taking
the money, Steve.
Hang on. I'll get it.
What was the carvery like?
- Yeah?
- Mr. Kerrigan.
- Yeah? What?
- I've just got a message to pass on.
- From who?
- I'm just passing on a message.
- Are you from the council?
- No, I'm not from the council.
- The company.
- I'm just passing on
a message, Mr. Kerrigan.
They always send
someone different, don't they?
The message is,
"Take the offer and shut up."
Understood?
- Are you threatening me?
- I'm just passing on a message.
- Fuck off, you clown! Fuck off!
- Mr. Kerrigan--
- You better watch your mouth, pal.
- You heard my dad.
- Now, fuck off!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa. Fine.
I'm just trying
to tell you.
And what the fuck do you think
you're doing?
You know what I said after Wayne.
No more guns in the house.
- Yeah, but he was threatening you.
- Where did you get it?
- Trading Post.
- And what did you pay for it?
- One-eighty.
- What was he asking?
- Two-fifty.
- He was dreaming.
- Yeah.
- Get rid of it.
Sell it.
Pricks!
All right. All right.
I might pass on
a message of my own.
Don't bullshit me, pal.
I know why you want Highview Crescent.
It's because you're
too much of a tight-ass
to fill in the quarry.
It's easier to knock down
people's houses than it
is to fill in a hole.
Well, what do
you say to that?
Get off my property
or I'll call the police.
Fuck the police! You're the asshole
who had my car smashed!
Settle down, mate.
Settle down.
It's just what
he wants us to do.
Let's just keep our cool.
We don't wanna do anything stupid.
- Darryl John Kerrigan?
- You know who I am, Mick.
- Darryl John Kerrigan.
- Yes, officer?
Were you on Lansell Road,
Toorak at approximately
2:30 this morning?
- No.
- Is there anyone who can verify
your whereabouts at that hour?
Yeah, yeah. Everyone in this house.
While we've still got it.
- Daz, I know you did it.
- I told you, mate.
I don't know anything--
- Shut up. I'm not going to book you.
This is just a warning.
I know what's going on.
No one wants to see you get
the rough end of the stick,
but you're gonna have
to watch yourself.
- Otherwise, you'll end up losing more
than this house.
- Mick.
Darryl, I've seen it happen, mate.
Now, settle down.
If you wanna take 'em on,
do it the right way. By the book.
- All right, Mick.
- Oh, and, uh, Daz?
- Yeah?
- Put them gates around the back.
Oh.
Now, listen.
Things are gettin' a bit serious.
Last night I had a visit
from some hired thug.
- Yeah, me too.
-What do you mean, you too?
A man, he come to my house and he say,
"Stop with the court business."
If no stop, he have friend
who come and beat me.
And I say,
"You have friend, I have friend.
My friend come to your house,
put bomb under your car
and blow you to fucking sky."
- What'd he do?
- He get scared and he leave.
- I bet he did.
- I-I don't really
have friend like this,
but, you know, I'm Arab and people think
all Arab have bomb.
You're a bloody ripper, Farouk.
That's fuckin' fantastic.
- Excuse the French, Evonne.
- Get your hand off it, Darryl.
Anyway, um,
I was worried for everyone.
I just didn't want to force
anyone into this. Farouk?
No, I'm with you,
Mr. Darryl.
- Evonne?
- What are they gonna do
my ex hasn't done?
- Jack?
- Yeah, fuck 'em.
Well, Dennis Denuto
is acting on our behalf.
We've gotta be
in federal court next Tuesday.
Does he think
we've got a good case?
Well, he reckons it just has
to contravene the Constitution.
And the Constitution
is the biggest law we've got.
How much?
Ah, good point, Evonne. Steve?
Now, all up,
it's gonna cost 1,500.
Now, that's 750 now,
750 in six months' time.
So 150 each.
And, Jack, I know you can't do it,
so I'm kickin' in for you.
Oh, good on you, Darryl.
I'll pay you back.
- Evonne?
- Yeah, fine.
- Farouk?
- I pay cash now.
No, no, no, hold your horses.
What is it with wogs and cash?
Anyway, it's
bargain-basement prices,
and, uh, you'd better
wear a suit this time, Farouk.
What's this Dennis Denuto
like, Darryl?
Ah, he's a lawyer.
This is about the law.
He's gotta know
what he's doin'.
Um... all--
all right.
Gi-Give me
one moment...
and I--
and I will.
Um... it's the--
the, um-- the--
the Constitution
of Australia.
This is a blatant violation...
of the Constitution
of the Commonwealth of Australia.
And when it comes
to violations,
they don't come
any bigger.
What section of the Constitution
has been breached?
Section?
Wh-What section?
There is no one section.
It's just the vibe of the thing.
I'm afraid, Mr. Denuto,
you'll have to be more specific.
Oh, yeah,
sure, sure.
I was just starting general,
and then I was getting...
more specific...
with the-- the, um--
Just one moment, please.
The, um--
Jesus, Darryl,
I am sweatin' here.
You're killin' them,
Dennis.
I don't even know
Roman numerals.
Um-- It's-- It's--
Ju--
I've got it here.
It's the... section 51,
uh, second
from the bottom.
"The Parliament shall
have power to make laws...
with respect to copyrights,
patents of inventions...
and designs
and trademarks."
It's all part of it.
This is what I'm getting at.
That's my point.
It's-- It's
the vibe of it.
All right. Taken.
Do you have a precedent
which supports...
this...vibe?
Uh... yes.
Yes, I do.
Um, just one moment.
What's the name
of the famous aboriginal?
- Cathy Freeman.
- No, the court case.
- Evonne Goolagong.
- No, no, no. Ma-- Mabo.
Mabo.
What about it?
That's your classic case
of big business...
trying to take land,
and they couldn't.
Mr. Denuto,
the Mabo decision...
pertains to the specific
issue of native land title
and terra nullius.
Yeah.
So what part of the judgment
is relevant to this case?
A-Again, i-it's just
the vibe of it.
Actually, may I
approach the bench?
Am I wasting
my time here?
Your case
is not strong.
- Am I sort of in the ballpark though?
- I'm a judge.
I understand.
Can you just give me an angle?
I'm sorry, Mr. Denuto.
I can't.
Understood.
I think I've got
a good one anyway.
In summing up,
i-it's the Constitution,
it's Mabo,
it's justice, it's law.
It's the vibe,
and, uh--
No, that's it.
It's the vibe.
I rest my case.
That was sensational.
Counsel for the respondent?
Your Honor, I don't wish to waste
any more of your time.
- Appreciated.
- All our arguments are contained
in the forward documents,
and we'd be more than happy
for that to constitute
the case for the respondent.
Thank you. So be it.
I call a one-hour
adjournment.
Good on ya, Dennis.
That shut 'em up.
I'm going for a bit
of a breather, mate.
How you goin'?
Oh, fine. Fine.
- Got a case comin' up?
- Uh, no, no.
I'm here to see someone.
I'm-I'm a spectator today.
- Are you?
- My son's first appearance.
Oh? Do you reckon
he'll get off?
Oh, no, no.
He's a barrister.
- He's appearing for
the first time as a barrister.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Uh, Darryl Kerrigan.
- Lawrence Hammill.
- G'day, Lawrence.
Barrister, eh?
He'd need a degree for that.
Yes, yes. He-He's got a couple,
actually.
- Ah, you must be as proud as punch.
- Well, you know.
Oh, I know.
I've got a daughter.
Diploma certificate,
fully qualified hairdresser.
The day she came home
and told me she'd got
into Sunshine Tech...
- was the proudest day of my life.
- Yes, yes, I can imagine.
Yeah, sure makes us parents
look like a bunch of dodos, eh?
You wouldn't have dreamt
of doing what your son's done.
No, no. Anyway, Darryl,
what brings you here?
Our bloody government's
trying to take my house.
This new Air Link thing.
I mean, imagine that.
Sal and me, we brought up
our whole family in that house,
and they think they
can just walk in--
Anyway, we're takin' 'em
to court.
Bloody outrageous.
It's gotta be against the Constitution.
Yes, it is outrageous.
Who's acting for you?
- Dennis Denuto.
- Uh, never heard of him.
You wouldn't have.
He just does our local area.
Yeah, but I've never heard of him
in Constitutional law.
Oh, no, you wouldn't.
No, he does conveyancing mainly.
You know, wills, petty theft,
that sort of thing.
But hey, it's all based
on the Constitution.
Yes. Yes, in a way.
- Good bloke though.
- Yes. Sounds like it.
Anyway, uh,
I'd better be going.
- Sure.
- Nice talking to you, Lawrie.
- Nice talking to you, Darryl.
- And good luck with your boy.
Thanks, Darryl.
I hope everything works out.
Ah, yeah, yeah.
I'm pretty confident.
I find in favor
of the respondent.
Yes!
It's them, Darryl.
But we was respondin'
to them.
We lost, Darryl.
I'm sorry.
Dad reckons he must have
sat there for an hour.
He said it was like being kicked
in the guts with the back end of a bus.
Dad had to explain to Farouk
that they had lost.
It was really hard
telling Evonne too.
But the toughest one
was Jack.
Trace and Con
were great though.
Good on you, Dad. You stood up to them.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm so impressed with your fighting
quality, Mr. Kerrigan.
Thanks, mate.
And can I just say how disenchanted
I am with our legal system.
Dad was very quiet
after losing the court case.
I'd never seen him so down.
He even stopped complimenting Mum
on her cooking.
You all right there,
Darryl?
Yeah.
Dad?
Someone's, uh,
sellin' a telephone box.
They said no
to an extension.
Dennis says we've got
to be out in two weeks.
Two weeks?
I haven't told Wayne yet.
I think Dad felt he'd let
everyone down, but especially Wayne.
That's why he'd been
puttin' off tellin' him.
He just couldn't think of a way
to break it to Wayne.
I told Dad not to worry.
I knew how to tell Wayne we'd lost.
- We lost.
- Lost?
Yeah.
Did Dad do his nut?
Nah, he's gone all quiet.
Quiet?
Yeah. I think he thinks
he's let everyone down.
Letus down?
Yeah, that's what I think.
See, especially you.
I think he was lookin' forward
to the day you came back to the house.
Well, you tell Dad...
the only reason
I loved that house is 'cause
it had him and Mum in it...
and like... everyone else.
Wherever they go,
I'll love...
as long as it
has them in it.
And all those lawyers
and government people
can just go and get fucked.
"...as long as it
has them in it.
And all those lawyers
and government people
can go and get fucked."
Ah, he wanted me to change
that " get fucked" bit, but I forgot.
On you, mate.
I'd better keep packin'.
Dad?
Steven.
I can, uh, get you
some more boxes, if you want.
No, I think I'll be all right,
Steve.
Dad?
You haven't let anyone down.
I don't know what the opposite of...
lettin' someone down is,
but you done
the opposite.
When are you
gonna sign 'em?
- I don't know.
- They gotta be done by Friday.
I can't.
lcan't.
I just can't.
Darryl, we gotta go.
Yeah, I know.
I know we lost.
I know we gotta get out
of this place.
I know this is no longer
our house, but I'll be buggered
if I can sign those papers.
I just cannot physically
pick up the pen and sign them.
Did you speak
to Jack?
Yeah, yeah. His son-in-law's moved
to Perth, so he's no help.
Poor Jack.
Listen, I-I told him
he could stay with us
until we work somethin' out.
How'd you go
with the agent?
Two-bedroom units
are $80,000.
A flat.
With four people,
the greyhounds,
five cars,
the boat and Jack.
It'll be okay.
- And what are we gonna do with Wayne?
- Wayne'll understand.
You know he keeps a photo
of this place on his wall.
I know.
He gets out after five years,
we have to put him in a laundry
smaller than his cell.
- Maybe we rent.
- Rent?
We not only lose our place,
we're payin' for someone else's.
- Oh, Darryl--
- I'm starting to understand
how the aborigines feel.
Have you been drinkin'?
Well, this house
is like their land.
It-It holds
their memories.
The land is their story.
It's everything.
You just can't pick it up
and plonk it down somewhere else.
This country's gotta stop
stealin' other people's land.
Dad? There's someone
here to see you.
G'day, Darryl.
Lawrie.
So I thought
I'd come and visit.
- But how'd you find us?
- You know us dodos.
- We've got a few tricks up our sleeves.
- Don't I know it.
I, uh, heard
about the decision.
Yeah. Yeah, well,
that's the way these things are.
- How'd your boy go?
- Oh, fine. Yeah, fine.
- Great.
- Darryl, I wonder if I
could put something to you.
Yeah, sure.
I don't think I
introduced myself fully.
You see, I'm retired now,
but I'm actually a lawyer myself.
Three degrees in the family.
I'd like to see your poolroom.
I'm, uh,
what's called a Q.C.
- Are you? A Q.C.? You're one of those?
- What's that?
- Uh, Queens Counsel.
- Oh, you counsel the queen?
Uh, they're the lawyers
rich people use, love.
Yeah, well, that's probably
the most accurate way of describing us.
I don't think Dennis
would be a Q.C.
N-No, no, I don't think.
Anyway, my specialty
as a Q.C...
was Constitutional law,
Australian Constitutional law.
Have you heard of
the Tasmanian Dams case?
- Um--
- Mabo?
Oh, the aboriginal guy,
told the government to shove it.
That's the one.
Uh, anyway, I've had quite
a bit to do with these over the years,
and I've had a look into your case
over the last few days,
and I think there's
a bit more to it.
- What do you mean?
- I think you've got a case.
- So Dennis was on the right track.
- Y-Yes.
I told you that judge
had it in for him.
I believe there's a section
of the Constitution...
about the government's right to acquire
land that hasn't been tested.
But Dennis tested it.
Well, I-I think we
could test it better.
Anyway, I would like
to appear on your behalf... gratis.
- No fee.
- Well, no, we couldn't.
I've done pretty well
out of this law caper over the years,
- so if you're happy for me
to take it further--
-Further?
But we've been
to the federal court.
How much further
can we take it?
Three weeks later...
Dad went to the High Court
of Australia, which is the
highest court in Australia.
Lawrie asked Dennis to be
his instructing solicitor.
Dennis was stoked,
but shittin' himself at the same time.
I'm shittin' myself.
- Shall we?
- Let's stick it up 'em.
And so Dad, or as he
was called by the judge--
Darryl John Kerrigan--
sat in the High Court
of Australia and put his case.
Or at least
Mr. Hammill did.
Dennis was very helpful too.
He was passing books around
like a librarian.
He even learnt Roman numerals
especially for the trip.
Um, paragraph, uh... 31.
- Thank you, Dennis.
- But Dad reckoned there
was no doubt about it.
From the moment he stood up,
Mr. Hammill was the star of the show.
Section 51,
paragraph 31.
"The parliament shall
have power to make laws...
with respect to the acquisition
of property on just terms."
Let's think about those words,
"on just terms" ...
and how they relate
to real people.
Your Honor, my client
built his home by the law,
in full accordance
with the law.
He doesn't know
about the extensions.
But does he have
the protection of the law?
How can the forcible removal
of a family, a good family,
from their home...
have the blessing
of our Constitution?
How can that be...
"just terms" ?
Dad reckoned it
was in the bag,
even though they had five times
more lawyers than we did.
My client has adhered
to the law, every law,
every statute from the Town Planning Act
to Civil Aviation Regulations.
But in what can only be described
as a last desperate measure,
my client is accused
of breaching none other
than the Constitution.
I mean, good Lord,
what else are we guilty of?
lnternational war crimes, hmm?
He's even paid people
to laugh for him.
I refer the court to His Honor
Mr. Justice Dixon's decision...
in Grace Brothers
and the Commonwealth.
As much as Dad hated to admit
it the other lawyer was good,
and he was gonna give us
a real run for our money.
A safeguard
to the commonwealth.
But if Mr. Hammill was worried,
he didn't show it. He kept right on at 'em.
...has acquired the status
of a constitutional guarantee,
which is designed
to protect the individual--
But everything he said,
they had an answer for.
- Your Honor, that statement
was obiter dictum.
- Was not!
Well, it wasn't.
- Was it?
- I don't know.
The interpretation of
"on just terms" was considered
in the Tasmanian Dams case.
The court took into account
the interests of the community,
such as, uh,
job creation--
Dad reckoned Dennis got
the hang of things real quick.
The main job of the senior counsel
was to provide backup for the Q.C.
Ah, yes. And this is further underlined
in Georgiades--
- And that's what Dennis did.
- Ah, utilitarianism.
The greatest good
for the greatest number.
But what this principle
fails to--
What this principle fails to take
into account...
is that competing rights cannot
be weighed one against the other.
Is a family's right to live freely
in their home outweighed--
It wasn't just
legal argument.
Mr. Hammill even put jokes in,
clever jokes.
...not that our children
will have a place to live,
but whether they'll have prompt delivery
of their parcels.
Dad thought
it was real funny,
even though he
didn't get it.
Suffer in your jocks.
In fact, there were
a lot of times he didn't quite
understand what was being said,
but one time he knew exactly
what was being said.
He's even approached
the appellant with an offer
of compensation,
a generous offer considering
the nature of the, uh, dwelling,
or as it might more accurately
be called, eyesore.
- What are you calling an eyesore?
- Darryl.
It's called a home,
you dickhead!
- Your Honor.
- Darryl!
It's a bloody fine one. If there
were more homes like that, we'd--
Have the jails full
of people like your son?
- Ah, this bloody asshole!
- Sit down, Darryl.
Mr. Hammill, I'm calling
an adjournment.
And I trust that your client
will, in the meantime, compose himself.
Mr. Lyle, I'll thank you
not to make any further value
judgments in this court.
I'm sorry, Lawrie.
That's all right, Darryl.
I was thinking
the same thing,
though not
in those words.
I wish I had your words.
How dare they?
I mean, an eyesore!
I mean, that--
that just goes to show
that they don't get it.
I mean, they're judging the place
by what it looks like,
and if it doesn't have
a pool or a classy front
or a big garden--
It's got a pretty good gate.
And then because of that,
it's not worth saving.
But it's not a house.
It's a home.
It's got everything.
People who love each other,
care for each other.
It's got memories.
Great memories.
It's a place
for the family to turn to,
come back to.
But that doesn't seem to mean as much
as a big fuckin' driveway.
Later it was time
for Mr. Hammill to sum up.
Dad said
he was unbelievable.
He reckoned he finished
like a champion greyhound.
People who love each other--
He quoted cases, he quoted laws.
But Dad nearly fell off
his chair when Mr. Hammill
finished by quoting Dad,
only better.
And somehow that's not worth
as much as a big driveway.
You may think our appeal
is based on emotion rather than law.
Not true.
It's about the highest law in
this country, the Constitution,
and one phrase within it:
"on just terms."
That's what this
is all about-- being just.
They want to pay only
for the house.
But they're taking away
more than that, so much more.
Sure, the Kerrigans
built a house,
then they built a home,
and then a family.
You can acquire a house,
but you can't
acquire a home,
because a home is not built
of bricks and mortar...
but love and memories.
You can't pay for it,
and you're just shortchanging
people if you try.
I can't speak for those
who wrote this document,
but I'll bet when they put in
the phrase " on just terms,"
they hoped
it would stop anyone...
shortchanging someone
like Darryl Kerrigan.
Thanks, Lawrence.
Thank you.
In the end, who knows whether
it was Dad's words or Mr. Hammill
or even Dennis' note passing--
...but we won the case.
...in favor
of the appellant.
Shit.
That's us.
Bullshit.
We won?
- We won.
- You little ripper!
Thanks, lads.
We won.
Dad was stoked
but suitably restrained.
He reckons the other side
didn't know what to do with themselves.
Dennis was so stunned,
he went all quiet.
Dad reckons he almost cried.
In fact, I think he did.
Mr. Hammill
just sat there for ages.
He reckoned it was the most satisfying
victory he'd had in 47 years.
Dad reckons it's important
to be noble in victory,
so he spoke to the other Q.C. ...
Oh, hey.
...the one who had a go at Wayne.
Bad luck.
You dickhead!
The case was all over
the news that night.
Good evening. First tonight,
a landmark decision in
the High Court today...
has confirmed the age-old saying,
"A man's home is his castle."
When the huge Air Link
consortium tried to compulsorily
acquire a string of homes...
on Melbourne's outskirts
earlier this year,
they didn't expect a fight.
- Well, they got one.
- It was a
case of Darryl versus Goliath...
in the High Court
of Australia today.
Mum reckons it's real funny
how one day you're not famous,
and then the next day
you are... famous,
and then you're not
anymore.
Dad had one of the biggest parties ever
that night back at home.
He invited everyone
from the neighborhood--
his friends,
family, in-laws.
This case has totally regained my faith
in the legal system.
Mr. Hammill even
brought his son along.
Really pleased to meet you.
Everyone was havin'
a real good time,
especially Mum and Dad.
I'd never seen them
so happy.
Dad invited everyone
up to Bonnie Doon.
I fix for you a special Farouk
pressure system.
Mr. Hammill said he'd love
to come. I don't think he'd
ever fished for carp.
Well, that party
went on and on and on.
Dad smiled all night.
See, this is why we need that patio.
The victory was reported
in all the papers.
It became known
as the Kerrigan Decision.
Jack, don't thank me.
This is the bloke.
Although Dad said,
as far as he was concerned,
it was Lawrie's victory.
And don't forget
Dennis here either.
That was the beginning
of a string of good luck
for our family.
Six months later
we got notice that Wayne would
soon be eligible for parole.
Dad rang Mr. Hammill,
who was more than happy
to come out of retirement again.
Wayne said the parole board
couldn't believe their eyes.
When Mr. Hammill walked in,
he reckons they granted him
parole out of shock.
Dennis became very well-known
after the case,
and people came from everywhere
to hire him.
He won a very big case,
a class action against people who put
lead in the landfill 15 years ago.
I think Mr. Hammill
helped him there too.
Dad is very happy for him.
He even bought himself
a new photocopier,
one that never breaks down.
And guess what. Mr. Hammill did go up
to Bonnie Doon.
At first Dad thought it was
out of politeness, but it can't be...
'cause he goes up there
all the time.
He and Dad still hit it off
as good as they did
the first day they met.
Coco never won another race,
but she had a son
which Dad called Son of Coco.
He hasn't won yet,
but Dad has high hopes.
Dad did finish the patio
in a Greek style, and the extension,
and he even put up those big iron gates
that he and Steve...
had gotten for a bargain
that night in Toorak.
Steve got back with Kerry,
his old girlfriend.
Eventually they got married
and had a little boy...
three weeks later.
"Baby carriage,
still in box."
Con and Trace
had a kid too.
He's already taken up kickboxing.
They are great parents.
Wayne started helping Dad
with the tow truck
and really made a go at it.
Dad's even more proud of him now
than when he was in jail.
It was Wayne's idea
to move into tray trucks.
Pretty soon they had two,
then three, then eight.
Who knows when it will stop?
Mum reckons 11.
She's as proud as punch
with all this.
And guess what. She did take up pottery.
She didn't even need lessons.
And Dad, well, he reckoned
he'd got everything
he'd ever wished for.
He often used to sit out on the patio
and just smile to himself.
And they still live
at 3 Highview Crescent,
even though it's only
them two livin' in it.
And Dad still calls it
"his castle."
My name's Dale Kerrigan,
and that was my story.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org