Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Just packed up a real money load,
and it's comin' your way.
Look for "Rodgers"
on the side of the truck.
Don't forget
my share of the deal.
Shit!
- Tuna on white, no crust, right?
- I don't know. How is it?
Every day for the last three weeks
you've been comin' in here...
and you've been askin' me
how the tuna is.
It was crappy yesterday...
it was crappy the day before,
and guess what.
- It hasn't changed.
- I'll have the tuna.
- No crust?
- No crust.
Thank you.
Talk to me, Jesse.
This ain't workin', brother.
It's your fuel map.
It's got a nasty hole.
- It's why you're unloading in third.
- I told you it was third.
I lengthen the injector pulse
another millisec...
and just tune the NOS timer,
you'll run nines.
What's up with this fool?
What is he, sandwich crazy?
No, V. He ain't here
for the food.
Chill out, bro.
He's just slingin' parts for Harry.
- I know what he's slingin'.
- He's tryin' to get in Mia's pants.
- What's up, guys?
- How you doin', Mia?
How you livin', girl?
Hey, Dom.
You want somethin' to drink?
Ah, he's beautiful.
I like his haircut.
Vince.
Vince!
- What?
- Can I get you anything?
You look good.
Thanks a lot, Mia.
See you tomorrow.
Sure.
- Tomorrow?
- Oh, I love this part.
Try Fatburger from now on.
You can get yourself a double-cheese
with fries for 2.95, faggot.
- I like the tuna here.
- Bullshit. No one likes the tuna.
Well, I do.
Jesus Christ, Dom!
Would you get out there?
I'm sick of this shit!
I'm not kidding, Dom!
Get out there!
- What'd you put in that sandwich?
- That's really funny.
All right.
- He was in my face.
- I'm in your face.
Relax! Don't push it!
You embarrass me!
Get over there!
Jesse, give me the wallet.
"Brian Earl Spilner."
Sounds like a serial killer name.
- Is that what you are?
- No, man.
Don't come around here again.
Hey, man,
you know this is bullshit.
- You work for Harry, right?
- Yeah, I just started.
You were just fired.
Hey, Dominic, I appreciate
what you did in a big way.
Dominic, I owe you.
Brian, you're messin'
with my business.
When Dominic drives,
he's golden.
Kids pour in here, want everything
he has, every performance part...
and they pay cash!
- What did Dominic say?
- You don't wanna know.
- He wants you outta here.
- He wants me outta here?
- Yes!
- And what did you say to Dom?
- What do you think I said?
I told him,
"Good help is hard to find."
Relax.
I need NOS.
- I need NOS.
- No.
My car topped out at
140 miles per hour this morning.
Amateurs don't use
nitrous oxide.
I've seen the way you drive.
You got a heavy foot.
- You'll blow yourself to pieces.
- I need one of these.
One of the big ones.
Actually, no.
Let's make it two.
And, Harry,
I need it by tonight.
Hey, hold up, hold up.
Look at this snowman right here, man.
Sweet ride.
What you runnin' under there, man?
- Making me find out the hard way?
- Hell, yeah.
You brave. You brave.
They call me Hector.
I got a last name too,
but I can't pronounce it, so...
Brian Spilner.
Typical white boy name.
Know what I'm sayin'?
See that over there?
That's mine. It's my baby. But
I ain't cuttin' her loose tonight.
- Why not?
- 'Cause I'm goin' legit.
Tryin' to get on the NI RA circuit.
You heard about that?
Hell, yeah.
- So what's up with you, man?
- I'm just waitin' for Toretto.
Shit. Better get in line.
- This yours?
- Yeah. I'm standin' next to it.
That's funny. You know,
Edwin happens to know a few things.
And one of the things
Edwin knows is...
it's not how you
stand by your car.
It's how you race your car.
You better learn that.
Oh, shit.
Here they come. It's on.
- Dom, how you doin'?
- Hey, Camille.
You been doin' yoga?
You did?
Of course you did. Monica.
I smell skanks.
Why don't you pack it up before
I leave tread marks on your face?
- Letty, I was just talkin'.
- Whatever.
Okay, Hector.
Yeah? What's up, man?
- What's up?
- Edwin.
- How we doin' this tonight?
- One race.
Two-G buy-in.
Winner takes all.
- Hector, you're gonna hold the cash.
- Why Hector?
He's too slow
to make away with the money.
- Good luck, guys.
- Wait. Hold up.
I don't have any cash, but I do
have the pink slip to my car.
You just can't climb in the ring
with Ali 'cause you think you box.
He knows I can box.
So check it out.
It's like this.
I lose, the winner takes my car,
clean and clear.
But if I win, I take the cash,
and I take the respect.
Respect.
To some people,
that's more important.
That your car?
I see a cool-air intake.
It's got a NOS-fogger system
and a T-four turbo, Dominic.
I see an AIC controller.
It has direct port
nitrous injection.
Yeah, and a stand-alone
fuel management system.
Not a bad way to spend $10,000.
You see that shit?
He's got enough NOS in there
to blow himself up, period.
What do you say?
Am I worthy?
We don't know yet.
But you're in.
Let's go.
What the hell's
goin' on around here?
Street's closed, pizza boy.
Find another way home.
Goddamn street racers.
Log on 22, code three.
Tension is high.
They've blocked the street.
Edwin...
this is yours,
whether you win or lose.
But if you win,
you get her too.
You're gonna win.
I'm gonna win.
We had a reported homicide, 187,
at Barakian Liquor.
I've got a 187 in Glendale.
Cops are all over it.
We're good to roll.
I repeat, good to roll.
- Let's race!
- Right.
Go!
Hell, yeah!
Damn, that guy's fast.
Let's go!
"Menage a"!
No! Monica!
Shut up!
Let's go now, baby!
- Here's what you want, right here.
- There you go.
You were racin'
a bunch of skateboards.
My sister holds the money.
Count it.
And you're my trophy.
Hey, Monica!
What's up, baby?
What's your problem, nigga?
You didn't win.
Fuck you, then!
- Was that fun?
- Got a problem there, huh, buddy?
- What are you smilin' about?
- Dude, I almost had you.
You almost had me?
You never had me.
You never had your car.
Granny shifting,
not double-clutchin' like you should.
You're lucky that hundred-shot of NOS
didn't blow the welds on the intake.
Almost had me?
Now me and the mad scientist
gotta rip apart the block...
and replace
the piston rings you fried.
Ask any racer, any real racer.
It don't matter if you win
by an inch or a mile.
Winning's winning.
Available units, we have reported
street racing along Hawthorne...
Oh, shit! We got cops!
Go!
Dom, get in the car! Go!
Toretto, stop right there!
Get in!
You're the last person in the world
I expected to show up.
I thought if I got in your good graces,
you might let me keep my car.
You are in my good graces,
but you ain't keepin' your car.
You drive like you've done this before.
What are you, a wheel man?
You boost cars?
- No. Never.
- Ever done time?
Couple of overnighters.
No big deal.
What about the two years
in juvie for boostin' cars?
Tucson, right?
Yeah, I had Jesse run a profile
on you, Brian Earl Spilner.
He'll find anything on the Web,
anything about anybody.
So why bullshit?
So what about you?
Two years in Lompoc.
I'll die before I go back.
- Oh, great.
- What?
It's gonna be a long-ass night,
that's what.
Follow us.
I thought we had an agreement.
You stay away, I stay away.
Everybody stays happy.
We got lost, Johnny.
What do you want me to tell you?
- Who's "we"?
- My new mechanic.
Brian, meet Johnny Tran.
The guy in the snakeskin pants,
that's his cousin, Lance.
So when are you gonna give me
a shot at that Honda 2000 of yours?
- This your ride?
- It was. It's his now.
No, it's not.
I haven't taken delivery.
Then it's nobody's car.
Somebody put in the wrench time.
- What do you think, Lance?
- It's an amazing machine.
Yes, indeed.
Let's go.
I'll see you
in the desert next month.
Be ready to have
your ass handed to you.
You're gonna need more
than that crotch rocket.
I got somethin' for you.
What the hell was that about?
Long story. I'll tell you later.
Let's get outta here.
NOS!
So, what the hell
was that all about?
It's a long story.
We got a 20-mile hike.
Humor me.
A business deal that went sour.
Plus, I made the mistake
of sleepin' with his sister.
Yo, Spilner.
You want a beer?
Oh, shit.
We were all there, right?
Falling behind.
- With all that nitrous.
- Yeah.
Yo, Dom. We were just about
to go lookin' for you, brother.
- Where were you?
- There were mass cops there.
They came in from every direction.
Their shit was orchestrated.
- This your beer?
- Yeah, that's my beer.
Yo, Einstein.
Take it upstairs.
You can't detail a car
with the cover on.
Can't even get that right.
You all right?
Am I all right?
It was just a question.
Yo, Dom! Why'd you bring
the buster here?
'Cause the buster
kept me out of handcuffs!
He didn't just
run back to the fort!
The buster brought me back.
You can have any brew you want...
as long as it's a Corona.
- Thanks, man.
- That's Vince's, so enjoy it.
You...
Hey, bro, you got a bathroom?
Yeah, upstairs.
First door on the right.
He's got no call
bein' up in here.
- You don't know that fool for shit!
- He's right, Dom.
Vince, there was a time
when I didn't know you.
That was in the third grade!
Yeah, so, what girls are here?
- You name it. You want mine?
- You need to shut the f...
- You don't have anything?
- You look a bit tired.
I think you should go upstairs
and give me a massage.
Look at all our guests.
How about we go upstairs
and you give me a massage?
Crazy lady.
You know you owe me
a ten-second car, right?
Ouch.
Oh, shit.
Did you wipe the seat?
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Would you cut the shit already?
Come on!
Come on.
Let's go get me a drink.
Come on, man.
We were just about to get along.
- So, what do you want?
- Anything, long as it's cold.
My brother likes you.
He usually doesn't like anybody.
Yeah, he's a complicated guy.
Yeah? What about you?
- I'm simpler.
- You're a shitty liar.
Well, I'll take that
as a compliment.
- But there's a problem.
- What's that?
You need to get some sleep.
And you definitely,
definitely need a shower.
Come on. I'll take you home.
Show me your hands.
Very good. Now open the door.
Put your hands on your head.
Behind your head.
Face the front of the vehicle,
walk backwards towards the rear.
Take two steps to your right.
Stop right there.
What'd I do?
Shut up.
He's clean, Sarge.
Damn! Muse, will you
take these things off?
- Shit. You put 'em on so tight.
- I like realism.
- You like realism.
- You never know who's watching.
Nice crib, Sergeant. It's a lot nicer
than that last place you confiscated.
Ain't it? Eddie Fisher built this house
for Elizabeth Taylor in the '50s.
See? Even the cops
are Hollywood in Hollywood.
Here he is, fresh from
Toretto's hot rod heaven.
That was an $80,000
vehicle, officer.
- Wait. You tell him what happened?
- He knows what happened.
- Send the bill to Johnny Tran.
- The kid's givin' me attitude?
That doesn't speak very well
for police-FBI relations, Tanner.
- I walk in, the guy's already givin'...
- All right, all right.
We'll talk, okay?
Let's talk about it.
Muse, why don't you make us
four iced cappuccinos, please.
- Come on.
- Regular or decaf, Sarge?
Decaf, I think.
Four hijackings in two months,
and we don't have anything.
DVD players and digital cameras alone
are worth a million-two...
which brings the grand total
to six million plus.
We're in the political
crosshairs now, Brian.
That's why you're undercover.
You want that detective badge fast, kid.
And you wanna know something?
The FBI can help,
if you come through for us.
- What does the truck driver say?
- He gave us the same M.O.
Three Honda Civics,
precision driving...
the same green neon glow
from under the chassis.
Lab says the skid marks
came back the same:
Mashamoto ZX tires.
So we know that it's somebody
in the street racing world.
We don't make this case soon...
the truckers will take matters
into their own hands.
I tell 'em we're close.
You gonna make me a liar?
Look, what do we know?
We all know this world revolves
around Toretto, right?
I'm not sayin' that he's necessarily
the one that's poppin' these trucks...
but I can guarantee the both of you
that he knows who is.
- It's just a matter of time until...
- You want time?
Buy the magazine.
We don't have time.
Just get me something I can use.
Is Harry cooperating?
Yeah, like a guy who's gonna do time for
receiving stolen property if he doesn't.
What kind of vibe
is he getting from Toretto?
He's scared of him, but he doesn't think
he's jackin' trucks in his spare time.
- He's too controlled for that.
- Wait.
Not that I want to contradict
Harry's fine judge of character...
but Toretto did hard time
for nearly beating a guy to death.
He's got nitrous oxide in his blood
and a gas tank for a brain.
Do not turn your back on him.
Hey, Tanner.
I'm gonna need another car.
What about parts and service?
- Hold off on that.
- What should I do with this?
All right,
what the hell is this?
What do you got there?
- This is your car.
- My car?
I said a ten-second car,
not a ten-minute car.
You could push this across
the finish line, or tow it.
Couldn't even tow that
across the finish line.
No faith.
I have faith in you,
but this isn't a junkyard.
- This is a garage.
- Pop the hood.
- Pop the hood?
TwoJZ engine.
- No shit.
- And what did I tell you?
- I retract my previous statement.
- You know what?
This will decimate all
after you put about 15 grand in it...
or more, if we have to
overnight parts from Japan.
We'll put it
on my tab at Harry's.
Yes!
I gotta get you racing again
so I can make some money off your ass.
There's a show in the desert called Race
Wars, and that's where you'll do it.
Tell you what. When you're not workin'
at Harry's, you're workin' here.
If you can't find the right tool
in this garage, Mr. Arizona...
you don't belong near a car.
You don't belong near a car.
He owns you now.
Tell me what you think about this.
Koni adjustables.
Gonna save us about two pounds.
And they're gonna give us better
traction for the hole shot.
All right?
This is your basic
layout of the car...
and that's pretty much what
it could look like when it's finished.
Red, green.
Man, you should be goin'
to MIT or somethin'.
Yeah, right.
No, I got that...
Oh, what's it called?
- That attention disorder...
- ADD?
Yes, that shit. Yeah.
You know, I was good
in algebra and, like, math...
and shit.
Everything else I failed.
Dropped out of school.
I don't know.
It's just somethin' about engines...
that calms me down, you know?
- I'm outta here.
- Come on, dog.
Vince, get over here
and give us a hand.
Looks like you got
all the help you need, brother.
- Mia!
- All right already.
- The chicken's dry.
- I'm comin' out already.
Hey, hold up.
Because you were the first
out of everybody here...
to reach in to get the chicken,
you say grace.
Dear heavenly, uh...
Spirit.
Spirit. Thank you.
Uh, thank you for providing us
with a direct port...
nitrous, uh, injection...
four core intercoolers
and ball-bearing turbos...
and, um, titanium valve springs.
- Thank you.
- Amen.
- Not bad.
He was prayin'
to the car gods, man.
- These are the best.
- What do you want?
- Practice.
- Thank you, girl.
Look who it is.
Old Coyotes 'R' Us.
I thought you weren't hungry,
pumpkin.
- You know, I gotta eat.
- He's always hungry.
All right, sit down.
How you doin', Mia?
- Jesse, hand me that chicken.
- Let's eat some grub.
- Want some of that chicken?
- Did you rent a movie or somethin'?
Need a hand?
No, I'm good. You can go join
the boys watchin' the movie.
Well, the cook doesn't clean
where I come from.
I'd like to go there.
I think we should
go out sometime.
No, I don't date
my brother's friends.
That sucks.
- I guess I'll have to kick his ass then.
- I'd love to see that one.
No, I would... I would pay
to see that one, actually.
Wash my car when you get done.
- What was that?
- No, Mia.
I'm talkin' to the punk.
And wear your favorite dress,
'cause when you're done...
I'm puttin' you on the street
where you belong, cutie.
Is this thing broken?
What's wrong with this thing?
V, what was that Cuban restaurant
you wanted to take me to?
The one with
the peccadillo and the...
- Red candles and the wooden table?
- Yeah, the plantain too.
- What was it called?
- Cha Cha Cha.
Yeah, that's it.
Well, you can take me there.
Friday night at 10:00.
Is that good for you?
- Yeah, it's perfect.
- Good.
- There's no popcorn?
- Make your own goddamn popcorn!
All right.
Now that's valet parking.
- Harry.
- What's up, dog?
Excellent, brother.
Come on in, man.
- Check it. It's yours.
- What do we got here?
- Hired some new help, huh?
- Don't even think about it.
- What's up, Hector?
- How you feelin'?
Pretty good.
What do you need?
I need you to hook me up.
Three of everything. I made a list.
Why don't you look that over.
- When do you need this stuff by?
- Tomorrow. Today.
- Now.
- Right.
White boys work fast,
don't they? Beto.
That's right.
You said you need
three of all this?
Yeah, three of everything.
What do you think about that?
Check this out.
He moans like a cop.
Brian, this is
one of those times...
when you need to be very clear
about what you say.
Nod if you understand me.
Nod!
Sit up.
Tell me what the hell
you're doin' down here.
Oh, shit.
What I'm doin'.
I owe... I owe you
a ten-second car.
And what this is about,
this is about Race Wars.
I just went in there,
and Hector is gonna be runnin'...
three Honda Civics
with Spoon engines.
And on top of that,
he just came into Harry's...
and he ordered
three T-66 turbos...
with NOS,
and a MoTeC system exhaust.
So, what are you saying?
You're gonna go around
and check everybody's shit out...
one garage after another?
Yeah.
Because Dom, you know...
I can't lose again.
He's a cop.
He's a cop!
You a cop?
Let's go for a little ride.
Walk!
All right, kid, stand watch.
There's no engines.
What are they plannin' on racin' with?
Hopes and dreams?
I don't know, but I know
they're sneaky as shit...
and they've got enough money
to buy anything.
What?
Dom, we got a wolf pack.
It's Johnny Tran, and he's
comin' your way really fast!
All right, we got company.
Spilner!
Come on. Move!
Let me ask you a question, Ted.
Do you see anything wrong here?
- We got no engines, do we?
- No!
- Do we?
Nissan SR-Twenty motors will pull a
premium one week before Race Wars, huh?
Yeah, probably.
You're a smart fence, Ted.
Maybe too smart.
What are you feelin', Lance?
Forty weight?
Fifty weight?
A forty weight sounds nice.
Where are they, Ted?
Where are they?
- Enough!
- Where are they?
They're in a warehouse.
They're in a warehouse, man!
Kiss my shoes?
Let's go get our engines.
My superiors are flying in
from D.C. Day after tomorrow.
I want somethin' to show.
Now, we have a top-echelon fence...
with a lube hose in his mouth,
automatic weapons...
a jacket full of priors
on every one of these Asian punks...
a garage full of DVD players
and generally psychotic behavior.
Why not move on Tran now, see where
we are when the dust settles?
Because all we have is behavior.
Let me get some hard evidence...
because what we have now
is circumstantial...
What we have is probable cause
and truckers arming themselves...
for some
good old vigilante mayhem.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org