Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Hey, this is Andrew Gurland,
one of the writer and directors.
Huck Botko, the other writer and director.
Zack Pearlman, I play Zack.
Matt Bennett, I play Matt.
I'm Zack Pearlman's dad, Dr. Pearlman.
God, Zack, what is this?
I've never seen this movie.
I can't wait for you to see it.
That's Will Ferrell's voice, right?
Or is that Gary Sanchez?
You're asking me?
- Your dad.
- I shouldn't ask my dad.
One thing that I know,
it's gonna be a little bit tough,
but it would be awesome
if none of us laughed at our own jokes.
Just other people's jokes.
Only laughing at other people's jokes.
All right, Zack?
Lmpossible!
This is the beautiful
Jacob Davich speaking...
This is actually funny. They used Hannah
because Hannah is my little sister's name,
and they were just trying to piss me off.
- Oh, God!
- I remember that.
Poor, sweet, innocent Hannah.
Sweet, innocent Hannah!
How could you, Zack?
Wait, what was the title of the bong?
The Devil Hookah Bong Number Two.
Devil Bitch Number Two.
You know, people have asked us
if the ritual of the virginity bong
is rooted in any of our lives,
and, no, it's something that was
just made up for the script.
It's Hollywood, people. Everything's not real.
There's a spiritual bond
between the four of us.
Jacob is very spiritual.
My daughter wanted to know
why Jacob looked all greasy in that.
And we're trying to make it look
like it was a long time ago,
so we made everybody change their look.
And you bruised your eye, right?
Yeah, I used makeup to make my eye
look like I got punched in the eye.
Trying to make it look like
you guys were friends
for a lot longer than you really were.
And this is the house
that you guys lived in, for real.
Right.
- They put us up in this huge mansion for...
- And that's our maid.
No, but, for real. You guys,
in addition to being in the movie together,
you were forced to live together.
- Yeah.
- It's true.
- And what was that like?
- Amazing.
I think a lot of the friendship that happens
in the movie is true to how good friends
we became while we were filming.
When people are mad at each other
in the movie, it's usually
in real life we were mad at each other.
So the feeling is real in this movie.
Did you guys fight a lot?
- Yes. Me and...
- You and Justin fought a lot.
- Me and Justin...
- Jacob stayed up in his loft.
Jacob had this bachelor's pad.
I remember getting a lot of calls
at night from you, Zack,
about being pissed off at somebody,
and you wanted me to get involved
in some kind of argument or something.
It was mostly like...
Someone wasn't wearing a condom
when they should have been.
Because we had a lot of gay sex.
Oh, God! Zack!
The one thing I know
about them living in that house
is that I didn't get
my security deposit back.
I'm a guarantor on the lease,
and I'm heavily in debt.
They're remodeling the...
- This woman's the creepiest.
- This lady is real.
Everybody in these scenes are real.
This lady was so creepy.
The best one was that old lady who was like,
"Are you gonna go buy some diapers?"
- Yeah.
- We were like, "What?"
And she was like, "Well, you're having sex,
you might as well go look at baby stuff."
- Yeah, but that's not...
- Yeah, that makes perfect sense.
- That's on SUPERZACK1000.
- Yeah.
And, now, who is this girl over here?
- That's Nicole Weaver.
- Yeah.
The young, beautiful Nicole Weaver.
Nicole still is working in a Friday's
in Flemington, New Jersey.
- At this point in time.
Which is the Friday... It's September 23?
- Something like that.
- Yeah.
What do you mean?
- As of today, September 23...
- The date.
I'm just gonna predict now, since the movie
hasn't really officially released yet,
I'm gonna predict $100 million,
opening week?
I'm gonna predict...
I feel like we're gonna beat Avatar.
I feel like people
are gonna start calling this movie Avatar 2.
- Avatar 2.
- I feel like, guys, it's important...
Do not measure the movie's success
in box office performance,
but rather in pregnancies
that resulted from people seeing the movie.
They've been playing the trailer
during Teen Mom on MTV.
- Oh, no.
- Makes me so happy to hear this.
Oh, my sweet Lord!
And what did you say was so weird
about this woman? She told a story or...
- What was she talking about?
- She talked about her first time.
She was like,
- "Well, you know, I was 13."
- Wasn't it with an amputee or something?
Yeah, so weird.
She was like, "He was missing his leg,
'cause he was in the war."
That was it. Yeah, he was in the war
and he was missing his leg.
"Good thing he wasn't missing his penis,"
she said.
And now, these scenes...
- This is real.
- That was real.
That was Krysta. Krysta really got scared.
- That was Davich's idea, I remember.
- That's CGI.
That's CGI. That's CGI.
- That's real.
- That's green screen.
That's CGI. That's CGI.
The SUPERZACK flying in,
we filmed that over 14 days.
So, this, Zack, you shot off-hours.
Yeah, I was trying to get into character
the whole time.
So I would actually just grab cameras
and shoot as much as I could.
And I bought an HVX,
which is a camera
that we ended up shooting a lot on.
And I would shoot on it as much as I could.
Yeah, and we actually didn't know
this footage existed until late in the edit,
when we were kind of digging through stuff,
and we found it.
- Really?
- 'Cause you didn't tell us about it.
- And we said, "This is perfect."
- This is awesome.
If you guys don't know who Justin Kline is,
he is easily the funniest person
I've ever met.
He's amazing. He does the best characters
and the best songs.
He has a song that I just finally heard.
The whole song.
- Other Places To Put It.
- So good.
- So amazing.
Yeah, well,
Justin is actually an interesting story,
because this is his first movie
that he's ever been in.
Actually, it's almost everybody's
first movie that they've been in.
- Yeah.
- But Justin wasn't even acting before.
I believe he was
a production assistant, Huck?
He was a PA in New Orleans.
And then he ran out of money,
so he went back home to Nebraska,
where his parents run
an assisted living home.
And he was living there
when we gave him a call,
just to meet him on Skype.
And he started playing songs
on his keyboard
and was amazingly hilarious and confident,
and we said, "Come on down
to New Orleans. Come back."
And the other thing
I want to add about Justin
is that there were no lines in the script
really written for Justin or Jacob.
So, so much of what you see them doing
is just them being themselves.
I mean, Matt and Zack, there was very much
a script and a structure for,
but they truly carved out their parts
out of nothing.
Every line you hear from Justin
is just pure Justin.
- He is the best.
- He was always so awesome.
He is awesome.
Jacob has probably the most film experience
of anybody in the movie at 18,
because he starred as
the young Howard Hughes in The Aviator.
- And he will never let you forget it.
- Really?
- That's actually me.
- That's baby Zack.
This is amazing that they found
footage of both of us.
- Playing mini-golf. That's actually me, too.
- That's really cool.
On what looks like the same course.
Which just means our parents are obsessed
- with recording the stupidest stuff.
- I love you, Zack.
I gotta say that's my real mom.
That's Gina Bennett.
- The young girl in front of Matt.
- She's actually not really dead.
- Well, she's not as dead as...
- Dead inside.
At the failure that her son became,
made her dead inside.
You know, I have a lot more footage
of Zack playing miniature golf,
if you want to put it in the movie.
It's cut, Dad. Dad, the movie's cut.
Speaking to that section,
on the way it looks like
those two guys are miniature golfing.
It's really amazing
and that's a testament to Geoff Richman,
who really went through
everybody's home movies
and created this feeling
that these guys grew up together,
which was really crucial
for people dialing into
the characters' relationship with each other.
Andrew, you're really doing
a commentary track?
- Yes, I am. Sorry.
- That's awesome.
- I like the cut of your jib.
- That's real love in Nicole's eyes.
She was really in love with me.
- Well, I do think that Nicole...
- That bird is the passing of this movie.
- What?
- Just how it soars overhead,
unannounced, but everybody loves it
and watches it.
Does anyone remember
what day of shooting...
Guys, I'm on mushrooms.
Does anyone remember
what day of shooting...
- This was before...
- Forty?
...we actually officially started.
- This is the first day that we actually
- got to New Orleans.
- I think this was the 17th?
- This was the first day of shooting...
- This was before principal photography.
- This was before principal?
- Yes. This is negative...
Yeah, I think it was the 17th of May.
- You remember the date?
- Yeah.
But the point is we hadn't
done anything yet.
Because two days later, I turned 21.
Yeah. So, this is Justin actually shooting...
Our DP hadn't got down yet,
so we wanted to get warmed up.
And so we went to Kenner,
and we said,
"Go to the parking lot and do the scene
"where you find out
that Nicole cheated on you."
And then what you don't see is,
right at the end of the scene,
- is when the cops show up.
- Yeah.
'Cause they saw Matt
chasing Zack around the field.
That area was supposedly really, really bad,
and there had actually been
a murder committed with a baseball bat.
And somebody saw me chasing Zack
with a baseball bat.
They called the cops on us.
But, yeah, that was the first day,
and Justin was actually shooting,
and he was acting while he was shooting,
and that was how we achieved
the documentary feel of this movie a lot,
is having characters actually shoot it
and acting behind the camera.
Yeah.
I like it best when Zack's shooting.
- I'm gonna ask my dad to leave.
- What?
Now, this guy was wearing a shirt before.
I asked him to remove it,
because I wanted to give
the ladies something.
The penis shot.
We were getting a lot of crap
about how there wasn't,
from our wives and other women,
there was nothing for the ladies.
- And this wiener shot is also for the ladies.
- What?
There's a wiener shot?
One of my favorite comments
was on Twitter.
One of the guys was like, "Usually,
you pay a stripper to leave, not to stay."
This whole scene just went
right over that guy's head.
- Hey, I got pickle juice all over me now.
- Harry!
- Zack, what's Twitter?
- That's Danie Coleman.
- Danie Coleman and Harry Zittel.
- The great Danie Coleman.
She was so funny.
Harry Zittel, actually,
was the original person...
He's an original man.
- He's an original man.
- Original man.
- Yeah.
- He's my baby boy.
Bouncing baby boy.
I think there is something to say
about Monique dressing this house
to look like an actual frat.
Yeah, this was actually
an apartment building.
And we made it look like a frat house
and Monique really did an incredible job.
This wasn't a kitchen
when we found it, either.
That was just an empty room, so...
I mean, she killed it.
Just nailed it.
Now, this shot over here is something
that Huck and I have been dealing with
over and over again in our short films
and other feature work,
where we just pull out
to have somebody else watching something.
Always trying to figure out
a new way to do it.
There we had it on the actual
Handycam pull-out.
Looks yummy. Cookies?
You used to make cookies all the time...
I remember doing this scene
and I kept eating cookies,
and Andrew was like,
"Don't do it with your mouth full."
And I refused to not eat cookies.
Yes, and also I remember
during the birthday party scene,
Matt's birthday party.
Even though you were off-camera,
you were eating cake the whole time.
I was eating cake the whole time.
Here we go.
There's me actually grabbing a cookie.
Yeah.
Zack has both a sweet tooth
and a savory tooth.
And I also have a tooth...
I tried to knock out my sweet tooth.
Just gets sweeter whenever you hit it.
That's the dumbest joke I've ever made.
Not true.
I tried to get Zack on Jenny Craig.
- Grab the camera. You got it?
- Yeah.
This band playing right now,
Lightning Love,
is from Ypsilanti, Michigan,
which is from my hometown.
Well, right next to my hometown, Ann Arbor.
And funny enough, the dude, Ben Collins,
who's in the band,
is one of my good friends.
And it was complete coincidence
that he ended up in the movie.
He used to come into the house
with a backpack, go up the stairs.
I was like,
"What was in that goddamn backpack?"
I knew it was something bad.
Drugs or pornography.
This sequence of Zack throwing Krysta
in the pool is indicative
of what really inspired Huck and I
to start the project in the first place.
We started watching all these clips
of teenagers throwing girls in pools,
and we were like, "God, I just wanna know
who these kids are and have a whole movie
"that exists in this world."
So this is really the genesis
of this whole big mess that we made.
Girls in pools.
- That was the original title of the movie.
- Yeah.
Our first cut that we showed...
The first notes we got back were,
"There's too much pool stuff."
We had all sorts of pool stuff in the first cut.
The second note was that
there's too much poop stuff.
We shy away from that.
- Have sex with her there.
- Go on the date.
And that's Krysta Rodriguez.
- The beautiful.
- You could see her on Broadway.
Anybody want to finish that?
As Wednesday Addams
in The Addams Family.
She was also in Spring Awakening
and In The Heights.
- And in my bedroom.
- And in my dreams.
- She's a very lovely human being.
- She's the best.
I love Nathan Lane.
Zack, I've never told you that,
but I love Nathan Lane.
I was feeling kind of sick, kind of ill.
And now, this house... That's all I got.
This house had so much porn in it.
It was like loose-leaf paper
just strewn about. It was crazy.
This was a separate house
from what they made us live in.
This was some weird house
on some backward street,
and there was porn everywhere.
I don't know. Porn everywhere.
This is actually right near the house.
- Yeah.
- This is a cool location.
And now, let's talk about Sunny Leone
for a second.
Now, had any of you heard of Sunny Leone
before the movie?
Were you guys aware of her?
No, I thought she was a robot
the whole time.
No, but I'm saying,
I don't know if you guys know anything
about the adult entertainment universe.
I mean, everyone either takes dick
or gives dick.
That's adult entertainment?
Let's clean it up a little, young man.
Sorry. Penis.
Everybody takes penis or gives penis.
- This place rules.
- I've never heard of Sunny Leone.
Never heard of her
or seen any of her movies
or downloaded them.
What is browser history?
Gosh, it's John.
- Was this scripted?
- Yeah, this was scripted.
I forget.
You know, I don't know if it was
in the script.
I think it was stuff that we were just feeding
right before.
- The innkeeper was in the script.
- Yeah, yeah.
The idea, but what he was saying,
that was mostly improv.
- There was a lot of improvisation.
- And he just owned it.
And actually,
he added me on Facebook recently.
And I went to look at his pictures,
stuff that he's done.
There was a picture of a shoot that he did,
he played an ax murderer after this,
and it was pictures of him
with decapitated women.
- It was just really funny.
- I think he gets that a lot.
- I think we allowed him to stretch a little.
- Yeah, and he was great.
My favorite thing that he did,
and it didn't end up in the movie,
is when he said, "I wanna show you guys
a trick that I learned in the Army."
And then he just took off his pants.
That was so awesome!
'Cause that was when everyone was there.
All the girls and everyone sort of screamed.
It was so funny.
Everyone started screaming.
- It was chaos.
- That was the most fun having him.
- He has a bolo tie on, I just realized.
- Yeah.
Because you never knew how things
were gonna come out of his mouth
before he said them,
and so every time it was a surprise.
This laugh, I had no idea
it was gonna come out like this at all.
We knew he was gonna do it,
but his interpretation of it was insane.
I could literally just watch this.
Yeah, and another thing
with the old-timers' joke,
we've screened the movie a bunch of times,
and sometimes people go crazy
and sometimes people are
so uncomfortable and nervous,
and it's like you just never know
how that's gonna play.
Let's count down to my stupid face. Ready?
- Five, four, three, two, one.
- Four, three, two, one.
You're beautiful, Zack. You're as beautiful
as the day you were born,
coming out of your mother's vagina.
Face stretched, smiling at the world.
- I was born with alopecia.
- Now, Matt, a lot of times in this movie,
you have to act uncomfortable or uptight.
Was that a stretch for you
at that point in your life?
No, it was not.
No, I don't know.
It was a pretty awkward shoot. Yeah.
Actually, I'd say
he's the most established actor.
- Yeah, yeah.
- David.
But he's been in every Soderbergh movie.
- Not true.
- A lot of them.
- He's been in a couple.
- He's a terrific, terrific guy.
- Yeah.
And I'm really upset that they cut
the neck brace thing.
- Yeah.
- That was awesome.
If you watch
in one of the next coming shots,
there's gonna be a big TV,
and to the left of it is a neck brace.
There's a whole story he was giving
about how he broke his neck.
Oh, gosh, I forget it.
It was like he was gonna take two years,
but he did it in eight months.
But this is a much better bit.
Whose idea was this?
'Cause this wasn't in the script.
It was David Jensen.
He's really into those green smoothies.
But he understood
how inherently funny they are.
This was so awesome.
He brought the gear and everything.
- He was just like, "I'm bringing my stuff."
- He showed up with the blender,
with the vegetables and just said,
"Hey, I wanna do this."
We're like, "Great!"
And as far as the neck brace,
it was kind of that or the neck brace.
- You can't really just do...
- Two crazies. Here's the neck brace.
There it is, right behind my head.
I feel like David broke character a little bit
when he goes, "Hubba-hubba."
That's funny.
I think it was one of the funniest lines.
- I think it's so good.
- Yeah.
He broke character, but he showed his own.
- It's because he's...
- Neck brace.
- He saw Nicole's feet.
- Yeah.
And that car, that van,
was the worst place in the world.
That van smelled like poop.
Well, it was the hottest place on Earth
'cause there was no AC,
and we were in that van a lot,
hiding Tammy, our sound person,
in crazy places and it was awful in there.
- Awful, awful.
- Tammy!
Tammy was my favorite.
Now, in this scene coming up,
you guys have all these...
There's a lot of extras, a lot of girls
that were re-occurring extras in the movie.
Did you guys develop any friendships
with those young ladies?
- Yeah, a lot of them.
- Yeah, there's Mallory Slack.
- She's really great.
- Mallory Slack, Kathleen Barnes.
- Amanda Punch.
Amanda Punch has come and visited
in California a whole bunch.
She came to Thanksgiving.
She ate all the pearled onions.
I love pearled onions. It's the only thing
I want at Thanksgiving. She ate them all.
Zack.
- Did we just do the same thing?
- We just yawned at the same time.
We're so lame.
Matt and Nicole,
they didn't know we were filming.
They were actually going to dinner.
And then I asked the dumbest question.
Let them pop it.
- Idiot.
- Well, that's part of your charm, Zachary.
Is that I'm an idiot, idiot.
That's what I've always said about you, Zack.
This is one of my favorite parts
'cause this was never...
Jacob Davich just wanted
to jump over everything.
We must have shot this four times where
Jacob is like, "You want me to jump this?"
Yeah. A lot of the stuff,
we were not in the room,
and Zack was just shooting,
and guys were just hanging out for real.
That's her.
- That's Amanda.
- That's who ate all the onions.
Golly!
Checking. We're by the bed.
Can you hear this?
It's Dacia, right? Dacia? Dacia?
Dacia. And there's me
actually laughing at what they're saying.
Kathleen Barnes.
Devil Bitch. Weed.
And, now, did you guys smoke any weed
during the making of the movie?
- No.
- What was that?
That was called Wizard's Brew.
- It was like herbs.
- It was the harshest...
It was like smoking cardboard.
It was my least favorite part of filming,
the Wizard's Brew.
That and being wet.
Yeah. That's my pet peeve.
I hate being wet.
- Matt never takes showers.
- No, no.
I do what's called the whore's bath,
which is I take a wet wipe...
He used my car shammy when he slept over.
Wiped himself down with a ShamWow.
- My dad invented the ShamWow.
- That's goddamn right.
- For 'ginas.
- That's right.
- I remember...
- Who is that guy?
He had the same name
as either Justin or Jacob.
That's all I remember.
Since I didn't film it, I never met the guy.
And I was watching this in the theater.
- Who is that guy?
- Now, a lot of people...
- That's Cheese, man.
- That's Cheese.
That's my illegitimate son.
Zack, I never told you.
He looks so much like you.
You guys want to talk about Cheese?
Like why we invented Cheese?
There's another guy in the mirror, too.
- Who is that?
- I think it was me, Andrew, Huck,
Justin and Amy Hobby.
We all went out to the swamps
and I was loopy,
and I was talking about a movie,
a new cop-buddy movie
- called Hotko and Cheese.
- 'Cause Huck Botko's...
Huck Botko, if you switch it, it's Buck Hotko.
And that sounds like a perfect
'80s cop name.
"Babe, what's up? I'm Hotko."
And then Cheese is like the slack buddy.
Always has French fries
coming out of his pocket.
I have a feeling that's not what Huck meant.
That's not. Yeah.
- There's no way.
- But very good.
But Cheese ended up being the fifth friend.
Right, because whenever you guys
had to do exposition on the phone
or tell part of the story,
and you needed someone to talk to,
- you would always call Cheese.
- Cheese.
And it made it in.
Usually it was Huck or I talking to them,
trying to get them to say
what we wanted them to say.
But they would pretend
like it was one of their friends.
- So I think that's what Huck meant.
- Right.
We had no idea about any of that other
great stuff you guys were talking about.
We had an interesting set,
where usually you're supposed
to turn your cell phones off,
but we wanted all the actors
to have their cell phones on,
so that if we wanted to be in the other room
and kind of give some distance,
we could call into the room
and give directions that way.
So when you see people on the phone,
it's probably us calling in.
If you watch,
I have the oldest cell phone in the world.
- I have a little brick.
- I gave it to him. That was my old cell phone.
It didn't accept text messages,
that's how old it was.
I engraved it,
"To Zack. Love, Dad. Call me, please!"
I loved that phone.
Oh, my God! She's in her underwear.
This is The Columns Hotel.
You may recognize it
if you've been down to New Orleans.
It's very lovely.
I murdered a mistress there.
Don't tell your mother, Zack.
She's gonna find out.
You just said it on a commentary.
Tell your mother not to watch
the commentary.
It's gonna make her more suspicious.
- Nicole bringing it.
- I know.
Nicole crying every single time.
I can't watch girls cry.
- Makes me so sad.
- She's amazing.
Now, you helped her cry a little bit.
Is that right?
I punched her.
No, I know that you helped her
get to that place.
- Can you talk about that a little?
- I told her that she broke my heart,
and I hate her,
and I will never get back with her.
When she first auditioned, she came in
and told me that she was in love with me.
And was totally in character forever.
And I don't know,
I just told her terrible little things
that I wish I could take back.
David Jensen had eight different ones.
Yeah, did you know that was coming, Matt?
- No.
- We did a whole bunch of different ones.
There's also one where he took off
my glasses and stomped on them.
That was awesome.
What else did he do? Did he fake-punch me?
- He punched you a couple times, yeah.
- Yeah.
But the throw was completely by surprise,
right? You had no idea that was coming.
No, I had no idea.
He just started walking me.
I thought he was gonna walk me to his car,
you know?
Were you intimidated by him at all
during that scene?
Absolutely.
He's a method actor, so he's not afraid.
The scene where we break into his house
and he starts hitting me.
- He grabs my head.
- Talk about it then.
- Okay, I'll talk about it then.
I don't have to say it. He actually hit me.
That's basically it.
I would love for someone,
for this to be their first viewing of the movie.
They're like,
"None of the voices are syncing up."
This is Lee, and he is a mechanic
for Continental Airlines.
- Is he?
- But he loves movies
and he wanted to come down.
He and John McLeaish.
That was the same day, right?
Yeah, they came together from Shreveport.
They drove down together. They're buddies.
So, the innkeeper and Lee are good buddies.
I didn't even know that.
I love this.
There's some old guy right next to me.
Seth Barrish writes songs for kids.
- He does?
- Yeah, he does.
- Really?
- He played music.
- They're actually pretty good songs.
- They are really good.
I was surprised. I was like, "Oh, no!"
He was like, "I write songs for kids."
I was like, "Oh, no, Seth, no."
And they were really good.
Seth Barrish, the New York actor.
He was recently in Margot at the Wedding.
- Is that correct?
- That looks like Adam.
- That old guy?
- Yeah, like his dad.
- Like Adam McKay's dad?
- Yeah, that's who I'm guessing it is.
Best birthday present, ever.
I like that Seth says "man" and "dude" a lot.
This was actually one of the more
complicated scenes for us
to get right, editing-wise.
And I remember that it was
originally scripted that the lingerie,
or the Sunny Leone panties,
were in the beginning of the scene,
and then it got dramatic at the end.
And it always was a real momentum problem
for us and we ended up inverting it
and ending with the comedy,
and then it just flowed much better
after that.
Bernard kills in this scene
with his lines, too.
- Bernard, Zack's dad.
- Zack's fake dad.
I'm his real father.
I remember when we were shooting
the first time with Bernard and Ramona,
the parents, we could hear everything
that they were saying
'cause they were miked.
It was in the house,
and we were wandering between rooms.
I remember Bernard saying to Ramona,
"What are they doing?"
'Cause we just started shooting off script.
They said, "Are they gonna tell us
what to do, or are they just gonna
"keep walking around? Are they shooting?"
I was very confused for about an hour,
and then by the time we hit this scene,
this scene was a half hour one-take,
everybody was on their game,
just totally improvising.
And I think after it was done, we all
just stood up and gave them an ovation,
- because it was just like a one-act.
- Matt!
Dude, do you remember that crazy lady
who wanted to take pictures with us?
- No.
- You don't?
- No. After that my hands smelled so weird.
- Can I tell the story?
Why did your hands smell weird?
No, my butt!
We did a whole bunch of these
where tissues were all over the bed.
Yeah, that was a good one.
I don't know the story. I forgot this.
We were filming that scene outside,
that isn't in the movie.
It was the scene outside that was
you talking to your dad
trying to get the photo albums.
- Zack, I don't care.
- Okay.
- That's the beautiful Savannah Welch.
- Oh, my God! I love Savannah.
No one loves Savannah
like Savannah loves Savannah.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know. Doesn't mean anything.
- That's not true.
- That's not true at all.
I mean, I love myself
probably more than anyone else loves me.
- That is true.
- I just wish she would add me on Facebook!
- Zack, don't take this the wrong way...
- That is true.
Zack, don't take this the wrong way,
but I would leave my family for her.
Don't take it the wrong way,
and don't tell your mother.
Or Hannah. Sweet Hannah.
God, sweet Hannah.
Why is it focused on her lips?
Because her eyes got poked out.
She's beautiful and she was really great,
every single thing that she did.
She's a real southern belle.
This scene was also a 30-minute one-take.
Wasn't it?
Strangers kill other strangers.
- Strangers also blow other strangers.
We've watched the trailer too many times.
Guys, the trailer rules.
Is that an Xbox behind us?
No, those are all cameras.
That's all camera stuff 'cause it's my room.
You guys seem to have
a real rapport with each other.
How long did you know each other
before the movie?
- Zero days.
- We knew each other for a whole year.
- What happened was we both got cast...
- Before we started filming?
- Yeah, before we started filming.
- Okay.
We both got cast
way before the movie got started.
- I got cast May 1st.
- There were changing studio problems.
I got February,
the day before Valentine's Day.
We met. We had shabu-shabu together.
- That's right, the night before the audition.
- Just me, Zack, and my dad.
Yeah, we talked about Weezer.
And the next day we both got the part,
and we were shooting a teaser.
And the next day he shaved my balls.
Yeah.
So, shabu-shabu, Weezer, shaving my balls.
And then what happened during that year
where you guys were waiting for the movie?
We talked on the phone almost every day.
- He was in Ann Arbor, Michigan.
- Literally.
I was on Long Island, New York.
You should see my phone bill.
It was ridiculous.
Dr. Genoa is Andrew Gurland,
just to put it out there.
- So, just saying it fast.
- The voice of the doctor is Andrew.
Yeah, that's Andrew Gurland.
Matt and I hung out. I went to New York,
- and Matt came to Ann Arbor.
- I went to Michigan.
We hung out, practiced.
I'm not gonna specify what we practiced,
- but we practiced.
- Man.
That's Brent Caballero,
our casting director in New Orleans.
Can we say who this blurry faced guy is?
- Yeah, it's Chris Henchy.
- That's Chris Henchy.
Chris Henchy, producer from Gary Sanchez.
You can see some terrible sunburn
on my nose there.
God, use some zinc.
Cover up, 45!
If you can't find 45, use house paint.
- Zack used to wear pajamas on the beach.
- Now, Matt,
how old were you
when you were shooting the movie?
- Seventeen.
- And was any of the sexual stuff
uncomfortable for you at all?
Actually, I was very surprised
how comfortable I got.
It was extremely surprising.
When we did the Becca loft scene,
I was just in underwear the entire time.
And in between takes, they're like,
"You want a robe?" I said, "No."
And I started walking around the streets
of New Orleans
at 1:00 or 2:00 in the morning
just in my underwear.
That sounds like
you were really uncomfortable.
I just came, okay?
Thanks, you guys, it has been fun.
I'm out of here.
Zack, I'm calling your mother.
I'm leaving the family.
It's up to you, pal.
My dad just left.
No, but was there a scene
for either one of you
where you guys were nervous
about it coming up?
"I don't know how I'm gonna do this."
No, because I shaved Matt's balls
a year earlier.
I was like, "Back to this!"
I don't know.
I was so excited the whole time,
I let everything go.
I was nervous with the jump...
It didn't make it in, but we jumped
from the top of the house into the pool.
That scared me a little bit.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But I did it.
- Dude.
- That was awesome.
Matt.
This guy was so professional the entire time.
Yeah, that guy was great.
- Never broke character.
- Best joke.
- "$1,700!"
- Yeah, that's good.
I'm such a dummy.
- There's Matt wearing a Graf Orlock shirt.
- I love Graf Orlock.
Graf Orlock is this awesome
hardcore punk band from California.
And I told them, "You guys,
I'm wearing your T-shirt in the movie."
They were like, "Yeah, right,"
and I was like, "Yeah, totally."
- And totally made it in.
- And then seven people saw the movie.
Seven people saw it.
Seven whole people. Well, seven and a half.
All of those shoes,
those are all Owen Burke shoes.
If you don't know who Owen Burke is...
- That sucks for you, I guess.
- Owen Burke?
That's Owen Burke right there.
Owen Burke is the predator
on the Graf Orlock shirt.
- It's not like you don't have the money.
- I don't have the money.
You have a college fund
that's overflowing with money.
Your mom would want you to do this.
Matt, this is your last tape...
- That's not my mom.
- That's Jacob Davich.
I've put away a little money for you.
I hope it will help with college
and make your life just a little easier.
I remember this bank.
Nothing cool happened there.
Except for that dance.
That was the most fun they've had
in a long time.
And now, Huck, this looks old, that footage.
How did we get that?
Well, we Trash-Humped it. We did the thing
that Harmony Korine did on Trash Humpers,
which was we put it through a VHS machine
over and over and over and over again.
- Wow.
- Finally it got older and older-looking.
I'm so excited.
I just downloaded Trash Humpers.
I'm really not kidding.
- I believe you.
- I'm gonna watch that when I get home.
I've got so many VHS tapes.
I just don't know what to do with them.
I don't wanna get rid of them.
'Cause I don't believe in DVD.
My dad is using Netscape.
- Oh, gosh!
- Netscape. Net.
It works the best on Web TV.
Zack's dad at netscape. Net.
My dad uses Altavista
to search for his favorite things.
I wanna know
who this Jeeves is that everyone asks.
- Let's go.
- Well, I'll confront him...
- Krysta.
- Funny thing about that monkey.
That monkey was in our house
the whole time, right behind Krysta.
- It's a funny thing about that monkey.
- That's really funny.
- Hilarious, Zack, once again.
- You can hear us yell, "Cookout!"
That was Justin's original name.
We changed it, for the movie, to Justin.
Now, Justin's wardrobe in the movie
is pretty unique.
Can you talk a little bit about
where that came from?
Why don't you talk about it,
Andrew Gurland?
- The back of his car?
- You seem to know a lot about it.
Well, all the clothes that Justin wears
in the movie are his own clothes.
That is his unique fashion style sense
that you're seeing.
Andrew has a crush on Justin.
I'm a big fan. My favorite of Justin's songs
is Tyler Nelson (Please Don't Date Dannika).
- I love that song.
- That's a great song.
- That kills me.
- I bet everybody on Nickelodeon
knows that song 'cause I kept singing it.
It's so good, right?
And I also like I'll Never Be Your Boy Scout.
- I really enjoy that one, as well.
- Yeah, that one's good.
Matt, you were very upset after
that watermelon went on your head,
- I remember.
- I hated it.
I don't like being messy.
- You got very pouty after you got...
- Those are Matt's shoes on the dashboard.
What I would say about Matt
is that he is anal
in the most classic sense of the word.
I just don't like to be messy,
and I don't like having fun.
Everyone is actually miserable in this shot.
And then this part right here...
That's CGI.
- CGI.
- That's me, by the way.
That's my dad.
God, I wish Justin was my son.
You know, this sequence
was originally scripted as a commune.
And it was gonna be a farm,
and hippies on it.
But we just saw this location one day,
and we changed it.
Also, there are no hippies in New Orleans.
- Only Slim Goodies.
- Courage.
- I love the name of the boat.
- Yeah.
- Actually, I haven't seen this part yet.
So everybody be quiet, please.
In the script, it was not a boat.
Is that right, Huck?
- It was a horse?
- I do believe that it was a boat.
- It was not a boat.
- It was a tractor.
It was a tractor.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- I believe it was a tractor-boat.
- I feel like I just ruined that question
that was for Huck.
I'm just trying to get Huck more involved,
that's all.
Okay, everybody stay quiet until Huck starts.
It feels awkward.
I don't know if you know this or not,
but your dad is a little bitch.
You know, Huck,
when things get tight and uptight
around the Pearlman household,
we all just take off our clothes,
and just sit free for a while.
- Dad, shut up.
- Yeah, I'm gonna take off my pants.
Oh, God!
There it is.
- That's it.
- Here's something interesting about Huck
that everyone might not know.
Everything disgusting in the movie,
that's Huck's idea.
Well, more of the bathroom humor.
Huck loves the bathroom.
- Just love it.
- Yeah.
He did a series
of really awesome short films.
Originally, this chicken
was supposed to poop,
but we couldn't make it.
But that was Huck's idea.
He did a couple of really great films.
The dessert trilogy or quadrilogy?
How many? Talk about it.
The Dessertumentaries,
there are four of them.
What do you think about them?
Have you seen all of them?
Did you watch all of them?
I've actually watched all of them.
And basically what he does is,
he does terrible things to his family's food.
They're revenge movies, where I taint
some food that I give to my family.
- We had to shoot this boat scene 230 times.
- And we mean "taint"
- in the most classic sense of the word.
- This made it in?
I've always missed this part.
I haven't seen this yet.
Now, Huck, do you remember shooting
this thing with the boat at all?
- Were you there that day?
- Yeah, it was amazing
how we got it to just flip over like this.
I was really pleased with the shoot that day.
They put a stick of dynamite under it
and it set it off, blew it up.
No, for real, the boat did not do anything
but just kind of go straight up
to the shore, but we were able
to fix that in post-production.
Is that right, Huck?
- Yes, I recall something like that happening.
- Who did that?
Who did we do that with?
I don't remember his name.
Joe? Joe Bolero?
- That's pretty good.
- I love this scene.
- Sounds about right.
- So, what is it, a cartoon?
- The boat?
- Kind of. Yeah.
- It's like a cartoon.
- Yes, Mr. Pearlman.
So, this is like Cool World.
This is like that movie Cool World,
where it's cartoon and live-action.
- Yeah, like Howard the Duck.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Who Framed Roger Rabbit.
- Roger Rabbit.
- Never saw that.
Guys, I don't smoke cigarettes.
- These are not real cigarettes, I don't think.
- That's CGI.
- Really?
- Oh, my God.
- No, they were Herbalettes.
- Herbalettes?
This is a song that I wrote.
It's called Need You to Know.
And I wrote it when I was in eighth grade
and we used it. That's it.
And is this the only song of yours
that made it into the movie?
Oh, God, no. There's too many.
Zack and I did Birthday/Hurt Day.
That was an improv song.
Oh, Nicole.
I'm trying to think about all the other ones.
I think that's it.
Probably more.
Do you write for Keesha?
That Keesha, that singer?
- I think it's Kesha.
- Kesha?
Matt and I recently smelled Kesha...
- No comment.
- From across the room.
So, Zack, did you have any drinks
on the night of this shoot?
- No, I did not.
- Because you play it drunk.
- It's so good...
- Well, thank you.
...that people think
that you are actually drunk.
There is actually Oscar buzz
- over this exact scene.
- Just this scene.
- Just the scene.
- Supporting role.
I am not drunk.
But I've seen people drunk.
Zack's never drank before.
- I've never drank in my life.
- No, never.
This is a little shout-out
to drunk people everywhere.
- Now that also...
- That is the best outfit.
That is Justin's shirt.
Justin found that...
- It was Buffalo Exchange.
- At a Buffalo Exchange.
- That was awesome.
- It was amazing.
Now, some people think
you were really sleeping there.
Were you really sleeping?
- I wanted to be. I was tired.
- He was slipping. He was slipping.
I really am fat in that scene. I actually am fat.
You're adorable.
You can tell when Zack's sleeping,
because he does this little thing
with his lips.
A little thing, like he's kissing angels.
That's what we say. He kisses angels.
Such a little sweet boy.
He always has an erection
when he sleeps, too. Just a little tent.
- That tent's being held up by my penis.
- Emphasis on little.
Very little.
What do you remember about this stuff,
being out in the swamp?
I remember people were miserable.
It was super hot. But I loved it.
I thought it was super fun.
I remember there were a lot of fire ants
on the grass
- that were devouring people.
- Krysta got eaten up.
Krysta got bitten by ants,
and she got stung by a bee.
It was a wasp.
It was a wasp, yeah.
We all got bitten. We all got hurt.
I love this part
because I get to punch Matt in the head.
- I love that shot.
- I love Matt's face.
It's so weird.
Yeah, I punch Matt in the head
in three, two, one...
- I get you back, though. I slap your back.
- It's true.
It's true. He hits me.
Although, there was one...
- Adolf.
- Adolf Shitler.
I think my favorite play on words
for The Virginity Hit
was The Virginity Shit.
- We get that way too much in the comments.
- Yeah.
There's Zack Pearlman.
- Little baby Zack.
- Look at him sleep.
Guys, here's a little movie magic for you.
Even though it looks like dawn,
the sun was setting.
Movies.
And there'll be a lot more movie trivia
coming up in the commentary
right now.
Matt Bennett's really hot
in that sleeping bag. Movies.
Matt, why don't you give a little movie fact?
That's a foot next to my head.
- That's not my sleeping bag.
- Movies.
Movies.
Now, at the end of this scene,
something happened to you, Matt.
- Yeah. I pitched, "Rape, rape."
- That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about
when you ran outside the door
- after you stole the suit.
- Oh, my God.
Right. So I was yelling, "Rape!"
And some guy outside heard me.
And as I was running out, this exact take...
The guy lets me go, and I'm running out,
and the guy stopped me and was holding me
'cause he thought
that either I raped somebody
or I was the victim of a rape.
He's trying to help me
- in some way.
- No, I think it was because you were
- stealing a suit.
- Right.
As I recall, you ran out of the store
with a suit.
The security guard followed you
and a Good Samaritan on the street outside,
which was just unsecured,
tackled you and brought you down.
That's true.
I love the walk-up
when you're screaming those obscenities.
That's ADR, too, so, thank you.
Yeah, so, right here someone grabbed you.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. For those who don't know,
ADR means
Additional Digital Recording, right?
- Think it's "dialogue."
- Shut up. Movies.
Let's count the spots on a baby giraffe
Let's start with one
- One. One, two, three
- One, two, three, four, five
- I have the stupidest face.
- Do you still have it on your phone, Matt,
- your ring, Baby Giraffe?
- I think I have. Yeah, I do.
- Can you play it for us?
- No.
Are there any other original songs
that you have written
that we don't use in the movie?
Yeah, there's a lot.
I could rattle off a couple,
but I'm not Jacob Davich.
- Well, we'd love to hear a song right now.
- I love Jacob Davich.
- Lf possible.
- Okay.
It's acapella, let me start.
Jack Black, everybody. Jack Black.
Trying to get my voice
Think you're swell
Do you guys wanna call someone?
- For what?
- I don't know. Call someone in the movie
- who isn't here.
- Yeah, let's call Nicole up.
- Give Nicole a call.
- I'm gonna call Krysta.
In the meantime,
I'll sing a song that I wrote for Zack.
Renner was not scripted.
I didn't read the script.
Matt was just as lost as Justin and Jacob,
- for he did not read the script.
- Yes.
No, but that's true. A lot of the folks
in the movie had not read the script
and they just showed up.
I think, one day I came to Andrew
and I was like, "I lost my script."
And he's like,
"Well, what does that have to do..."
And I was like,
"I don't know what I'm doing."
And I asked for one and I never got one.
- So I don't think I ever read the script.
- I get it. It's my fault.
- It was totally your fault.
- I get it.
That woman is
an Academy Award-winning actress.
She's the third Gyllenhaal.
- This is a great ADR.
- I'm calling Nicole right now.
Oh, no. No, I'm not.
- I'm gonna try and call Krysta Rodriguez.
- Is it a good idea?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Call TGI Friday's.
She's probably working. It's 5:00.
- Cool.
- I know her schedule.
I don't think she works on Thursdays.
Okay, that's weird.
Yeah, weirdo.
Or you care about her.
And that's how you know.
- All right, I'm calling Krysta.
- I'm calling Nicole.
Hey, it's Krysta, leave a message.
- That didn't work.
- I'm calling Nicole.
America's darling, Nicole Weaver, everyone.
Guys, we are about to talk to the next
Shirley Temple, Nicole Weaver.
High-five.
- Bam Margera kickflip.
- Hi, this is Nicole. Leave a message
and I'll call you back.
I'm gonna call Justin Kline, guys.
- That's a better idea.
- The old J. Kline.
What if no one picks up
and this is just a failed experiment?
It's gonna turn her on.
Love that. Great joke.
Can I ask the filmmakers,
what did you see in my son, Zack,
that made you wanna cast him in this role?
I mean, what did you see?
"Slightly."
You know, the thing is that Zack auditioned
through Funny or Die
by telling an embarrassing story.
Is that true, Zack?
- You told us an embarrassing story...
- Yeah.
...about something that happened to you
in your own life. What was that story?
My sister walked in on me masturbating
when I was 16.
God, sweet Hannah!
- Sweet Hannah!
- No, no, Allie, the older one.
Okay.
And what happened from there was
I convinced Allie to be in the video
under false pretenses.
And so when I told the story,
she had repressed the memory,
- and it came out...
- This was the first day of filming.
Came out in a bad way.
She had Vietnam flashbacks,
that's basically what happened.
Yeah, this was also
before principal photography.
This is day one.
Was this day one of principal?
Because Luke wasn't there yet.
- I think it was the exact same day as the...
- The Kenner stuff.
- Yeah.
- That bat stuff, yeah.
That's Andrew Gurland's pubic hair.
- This is a great story.
- The best gag.
Is the teaser that we shot
gonna be on the DVD?
- Yeah, we think so.
- The first one we shot, I remember
we had just met.
We had all known each other for a little bit.
I don't know if you know this, Andrew,
we kept telling you that it wasn't enough
when it was clearly enough.
He must've come back, like, four times.
And we were just like,
"Tell him it's not enough."
"It's not enough."
And we kept sending him back.
He probably cut off all of his pubic hair.
- I'm very masculine in that area.
- Wearing black socks.
I'm wearing nothing but socks.
I mean, it's pretty amazing.
Matt was like,
"I do not want to wear a thong.
"I don't wanna wear a slip.
I wanna show my penis to the world."
And we had to block it out.
Now, it didn't end up in the movie,
but you did actually deep-throat him.
- Yes.
- Oh, God!
Sweet Hannah!
And I remember that you had
these bruises on your ears
- from where Matt was holding your head.
- My head, yeah.
It was a bitch for continuity.
I just have to tell you that it was a funny bit,
but it just got cut from the movie,
- because it wasn't as good...
- I still don't understand
why this is in an abandoned warehouse.
- Well, apparently, so the key...
- Sinister.
And now it looks like we just go into a door.
So, Matt, you were underage
when we made this movie.
So there were a lot of rules and regulations
about what we had you do.
For example, when you did
get your pubic hair shaved,
you actually were wearing a thong.
- I was wearing a thong.
- Right.
Then we digitally masked it out
so we couldn't see it,
and then we blurred it a little bit.
And then, coming up, with the tranny doll,
we had very strident, stringent rules
about what we could do,
and one of the things that's not allowed
was that you were not allowed
- to touch the doll.
- I could look at it. I could mention it.
I couldn't touch it.
So that's the only thing.
I've done all my own stunts
- for everything I've ever done.
- Stunts?
Except for that.
I guess that counts as a stunt.
I mean, they had a stunt double there.
- I've done all my own...
- When you say everything you've ever done,
- you mean during your entire catalogue?
- Yes.
He's always been on camera
when asked to be on camera.
This is a little tricky for everyone.
One of the people thought
the movie was over.
- Really?
- I was at a screening,
and someone was like, "That's it?"
And they were expecting our credits,
and I was like, "This person's a real idiot."
- But that would be funny.
- And that was actually your dad.
- And that was my dad.
- I know. I wanted to leave.
I want to go see Guardians of Ga'Hoole.
Can I get to go see
Guardians of Ga'Hoole now?
We should say, owl movie. The owl movie.
Well, yeah, it's an owl movie.
Guardians of Ga'Hoole!
- We're the Gyllenhaals.
- Guys, if you don't know,
that's one of the movies
we probably beat out this week.
- It was Guardians of Ga'Hoole.
- We're up against Wall Street 2.
- Who wants to see Shia anymore?
- It doesn't stand a chance...
And Michael Douglas?
- God, I love Michael Douglas.
- Virginity Hit.
Matt Bennett's balls.
Lot of people say
I look like Michael Douglas.
- Yeah, I could see that.
- Here's the problem. Wall Street 2,
they only made 2
so that they could make Wall Street 3-D.
The only reason they made 2.
The stocks really come out at you.
Talk about brokers.
I hope Wall Street 3
is like a teen sex-comedy.
- Direct to DVD, Wall Street 3.
- There was one
improv here where I know that
she was asking what you wanna try.
And you said something.
Do you remember what that was?
I kept breaking character. I couldn't...
Andrew, was it you? I think it was Owen.
Owen pitched the line.
That I would say,
"I wanna try double penetration."
And actually I don't think Savannah knew
what double penetration was.
She did not know yet. No, she did not.
And we showed her.
Yeah, she knew before she wrapped.
This is funny. Matt asked me to be on set
for a little bit of this.
And I did one thing,
and Andrew kicked me off.
I started singing,
and you were like, "Off now."
'Cause I couldn't take it seriously,
'cause Matt was walking around
in Superman underwear.
Yeah.
- That was pretty serious stuff.
- This is that scene we were talking about
where I was in underwear all night.
We shot this until 5:00 in the morning.
I love this line coming up
about eating out a girl.
Right here.
I mean, I got really close.
- It was, like, inches away from my face.
- Okay. Yeah.
Just you showing your hand to your face.
This is the most awkward movie.
So, yeah, I could look at it.
That's a penis on there. I could see it.
I could mention it, could not touch it.
And did you touch the doll at all
when we weren't rolling?
- Did you get to know it?
- No, I actually didn't.
- That would be not cool.
- He wasn't allowed.
- I'm a law abiding citizen.
- That would be not cool.
That'd be considered child pornography.
But I do remember we were looking at dolls,
having fun picking out which doll,
and Matt was just cross-armed,
- couldn't participate.
- So that's as close as you got.
- Yeah.
- Right, and then we got a guy.
- That's not me.
- This guy, Will Kennedy, right?
- Body double.
- Will "Thriller" Kennedy. That's not me.
- Will "Thriller."
- You can tell by the color of the underpants.
That's not me.
- And the thing is...
- I'm really not kidding. That's not me.
We cast Will from his headshot,
because he had the same...
We took a picture of him.
He had the same body, same hair.
He showed up,
he had no idea what he was gonna do.
- That's his first job, I think. Vagina Cam.
- His first job, and we said,
"You got to eat out this tranny doll."
He said, "Bring it on. Where is she?"
- That's not me.
- He'd be a great member
of the Greatest Generation.
I've seen enough.
Can we please turn it off, now?
Wait. It gets worse.
- I loved filming this scene coming up.
- Yeah.
Why is that, Zachary?
'Cause we were all in a room.
Actually, it was the only time
none of the four were behind the camera.
It was the first time
we could all be in the shot.
- Blocked off.
- That's me.
One interesting thing
about the room that you're in
is Monique,
who built this loft from top to bottom,
- it was an empty loft warehouse.
- She did an amazing job.
She did an amazing job
building Becca's loft.
Then the room that you guys are in,
didn't have to do a thing to,
because that house looked exactly like that
when we walked in.
With the Christmas tree thing, the surfboard.
We didn't have to do a thing to that house.
It's just this crazy, wacky house.
Yeah, this house ruled.
That house is amazing.
We got chocolate in that pool.
There's chocolate in my pool.
Wait, what is that? When you say
that there's chocolate in your pool,
- what does that mean?
- There's a video on SUPERZACK
that we did where we rained chocolate syrup
over Nicole and her sister Jessica.
And they jump into the pool.
There's a reaction shot where I'm like...
- They don't jump in.
- My chocolate is full of pool.
There's pool in my chocolate.
- There's pool in my chocolate.
- I'm sorry.
So, what does that mean, the SUPERZACK?
SUPERZACK1000 is a YouTube account
that is supposed to be
Zack in the movie's YouTube account,
but you guys and, I guess, Sony,
gave me some freedom to upload some stuff.
And that's Matt actually punching me
in the back of the neck.
- A great place to punch someone.
- Fight back, Zack. Fight back.
Did you hit him as hard as you could, Matt?
Was that as hard as you could?
One of them,
I remember Matt just clocking me
and I just saw double, 'cause he hit me
right in the back of the head.
There are a couple of times
where my notes were, "Be weaker."
Like, there's another scene
where we're jumping over a fence,
and I bounded it in the first shot.
"Matt, you have to struggle."
- I find that hard to believe.
- For the ladies.
You got to struggle for the ladies.
You can't let him just sleep all day.
He won't show his face over there anymore.
Can you blame him?
Good Lord, what that girl did to him.
Well, you know,
the school year's almost over,
so maybe he can just get his GED.
Male-Animal. Info really exists.
Once we created it.
Yes. After we created it, sorry.
- Here we go, jack off.
- Oh, God.
Classic Zack Pearlman.
This is a great joke.
Rain is CGI, I believe.
That's my 21st-birthday hat.
If you guys don't know what that's from,
that's from The Rocketeer,
which was a comic book
and then became a movie in 1992?
My first job in show business was
I cut a TV spot for The Rocketeer.
- What year was it?
- I just wanna point out, these girls,
we licensed this footage.
They're actually watching "2 Girls 1 Cup,"
but we repurposed it
for "On your knees, Matt!!"
Who is this guy?
He looks like a huge Andrew Gurland.
That's Norm Bar Stool.
Norm's Bar Stool, he's online.
You can find him.
- He's got great stuff. Yeah.
- He's fantastic.
- Dad, you know of him?
- Yeah.
Great recipes, great casserole recipes.
- Fantastic.
- Yeah.
Which I could say, Norm Bar Stool
looks like a fat Daniel Stern.
This is a great...
Dude, you look like a ninja
when you grab my arm.
Who's saying I'm not a ninja?
Listen, you got to be a ninja
when you're around
and there's cupcakes.
- In Sweden, they call them ninyas.
- Ninyas.
That's a call-out to my best friend,
Max Freiberg,
who could be anywhere in the world
right now.
I love how in the script we had
Matt being a budding baker and chef,
and these muffins are such a freaking mess.
- I know.
- They weren't cupcakes. They were muffins.
- I love this.
- We were icing muffins.
There he is. Mr. Pearlman.
- Good job, sir.
- Thank you.
That was awesome.
If only I could act like him.
- He's amazing.
- I love this scene. My sister's in this scene.
- Allie Pearlman.
- Oh, Allie!
Well, this is the sister scene,
because Nicole's sister is also in this.
We like to call this the sister scene.
- That's Amanda on the left.
- Sipster scene.
What's her name? Keri?
- Keri. That's Keri.
- That's Keri.
- I think Holly's in this, too.
- This is me.
- Here she comes.
- And there's the sisters.
- Boom, there's Allie.
- Oh, Allie!
That's Allie, and Jessica on the right,
and Nicole.
And that's Nicole in the middle.
That's me in a big tiger...
That tiger suit came into play a lot more.
Allie told me she was taking her LSATs
that weekend.
- I was so proud of her.
- There was a joke here
where, originally, we peed in the hat.
Sort of a YouTube-style prank.
- We cut it out.
- What a classic joke.
We should probably get that
onto SUPERZACK,
the peeing in the hat.
You fucking cheated on Matt.
I know this is gonna sound weird,
but, Matt, do you remember we called
- Paul Shearer on Owen's phone?
- Yeah, that was that night.
We called him up
and we said that we were big fans...
Huge fans and I was asking him
if his life was really based off of
- Pride and Prejudice.
- I think I said War and Peace after that.
- War and Peace.
"Is it true that your life
is based on War and Peace?"
I wanna name a kid Warren Peace.
- Warren.
- W-A-R-R-E-N?
- This is another original song.
- Let's just change the subject.
Zack always makes fun of me for that one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That clock is not on.
- That's a useless clock.
- That's Justin's...
I remember Jacob had a raging boner
while watching this footage.
I mean, Jacob had a huge boner
And my associate, Jacob, and I
have found a way to cure this problem.
With all the bad shit...
Right.
And that's the Sunny Leone website, right?
- You need to leave.
- No. Hold on, wait a second.
- Yeah, right there.
- Leave.
- Oh, God. Dad, leave.
- Oh, God.
Hold on. We got Nicole on the phone.
- Dad, leave. Dad, leave. Nicole's here.
- Don't tell your mother.
- Hey, Nicole.
- I've got to put a pen in my butt.
- How are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
- We're watching Sunny Leone get doinked.
- We're watching the commentary
- of The Virginity Hit.
- No, we're watching The Virginity Hit,
- and doing the commentary.
- You talk to Zack.
Say it again.
- I thought you were doing the commentary.
- We are doing the commentary.
- Hi, Zack.
- Matt's going crazy.
Nicole, can you tell us
about your participation
in The Virgiminy Hit?
Virgimininy Hit?
The Virgiminy Christmas.
- What?
- The Virgiminy Hit.
I don't know how to explain.
- You played Nicole in the movie.
- I was the only girl
besides Krysta.
She wasn't there the whole time.
- Ask her where she is right now.
- Where are you right now, Nicole Weaver?
- I'm in my kitchen.
- Which is where in the world?
- Flemington, New Jersey.
- Ask her if she's with Twilight.
Are you with Twilight?
Yes, I am.
- Who's Twilight?
- Ask her.
- That's my dog.
Your dog?
My dog.
No way.
- Yeah.
- That's really your dog's name?
I thought that was the name
of your boyfriend.
What?
I thought that was
your boyfriend's name, Twilight.
- 'Cause he dresses like Edward.
- No, his name is Violent Jay.
You're such a fucking dick.
Commentary rules.
Here's Matt. We miss you.
Nicole, I'm gonna hang up now,
but it was very nice talking to you.
It was super nice talking to you, too.
- Okay. I love you, too.
- Okay.
- What?
No, I will not make out with you.
That was so warm.
Matt just said, "I love you, too,"
without being told he was loved.
- Love is funny like that.
- Owen Burke just walked in.
I've got a clearance sheet for Nicole.
Where is she?
- She's got to sign this.
- She's in Flemington, man.
Flemington? All right.
I got to get on a JetBlue flight to Newark.
I don't know if you know this,
- but you sound a lot like Zack's dad.
- My dad.
Really?
I've never met him.
I've only seen pictures of him on Craigslist.
- He just walked out.
- He did?
You might have seen him in the hallway.
I saw a guy running around
with an erection and a pen up his butt.
- But I did not...
- That was my dad.
Oh, gosh, that's your... Oh, yeah!
That's great. Oh, man.
What is this, the movie?
Yeah.
- What are you guys doing, commentary?
- Commentary, Owen, yeah.
Owen Burke, everybody.
Owen Burke, producer,
who is with us every day pitching jokes,
and there's a ton of them in the movie.
Just keeping good morale
when we need to fire people.
And also a terrific friend,
I might add, as well.
It was really great to get to know all of you
so well, you know?
- It was a sweet time.
- I really value our friendship.
- I do, too. Well, we met so many years ago.
- Yes.
But I only saw a little bit of you
through that hole.
I only saw a little bit of you
Yeah, well, that's why they call it
a glory hole.
It was glorious.
I believe one of the classic lines
from the movie is yours, Owen.
It's Hitchcock...
"I'm gonna do to your virginity
what Hitchcock did for Birds. "
- That is Owen Burke, everybody.
- It's an OB.
- There were a lot of alternates.
- There was.
It's all about choices
in the editing room, guys.
There was a Robert Zemeckis one,
which was,
"I'm gonna do for your virginity,
what Robert Zemeckis did
"for old men and young boys
with time travel."
Did I say, "Old boys and young men"?
I love how the more we've been drinking,
the less we've been talking about the movie
that's in front of us.
I've said, "Pool in my chocolate,"
too many times.
You notice that girl on that pole?
Not that pole.
- The girl on the pole to the right of us.
- Yeah.
She was an extra.
- Oh, my God.
- She was an extra.
She's very beautiful.
This is actually by a band
called The Spyderz,
which has a member, a guy named Dirty,
or Daniel Weber,
who was dating Sunny at the time,
so they gave us clearance for it.
- And still is.
- I thought they broke up.
- No, no, no. They're tight.
- Ooh la la.
- Wait, why would you say, "Ooh la la"?
- Wishful thinking.
- I don't know. Hubba-hubba.
- You know what? Never mind.
He meant "hubba-hubba"
when he said, "Ooh la la."
I wanna read some YouTube comments
on how excited people are for the movie.
- I think they're available.
- Lf I could.
- You wanna take a look in and see?
- Owen, can you tell us
how you pitched Sunny her pole dance set?
Well, Sunny and I worked
very closely choreographing the set.
I worked the pole for several years,
and Sunny, actually,
she's never really worked the pole.
So I showed her a couple of moves.
That's my outfit she's wearing.
- They have the same body type.
- Here you go, guys.
So I just wanna let you know the Internet
is abuzz for The Virginity Hit.
With comments like,
"Rich, privileged white kids.
"I hope this movie flops."
- Here's another one.
- That one was me. That was my account.
Jacob in a sailor suit.
Always a pleasure
to see Jacob in a sailor suit.
Yeah, especially since he was in the Army.
- Yeah.
- That's a good one.
- One of my favorite jokes.
Here we go.
"250 people missed the dislike button."
Nailed it.
And look, there you can see Zack
holding the camera.
Occasionally we gave Zack the camera.
And an awesome cameo.
That's Miss Amy Hobby.
Amy Hobby is in the shot,
and her boyfriend, Joe McGinty,
is the composer of the song we just heard,
so it was the Hobby-McGinty moment
of the movie.
- Amy Hobby is the producer on the movie.
- And I came.
Thank you, guys, again, for everything.
I'll come back later. Thank you, Miss Sunny.
- That was a line that I pitched.
- Great joke. Thank you for that.
- Very good.
- Here we go.
Anything that has to reference
Matt's TV show is my favorite.
"Isn't that the kid with the stupid hair
on Nickelodeon?"
- But that's just his hair.
- "He can kiss his career goodbye."
Which everyone knows, starring in a movie
means your career is done.
Yeah, 'cause movies are terrible for careers.
"Nickelodeon is gonna fire that idiot."
"This looks gay." "This is retarded."
"This movie looks fucking..."
But spelled with two "K's." "...lame."
That's actually a compliment
when it's two "K's."
Yeah.
Hi. This is my boyfriend, Dirty.
"Flagged for being fucking retarded."
So, as the guys were saying,
Sunny and Daniel are together in real life,
and Sunny only does scenes with Daniel.
- Well, unless they're girl-on-girl scenes.
- Right.
- Right, she only does girl-guy...
- Girl-guy with Daniel.
Oh, Matty
Got fucked over by Nicole
And what really drew us to the lyrics
was the complexity.
Yeah, I thought it was funny.
So many layers and meanings
and metaphors.
I like how people question
why you're in the movie.
"That's the guy
from the Nickelodeon show, Victorious.
"Why the fuck is he in a rated-R movie,
when he's on a children's television show?"
And it beats me.
I don't know why I'm in a movie.
This bus was supposed to go
to some country star.
They were supposed to pick him up.
And we just left it a super mess.
I felt so bad.
- Really?
- They go pick up this country star.
I think it was Keith Urban.
Yeah, yeah.
- I'm pretty sure it's Keith Urban.
- Or Faith Hill.
- McGraw. It was McGraw.
- Gavin DeGraw.
- No. Not Gavin DeGraw.
- No. Sorry. Never mind.
- I'm retarded.
- Whoever.
Kav McGraw?
Scruff McGruff?
That whole purple thing Daniel's leaning
against was to cover a mirror.
We didn't want to show Luke, our DP,
in the shot.
- Luke Geissbuhler.
- Luke Geissbuhler, everybody.
Luke Geissbuhler, our Double Penetration.
Luke Geissbuhler, he would be sweating
by the end of every day,
'cause he was just constantly running.
Hardest working guy in the world.
Super hard-working guy.
He was also carrying
a giant, heavy camera all day long,
which none of us had to do.
He was the one guy with a giant camera
on his back the whole day.
And also,
one thing that I find interesting is that,
as a DP, your life is all about
making things look beautiful.
And for this movie,
we asked that he really make things
- not look beautiful.
- But he is a genius. He shot Borat.
Yeah, yeah. No. He is a genius.
He did. He was the DP for Borat.
It's just a different mindset for a DP
to say, "I'm going to dumb it down.
I'm gonna make it look grainy,
"or I'm gonna make it look worse."
You know, he employed, I think,
seven different cameras to shoot this movie.
But I think, in a way, because he spent
so much detail to attention...
- Attention to detail.
- Yeah, we get it.
- Guys.
- Another Greyhound, Zack?
- Greyhound.
- Greyhound, please.
He spent so much attention to detail that
this is actually, I would assume, harder.
Because you have to make it look bad.
It's not any easier. It goes against instinct.
Yeah, for sure.
This is a great quote.
"LOL. Way to make kids feel pressured
into losing their virginity.
"Abortion clinics are having a parade."
They actually do throw great parades.
Have you seen their floats? They're amazing.
- Grand master.
- Really fantastic, yeah.
I saw this shit on ESPN2, where, like,
these little Asian kids stack cups.
What is the deal with that cup stacking?
It's a sport, right?
Yeah, it's a sport. It's a recognized sport.
I feel like masturbating should be
a recognized sport if cup stacking is.
Thank you very much, sir.
- Breasts.
How did you like working with Sunny, Matt?
How were those scenes?
- They were actually really good.
- What happened back there
- when you guys were sitting back there?
- Sunny was very, very adamant.
"You're 17. You're not 18.
We can't do anything."
So we just sat back there
and just looked at each other, basically.
She actually thought
maybe you were gonna try and like...
I wasn't gonna try anything.
- But that's what she thought.
- We were working. She's like,
"I'm not gonna touch him."
I don't know what it was,
but she kept making a big deal
that I was 17 when we filmed this.
- Right, yeah.
- Way to make me feel comfortable, Sunny.
I love her, though. She's very sweet.
And working with her was great.
She's very, very beautiful.
- She's very cool.
- That's how I like them, beautiful.
This is a great one. "I hated Happy Feet,
"but this movie will be
10 times worse than Happy Feet. "
That was Lord Ramen X.
That guy definitely will enjoy
Guardians Of Ga'Hoole when that comes out.
I don't know. That guy sounds like
he doesn't like animals.
This is the fence.
Didn't you hurt yourself
going over the fence?
You were saying you need to be weaker,
but you actually injured yourself
going over the first time, did you not?
- No, I didn't.
- You didn't?
- Stop.
- It was acting?
- No, I acted hurt.
- Yeah, he hurt himself.
- It's okay, Matt. You can hurt yourself.
- "Fuck this movie and its promotion.
"Everyone who's involved with this movie
can die being butt-raped."
I think somebody has
actually died being butt-raped,
- who worked on this film.
- Yeah, it's not funny.
- The sound mixer was...
- RIP Jacob Davich.
- It was Tammy?
- No, not Tammy.
- No, no, that was...
- The boom op?
- After that, then we brought Tammy in.
- Yeah.
It was Bruce.
- Yeah, Bruce, and it was public, too.
- Yeah.
- It was right after...
- It was actually at Publix.
Guys, I think I just found
the Jewiest comment.
"Jew Boy shtups a sticka." Schika? Schikta?
- "Doesn't Hollywood have any..."
- Shiksa? Shiksa?
Yeah, shiksa.
So, it's, "Jew Boy shtups a shiksa."
- Shtups-a.
"Doesn't Hollywood have any new plots?"
- Yeah, but you...
- I... I couldn't...
You never assume someone's at their house.
That thing in the back said "Jesus."
You can't see it. Never mind.
- I think we flipped it down.
- That means Satan.
This video, surprisingly,
has some pretty intelligent comments
followed by, "Okay, people,
you're taking this too seriously.
- "Calm the fuck down."
- Zack's terrified face.
He actually hurt me.
We did so many takes of this scene.
- Yeah.
- That's good.
I actually bit David.
He asked me to bite him, so I bit his arm.
It is pretty amazing how seriously people
will take this movie on comment boards,
and how our vibe on it
was to not take it too seriously.
- Another Happy Feet joke.
- No way.
- Why Happy Feet?
- "Fuck this shit. I'm watching Happy Feet."
I feel like, dude,
- some tards talked about it on the forum.
- Okay.
- Here's a great cameo.
- Everybody, cameo's coming up.
- My favorite cameo in the entire film.
- Look closely.
- Watch the pool.
- Lf you pause it right now,
- that's Owen Burke.
- Owen Burke.
In the white chair, Owen.
This is amazing.
Dude! Run, now!
This entire scene was actually...
David Jensen, his one request was
that we didn't wear shoes
- while running around.
- I don't remember that. Why?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
'Cause he's a ninja or a ninya.
- And I think he wanted to look at your feet.
- Yeah.
Stop.
This was great.
Yeah, I had sex with that girl.
Famous Jacob Davich quote.
So, is that true you guys were...
In the making of the movie,
there was a lot of sex happening,
- is that right?
- Not for me.
Not for me.
Andrew?
- I'd say for Jacob Davich.
- I would say just regular for me.
Owen?
Yeah, I had about the same amount
of sex as I do in my home life.
I love how this got cut, so that your shirt
gets ripped, but we don't know why.
You're suddenly wearing
an '80s, over-the-shoulder...
- It's a Flashdance homage.
- She's giving a blow job.
The MPAA made us take out a version
in which her head goes up and down.
They said,
"No head-up-and-down blow job shot."
We had two different takes.
She's just sort of down there.
The sad thing was that that was
an actual Craft Service cooler.
And there were snacks in there for the crew.
He was bare-assing it.
A lot of guys got E. Coli.
We lost the grip department that night.
- Are you saying that Harry's ass has E. Coli?
- Pinkeye, I think, went around after that.
Guys, it's pretty funny to know
how people just judge
this movie by the trailer.
- There was one that...
- Yeah, I don't get it. "This trailer sucks.
"This trailer's awful. The movie sucks."
I don't get the combo.
- Why does this have so many dislikes?
- There's the baby kangaroo that was...
Zack's younger brother.
- Got him a cameo.
- Travis, coming up.
- Oh, yeah.
- Great cameo by Travis.
First AC or second AC or... He's like loader.
He got his dick caught in a bong.
- Why did we cut the zip-line thing?
- I think he made 200 bucks for that
two seconds of work there.
There was a scene where Harry gets
on the zip-line and goes zooming down,
and then holds her and is like,
"It's not Nicole!" It was funny.
Guys, I have to read this one.
"Fuck this Superbad and every movie like it
that's come out in the past couple of years.
"All the actors look like the douche bags
in my school, BT dubs.
"OMG! And Easy A, too!
"Did you guys hear about that 13 kid
that is a father?
"Who gives a fuck about fucking...
Question mark, question mark.
"Explanation point. Question.
Explanation point.
- "To me..."
- Explanation point?
- What's an explanation point?
- Another Greyhound, Zack?
I don't know. No, no, no. He spelled that out.
- Explanation point?
- Yeah.
"To me, fucking is only about
making a goddamn kid.
"Not being kool," spelled with a "K."
"And saying to your friends at lunch,
'Oh, man, y'all are gay. I'm fucked.'
"That is like modern day macho shit
for kids that don't even have chest hair.
"I'm a virgin and I'm more of a man."
And that has, no joke, 500 thumbs up.
No. No.
If people are really upset about this,
- how is this guy's grammar not...
- Under attack?
Come on. Grammar's hard.
Boner in five. There you go.
There you go.
Now, can you talk a little bit about how
we worked with the prop department
to make it look like you had an erection?
The prop department tickled Matt's balls.
They had a special feather
that they grabbed from a peacock.
How many of these takes did we do
where the camera turns...
- We did a bunch of alts.
- Lot of alts. Yeah.
...but you're gonna thank me later,
'cause your dick looks huge.
Now did you have fun shooting
that scene with Nicole?
Was that enjoyable or was it nerve-racking?
- Well, we're both really professional actors.
- Yeah.
And we really went at it
like professionals do.
And did you feel closer to her?
Something got close to her.
So, I don't know,
one of my favorite scenes in the movie.
It's good to go out with a good one.
But something happened here,
where there's some great confusion.
And this is genuine Zack.
Yeah. I was playing high, but I really didn't
know what we were talking about.
- Were you high at all during the scene?
- No.
Were either of you guys ever, in any
of the shots or scenes, drunk or high?
- No.
- Never?
Confused. Confused.
- "Give him some minutes."
- Yeah.
- Sweet berry wine.
That was one thing I was really
concerned with, is people being like,
"That's how movies are made.
People just get drunk and high."
"Get fucked up."
It's a long day. If you're getting drunk
and high while we're shooting, it would be...
- It would be more like today.
- Today.
- Here we go.
- You would not be getting very far
- in the day.
- Look at this.
This is true confusion in my face.
What's the name of the geyser?
- Old Geyser.
- No.
That idiot.
We've all been there.
Cookout pulls it out.
Here's, here's a better question.
Did Matt pull out?
Good question.
"Hell no."
Just quote the movie for the rest of the...
Oh, my God, this is amazing.
"White people..."
I love when it starts with white people.
White people are Jews.
"White people have to start acting
like they have some sense
"instead of making movies like this.
Man, I can't believe this kind of shit
"they waste their money making.
Make some good movies instead
"about something that actually matters.
"I don't care about some stupid white boy
losing his virginity."
That's funny and everything,
but Huck and I are both black.
So it's kind of weird for them to...
All of this stuff actually happened.
- That happened.
- This action...
- That was Matt.
- That's Matt. That was your scary moment.
- This happened.
- That was really fun.
- When was that?
This is fun.
That was fabricated. That was fabricated.
- That knee slap was not.
- Happened.
- That happened.
- She definitely ate that pizza.
That happened.
- That happened.
- And now we're about to review
It's Kind of a Funny Story.
Yeah.
It shares the same music.
Now, on to our second commentary.
- Ida Maria is doing good this fall.
- Yeah.
- There we go, the infamous college shirt.
- It's funny, because this montage
is kind of where it all started
for Andrew and I,
because we found a montage
like this online,
a great collage of footage
from this group of friends' life.
And they just strung it together.
- That was fun.
- At the end of the day,
we put it all together.
And it kind of came full circle for us.
If you guys missed it,
I just did a truffle shuffle.
And that's me doing dumb faces.
That's me doing another dumb face.
- It's my favorite gag. I love this.
- Yeah.
Everybody just gets on the train.
Everybody shut up.
- It's okay to talk. They can turn it off.
- This is a...
Hey, this is also Owen feeding John lines
and just seeing how John delivers.
Because, really,
you give John any line to deliver
and it'll come out in a way
that is truly special.
I remember this being halfway
through filming and everyone was lagging.
- This brought everyone back.
- Everybody up. I agree.
- Yeah, it was really...
- It was the best.
He sparked everybody, John.
- That was my favorite thing.
- Yeah.
- We're done.
- There we go, Andrew and Huck Botko.
Give them a hand, how about it?
Producers Will and Adam.
Chris, Peter, Paul and Mary.
- There he is.
- Owen Burke.
- I don't know who that is.
- Amy Hobby.
- I don't know that guy.
- Luke Geissbuhler, we mentioned.
- We talked about that guy.
- Geoffrey Richman, edited the movie.
Geoffrey Richman,
funny stories about that guy.
Mark Barnard.
Zork Porlboard.
- Jodi Collins!
- Jodi Collins! I love you, Jodi.
- I love you, too.
- I haven't seen her in forever.
A Columbia poop-shops...
A Gary San-pap.
Capst.
Map. Map Barnard.
- Zack Pearlboard.
- Your dad's back.
Look, there's my son's name!
- Shut up.
- Zack Pearlman.
Oh, my God.
Don't you have some vaginas to attend to?
I do. I'm doing vagina checks at the Target
up the street.
Who's Hipster?
Yeah, who is Hipster? Bill Posley.
- Google it right now.
- I love Frat Guy.
Dream Shop Owner?
Dress Shop!
- Zack, I have terrible news.
- What?
Hannah was waiting in the car and I didn't
roll down the window, so her brain boiled.
Sweet Hannah! Sweet Hannah!
My dad just ran off crying.
He's in the back of the room crying.
- All right.
Clinkinbeard?
We apologize for anyone
who had to listen to this.
That guy's name is Mike Bonnett.
No.
- There's a Mike!
- There was a Jarrid Clinkinbeard.
- The huge guy? You remember that guy?
- Oh, Mike.
That guy was awesome.
- Scotty Morris!
- Zack Earl Edwards.
Daniel Mortenson III tried to sell us weed,
and we said, "No, we're not like that."
We're not like that. There's Victoria Valles.
Naomi Goodman cut most
of our SUPERZACK1000.
Yeah, she was great.
- Zack Booger.
- Joe.
- Joe DiValerio.
- You were asking about him earlier, Andrew.
- Ken Weinstein, who is
- a billionaire who does this for fun.
- Gandhar Savur is actually my father.
Hey, by the way...
Just today, we put up iTunes.
Not that it's gonna be just today,
for everybody listening, but
- the Virginity Hit soundtrack is on iTunes.
- Wow. I'm gonna go buy that.
It's a great soundtrack.
Lot of great music in this movie.
I got to tell you, Lovesick Teenagers.
My Imaginary Friend had a Plastic Army.
And love you. Did I Love You Better?
You Knives, Bats, New Tats.
All But Over Now.
All right, everybody. Matt?
Go on to the end, Andrew.
Andrew wants to leave,
but we're finishing what we started.
Andrew, literally, is naked, ready to leave.
- Which I don't know why he's naked, but...
- That's not all.
Zack, look at your dead sister.
Look at Hannah!
- Why did you bring her in here?
- Look at her. Sweet Hannah!
That's not even my sister. That's a dog!
Oh, God!
Sparkles! I killed Sparkles!
Guys, I'd like to throw a special thanks out
to The Office of
Entertainment Industry Development
and the People of Louisiana.
DTS. Down... Down To Suck... Matt.
If I could show you what he was doing,
he's doing like a crab dance.
Guys.
What is this?
Have you never heard this? Listen, it's good.
No.
Oh, Matty
I thought I'd give you Sunny's hole
Yeah, this is the one I wrote.
No, Andrew wrote this.
He wrote that "Sunny's hole" line,
or he threw it out in the moment.
- It was an ad-lib.
- It's a collaborative effort.
- "So romantic."
- Great way to end it.
- There's a weird lady.
- Weird lady.
- Thanks for listening. Not.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org