Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
My name is Benjamin Keynes.
I work for the directorat
of operations within the...
Central Intelligence Agency.
Three days after 9/11,
reconnaissance satellites picked up
a radioactive heat signature...
in a remote tribal region
of Afghanistan.
The Agency feared Al-Qaeda may finally
got their hands on a nuclear weapon.
However, I was told by a local source
with a high degree of confidence...
that it was maybe something
much more powerful...
It has been more than ten years,
since I left this place.
I forgot how brutal it could be.
I feel like every time we enter this country,
it tries to spit us back out.
Almost everyone here at the TO
is too busy fighting a war,
to pay much attention to me.
Which is a good thing.
Sir, Agent Keynes.
I finally met the CO
and the teamleader,
Sergeant Wallis Hamer.
I gave them the official line, as if
I read it from the memo back at Langley.
Major Keynes, this may be your show,
but these are my boys, understand?
Absolutely.
No doubt they assumed I was lying.
My first order of business was to recconect
with my local source, Mohammed Aban.
He asked me come, therefore I hope that
he is there, when we knock at his door.
Sir, the men are ready for you now.
Major Keynes, let me introduce
you to the guys.
This is my team daddy, Master-Sergeant Tanner,
he's also our fox, intel.
He helped me put the group together
back in the day.
- Our senior medic, Sergeant Degetau.
- What's up, man.
Demolitions, Sergeant Trinoski.
The on the floor there is Sergeant Cole.
And last but not least, Sergeant Sadler,
he's weapons and resident Afghan expert.
392 is a shit-hot team.
You won't find any better.
That's why I'm here.
Gentlemen, thankyou for
coming together on such short notice.
My orders are to make contact
with an HVT called Mohammed Aban.
A cleric, living in
the Southern provinces.
We're to get his
recorded statement,
in which he supports
the American mission here.
This is our man.
Everybody take a look.
Aban is highly respected
by the local population.
He's considered the spiritual force,
that helped the Mujahadin defeat the Soviets.
I thought the CIA was the spiritual force
that helped them defeat the Soviets.
That depends of your definition
of spiritual, sergeant.
Aban has kept a very low profile
under the Taliban,
so it is crucial
that we make contact,
as soon as we have
a fix on his position.
Remember, when we hit the ground,
this is a meet and greet.
To smile at the locals,
we hand out pens,
we win hearts and minds.
No kicking in doors, okay?
The mission starts at 1400 hours.
0130 inspections.
- 0230 we are wheels up.
- Let's move out.
Remember nothing's routine.
Special Forces Team 392.
I'd actually heard of them.
They worked with the Zagran.
Smart men, men good with secrets.
But that goes without saying.
Nice camera.
I gave my wife one for our anniversary.
Still don't know how to use the damn thing.
That's because
you never let her use it, Ski.
What kind of a man gives his wife a
video camera for their anniversary?
- Very romantic, ski.
- I'll use it to film the baby when it comes.
Your wife's gonna
spread her legs,
let you put the camera right here
and film the head coming out?
My sister's gonna
do the recording,
I still don't know how to
use the damn thing.
All I'm saying is don't be surprised
if your baby's born with a suntan.
Two minutes!
Get ready!
When I stepped off the chopper,
I had an overwhelming sense of relief.
The time for second-guessing is over.
The objective is all that matters.
I have no choice now but to find it.
- It's pretty quiet from here.
- Those are the ones I worry about most.
I say we set an overwatch.
Yeah, you and Pete set up
down there on that hill.
Let us know
when it's good to go.
Everyone else, Keynes and I are the
welcome wagon. We go in first.
- Keynes, are you ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
Everybody keep your eyes open.
The place could be crawlin' with bad guys.
Hello.
Let me talk to her.
Nothing has changed
since I was here last.
The only way you can tell
which decade you're in...
is the colour
of the soldiers' uniforms.
Aban contacted me a week before I
received orders to come out here.
He was barely coherent at the time and
I thought he'd finally lost his mind.
That was until
we saw it for ourselves.
My grandfather says, he has gone because
the Taliban would have murdered him.
What d'you want?.
You want some chocolate?
Got some special stuff.
I got that from New York. For you.
You're a smart, little kid.
Looks like we're gonna be
ghostbustin' again.
Yeah, well,
that's what Spooks do, isn't it?
Hey, any of you guys get a close
look at that camera?
No, what's wrong with it?
He didn't pick that shit up at the PX,
I'll tell you that much.
Need to use the radio.
Serpent 76. Serpent 76.
This is Beast 92, over.
Serpent 76, we're at the location.
The package is not here.
Request immediate
extraction, over.
We found Aban's house,
but we can't tell...
if we're finding clues
or breadcrumbs.
I wonder what these people
would do...
if they had suddenly the power
to destroy nations.
The rest of us can only pray that
they have become weary of fighting.
My grandfather says that no-one
can liberate Afghanistan.
Only Allah can free us
from the Taliban.
Yes, I know. My father took me
there a few years ago...
He showed me the place
where he wanted to be buried,
But it's too late now.
He was kidnapped by the Taliban
last year. I fear he's dead now.
How did you know this?
What'd he say?
I think he can help us.
You have up to 0300, then we're
moving out for extraction.
- I have to make a call.
- Cole, the sat-phone.
- I have my own.
- Got his own.
- Fuckin' James Bond.
- You know James Bond?
Yeah, I know James Bind.
He washed out of basic training.
I told headquarters
I was moving on to phase two.
They told me
that our footprint was fading.
That's what they called the heat
trace that was seen by the satellite.
Chief.
- Good way to get killed.
- We need to talk. A change of plan.
This had better be good!
I have new orders to continue
searching for Aban...
now that we have updated intel
on his whereabouts.
Intel? What, that crap
Obi-Wan told us?
We suspected that Aban was in the mountains
by now... We had to check here first.
We're talking two days, three max. All we
need to do is get our hands on a vehicle.
Well, excuse me if I wanna
check with the TOC...
Little does he know,
we don't have much of a choice.
Man, there's no place
to shit around here.
Any of you guys
got any more chocolate?
- No man, I gave you all I had yesterday.
- I got some stale cigars.
- Hearts and minds, man.
- Whatever. Get in the truck.
Sorry, kids.
What's he doing here?
- He offered to be our guide.
- We have a full boat.
Someone who knows the area can
get us in and out much faster.
I understand that, but this
place is crawling with bad guys.
Any time we gain, is gonna be
lost by our having to babysit him.
I fought with my father.
I can take care of myself.
Good. You can feed him
your rations.
Go.
She is just my mother.
Keep going.
Where we're going,
technology means very little.
50 bucks to a local guide can render
a multi-million dollar GPS obsolete,
as soon as you lose your connection
or your batteries go dead.
The stakes were too high
to take that chance.
Chief, I know that we have our orders, but
we are pretty fuckin' exposed out here.
I don't like it any more than you do,
but I ain't the one in charge right now.
As far as we're concerned you are.
Everything looks the same
to me out here.
At least back home, you had a
Quick-Stop every now and again.
- Where're you from, Cole?
- Tampa, Florida, born and raised.
- How about you?
- Chicago.
Cole, Stop the truck.
- What's he stopped the truck for?
- No idea.
What the hell's he doin'?
Why in the hell are we stopping?
- That's why,
- Son-of-a-bitch.
- Fox said this road was clear.
- It probably was...
Look, see that hole?
Looks like somebody's been doing
some transplanting..
Guess so.
Good call, Keynes. You may have just
saved us from having a very bad day.
Let me guess, we're gonna be
going through that canyon.
Yes, we are.
There are few places on Earth,
that are as unforgiving as this desert.
Whole armies,
from Alexander to the Soviets...
have paid the price for wanting
to make it their own...
I can only hope
we aren't as foolish.
Ah shit. Not good.
- Gotta be booby-trapped.
- Cole, back us the fuck outa here.
- Hold on, I'll go check it out.
- No, hold on.
RPG!
Ski's down.
Let me look at this. Chief,
Ski's bleedin' pretty bad.
Hold that right there, okay?
Chief, keep firing
on that ridge, man!
Cole, get your ass over here!.
When he's reloading, you're gonna
go and take those fuckers out!
Let's go!
Reload.
- Pete, Keynes, cover them.
- Okay.
Let's go.
I gotta bag you, baby.
You guys okay?
Let's go check the RPG position,
see who these guys are.
Are you sure
this is the spot, Pete?
Yes, I sighted the first one
just left of the gully here.
- Maybe you just wounded him.
- No way.
I saw him pop one
right in the melon.
One was a headshot,
the other was in the chest.
I saw 'em go down.
- Then where are the bodies?
- That's a good question.
These guys aren't known
for carrying off their dead.
I got you, okay..
I got you.
Fuck!
He took a frag to the heart,
I couldn't stop the bleeding.
You did everything you could.
We need to get him in the truck.
The only body from that entire
firefight was one of our own.
It doesn't make sense.
As far as I know, ghosts don't
shoot real rounds.
Serpent 76, slang 76.
Beast 92, over.
I say again Beast 92
requesting extract, break.
Reporting KIA, break.
How's it look?
Not good. Radiator took some hits.
- Can you fix it?
- Small holes maybe, but not these big ones.
This took a hit as well.
Okay, Abdul says that there's a road
that will take us round this mountain.
So it should be about half a day's
drive to our next checkpoint.
Checkpoint? Maybe you haven't heard,
Keynes, but we need to extract.
Okay, look, I'm sorry about Trinoski,
but cancelling this mission is not an option.
We have more than enough assets
to reach our objective.
- Assets?
- Hey, Wally.
I think Ski would have wanted
us to finish.
If we don't complete this mission,
then Ski died for nothing.
Cole, change it to a resupply.
Serpent 76, Serpent 76,
Beast 92, over.
Morale is low. Understandable.
We just have to stay focused, that's
what these guys are trained to do.
Any one of them would
tell you that they would...
rather die than be the last one
picked for a mission..
Where the hell
is that bloody chopper?
I don't know. They should've
called in by now.
I hope they didn't get taken down
on the other side of that canyon...
- by that ratpack we ran into.
- That would be a pile of suck.
Hold up. I think I hear it.
I don't hear anything.
I know I didn't just imagine it.
Hey, we got headlights.
Two o'clock.
Looks like a single vehicle.
And he's headed this way.
It can't be one of ours.
It wouldn't have the headlights on.
- It's probably enemy reinforcements.
- Alright, we need to get outta here.
- Hold on, wait. They're splitting up.
- What?
God-damn!
What just happened?
Must be Taliban ordnance
or something.
- Rockets maybe.
- I don't give a rat's ass what it was,
because in an hour or two
it's gonna be light,
and we need to be on the other
side of that mountain.
When we're there, we can recon
for an alternate LZ...
and try and figure
where the hell the bird is.
Come on. Let's mount up..
Those must have been the intelligent lights
Aban mentioned when he contacted me.
At least I know we're headed
in the right direction
- We should have taken horses.
- It's a little late for that now.
Goddammit.
We're overheating again.
This mountain is making the engine work
about 10 times harder than it's supposed to.
Pull off up here
and we'll let it cool down.
- We're overheating again.
- I'll pop the hood. Let it ventilate.
How are we doing on time?
We have to pick it up if we want to
make it off this mountain by dark.
- Look, we still have a ways to go.
- My kingdom for some donkeys.
What's wrong with him?
You see something?
We shouldn't have driven
across the valley.
- Our tracks are erased.
- What's up with our trusty guide?
Must be car sick.
Hey, Chief. I'm getting
no satellite reception.
The mountains are blocking us.
I can try again
once we get through the pass.
Wally, if you want this bitch to go any place,
you're gonna have to put some water in it.
How are we doing on water?
Jug and a half.
Twin dust devils.
Unusual, but not an Act of God.
Superstition is the real enemy.
It obscures the truth and that's
what we need right now.
Our water supply is low.
What was left after the firefight went
into the truck to get us this far.
I didn't count on having to wait for
a resupply, but we have no choice.
Serpent 76, Serpent 76,
Beast 92, come in.
It must be these rock walls or something.
I'm not getting a damn thing on the radio.
Shouldn't be too much longer now.
The weather's good.
When's his wife due?
I think sometime in January.
What's he up to?
Picked a strange time
to be stargazing.
Maybe he wants to show the boys back home
what a full moon in Afghanistan looks like.
Hey...
You guys hear that?
Yeah...
- Looks like it's showtime.
- Let's go.
See anything, chief?
No, not yet.
It sounds pretty close.
Get on the horn, Cole.
Dust-off 01, Dust-off 01,
Beast 92, radio check.
Dust-off 01, be advised.
You're coming in broken...
I think it's behind that ridge.
- I think he's over there.
- These canyon walls.
Dust-off 01, be advised.
You're coming in broken...
and unreadable.
Say again your last, over.
Goddamn!
I'm getting some kind
of interference.
Sounds like he's right above us.
KT, pop a flare.
What the fuck just happened?
Dust-off 01, Dust-off 01,
Beast 92.
Hey, he couldn't have crashed,
we'd have seen a fireball or heard something.
Dust-off 01, Dust-off 01,
Beast 92, are you guys okay?
Dammit!
Why the hell
are they on our frequency?
- I don't know.
- Hey! What's he sayin'? What'd he say?
- Abdul, do you understand this?
- No, I do not know.
It doesn't really matter at the moment,
that chopper has compromised our position.
- Yeah? He fuckin' disappeared.
- Cole, we don't know that.
We gotta keep moving.
We can set up camp up the mountain.
I don't think so. How're we supposed to
carry Ski's body up the mountain in the dark?
We don't. We cache his body and
call the TOC with another report.
- We can check on him in the morning.
- I don't know about that.
What would you like to do then, Degs?
We can't exactly sit here
and wait for the bus, can we?
We need to get up that hill and
set up a good, defensive position..
And if we have to engage these pricks,
I wanna be shooting down, not up.
The team is rattled,
though they don't admit it.
No point talking about,
what you can't control.
It's not possible, chief.
It's not fucking possible.
I've never given
a bad grid in my life.
Then why would they say they were
there and we were a no-show?
I don't know why
they'd say that, chief.
I checked and double-checked and
tripled-checked those numbers.
Well, someone fucked up.
Fuck!
Jesus Fuckin' Christ!
Guys get up here, check this out!
- Who was on first watch?
- I was.
- You see anything, hear anything?
- No, nothing.
I was on second.
I didn't see or hear anything either.
- This is some messed-up shit, chief.
- Somebody's trying to fuck with us.
Degs, Cole, I want you down that site.
See if you can find Ski's body.
Watch your asses
and get back here ASAP.
KT, I want us out of here in 15 mikes.
Abdul, you know where
there's water around here?
Now would be the time.
Because if we don't get some in the next
24 hours, we're gonna be in deep shit.
Fuck!
Fuckin' savages.
Sydney, Sydney, this is Bucks.
Chief! KT!
- Take a look at that.
- You gotta be kiddin' me.
- What'd you think that is?
- I have no idea.
I don't think we wanna
stick around to find out...
what's behind door number one.
Let's get outta here.
I get the feeling they knew
we would be coming.
Keynes, let's go.
The longer I'm out here,
the more I'm convinced that...
I won't find the loose nuke
when this is all over.
That little voice in my head is
just waiting to say I told you so.
Everybody hydrate.
Don't try saving that shit.
How far is this watering hole?
Using those two peaks
as a refence...
I would say about... 10 or
12 miles according to the map.
- I hope you're sure about this, Abdul.
- I'm sure.
It is a small oasis.
Farmers water their animals...
when taking them to the highlands.
Chief, you better have a look at this.
My compass is telling me
that that's north,
but unless the Sun started rising in
the south and nobody told me about it...
I'd say we're being hit by some pretty
heavy magnetic interference here.
Must be the iron in these rocks.
- How about the sat-phone?
- Still nothing.
Pete, you got anything on the GPS?
Got nothing.
Well, Abdul,
I guess you're driving.
- Pete,
- Yep.
- Point.
- Okay.
Move out.
These guys don't wanna admit it but Abdul
is the most valuable man on our team right now
We might as well be on another planet.
Any movement?
- No.
- Alright. We're gonna clear it.
Chief, we may be best advised
not to engage.
Our mission here is to kill terrorists.
Anything else is fuckin' paperwork.
Hello?
He can't speak.
Hello!
What'd he say?
I think something about being
a warrior, like you, it's hard...
some of the words I can
make out, not others...
Does he know Mohammed Aban?
No he don't.
Try and thank him for the water.
For filling our canteens.
You see what he's wearing
under his robe?
Looks like some kind
of uniform... Soviet?
It's British... from the
44th Regiment a Foot.
- I wonder where he got that?
- More like when.
The 44th Regiment no longer exists.
- The "Hill of Bone".
- What's the "Hill of Bone"?
In 1842 the British decided...
to move four and half thousend
troops through a pass near here,
along with 1000's of women and children and
any merchant that was willing to go along.
The 44th week out...
Legend has it that 16,000 people
went into that pass.
Only one man came back.
He claimed to have witnessed
Satan's Miracle.
It's just a legend.
So you're saying...
that uniform is from that unit?
- I don't see how that's possible.
- Is the insignia of that period?
They certainly match.
I'm gonna have a look
inside that cave.
Aban told me about a guardian.
Could this be him?
If so, who is he guarding?
Or what?
He's sitting right
in the middle of a hotspot.
Low levels of the signature
radiation everywhere.
He's been near it,
that I know for sure.
The boys back at home,
gonna want to see this.
Old bastard.
Jesus Christ!
Contact. Contact!
Holy shit... Jesus, Cole,
you ripped this guy up.
Cole... Cole! What happened?
I saw fighters.
5... maybe 6... He was
talking to 'em right here.
Fuckin' swords and black pyjamas.
They're fuckin' comin' right at me.
- Cole, tell me exactly what you saw.
- When I put my goggles on, I could see'm.
He was talking to a group of them... and
they were right here and they were armed.
They were armed...
I swear.
There's nothing we can do now.
We need to beat feet. If he's got any friends,
we need to be gone when they get here.
Come on, let's shake it up!
Let's go!
Cole, let's go.
You believe me right?
- You believe me right?
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
You can't let him there.
Keynes, take care of that.
Abdul we have to go.
It's too dangerous.
- Come on.
- How can you do this?
You Americans just kill him,
for no reason.
We didn't mean to.
It was an accident.
We have to bury him.
It is a bad luck for us...
we have to bury him.
Abdul, please listen, we have to go.
There could be enemies around, oaky?
Please, let's leave, come on.
An unsettled silence has fallen
over the group since we broke camp,
It's hard to determine
if the guys are more concerned...
about what Cole did...
or what he saw.
Hey... Pete! Take five.
Oh fuck. My stomach
feels like shit right now.
Wipe your face, there you go,
wipe your face.
You're just dehydrated.
- Here, start drinking this.
- Don't worry about it, Degs.
What the fuck? What're you doin'?
That's not funny, man.
I didn't do anything, man, I filled
this thing up with water last night.
Fuck, man.
What the hell's going on here?
- What the fuck?
- We filled this shit up.
- We have been cursed. I tell you.
- Abdul take us to the oasis, now.
No one likes to admit that they
may be losing control.
But it's even harder when you feel
that everyone around you, is too.
Fuck, this thing is worthless.
It's not even tracking.
That's fucked up, man?
We should be getting really
a good reading up here, right?
Maybe that thing
got shook to dead?
- Something is wrong.
- What? What is it, Abdul?
This is wrong.
I don't remember this valley.
Don't fuck with us, Abdul.
You said there was a spring up here.
Yes, but the terrain has changed.
So what's the deal?
- Abdul here is lost.
- Why am I not surprised?
This is... that peak...
which puts us on...
- on this ledge.
- Okay... okay, I'll buy that.
So, where is that?
- You got a bad map?
- It may not be 100 %.
But I find it hard to believe,
they lost an entire terrain feature.
This is... it makes no sense.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have paid this
guy up front, Keynes?
- No shit, man.
- He's going off memory, okay?
Yeah, I know, but we're paying
this guy to be our guide...
and we end up
on the fuckin' moon.
Chief, we may be dealing with some sunspot
interference or something like that.
It could take a day
or two to clear up.
Sunspots don't explain
sand in the canteens, man.
Alright. We're gonna find
somewhere to hunker down.
We got no business humping around
here in the daytime anyway. Let's go.
Maybe this is what it takes.
Getting completely lost first, before
you can find what you're looking for.
- You alright, man?
- No, man.
My stomach feels like it's eating
itself from the inside out.
Can you hand me my Cipro?
In the front bottom pocket in my bag.
- These?
- Yeah, thank you, man.
You think we're cursed?
No problem.
How'd you smoke that shit
with no water, man?
Easy... it's one of those
new-fangled waterwick cigars.
What're you doing, documenting
our demise, Agent Keynes?
Why, sergeant?
Do you plan on dying out here?
No soldier plans on dying.
Ain't this the shit?
Stuck out here in the middle...
of the Devil's Asshole,
working for the CIA.
So, what exactly is our objective,
Agent Keynes, huh?
Or should I say,
was our objective?
I explained this to you at the
briefing, sergeant.
Alright... Top secret.
Must be pretty fuckin' top secret for the
CIA to send one of their own out here, huh?
I mean, usually you boys just phone
in these clusterfuck operations...
and we come in afterwards and
clean up your mess.
I know a cover story
when I see one.
So whatever the real mission is here,
it had better damn well be worth it.
Because you don't wanna know
what I'm gonna do to you...
if I find out, Ski died just
to make you a better pay grade.
He died for his country,
not for me.
Kenny... lighten up, mate.
We're all in this shit together.
How d'you like that? You can always
count on an Aussie to watch your back.
Degs.
Degs, wake up.
- Degs!
- Let me go! Let me go! No!
No! Let go! Get off me!
Get off of me!
He's dreaming!
You're dreamin'!
- Jesus.
- Yeah, you alright?
Yeah?
Sit up.
- I'm okay... okay.
- You alright?
- Yeah, I'm okay... I'm okay.
- Cole, take care of him.
- Think it's dysentery?
- No, I'm shitting all by myself right now.
If you've got anything up
your sleeve, now would be the time.
I'm as thirsty as you are, chief.
Maybe this place is cursed.
Cover!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck is that?
- Too high to be a truck.
- Too quiet to be a helo.
Where's he going?
I don't see any bad guys.
KT, take Cole...
flank around these guys,
and see what's going on.
Check.
Pete, watch on six, to make
sure this isn't a diversion.
We don't want anybody
coming up our ass.
Okay, got it.
Stand by.
Go.
Motherfuckers!
Cease fire!
Everybody stay down.
Stay down!
Did you see that shit, chief?
That voice in my head
just cashed in.
Now, it's more important
than ever to document everything.
The Hill of Bones only had
one man's story.
But we'll have verifiable proof.
Look.
O-ring.
Jesus... is that all
that's left?
What'd you think it was?
I'm not sure.
It's definitely something
we haven't seen before.
The Taliban, they don't have
anything like that.
Had to be the Soviets.
Some experiment.
Chief, it's not a good place to be.
We should break camp.
Who knows when this thing's
coming back.
If we don't find water soon,
it ain't gonna matter...
- Hey, Degs
- Hey, Wally.
- We gotta move. You gonna be good to walk?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- What about him, though?
- Abdul, let's go. We're movin' out.
God dammit!
Abdul, did you not hear,me?
I said we're leaving.
We are going to die.
My grandfather was right.
- We should not have come here.
- Well, it's a little late for that now.
- Get your shit and let's go.
- I'm not going with you.
Don't be an idiot, Abdul, you break
with us now, you'll die out here.
- We are already dead.
- I'm so sick and tired of this shit.
Nihilism may be a way of life
for you people, but...
I'm not gonna put up with it,
when your with my team.
- Hamer!... What's wrong?
- You need to talk to your man, Keynes.
- He said he was...
- Abdul, no!
Crazy son-of-a-bitch
- It's not like he was doing us much good.
- We needed him!
For what? he's been leading us
on a wild goose chase...
- I'm telling you, we needed him.
- Oh, really?
Well it certainly
wasn't to find water.
Or Aban for that matter.
It's more than that.
Why don't you tell us just what
the fuck 'more' means.
- It's on a need-to-know basis, chief.
- You gotta be fucking joking me.
Who needs to know more than we do?
Hey, motherfucker! I just lost three men
on this goddamned goose chase of yours!
I wanna know what the fuck is going on.
Tell us what's happening.
What was that thing last night?
- We don't know.
- We?
- What, you and those pinheads at Langley?
- Look... chief...
all I can tell you is that I'm working
for a special group inside the Company.
That's fuckin' beautiful.
If I find out we're out here dying,
while you go on a little ghost hunt,
I'll put a round in you myself.
- We all have our orders to follow, chief.
- Well, maybe you haven't heard...
dead men don't follow orders.
I wanna tell them.
In a way, I need to tell them.
I search my mind through all
the protocol, all the secrets...
and ask myself, what good does it do
to die with this locked in my head?
What will the powers that be do
with the information I'm sending them?
Mohammed Aban knows.
He's always known.
And is he alive?
Keynes, what is it?
Stand by.
What is it?
You see something?
- I saw Mohammed Aban.
- You kidding me?
Look.
- What the hell is that thing?
- I don't know.
But I think it's what killed your men, chief.
It's what I've been looking for.
It's why I'm here.
I don't understand.
Is it some kind of weapon?
We don't know.
Something Soviet?
Hey... we can't fight this thing
if you don't tell us what it is.
Okay, sergeant.
Get your guys.
How long have you been keeping
an eye out for this thing?
Since we were here in the Eighties,
when we were training the Mujahideen.
We... huh, tried to use this area,
to... set up training camps.
But we found
that most of it was dead.
- What d'you mean, dead?
- Nothing worked.
Radios, compasses, anything with
an electromagnetic transmission.
So my group began to study it.
But we couldn't figure it out.
Then in 2000... we saw...
something, an image...
- a satellite image.
- What did you see?
- Have you ever heard of the Vimaanas?
- No, I haven't.
I have. Quite common in East Asian
folklore... especially in India.
It's kinda like a... UFO,
but in the shape of a triangle.
Alexander the Great even documented
seeing them attacking his troops here.
- He referred to them as Flaming Shields.
- So this is a fuckin' UFO hunt!
No, no, chief. This was identified.
There is evidence.
We believe it to be a weapon
of unimaginable power...
and that is why you and
your men were recruited.
What good is it going to do if we find
the thing and get killed in the process?
Not exactly a stellar recon, is it?
Okay, look... this is my
connection to the outside world.
What?... Your camera?
What are you talking about, Keynes?
I've been relaying video optically during
our mission, using this laser uplink.
Terrific.
Now you tell us.
So you people have been following
us through this entire thing.
You probably know
where we are right now.
Chief, it's the only way we
can obtain verifiable evidence.
We had no way of knowing
if any of us would return.
- This is insane.
- This is a fuckin' suicide mission!
There's a big difference
between suicide and sacrifice.
Truth! That's the fuckin'
difference, you piece of shit!
This is bigger than
you and me, okay? Just relax.
I should put a fuckin' round in you
for what you've done to my men!
- Your men were patriots, chief.
- They were my friends!
Fuck!
That's enough!
It doesn't have to be like this, chief.
I'm not the enemy.
You might as well be..
I'm sorry, sergeant.
I'm sorry.
I'm willing to die for my country,
but this...
I don't know if this is
life or death.
Maybe it's something in-between.
- Keynes? Keynes, get up!
- What is it?
- The chief... he's gone.
- How long?
I don't know. He left his rifle.
I don't know why he'd do that.
Well, we have to assume
he's not coming back.
- How's Degetau?
- He's not good.
Look, can you at least
use your uplink...
to tell whoever's at the
other end to come and get him?
- They won't come.
- Take a look at him!
It's not like he's of any use
on this mission.
We are the mission, sergeant.
Don't you see that? Our objective
is to find these Vimaanas...
their objective, is to see what
happens when we do.
- The end justifies the means.
- Yeah? Well, that's the problem, isn't it?
Is that we never
seem to reach the end.
We gotta keep going.
- Is that what I think it is?
- It's the Hill of Bones.
Unbelievable.
- Feels like we're in Hell out here.
- Close enough.
I have no doubt that this is the
footprint we saw from space.
Man's fate piled up in an
ancient heap in front of us.
Is this a message, a warning?
Am I the messenger?
- What's wrong?
- Look.
My God...
It's them!
Oh God! Oh, fuck!
We gotta get outta here.
How are we supposed to fight
something like that?
Well, we don't.
I gotta go, okay?
Before it gets too dark.
You late for a meeting?
Motherfucker.
- I can't carry you, Vince.
- you better get goin' then.
You're a good soldier.
Your country will be proud.
My country
will never know who I am.
Goodbye.
Something is telling me
to keep walking.
The search for water,
or something else.
I really don't know any more.
I seem to know the direction,
but not the destination.
Am I being led here, or is it a
pitiful attempt to die with dignity?
Is there even
such a thing any more?
Go to your God like a soldier.
He will save us all.
Okay, Stacey, let's start with
when your husband left.
Can you tell us anything about
this mission he was on?
Um...
It was a just little over
a year ago... last November.
He didn't tell me much about his
missions, as he was in the CIA.
But... um, I do know
that he was in Afghanistan...
and he was looking
for one person in particular.
Your husband was part of a special
group within the CIA, correct?
Yes, that's what he told me.
Do you know of anyone
else who is part of that group?
Well, I know he was meeting
a... a team out there...
and... that they were going
to help him look for Mohammed.
But I don't know who they are.
Nobody seems to know anything.
I don't get it. How can they
just forget about him like this?
He dedicated his life
to his country.
That journal you're holding...
is that the only evidence
you have of him during this time?
Yes... It was sent to me
a few weeks after he left.
I know it's his. Even though most of
it's in code, I recognose his writing.
I just wanna know
if he's still alive.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org