Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
for her activities
in college.
I didn't hear about this.
Well, it's, uh...
It's, um...
It'll be in...
tomorrow afternoon's edition.
Just in time for the congressman
to make his statement...
and just in time for it to stick in
the minds of Americans over the weekend.
Wh... What's the source?
Where'd they get the story?
- Unnamed sources
close to the investigation.
- I see.
Al.
- Al!
- Yes?
We can, um... Let's...
Let's dot the I's, cross the T's
on this one later.
All right, thank you.
I, uh...
I think I have some self-righteous
indignation coming my way.
Well, is there any truth
whatsoever to the story?
- There will be an investigation.
- She's gonna have the truth on her side.
- She's gonna deny it and
make us all look like fools.
- Let her.
Let her deny just that part
of the story.
- Hold here.
- What? Oh.
That's all right.
I can do that myself. Yeah.
Thank you.
- America Live is not in
the circus business.
- Pete's always fair.
Should I hear anything in this?
You're gonna be vice president.
- You'll talk about
legitimate issues of concern.
- Right.
Where is the senator's monitor?
There is no monitor for her.
She'll hear Pete in the earpiece.
That is a piece of shit.
We talked about this, Ray.
If Peter's gonna be able to see her,
she has to be able to see him.
- He's got a sensory advantage over her.
- You wanna pull her?
I'm not talking about pulling her.
I'm just saying it's bullshit.
She was just great in the hearings
today. Cool and collected.
- Steve Poullet.
- Hi.
Should I hear anything?
Oh, I got it. Okay, great.
Oh, it's that one.
Yeah, I know.
Can't hear...
Yeah, right, got it.
Okay, I've got
the intro now.
Thank you for having me, Peter.
Sure, that'd be fine.
Well, it has been
a taxing experience...
but if we're forced to take
the voters out of the equation...
I think that the vetting system
by simple necessity must be arduous.
Mmm.
I have to plead motherhood
on that one, Pete...
but I not only served
on the Foreign Relations Committee...
I sponsored the Hanson-Fineman Bill
which readjusted the War Powers Act...
to allow the executive to respond
to state-sponsored terrorism...
like that of Iraq, Libya,
North Korea, for instance.
But rather than boring you
with my résumé...
I'd rather answer your questions
on specific issues of foreign policy.
I suppose I could ask you, Mr. Crenshaw,
how you'd feel in the same situation.
Why would I answer that for you?
Sorry. It's simply a privacy issue.
Look, I won't address issues
of sexuality in a hearing room...
or on national television
or anywhere else for that matter.
- Where's the control room
for America Live?
- Down the hall.
Excuse me.
The control room for America Live?
- Where is the fucking control room?
- Right down there.
Fuck!
Down here, down here, down here!
Don't tell me
we're gettin' sandbagged!
We're getting sandbagged! I knew
you couldn't trust this fucking guy!
Senator Hanson,
do you recognize Mr. Poullet?
Un, no. I don't have a monitor,
so I can't see him.
The truth is,
Lainey and I had that one incident.
I don't believe we ever
saw each other again after that.
To her credit, she was very drunk
when she had sex...
with my friends,
uh, my brothers and I.
A sandbag is what it is.
He's fucking your friend.
He has obviously infiltrated
your show.
Mrs. Hanson, you still have not taken
a stand on the accuracy of this report.
It's very accurate,
and those photos are accurate too.
We had them on the frat house
bulletin board for months.
We called that
"Life in the Sex Laine."
- What are we gonna do now?
- We're gonna sue him.
I will not dignify those remarks
or your questions with a response.
Good evening.
The guy's a jerk. We're never gonna
put our people on that show again.
Some asshole called in
and made this idiot claim.
Hell, they've gotta investigate.
The whole situation's
a son of a bitch.
I would like to start
by saying...
that much has been made of the reports
in the press of an investigation...
into the possible...
possible, I say again...
criminal behavior
on the part of the nominee.
This committee will wait
for a report from the FBI...
before taking this matter up.
However, I'll once again afford
the nominee an opportunity to respond.
I, too, will wait for the FBI report
before responding.
Madam Senator.
Tell us a little bit about your family.
You have a son.
Mm-hmm. Yes, I have
one six-year-old boy, Timothy.
That's a very nice age.
Now, I see here
that when you...
had Timothy,
you were absent from your duty...
for a few months'
maternity leave.
- It's the right of every mother
to be able to take maternity...
- Paid maternity leave.
Yes. I don't believe we should penalize
our citizens for having children.
I think I'm on safe ground saying that
valuing motherhood is quite nonpartisan.
- Um, were you to get pregnant again...
do you plan
to take maternity leave?
Um, I've not given that
any consideration.
No? Are you still able
to bear children?
Yes, I am...
I believe, yes, I am.
Yet you have not given
this matter any consideration.
Perhaps that means...
No, strike that.
Madam Senator...
let us assume you ascended
to the presidency...
and you were to have a child
during your term.
Would you cede your duties
to your vice president and for how long?
Mr. Chairman, would the chair
expect to have the designate
assure this committee...
that she would have her tubes tied
before she assume office?
- Mr. Chairman, I humbly
request a point of order.
- You will be afforded one.
- With all due respect...
- You will be afforded one
when I am finished.
The truth is that while we have
not put a seal on the concept
of having another child...
my husband and I practice
birth control.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I would
now like to...
enter the arena of loyalty.
Loyalty is a revered quality
among vice presidents. Would you agree?
- Yes, very much so. Yes.
- Yet you chose to officially move...
from the Republican to the
Democratic party when you left
the House to run for the Senate.
I view switching parties as a testament
to my loyalty to my country.
I felt that the Republican party
had shifted from the ideals that
I cherished through my youth.
As a Republican,
did you ever...
vote along party lines
but against your own beliefs?
No, never.
- You still believe in
every vote you made?
- Yes.
- Including your vote
to impeach President Clinton?
- Yes, I do.
That was an issue of fairness.
The president,
as commander in chief, stood by...
while several military officers,
including candidates for the
chairman of the Joint Chiefs...
were prosecuted for adultery
or were not permitted...
to advance their careers.
I am opposed to making adultery,
or even lying about it,
a crime in our armed forces.
But while it is a law,
it should be enforced
without consideration of rank...
even if that rank
is commander in chief.
Perhaps the senator is unaware
that commander in chief
is not actually a military rank.
I am aware of that.
What I think we can say
of President Clinton is that he
was not guilty but responsible.
"Not guilty but responsible."
I am...
I like that.
I, uh, I-I may, uh... I may use that.
- If you wish, you can go ahead.
- Thank you.
When...
When considering you
for the vice presidency...
we must also consider your worthiness
as commander in chief.
- Would you agree?
- Yes, I do.
In that case, given your feelings
on the matter...
have you ever
committed adultery?
- No, I have not.
- No?
You're quite sure? Madam Senator, you
understand that, uh, you are under oath.
Yes, I understand that, between the two
of us, I'm the one that's under oath.
When you guys go before
the Antitrust Committee,
don't you want Hank on your side?
Sure, but not at any price.
Last time we spoke,
you were sitting where you are now.
Hank was sitting where Len is.
You started telling him
what a shame it would be...
if the refrigeration systems
on the trucks went out.
Hank's a hothead,
and he took that as a threat.
If we were threatening him,
he'd know it.
That's what I thought,
but now we have some massaging to do.
Hank's gotta be treated
with kid gloves.
- Senator Hanson?
Congressman Webster's here to see you.
- Sorry. Yep?
- Guess we got our ten minutes.
- Okay, send him in.
No, I want to resolve this.
I do. Just give me a few minutes.
If you want something to drink,
Jerry will take care of you.
- We're gonna get back into this?
- We will. We will.
Senator, you want me to sit in?
Make sure the congressman's
clear on everything?
We'll be fine. Won't we, Mr. Webster?
We'll be all right. Thanks.
Proud of yourself?
So, what can I do for you,
Mr. Webster?
I'm sure you're wondering
why I'm here.
I think you're here because you want
to know why I'm not fighting back.
Because despite it all, you've got
some odd sense of fair play.
You're kicking my ass.
It's gone from feeling like
easy pickings to out-and-out bullying.
I feel like there should be
some back and forth between us,
you and the committee.
I'll give you back and forth on Social
Security, relations with Israel...
on the Dow Jones, the census,
almost everything, but not this.
No, not my personal life.
It's just nobody's business.
That's not what the people
will tell you; the people will
tell you it is their business...
that you're setting standards
of morality for their children.
Especially their girls.
Have you ever heard
of Isaac Lamm?
- Isaac Lamm? No.
- He was the first one
to come before HUAC...
the House Un-American
Activities Committee.
He was also the first one to name names,
first to cooperate with the government.
The dominoes fell from there.
Careers crushed,
families destroyed.
Just imagine, Mr. Webster,
if Mr. Lamm had just said,
"Fuck you," to the committee.
Imagine how much harder
he would've made it for them.
Are you accusing the committee
of sexual McCarthyism?
Well, it's not necessary
to make the accusation.
Oh, I just can't respond
to the committee's lightly
veiled accusations...
because it's not okay
for them to be made.
Or maybe you can't respond
because the answers you have
to give are too embarrassing.
You know what?
You're young.
That's okay. That's okay.
I'm gonna choose to be amused
by your naiveté, give you
the benefit of the doubt.
I'm gonna spell it out
for you even more clearly.
If I were a man,
nobody would care...
how many sexual partners
I had in college.
And if it's not relevant for a man,
it's not relevant for a woman.
Jerry, send the folks back in, please.
I gotta finish this up.
He's not a bad man.
He believes in what he's doing.
There's an odd sort
of integrity there.
But in this business,
with so much at stake...
it's not enough to believe
in yourself, you have to be right.
This is an ideological rape
of all women.
- Timmy, that's a little too high.
- Okay, Mommy.
Thank you, sweetie.
Well, then I'll survive it
for all of us.
Tomorrow morning Congressman Marshall
is gonna ask you questions.
He's going to hit you
with abortion.
I promise you that Shelly will find
some way to call you a baby killer.
We're ready for him.
Our position papers are first-rate.
- Every one of them.
- You let him finish.
Then you look him in the eye
and you ask him...
"Mr. Runyon, 20 years ago
your wife Maggie had an abortion.
Do you think her a murderer?"
He's a hypocrite.
No, he's not.
Shelly has no idea.
Are you saying you would appoint
a Supreme Court justice...
based on his being pro-choice?
Mr. Marshall, the vice president
does not appoint Supreme Court justices.
Should you succeed the president
or even advise the president?
I would be inclined,
though not without flexibility...
to disregard any man or woman who is
pro-life from serving on the High Court.
So you would allow a personal political
belief to enter into such a decision?
Abortion isn't
a constitutional issue.
The fine ladies and gentlemen
who serve on the Supreme Court...
which is now stacked
with right-wing appointees...
have no business deciding whether women
have to resort to back-alley abortions...
You mean they have no business
deciding whether women have
a license to commit murder.
Mr. Marshall, your time has expired.
Sir, if the distinguished "gentlelady"
from Ohio would answer the question...
I think the lady has made clear
her propensity for abortion.
- Come on, Mr. Runyon!
- Mr. Lewis, you do not
have speaking privileges.
Mr. Chairman, I find your term,
"propensity for abortion"...
misrepresentative of my position.
I have a propensity
for a woman's right to choose.
- To abort a child!
- A fetus.
To kill a baby
as it grows in the womb.
Personally, Senator...
I do not believe that it is
the right of our citizens...
to... to butcher
a defenseless human being simply...
simply as a matter of choice.
At the risk of my own future,
I tell you this:
If you support the right...
of a woman to choose,
you are supporting...
nothing less than
a-a-a holocaust of the unborn.
Mr. Chairman,
are you calling me...
I believe my position
on this issue is clear.
Yes, madam,
it most certainly is.
God, I love this game.
When she tries to tell me
how to do it, I do it my way.
Then she comes back and changes it
afterwards, and that way...
Jeez.
Good one, sir.
You're an all-weather golfer,
I see.
What kind of stick
you using there?
- It's a putting stick.
- Right, putting stick.
When I asked for you last week,
they said you were in Vegas.
- Business, sir.
- Vegas is business?
I did blow
a roll of quarters.
Will you excuse us?
- How's that cough doing?
- Aah.
That's her casino account balance.
She offered to take her sorority sister
to Vegas, her treat.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth so help you God?
I do.
Please state your name
for the record.
Cynthia C-H-A-R-L-T-O-N Lee.
Thank you.
Please be seated.
We will start the questioning
with Mr. Skakle.
Mr. Skakle, the five-minute rule
is in effect.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Miss Lee.
Miss Lee, hello. I'm over here.
Thank you for joining us.
Now, you are under subpoena,
is that correct?
Yes.
- Miss Lee, could you speak
directly into the mike?
- Yes.
I understand you're nervous, but believe
me when I tell you you're among friends.
Miss Lee, you are not married.
No... No.
- No, I'm not.
- But you once were.
I was married
to William Hanson.
- Who is now married to the nominee.
- Yes.
He married Laine after our divorce.
It was about seven years ago.
Divorce. Right.
I've read your divorce papers.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that by the way is tab 76.
They cite
irreconcilable differences.
Could you tell us, what were
those irreconcilable differences?
I can't really pinpoint them.
- Was your husband
physically violent to you?
- No.
Did you have financial
disagreements or disagreements
over how to raise your kids?
We didn't have children.
- Were there infidelities?
- Yes. There was one.
Is it safe to say that this infidelity
precipitated the divorce?
Miss Lee, please answer
the question verbally. Was that a yes?
Yes, it was.
It was a yes.
- Did you, ma'am, have the affair?
- No.
- It was your husband then?
- Yes.
Will...
Will was in charge...
of Laine Billings's
first senatorial campaign.
He was with her all the time.
Are you suggesting the senator,
the nominee, had an affair
with your husband?
- Once again, Miss Lee...
- I'm sorry. Yes. Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Did the nominee know
Mr. Hanson was married?
Laine was my friend.
My good, good friend.
Miss Lee, would you explain
to this committee as you
did in your deposition...
how you discovered
that the nominee was involved...
in an affair
with your husband?
Yes. Um...
On the night of the elections,
I was at home.
I had the flu.
I was watching TV, watching Laine
about to make her acceptance speech.
I was very sad
that I couldn't be there.
It was a triumph
for Laine and my husband.
She was up at the podium.
Will was by her side.
He was holding her hand
in victory.
On the other side
of Laine...
she was just sort of clasping
that person's hand.
But with Will...
their hands were interlaced.
It was odd
that I noticed it, but...
Um, my doorbell rang.
I answered the door,
and there was a gentleman there...
dressed very nicely,
he had a yellow tie on.
He had papers for me.
- Papers? I'm sorry.
- Separation papers.
Since the committee
chose to humiliate a private woman
in the most public possible setting...
I would like to apologize
to her alike...
and I will also do so privately
when she allows me to do so.
Um, what I did to Miss Lee
was wrong.
It was not done out of malice.
Indeed the opposite.
Um...
love is an involuntary reflex,
and I fell victim to it.
Um, I deeply regret
causing Cynthia pain...
and it is especially saddening
for me because...
of how close we once were.
And whether or not the affair
that Will and I had...
should have any bearing on my assuming
office is for the committee to decide.
I dare not assume that I have
the objective wisdom to make
that determination. Thank you.
- Senator,
are you suggesting the public...
- Okay, she's had a long day.
You know what she's going through.
Come on, come on.
She was your best friend.
Runyon deposed Will's
ex-wife today, and, uh...
she stated that Will and I
had had an affair...
She saw her fucking holding hands,
interlocked fingers with this gal...
and she knew
that she'd been fucking him.
That's what she said.
- I'm sorry.
- It's a bad beat.
I'm not sure that I get
the point of all this.
- You said under oath
that you never committed adultery.
- That's right.
- You perjured yourself.
- I didn't commit adultery.
- You were fucking Will
when he was married.
- All right.
Even the most loose definition
of committing adultery
would not include that.
Goddamn it, she's right.
You're right.
In order for it to be
committing adultery, she'd have
to be married at the time.
You're nitpicking
in reverse now.
Your husband may have been
an adulterer. You're not. Fine.
What you are is a sex-crazed,
home-wrecking machine.
The female Warren Beatty.
Runyon knows
that you're clean of the perjury...
but he's got the world thinking you're
something out of a bad soap opera.
You've goddamned crystallized
the difference between being
guilty and being responsible.
Are you asking me
to step down, sir?
No, it's not gonna be
that easy for you, and it's not
gonna be that easy for them.
They caught you being
a human being. That's all.
I'll die before Shelly Runyon
checkmates me.
I think the president's trying to say
the Sitting Bull routine isn't working.
- The Sitting Bull routine?
- No!
Fight back.
Show them Laine Hanson isn't gonna take
their shit. Take the fight out of 'em.
- What's the process?
- Confess.
- Confess?
- Yeah, confess.
- Confess.
Confess to the gang-bang.
Confess to all of it.
- Look what it did
for Clinton with Flowers.
- Play it any way you want.
It didn't hurt his numbers.
It improved his numbers.
Show indignation about how a man
would never have to go through
hell for having done this.
Confess and demonstrate
to the young women of America...
how such sexual impropriety
can ruin their lives.
Confess and preach about the dangers
that alcohol can bring to you.
For God's sakes, just confess!
I understand, Kermit, truly.
I understand, and you know what?
It's really nobody's business.
Well, it is
our fucking business!
Listen, Laine...
I don't care who you fucked...
and how many times
in how many positions...
as long as it doesn't threaten
the administration.
You can be cavalier
on your own dime.
Mr. President.
I am fully prepared
to step down...
but my personal life...
and my past...
are just that.
But I will do
whatever you say.
Show them why Laine Hanson is my nominee
with your closing statement.
Mr. Chairman...
ladies and gentlemen
of the committee:
Uh, remarkably enough, it seems
that I have some explaining to do.
So...
let me be absolutely clear.
I stand for a woman's right
to choose.
I stand for the elimination
of the death penalty.
I stand for a strong
and growing armed forces...
because we must stomp out genocide
on this planet...
and I believe that that
is a cause worth dying for.
I stand for seeing every gun
taken out of every home. Period.
I stand for making
the selling of cigarettes
to our youth a federal offense.
I stand for term limits
and campaign reform.
And, Mr. Chairman, I stand for
the separation of church and state...
and the reason that I stand
for that is the same reason that
I believe our forefathers did.
It is not there to protect religion
from the grasp of government...
but to protect our government
from the grasp of religious fanaticism.
I may be an atheist...
but that does not mean I do not
go to church; I do go to church.
The church I go to is the one
that emancipated the slaves...
that gave women
the right to vote.
It gave us every freedom
that we hold dear.
My church is this very chapel
of democracy that we sit in together...
and I do not need God to tell me
what are my moral absolutes.
I need my heart,
my brain and this church.
Get in there, get in there.
Oh, shoot!
Come on, come on, come on!
- Senator? Oh...
- Hello, Freshman.
Senator, I just wanted
to steal a couple of seconds.
What? See what whores do
on their time off?
Listen,
I know the things I've done.
They may not have been nice
or considered politically savvy...
but they have served the greater good
and they have been honest.
Okay.
Look, I know
you're not a whore.
- I'm not gonna talk about it.
- I know. You're not talking about it.
Somebody else
has come forward.
Somebody else from the night
of the incident sent me this letter.
They didn't send it to me.
They sent it to the committee.
I just happen to be in charge
of all the correspondence.
I don't think you can keep quiet
about what's in there.
Mr. Runyon has a copy,
and now so do you.
I beg you, Senator,
to deal with this.
- How long is this flight?
- About an hour and 40 minutes.
POTUS is scheduled to address
the American Legion on the third.
- American Legion? Who approved that?
- I don't know.
- I thought he had
the D.A.R. Dinner that night.
- We have a five-hour window.
- Hey, Chuck.
- Hey, Kermit.
Did you get the AP reports?
- What's that?
- POTUS's poll numbers are down 23%.
- And Hanson's in the low 30s.
- Get in there.
I'll talk to you in a minute.
- Are you Willomina?
- Yes, sir.
You asked to see me?
- Is this your handiwork?
- Yes, sir.
- How many people have seen this?
- I gave it only to the director.
- And who have you talked to about this?
- Nobody.
Not a husband? Boyfriend?
- Grandma in Kalamazoo?
- No, sir. Nobody.
- Keep it that way.
- Yes, sir.
You did a good job,
Special Agent.
Sir! Uh, sir, I just... I just wanted
to ask, ask you. Um, well...
Are you gonna dump her?
Sir, this may be really,
really inappropriate...
but if that's what you guys
are thinking...
Please, you can't do it.
She's hope.
Hope that the standards...
That there is no double standard.
Hope that the goals
can be the same.
You know what?
You're goddamn right.
That was absolutely inappropriate.
Robertson.
I wouldn't take it too hard.
It's not exactly fair
when six foxes and one chicken...
are voting on
what to have for dinner.
Well, that's not
playing fair. I'll give you that.
You want an oatmeal cookie?
- Trevor?
- I'm getting them, sir.
I find these giant raisins...
Well, you'll see.
Taste like grapes.
Shelly, you really made
a mess of things for me.
You sure did clobber me.
Isn't it possible, sir,
that I was... that I was acting...
- in the best interests
of the United States?
- No.
It's not possible.
That's what pisses me off. It's all
about retribution for Hartford.
Thank you, Trevor.
That'll be all.
- Go ahead. Try this. It's wonderful.
- No.
I may have taken the presidency
from you, but you one-upped me.
You took away my legacy.
I look at her and I see someone who
has proven the capacity for disloyalty.
Or the capacity
for seeing the light.
We're both sticking
to our guns.
The difference is...
mine are loaded.
Look, it doesn't matter, does it?
She's not being confirmed.
We can talk for days
about greatness and leadership...
but Laine Hanson
will not be confirmed.
I have seven from your side
who are giving her the ax.
Oh, indeed, the ax?
We can go through
the process of a vote.
You can waste time...
and suffer the humiliation,
or... or we can just move on.
- There's a lot of good folk
to choose from.
- Who?
Who can I be certain
you'll confirm?
The man you wanted in the first place:
Jack Hathaway.
Shelly.
Good man.
Okay, Shelly...
I'll give you Governor Jack Hathaway,
but I wanna make damn sure...
- you'll give him a smooth ride.
- My word. There's a reason
they call me Honest Shell.
Irony, Shelly.
I want an insurance policy.
I want a piece of the rock.
I wanna make sure...
you're not gonna pull
some kind of baloney out of your hat...
and make a mockery
of my administration again.
Listen. This is
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna ask Mrs. Hanson and
Mr. Hathaway up to the Oval Office...
before the D.A.R. Banquet
tomorrow night.
I want you there as well,
but, Shelly...
before then, I need you
to marry yourself to this guy.
I need you to make a public statement
that makes his sinking your sinking.
- Otherwise...
- But I'm not sure I can...
Let's make this confirmation
fast and furious.
- Help me save face on this one.
- Okay.
Oh, man. Mr. Runyon,
prefer I take you around back?
- No, I'll be fine.
- Yes, sir.
How do you respond to the rumors
that Mrs. Hanson has withdrawn her name?
That is a rumor
I've not yet heard.
Have you heard about the possibility
of Governor Hathaway...
- returning to the list
of vice presidential...
- Governor Hathaway is a fine man.
Will he have a smoother ride
than Mrs. Hanson?
Let me go on record
as saying...
that in my opinion there is
no man alive... no Democrat alive...
who could bring...
more integrity
to the office of the vice presidency.
I would stake my career...
on Governor Hathaway's, uh,
smooth and efficient confirmation.
As for Laine Hanson...
- Got everybody, Glenda?
- Yes, sir. He says you can
go in whenever you're ready.
- Great. Hello, Jack.
- Kermit.
- Fiona, you're looking
particularly fetching this evening.
- Thank you, sir.
- I believe this is the first one
of these affairs for you, right?
- Yes.
- My 37th.
- You look great.
- Hello, Shelly.
- Newman.
Everybody would understand if you
wanted to delay for two weeks.
I'm not sure I could stomach
another two weeks.
Oh, Jack.
- Jerry. Good.
- How are you?
Mr. Hanson.
- Gentlemen. Jack.
- Mr. President.
There he is! Shelly!
Hello, Mr. President.
Uh, you know what?
Before we get started...
I can't stomach the idea...
of touching that chichi food we always
get served at these state dinners.
- Glenda?
- Yes, sir?
Could we put together a grilled
cheese sandwich? Muenster on rye.
Right away.
Oh, sorry. Where are my manners?
You guys want anything?
- No, thank you, sir.
- Shelly?
Jesus, uh, Shell,
those were some...
very nice things
you said about Jack.
Jack, there. I understand
that you two have never met.
- Laine Hanson, Jack Hathaway.
- It's a pleasure.
- I'm quite in awe of you.
- Thank you.
Mr. President?
- Yes, Glenda?
- Sir, the kitchen's
all out of Muenster.
Really? Wow.
Well, um, let's get on that.
We don't want the wheels
coming off the wagon.
This is, uh...
This is quite an event.
Here we are. Quite a sad event.
- Mr. President, if I may?
- Yes, please.
A short while ago,
you told me that you thought
I might be the future of the party.
I know that these
are tough times...
and the future is uncertain...
but I'm very pleased to think
that I might be able to help
make things a little smoother.
The future, yes.
Well, there is one thing...
quite certain
about the future.
- What's that?
- Sir?
- You have the right to remain silent...
- Fred.
- I have to read him his rights.
- Fred, the governor,
he knows his rights.
You know your rights, right, Jack?
You don't have to humiliate him.
You fucked up, buddy.
- The girl, do you know what she was?
- What girl?
- The girl in the river.
- She was a paralegal.
- Before that.
- She was military. Fourteen Golf.
We found the money that you put
in her account at the Bellagio.
- Two hundred thousand dollars.
- And that ad in...
- Soldier of Fortune.
- Yeah, Soldier of Fortune.
I don't mind confessing,
I am at a total fucking loss.
Shelly, he paid her
to go off the fucking bridge.
He paid her to save her.
Jesus Christ.
- Shelly, maybe I...
- You shouldn't say anything.
- Jack, look, we respect...
- You're going to have
to come with me now.
Fred. We respect you.
We're trying to make this go
as smoothly as it possibly can.
I know you meant no harm.
- Hell, I don't even know...
What would the charge be?
- Negligent homicide.
Oh, negligent homicide.
Sir.
- Good luck, Mrs. Hanson.
- You too.
Who doesn't want
a shortcut to greatness?
Oh, it's a goddamn shame
about the Muenster.
Mr. President.
Yeah, Shelly?
You set me up.
Just this once.
For the record, sir...
I find what you did
to be manipulative...
Mr. Chairman, let's just say...
"I'm guilty
but not responsible," hmm?
Shelly, you needn't worry
about us exposing the fact...
that you leaked all that horrible
material about Laine on the Internet.
We know that you were
just following your heart.
Yeah, Hartford,
it was a tough one.
But... Well, it doesn't
make a difference.
- She still is who she is.
- Yes, she is.
And you are who you are.
You're still coming
to the banquet, aren't you?
Because I'd love to see you.
Is your wife in town?
May I introduce
tonight's honoree, Miss Barr?
- Congressman Webster.
- Honor, madam.
And, Congressman,
you know the senator, of course.
We go about two feet back.
I asked them to have you seated
at my table tonight.
- If you want to break bread with me.
- Absolutely.
- Don't eat all the hors d'oeuvres.
- Shark steak sandwiches?
Yeah. Save me some.
Last time I shared one of these,
it was with the president of Russia.
Or maybe it was the kid
who won Wimbledon for the second time.
I'm honored, sir.
You're not supposed to inhale.
Maybe that's the first thing
you should've told me.
Recognize this affidavit?
Where'd you get that, sir?
Where you got yours.
Where Shelly Runyon got his.
From Mr. Webster.
He may not know
his right from his left...
but apparently
he does know right from wrong.
I understand you
even less now, Senator.
- You are an enigma wrapped in a riddle.
- Wrapped in a riddle.
Watch your step, Senator.
What if I told you that I'm just
busting at the seams...
to know what exactly
happened that night...
to hear the truth
from your own lips?
Totally off the record.
Not between the president
and the senator, but between
the president and Laine.
Better than that.
Between Jackson and Laine.
Well, I had just turned 18
when I got to college...
and I had never been
away from home, not really.
And I was immediately...
I was immediately lonely.
And that's when
the sorority kicked in.
I wanted them,
they wanted me.
I was the daughter of the governor,
for chrissake.
- True blue catch.
- I guess so.
And like any other sorority,
they have an initiation, a rush.
And they have this girl, this woman
that Runyon deposed, Patty LaVamere.
She runs the sorority,
and she gives it to me straight:
If I wanna be in, I have to go to
their brother fraternity and have sex...
with two boys.
What a coup for them, huh?
Daughter of a big-time Republican
doing a frat house?
But I say,
"There's no chance."
- The whole thing was pretty hairy.
- I bet.
But six beers later,
I'm talking a different tune...
so off we go
to the frat house.
Half the girls were there,
about a zillion boys.
They're cheering my name.
"Laine! Laine! Laine!"
And I'm just stumbling around.
Eventually I just say,
"I'm gonna go for it."
If getting laid is a common initiation
for boys in the frat...
then why not for us, right?
- You're asking me?
- No, I'm not.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry. Go ahead.
That's okay.
So they send me
into this room.
It's dark and dim.
There are these two guys.
They both have towels
wrapped around their waists.
And the first guy,
he slips his towel off.
And I see his thing, and...
I take it in my hand...
and I say...
- It was the first thing
that came into my head.
- What did you say?
I said,
"I'm sorry, I don't smoke."
And then I just got
the hell out of there.
You okay, sir?
Oh, no, I'm just thinking what I'd pay
to be back in college again.
The next day, the campus
was rampant with word...
that I had been
the center of a gang-bang.
I mean, the governor's daughter.
Let me tell you.
That's one hell of a bell to un-ring.
- What about the photographs?
- Not me.
I never took my clothes off.
Even if I had, I've got
this big birthmark on my right thigh...
that the lady with the lovely physique
in the photo lacks.
- No witnesses?
- Pure urban legend.
A little bit of wishful thinking
thrown in, I think.
You know, Laine...
you could've looked those pricks
in the eye and told them the truth.
Under oath. Told them
they were full of shit.
And barring that,
you could've at least told me.
But see, it really wasn't any of your
business either, and it still isn't.
There's something about
almost puking on a Havana...
that just turns a girl...
to blush.
This letter from Jack Bennet...
and Larry Bellows, affidavit, I guess,
that you got from Webster.
It pretty much says
that nothing happened that night.
- They're ready
to come forward to be deposed.
- That's very good of them.
So, that's it. The end.
Good guys win.
I'm gonna call a press conference
tomorrow, read that letter...
and damn it if you don't have
the fastest confirmation on record.
No, sir.
"No, sir"?
What, "No, sir"?
I would prefer that we not
have the press conference, sir.
Laine, maybe you've been out
of law school too long.
- This is what they call
exculpatory evidence.
- Yes, I realize that.
- This is your ticket to wherever
history is gonna take you.
- Yes.
But principles only mean
something if you stick by them
when they're inconvenient.
If I ever did
answer the questions...
you know,
even to exonerate myself...
that would mean that it was
okay for them to have been
asked in the first place...
and it isn't.
- You would sacrifice your reputation?
- Yes, I would.
People have sacrificed
a lot more for a lot less.
- We've got him! We have Goliath.
- Sir, are you all right, sir?
- It's okay, guys. Busted.
- POTUS is secure.
Of course, the president addressing
a joint session of Congress...
is always unusual,
always an event.
This speech is scheduled
to begin momentarily.
We understand the president
has arrived at the U.S. Capitol.
I don't care if I never
see any of these guys again.
Sources in the White House
have told us that the president...
- It's gonna be okay.
- Does intend to withdraw the name
of Senator Laine B. Hanson...
I still have a year and a half on
my term. That's a long time to recover.
- Then there's always...
- Given the stunning charges
made against Governor Hathaway...
- Laine, honey, it's gonna be fine.
- Those on the inside are suggesting...
- It's gonna be okay.
- The president will designate...
- Ambassador Francis J. Malloy
as his number two.
- Yeah, thanks.
Pace me at five to ten, okay?
... after the greeting
of the president of the United States.
Mr. Speaker, the president
of the United States of America.
Thank you.
Napoleon once said,
when asked to explain the lack
of great statesmen in the world...
that, "to get power...
you need to display
absolute pettiness.
To exercise power,
you need to show true greatness."
Such pettiness and such greatness
are rarely found in one person.
I look upon the events
of the past weeks...
and I've never come so to grips
with that quotation.
So, ladies and gentlemen
of this Congress...
it pains my soul to tell you
that you have brought blood
and shame under this great dome.
Your leadership has raised
the stakes of hate to a level...
where we can no longer separate
the demagogue from the truly inspired.
And believe this,
there are traitors among us.
And I'm not talking about those of you
who sided against your party leadership.
I'm talking about those of you
who were patriots to your party...
but traitors
to the necessary end result:
That of righteousness,
the truth...
the concept of making
the American dream blind to gender.
And you know,
I am not free of blame.
Right from the start
I should've come down here...
pointed a finger your way...
and asked you,
"Have you no decency, sir?"
Yesterday...
I met...
Mr. Runyon...
you may walk out on me,
you may walk out on this body...
but you cannot walk out
on the will of the American people.
Americans are a good people,
they're a just people, Mr. Runyon...
and they will forgive you,
but they will not forget.
Hate and ego
have no place residing...
in what my good friend Laine Hanson
calls the chapel of democracy.
So, let me make one thing clear.
You come at us with whatever weapons
that you have in your arsenal...
but there is
no weapon as powerful...
as that of an idea
whose time has come.
A woman will serve in the highest level
of the Executive. Simple as that.
Yesterday...
I spoke with Laine Hanson.
I told her that she could decide
her own destiny.
If she wanted to continue
her fight for confirmation...
that I would stand beside her.
She has asked me
to allow her to step aside.
She told me that she wanted
my administration to end on a note...
of triumph
and not controversy.
Understand, those of you who worked
to bring Laine Hanson down...
that she asked to have her name
withdrawn from consideration...
not because she isn't great,
but because she isn't petty.
Because those two
conflicting leadership traits...
could not live as one
within her body or her soul.
Greatness.
It comes in many forms.
Sometimes it comes in the form
of sacrifice. That's the loneliest form.
Now, it turns out
that Laine Hanson is a woman...
an American
of devout principle...
and she has inspired me
to act alike...
and I cannot accept
Senator Hanson's withdrawal.
And I'm now calling for an immediate
vote of confirmation of Laine Hanson.
And, Mr. Speaker...
I would like to make this
a live roll call.
I want to see the faces
of those of you...
who would eliminate the possibility
of greatness in American leadership...
because of half-truths,
lies and innuendoes.
I will not be deterred
by partisanship.
by misogyny.
I will not be deterred
by hate.
You have now come face-to-face
with my will.
Confirm my nominee,
heal this nation...
and let the American people
explode into this new millennium...
with the exhilaration of being true
to the glory of this democracy.
Thank you.
How's that for a swan song?
You're back, Laine.
Yeah, I know.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org