Nice view.
Perfect timing.
Wait a minute. He's not alone.
That's heartbreaking news.
Pull the plug. A kid's in the car.
The drug lord's in the car.
Kid took a bad ride, that's all.
Abort the action.
You're the rigger.
I'm the trigger. I decide.
You just sit back and watch the show.
Okay, sport?
Activate the fail-safe, you psycho!
Here's a tip, Ray. There is no fail-safe.
Come on! Come on!
He'll never make it.
You're an arrogant man, Raymond.
I taught you everything you know,
and you dare to turn on me.
Gonna kill me too, Colonel?
You're a specialist, Captain.
You deserve better.
Don't forget to write.
You like watching her die?
Taking them down?
Now I'm taking you down.
You're finished in the Agency.
You're goin' nowhere...
...you're as dead as those people...
...in the river.
We both are!
Have you decided to take thejob?
I saw your ad today.
- I know it's late-
- It's never too late.
After all, you're giving me a new life.
Really? When?
When you kill those three bastards.
I'm flattered.
You better get somebody else.
I like your voice.
You don't need an explosives contractor.
Yes, I do.
- You're my only hope.
- Go to court, use the law.
The law's been bought.
Use a bullet.
Bullets...
...are imprecise.
I heard you control your explosions...
that you shape your charges.
What I shape is my business.
All I'm saying...
...word is you are the best.
Whose word?
If we couldjust meet...
I don't meet or work in Miami
and I don't do jobs like this.
Why do you keep calling me back?
Why?
I like your voice.
Is it my cologne?
They're killers.
You'd be doing the world a favor.
I don't owe the world any favors.
Why did you wait so long?
I thought...
I thought maybe it would pass.
Every day is worse.
Remembering what happened.
That's what I do instead of being alive.
My father hid me in the closet.
I could still see.
My mother suffered.
They tortured her to get my father to talk.
We're going to have to kill her.
He walked by something
he shouldn't have seen.
They covered his face
with the pillow from my bed.
Waste them.
It was too small.
So they shot him.
I never thought...
...blood would be so sticky.
Sometimes I think I can never wash it off.
The only thing I understand
anymore is revenge.
I'm going in, and I'm going to do it myself.
You'll only get one of them.
That's why I need you.
I don't do this kind ofjob anymore.
I know you've been watching me,
trying to decide if...
...I'm on the level,
ifyou're going to take thejob.
I can't wait anymore, I'm going in.
- They'll make you.
- I have an alias.
Adrian Hastings.
Wish me luck.
Señor León.
How's it coming in?
Oh, boy. You don't give up.
It's packed in Monopoly boxes.
That's great, Papa.
You get it in. I'll put it on the street.
Come here.
- How are you?
- Nice party.
You went all out. It's fantastic.
- So let's talk numbers.
- Forget business tonight.
Go grab yourself a nice mulatta.
I want my money.
An advance.
Small token of my family's goodwill.
Token?
Token.
Listen to me, boy.
You know what the Dark Ages are?
The Dark Ages are what I brought
the León family out of.
I computerized your operation.
I streamlined your security.
I dragged you into the 20th century.
So don't fuck with me.
What is this?
A tip? I don't work for tips.
She works for tips.
I want my money. I want it now.
Go get it.
It's always a pleasure working with you.
Champagne, please.
Is there something you want?
What I want, I take.
Champagne?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Welcome to our bank.
I've never seen you before.
I lived here when I was little.
A lot's happened since you left.
Like what?
Like me.
Insecurity is a terrible thing.
It would be.
I'd like to dance.
What's wrong with keeping
the conversation going?
Later. Right now, I'm taking what I want.
You look beautiful tonight!
I'll have my driver to pick you up
tomorrow and I'll show you my Miami.
Right on time.
Should I do it, Timer?
- Kind ofyoung to be riding the bus.
- Stop it!
What? I'm not good enough for you?
I wanna play.
Come on, baby...
- Stop! Leave me alone!
- Come on now, what's up, huh?
Here, you can take my seat.
Thank you!
That seat's taken.
Fuck you.
Excuse me?
Hold these, please.
What's going on?
I hate knives.
Fuck you! You son of a bitch!
I believe there's a vacancy.
- What do you drink?
- Martini.
Martini on the rocks.
Gold tequila, straight up.
No one knows Miami like I do.
You like spending the day with me?
Yeah.
Do you?
Kiss me.
I hardly know you.
Wait 'til you try to spend the night.
Thanks.
Stay here. I must take care of something.
Got a light?
Is that the piece of shit?
Where were you?
Home.
Thanks.
What happened to you?
I didn't like the show.
You don't...
...walk away from me...
...ever.
You understand?
Sorry.
Get in the car.
Sure.
Every time...
...he touches me I...
I mean...
...he's the man who shot my father!
And he's...
...kissing me and...
Oh, God!
You don't have to do it.
It's the only way I can get
close enough to kill him!
You see, I have this dream:
I'm right there when it happens.
He looks at me like I'm a stranger.
And I say my name.
And it's the last thing he ever hears.
They don't suspect you?
I'm trusted, for the moment.
He's always with you. How do you live?
Alone.
That's not what I mean.
How do you live...
...with yourself?.
How do you?
Hey, you!
I'm talking to you.
You think you know me?
I asked you a question.
Do you think you know me?
'Cause the way you're looking at me,
we must be old friends.
Where did we meet?
Nowhere.
You like the bitch?
Maybe you like me.
I don't like you.
Then don't stare so hard.
Somebody could...
...put something in your eye.
Fucking pervert.
Let's move it.
Good night.
Adrian.
Are you listening?
The first rule:
Don't go near them again.
Second rule:
Don't contact me.
I'll contact you.
Maybe I can help you.
- Let me see-
- No.
They're my problem now and I'm theirs.
Are you close enough to walk over?
Rule three:
If this is a setup...
...I...
...will kill you.
Now what?
That cop was a regular.
Juanita's moving in on me.
Get out of here!
I don't solve domestic problems!
Asshole!
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
Lucky me.
Hey, Charlie!
J & B.
The word is, Manny...
...you're skimming.
Somebody's lying. I never took a dollar.
I hope it ain't you.
Because if you're trying
to screw Joe León...
You've known me, what, ten years?
I'm clean.
Good.
Very good.
Then you have nothing to worry about.
Let me see the books.
That is it. What?
- How about a drink?
- Sure.
September's missing.
See you, Manny.
What do you feel like doing?
What?
I'm working.
You have two hours!
Get another job, kid.
They got two bodies in there.
Something that used to be Charlie...
...and a hit on your brothel manager.
That was a bright move.
Something you ordered?
Didn't bother to tell me?
He was a thief.
- Tell me about the bomb.
- Very clean.
There was no damage
left or right of the blast.
The arming device was impacted
inside the C-4, so it was vaporized.
Brilliant plan, totally professional.
Must be a specialist.
- This guy is good.
- Yeah, okay.
He could put a bomb in your crab shell
and you wouldn't even know it.
I'll kill him!
You can't kill anyone
until we know who he is, can you?
I'll find him.
The important thing to find out
is who he works for.
Maybe he's with the CIA.
Maybe he works for the Mafia.
But we have to find out who.
Overview.
What does eliminating Charlie mean
in the overall picture?
- Nothing.
- Less than nothing.
So this target wasn't territorial.
It was personal.
How the fuck do you know so much?
He's guessing. Let me take a few boys,
I'll find this bastard.
Wait a minute. Give me a second.
I have to make a decision.
Little time to think here, huh?
You take over, OK?
I said, Trent will handle it, OK?
I don't hear you saying '"OK'"...
- What did you say?
- OK.
That's nice. Thank you.
Fuck you.
I'll need resources on this one, Joe.
Also, the place was crawling with cops.
I can't be tripping over civil servants
every move I make.
I need total control.
Yeah, OK, I will...
I will take care of that.
Personally.
Hello, Timer.
Having a good day?
Here you go. Knock yourself out.
I saw it on the news.
You got the first one.
Thank you.
Well, I'mjust doin' myjob.
You gotta stay away from the other two.
I could help you.
I could...
...set them up for you.
No, you stay clear.
Their future is about to become very dark.
You're still following me.
Aren't you?
It's gotten so I can feel you.
It's all part of the work.
Do you think about me?
I think about you.
My own personal ghost.
Or angel maybe.
- We could meet.
- You're a beautiful woman.
But, I don't meet.
- When this is over, I should leave.
- When are you gonna do it?
Soon.
Very soon.
Trent, you know the Chief of Police.
Trent is going to work with us
on this problem.
He was a former employee of the...
...CIA.
He is an explosives expert,
and I think he can be a big help.
I don't know.
This has become very public.
I'm sure you want a low profile.
Yeah, please.
It would be hard for Ned to go unnoticed.
I think there's more involved here
than keeping a low profile.
I'd say that I'm the one you can trust,
which is the main word here... trust.
To take him out clean.
Our bomb boys are the best.
I hope that's true.
They better be fucking magicians...
...because this man's impressive.
What are you, a fucking fan?
Come on! Stop that, this is serious, right?
Don't you two start!
We're here to find a way to protect
the business. Don't forget that.
Is that understood?
I must tell you...
...that this one is not negotiable.
I'll do what I can. Put him on as a fed.
Chief, always a pleasure.
Good to see you again.
OK, Danny, help me up.
Oh, boy. I hate that deep couch.
Now, listen. Danny, you'll do me a favor.
Do your best to make
this thing look official.
No, please. You do that,
and I promise you...
...I will not forget you.
A man's got to eat.
Idiota.
Where's the bomb squad?
Come on, boys and girls,
what are we doing? Look alive.
What've you got?
We're doing a complete background
check on everybody at the party.
Give me the next one.
Listen, I'll handle the biographies.
You trace the C-4. OK, Ace?
Chief says you're on this. Fine.
But I don't take orders
from any ex-anything.
OK, Ace?
I must tell you. I'm sorry,
I thought your chief said...
...the fullest cooperation
would be forthcoming.
I must tell you something.
This doesn't feel like full cooperation.
Look at this shit. What's this?
This is, uh...
Shouldn't this be in the lock-up?
I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
You guys are the experts.
Maybe you don't need me.
I mean, like what is this? This is...
This is Semtex.
Am I right? Plastique.
Plastic explosive.
Am I right? You're the expert.
This could blow up this whole area,
and if this area goes...
...the whole building could go up.
Am I right?
I don't know.
Maybe if I put this in here...
What else do we have here?
This is a plunger detonator, right?
And that's a little mini-receiver.
This looks like American circuitry to me.
Call me a patriot...
...but American craftsmanship
is the greatest.
Watch.
Here we go.
Let's see.
Perfect fit, first time...
...every time. Screw it on.
One little twist.
And, voilà.
A perfect receiver bomb.
Which of course is...
...absolutely worthless without a...
...transmitter.
Twenty seconds, and...
...we're hot.
Deactivate it, you sanctimonious prick!
Cut that shit!
OK, you made your point!
Have I?
- That's enough!
- What do you mean?
You think I give a shit
if the whole block goes up?
I don't!
You've had enough. Is that it?
Yes, enough is enough!
- I can't do it.
- Twelve.
What the hell, are you crazy?
I'm the craziest person
you'll ever meet in your life.
Six.
Five.
Four.
- Three.
- Please!
Now, here's a tip...
...you take care of the shit work.
And leave the fox at the party to me. OK?
We on the same page?
Ace?
Do you like it? Those go upstairs.
I like where I live.
I like you where I live.
Thanks.
Close the doors. Leave.
Better than you're used to?
Next time you order a hit you might
consider taking out your decorator.
You like to live dangerously?
A little danger never killed anyone.
Right, baby?
Sometimes.
You know...
...when I look at you...
...I see something I like very much.
Know what it is?
I'm breathless with anticipation.
I see me.
Let's get this over with.
Wait a minute.
You're the Mob's accountant, Bill.
Is that all you've got for me?
No. I have something else for you.
See you later.
Don't touch that! It could be a bomb!
Very funny.
Son of a bitch!
Kid!
Look at the way you parked
my fucking car.
Sir, I didn't park your car.
Sorry.
I'll get it for you.
Here's your tip.
Some ride that must have been.
Is this the decoy?
Who was this supposed to fool?
Any witnesses?
The kid?
Nice one, Ray.
Clever boy.
'"Bye-bye. '"
At least he hasn't lost his sense of humor.
Who gave you permission to smile?
Shut up.
Quite a step up for you, isn't it?
Depends on how you look at it.
- Tomas is on his way-
- Shut up!
Who are you?
I said, '"Who are you?'"
I'll tell you who you are.
You are nobody.
I created Adrian Hastings.
I got you inside.
You work for me.
Don't you ever fucking forget it.
You should have him
out in the open by now.
You get your three corpses,
I get Ray Quick.
That was the deal. What happened?
I can't keep him on the line
long enough to get a trace.
He doesn't want to take a meeting.
What should I do?
Wish him out of hiding?
You're in over your head.
Maybe you've outlived your usefulness.
Is that possible?
You need me.
I studied him, I drew him out.
With my voice, with my ads. He trusts me.
Why do I need you?
Why don't I just grab him
before he brings Tomas down?
Why do you even need...
...to live at all?
Maybe he's not interested in a big-mouth,
hotshot asshole like you.
You know what I love about you?
It's not just this...
...poetry.
It's your heart.
It's the heart you bring to your work.
But if you don't set up a meeting with
him before he drops the third target...
...you'll pray for a lifetime
of Tomas's attentions...
...his delicate touch.
- I promise.
- Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
I've always wondered...
...what was it like...
...after you watched your parents die.
Did you go over to the bed?
Did little May hug them?
Did you try to shake them awake?
How much blood?
I'm just curious, was there...
...a lot of blood?
Don't push me.
What are you doing here?
Take it easy, hotshot.
I'm checking up on you.
I don't need you goddamn
babysitting for me.
Why don't you look for who's hitting us?
What's the first move?
Door-to-door search?
I'm sick of you.
My father thinks he needs you.
When he finds out he doesn't...
...you're mine.
Well...
I feel threatened.
You are threatened.
Five hundred.
OK, I'm out of here.
Just a second.
May Munro.
Where are you going!
Get up!
Go in there! Get him!
Get the fuck in there!
Keep them back.
Get them out!
Good one, Ray.
Really good.
Joe, I am so sorry.
You're sorry?
My son...
...is in a closed casket...
...and...
...you are sorry.
I hold you responsible.
He wouldn't lay low.
What did you say?
I said, '"He wouldn't lay low. '"
Are you trying to tell me
that was his fault now?
That's how it was.
The way it was!
You were supposed to protect his back!
His life was in your hands!
You know what you did?
You cut my heart out, you know.
And now you look, my...
...my son...
...is lying in a box.
You know...
...you were the one...
...who let it happen.
You're not thinking straight.
Jesus Christ, don't you try to tell me.
I swear to God, don't say another word.
Not another word or I'll kill you here.
You understand?
Now...
...you go out...
...you go out and you find
this explosives expert...
...and you...
...bring him to me alive...
...before I bury Tomas.
"Adrian Hastings of Miami, Dade County.
"Services 3:00 p. m., Friday
at San Juan De Bosco. "
Her body's in cold storage
at County General.
How does this sound?
'"Lonely, needy, deeply hurt.
Will be discreet. '"
Story of my life.
Get this on every major
bulletin board service.
Put the response number through
long-distance and be ready to trace.
OK?
OK.
Guys like this, they won't advertise.
You must draw them out.
Do your best.
Hi, baby! Are you wearing any underwear?
Get rid of him.
Your experience doesn't match my needs.
- Get rid of him.
- I am.
Thirty calls and nothing.
I don't know if this makes sense.
I'll decide if it makes any sense or not, OK?
Go on, take it. Take it!
Line five and...
Go.
Hello?
Calling about the ad, right?
Yeah.
Right.
I thought you were someone else.
The ad was similar to others.
Give me a number.
I can't talk on this phone.
Forget it.
You have a message from May.
I've got a message...
...from May.
- Who is this?
- She's OK.
She wants to meet you.
No, I don't think so.
Put Trent on the line.
What did you say?
Trent. He's standing next to you.
I want to talk to him.
Put him on the line!
Ned, can you hear me?
Talk to me. Talk to me, Ned.
Your playmates know what kind of man
you are? Why the Agency fired you?
That killing people
was like jerking-off for you?
Watching those bloody bodies
going though the air gets you off.
Talk to me. When you crawl
into your hole at night alone...
...and you are alone, aren't you?
Tell me what burns you the most.
Losing yourjob as a CIA attack dog...
...or knowing that I turned you in
and I'm still alive?
Talk to me!
You'll sell your service
to the highest bidder!
You stinking maggot!
Fuck you, Ray! Fuck you! You killed!
Your bombs!
How many? 10, 50, 100,
before you lost count?
It was your bombs on the bridge
in Bogotá! Your bomb in the cabana!
But you're getting sloppy.
You broke your code.
You killed an innocent bystander.
It is eating you up inside, isn't it?
You were always too sensitive.
But guess what?
I'm coming to take all the pain away.
I'll fucking cut it right out of you,
and close your heart in my hand.
I'm right behind you! I know you!
You've got no mercy.
You got no fucking loyalty.
And you got no code.
- Listen to me, you son of a bitch!
- Time's up, 58 seconds.
Goddamn it!
Son of a bitch!
I'll fucking kill you! I'll vaporize your ass!
What're you looking at?
Turn around!
Nobody...
...says a word.
Tell me that you got a trace.
Just tell me.
He jumped off before we locked him.
- We got a partial trace.
- Shut up.
She gave of herself...
...for 40 years.
She dedicated her life...
...generously...
...courageously...
...to all of us, Cuban orphans everywhere.
She has shown us a road.
For the wages sin pays is death.
But the gift God gives...
...is everlasting life...
...by Christ, Jesus, Our Lord.
How did I look?
Why did you do this?
I wanted to meet you.
I wanted to know if you were
everything I ever thought.
Nobody ever is.
Hold it.
Open the casket.
Who are you?
I said, '"Open the fucking casket! '"
Bitch!
Fuck!
We shouldn't be here.
Not if we want to stay alive.
Is it worth it?
I think so.
I hope so.
Let me see this beautiful face.
Why'd you let me think I killed you?
It was the only way
I could get Tomas's men off my back.
Give me some details.
Poor lady O.D.'d in the emergency room.
I dropped my wallet in her purse...
...and here I am.
Pretty good, especially...
...if you're an amateur.
You could've been killed.
I had to be there when he died.
I needed to see it.
Anyway...
I knew you'd choose
the safest way for everybody.
I studied your style.
I know you always focused
your detonation.
So I knew...
...as long as I was facing Tomas,
right in front of him, like this...
Even closer, like this...
...I knew I'd feel safe.
Excuse me.
Police are looking for these two.
If you see them,
call the number on the back.
Wait.
I have seen them.
Back from the dead.
Jesus.
Thank God.
I was just going to call you.
About the funeral thing,
I'm sorry, there's just...
It was the only way to draw him out.
It worked. I don't have to tell you.
I used the '"attachment'" thing,
and I got him.
Couldn't stay away from me.
So?
I just want to get one thing straight.
You did all this to deliver him to me?
We had a deal. I hold up my end of a deal.
You're a classic, May.
Where is he?
- Here!
- Where?
- In the hotel.
- I know. Where?
I got a key. I think it-
This key?
I mean, I do have a key.
- He's on a high floor, it's 10 or 11.
- Take her to the car.
- Go on.
- I left my purse, I have to-
- Shut up. Take her to the car.
- I have a couple of things to do.
Stop yanking me around!
He made me so nervous.
It'll take me one second.
Where can I go?
Harry, listen-
Harry, she'll call you back.
Give me my phone!
Room 1205.
León's men are on their way up.
You set me up.
- Why?
- I did not.
Hit it. Let's get out.
There's a fire. Let's go. Rush.
Where you going? Use the stairs.
This one's full. Get out of here!
We're sorry.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
Please check the number and
dial again or call the operator.
Ifyou have to make a call,
please hang up and try again...
Ifyou need help,
hang up and dial your operator.
Don't move!
Don't touch anything!
Give me your hand!
Holy shit!
Go! Go!
Hey, what's with the lights here?
Security, get him!
Come on, asshole! Come on!
There has been an accident,
but there is no danger.
No cause for alarm.
That's her.
Her who?
That's the bitch who was banging Tomas.
Her ID was faked.
Ray Quick is working for her.
Alice...
...and Stan Munro.
What are you talking about?
I was the kid your little boy
missed in the closet.
That was a long time ago.
Not to me.
Now I understand.
Now I understand. You...
You think...
...that my son Tomas gave the orders
for the killings. Well, you are wrong.
If anybody in this house has power to give
orders, it's me.
Understand? I give the orders.
I give the orders of who is killed...
...and who is not killed.
Is that understood?
I need her...
...to get to Ray.
I must make one phone call,
then she's yours.
But I need her now.
You sure?
Joe, please.
Take the bitch.
Show time.
- Hello?
- It's me.
I'm sorry. I didn't know they were coming.
Believe me.
I'll tell you what I believe.
I believe you're very good on the phone.
I need to see you.
And get set up again?
No, I'll pass.
I'm through taking risks.
So that's it?
We just walk away?
Forever?
It's safer for everybody.
Come on, I don't know what
this relationship is about...
...but I know it's not based on safety.
You're too much of an unknown.
Adrian Hastings, May Munro.
Who the hell are you?
Remember the Fontainebleau?
I remember.
Remember touching me?
Do you remember my voice?
Not over the phone...
...but carried on breath.
On you.
Near you.
Close enough to feel.
Why are you saying this to me?
Because I have to.
Come on, Ray.
You gotta see me.
Please.
Please, baby.
Double-M Seafood, right now.
All right.
And Ray...
I'm here.
Do you remember the note
our relationship ended on?
The last thing I said to you?
I remember everything.
I meant every word.
You're goin' in alone.
And if this is a trap...
...I promise you, you're gonna die.
But if he's in there...
...make him feel safe and secure.
And I'll be listening...
...on this microphone.
The second I hear his voice...
...we move in.
Understand?
Now get out of the fucking car.
When this is all over...
...I can see us spending time together.
You know, you wash...
...the stink of Tomas and Ray off you...
...you might clean up pretty good.
Go ahead.
And then you can go in
and get him yourself.
I don't give a shit!
Go on!
Move!
If she blinks...
...kill her.
Bad plan, Ned.
That's it, we've got him. Move in.
Go, you chicken shits!
You think he'll top that? Get in there!
Watch the river and the side streets!
Fucking crabs!
Nice one.
Watch the river!
You want to set me up again?
What's that?
Break it down.
Air brakes.
Complex sound, slightly muffled.
People talking...
...clamping down steps.
A clapping shut.
Voices... mechanical sounds.
- A hiss!
- People getting off a bus!
You must have an overview.
Are they on both tapes?
I knew it! We gotta have bus routes.
What do we have?
He uses pay phones,
but he gets there by bus.
Oh, Ray, always so precise.
Let's say, he gets on a bus
wherever he lives, and he...
...goes in both directions.
Good counter-surveillance technique.
He takes the bus 20, 25 minutes
in each direction. So we have...
Four, four and four.
Here we go, triangulation.
Three routes, that's it.
We want checks in five-minute intervals.
How about the restaurants?
He must eat sometime.
Try to remember. He'd have gotten off
the bus alone, bought cigarettes.
Look at that face!
We have a lot of regular customers,
but he ain't one.
Look at that face again!
Come on. Come on!
Nothing.
Hey, Henry!
I forgot to tell you, we deliver.
Now there's a vision.
Good morning, stranger.
I've got to go.
Where? I think we already wore out
our welcome at the Hilton.
I want to stay with you.
But it's not over for me.
Joe León ordered the hit.
Let me get this right.
You think killing Joe
will make everything OK?
Something has to.
You did the job. I'm not asking
for your help. I'll do it. I owe him.
No.
You owe her.
Her. A whole life. Come here.
Come here.
Put all this behind you now,
or the past will eat you alive.
I know what I'm talking about.
I have to go.
Wish me luck.
No.
Come here. You're not going.
Detonation sequence primed. Enter code.
Top of the world, Mom.
Controlled!
One... two... three...
I'm afraid to ask.
Explosions will occur
if the inner perimeter is breached.
Each one of these lights is a pressure
mine. If one goes, they all go.
- Where are they?
- Everywhere.
Don't worry, they're not armed yet.
When these lights turn red... worry.
This is good. Nice sneak attack!
Do not approach the warehouse.
Perimeter is armed.
Please, cut the bullshit.
That's a good one. I taught him that.
Nice sense of irony,
blowing up the bomb disposal unit.
Nice work, Ray.
WARNING!
Gunfire will automatically
detonate B-20's...
...sufficient to destroy two square miles.
Give me that.
Listen up! Anybody shoots...
...anybody shoots, I shoot them!
This whole place is wired and
I'm taking him alive. Got that?
That's new.
How's that feel, Ace?
Fuck this amateur hour.
You're crazy.
All the highly trained professionals
of the world...
...all the hardware...
...all the technology,
and what have you got?
Nothing.
You gotta do everything yourself.
And why?
You can't get good help these days.
A surprise for you, Ray.
It's set. Let's go.
Don't move!
- I'll lead you through the mines.
- Evacuate!
Ray...?
I'm sorry. Should I have knocked?
You lose, I win.
She's hot, Ray.
Semtex, sprayed with nitro.
Cigarette case. Honest Injun, take a look.
Just a peek, no touch.
You might ask yourself,
'"Why is today my time to die?'"
Take it out. Slowly.
Slowly.
Open it.
Everyone deserves to die.
Ask God.
He kills across the board.
So why shouldn't I?
Bye.
Here's a tip I learned from you.
It's a focused detonation. Only she blows.
- It's pretty nifty.
- Don't move it. It's a mercury switch.
Any change in angle, it goes.
Got it.
Anyway, Ray, she's dead already.
What I need...
...what I need is to take you alive
because my boss...
...wants to look in your eyes when you die.
Sick fuck.
I'm touched, really.
What happened to us, Ray?
We were...
...we were good together.
You were the rigger and I was the trigger.
You shouldn't have taken me down.
Because now, you fuck!
I see you're still into
the old memories, Ray.
Those memories always do you in, right?
It's that '"trying to save the innocent. '"
You know your problem, Ray?
You're too sentimental.
There's nothing wrong
with being sentimental.
Sometimes it can save your ass.
Here's a tip: no fail-safe.
Pressure pads.
30 seconds to total destruction.
Slide it to me.
25 seconds.
It's all right.
Just do it, May.
Slide your hands out.
20 seconds.
Get out of here.
Straight down the right side.
Not without you.
I'm right behind you.
10 seconds.
5 seconds.
Come on! Come on!
3 seconds.
Thank you.
You are a kind God.
You bastarda!
How do you feel?
Better.