Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I think we can begin.
The first parole request
for Carter "Doc" McCoy.
Is legal counsel present?
Yes, sir. I'm Eugene Stewart,
representing Mr. McCoy.
"Carter McCoy, one to ten year sentence
for armed robbery.
"First offense in the state of Texas.
"Wanted by the state of Ohio
for assault with a deadly weapon...
"...and armed robbery. "
The State of Ohio has waived jurisdiction,
Mr. Chairman.
Mr. McCoy is no longer wanted
in that case.
Good luck, man.
Mr. McCoy has served
four years of his sentence.
His record's satisfactory.
Applied for parole
on September fifth of this year.
Remarks?
I would only, once again,
like to point out to the committee...
...Mr. McCoy's good behavior
while a prisoner.
-Notice is taken.
-Thank you, sir.
The board met
in closed chambers last week.
Have you reached a decision regarding
Mr. McCoy's request for parole?
Request for parole is denied.
The prisoner may re-apply
after one calendar year.
Lock 'em up.
Open the gate.
Lance said to have eight hole,
Gallo one, Kirksky two.
Eight hole colored.
Go down to the garden house,
turn to your left, go to the woods.
We're going on to the brush. Burn it.
Take the stumps up out of the ground.
Bob Field, get them dogs out there
close to the trailer.
One hole.
Eight hole.
Thirty.
Come on.
-Fifteen.
Get them dogs in close to 'em, Bob Field.
-Thirty.
Hogfield, you go to the left
and start rounding up on that brush pile.
Time to go.
Put it back. Catch them, this squad.
Round this pile up and get it burning.
Oh, man, that's just a game.
Man, get on this stump.
Look out, McCoy.
Get your axe and come on up here
and pitch in.
Go to work. Go to work.
De Leon, get the fire going.
That Mexican there...
Get up all this little stuff
and put it on this pile.
Thirty.
Eight hole.
Catch that brush pile here
and get it rounded up.
I want it tight to where it'll burn.
Get these stumps down under the ground.
Bob Field...
...round up that pile.
Get it to burn.
Kirk Shaw, over on the ground...
Keep that line straight.
Keep that line tight.
Hello, Doc.
I'm sorry.
Get to Beynon.
Tell him I'm for sale. His price.
Do it now.
Hello, Mrs. McCoy.
I'd like to see Jack Beynon.
Go ahead.
Class. Is she a regular?
No. Doc McCoy's old lady.
Jeez, is that Carol Ainsley?
Shut up!
How are you, Mrs. McCoy?
Ready to talk about my husband,
Mr. Beynon.
Please sit down.
So the good doctor comes up again.
He asked me to come and see you.
Why?
Can I help?
Yes, I think you can.
How about a drink?
Yeah, I could use one.
Come on over.
You'll be back, Doc.
Mr. Beynon will see you
the day after tomorrow.
12:30 at the River Walk.
-Hi, Doc.
-Hi.
Feel okay?
I'm a lot better off now
than I was an hour ago.
-You want to drive?
-My driver's license has expired.
Sorry I'm late. I was having my hair done,
the girl was slow.
You look fine.
-You feel good?
-Yeah.
-Where do you want to go?
-Take a walk.
What do you want for dinner?
Drinks. Whiskey, whiskey, whiskey...
You okay?
Pretty good.
Made a trip to Oregon
to see my brother and his kids.
I figured it'd be
the last time I'd see them...
...unless they decide to travel.
How's Estelle?
Fatter.
You know, some things never change.
Yeah, that's right.
That's not all of it.
It's been a long time, Doc.
Did you go out much?
Four years, and now
the question comes up.
I couldn't handle it inside.
But I can now.
I'm still here, Doc.
It does something to you, you know.
It does something to you.
It does something to you in there.
We've got time, Doc.
We've got lots of time.
Just give me a minute, baby.
Listen, I'm just as nervous as you are.
Really?
Really.
Let me make you feel good, Doctor.
It's been so long.
So long.
Fantastic.
She's here.
Hey, I was gonna fix you breakfast.
You were sleeping.
A little ketchup.
And then we have a little...
Thank you.
-For what?
-For getting me out.
It was a pleasure.
Thank you, ma'am.
Hey, Claude. Here's your boy.
You have to be kidding.
Not at all.
Just a pleasant way to have lunch.
Sit down.
It's good to see you
in them civilian clothes.
It just takes a long arm, Beynon.
You know, it's hard to say
how those things happen.
The parole board almost never
changes their decision.
It must be because I'm a model prisoner.
This is the only time
you and I meet in public.
Any business with me...
...you handle it with him.
He's my brother.
Back with your own people, now.
I got you some professionals.
I'll get my own men, Beynon.
You run the job, but I run the show.
And don't forget it.
You've got two weeks to set it up.
It's not a big bank, but it handles
the cash deposits for an oil company.
Over half a million dollars.
It's a family bank.
The brother of the bank director...
...is on the board of directors
at Con-Sol Oil in Beacon City.
Here's a couple of fellas
I'd like you to meet.
Rudy Butler, Frank Jackson.
Yeah, I've heard of you.
You work with Miller?
You're out of touch, Doc.
Miller got blown up.
Where?
Fort Lauderdale.
-Were you with him?
-Yeah.
I got out.
You?
I was backup man on a payroll job.
I'd hit some liquor stores. I drive good.
I drive.
Sure.
I want Mexican visas and passports.
They'll be ready.
You boys just do your job.
Carol.
Bank guard, 7:59.
He's early.
You got a flashlight, some light batteries.
A-hooks, pliers, wire cutters...
What do you want all this stuff for?
-I'm going on a picnic.
-Going on a picnic?
Well...okay.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
especially you gentlemen...
We very proudly present
the pride and joy of Beacon City.
Our own high-stepping and high-kicking...
...Southwest Texas Ropers.
Following the strutters...
representing the Ladies' Auxiliary of...
...the Volunteer Fire Brigade.
We have the first beautiful float...
...which consists of the Constitution
in the history of the Lone Star State.
Good morning.
I'd like an application
for a checking account, please.
He goes here, follows down here.
Now, this is the spot you're looking for.
Here. Yeah.
-Can I get a copy of this?
-Yes, sir.
-Thanks a lot.
-You're welcome.
Change for a $50, please.
$20, $30...
...$40, $45, $50.
Thank you.
Y'all come back and see us soon.
Set your clocks for five minutes after 9:00.
All right, on the nose, now.
The diversionary explosions are spaced
20 seconds apart.
That gives you...
...one minute and 38 seconds,
before they blow.
You've got a bank president,
you have three tellers.
And you've got a bank guard.
Usually on the right as you come in.
Pin him right away.
Careful he doesn't panic,
and go shoot somebody.
You got one local police car.
Now he's a rover.
Shouldn't be anywhere near the vicinity
when we make our hit.
Traffic is usually light at that hour.
There are three exits. One at Hopkins,
one at Guadalupe Street...
...and then there's the alley.
Will you put that away and pay attention!
Now the guard carries a .38.
The cops carry 357-magnums.
You know what this is.
This'll stop an M-2 army rifle at 50 yards.
I've been working ten years without one.
-Suit yourself.
-Thank you.
What about the vault?
It's a Chambers Reilly.
It's on a time lock.
Opens up 20 minutes before office hours.
Wire pull over?
No, one-inch stuff
on a three number combination.
That's me.
No, no. I'll handle the fine stuff.
You're backup all the way.
Whatever you need, brother.
Right.
You keep going over this.
I don't want anybody lost.
If we're clean,
Gollie will take us across at Laredo.
If we're hot, we'll have to try Laughlin's
in El Paso.
Aren't we going a little bit hard?
That's a walk-in bank, man.
A piece of cake.
You don't have to be Dillinger for that one.
Bang.
Dillinger got killed.
Not in the bank.
Take it with you.
Expenses.
Tell Beynon I don't want any mix-ups.
I make one phone call.
And his people better be there.
All of them.
I understand.
Beynon's to be alone at the drop.
Only one car in the garage
at the ranch and that's it.
Now, I'm not gonna have the money.
And she's not gonna know where it is
until I know I'm clear. Got it?
-He understands.
-Good, good.
Make sure everybody does. Okay?
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Morgan. How are you?
Fine, thank you.
Hold it.
Come on, move it!
Relax.
Superior technology, my ass.
Hands up!
Mr. President? Up!
Everybody, out this way.
Come on, come on! Hurry it up! Move it!
Go!
Come on, move it!
Come on, honey, get on it.
Now just relax.
Face down!
Move it. Move it, honey.
They're on their way. Just relax.
Everybody relax.
Ninety seconds.
Seventy-five.
Sixty-five.
Fifty, brother.
No!
Stupid bastard!
Take the wheel.
How did it go?
Bad. Jackson killed the guard.
Fourteen seconds till the next one goes off.
Come on, come on.
Shit.
Where's Jackson?
He didn't make it.
Neither did you.
...was held up this morning
shortly after opening.
The bank officials state that $7 50,000
was taken by three masked men...
...who forced the employees...
Hey, there's only $500,000 here.
-You sure?
-Yes, I'm sure.
Doc?
I see it. Take it easy.
They're looking for three men, remember?
What seems to be the problem, Officer?
Okay, drive on.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill that mother!
He's on.
I'm here.
Yeah?
They checked in.
Tell me about Beynon's ranch.
I've never been there.
When we met, it was at his office.
Do you trust him?
I don't figure he's gonna try to cross us.
At least not until he gets his money.
Well, let's just send his cut back
and just get going.
If we make a mistake, he's gonna burn us.
You make a deal,
you're better off keeping up your end.
I don't want to go there.
Let's do it my way.
Stay here.
I'll wrap it up as quick as I can.
News said two people killed.
Three. Rudy got ambitious.
And you got him.
That's right.
What about your wife?
Let's cut up the money, Beynon.
I want to get north.
She told me no one would get killed.
I'm in a hurry, Beynon.
You still don't get the picture, do you?
And I've always heard
what a smart-ass operator you was.
No applause.
Let's examine the situation.
One. An extremely attractive woman.
And there's the woman's husband.
And there's a man with political influence.
A man who can easily get a parole
for a convict.
Why should he?
A simple reason, McCoy.
Let's get down to it.
Radio's rapping about $750,000.
There's a half a million, here.
A little more was taken out before.
You see, my brother's
the director of that bank.
We had a few problems we had to iron out.
Okay. We covered you...
Yeah.
You surely did, Doc.
My old lady must've made you
a lot of promises.
Close.
I wouldn't feel...
Stupid!
Why didn't you tell me, huh?
Why didn't you tell me?
There wasn't any way to explain it.
You sent me to him, you know.
What the hell do you want anyway?
Goddamn you!
Still no answer.
Something's wrong.
Come on! Come on!
What's the damage?
Your collarbone's broken
but it's not shattered.
There's no infection, yet.
Those bandages ought
to be changed twice a day.
It's okay.
I got a nurse in mind.
The three of us are gonna
do some traveling.
We're gonna take your car to El Paso.
We...we can't leave here.
That's not possible.
I mean, we have all of this.
Is that possible, Mrs. Clinton?
Just tell us what you want.
What kind of a car do you drive?
A Ford. We have a Ford.
That's good.
That's very good, Harold.
You run on out and gas up the Ford.
If anybody but you comes back, Harold...
...she gets her clock stopped.
You do what he says, Harold.
Just do as I say.
You. Get a cloth.
You're gonna wash me.
They still may be on the way to Laredo.
What about El Paso?
He's a friend of Laughlin.
Well, we have to cover them both.
We've got to get somebody down there.
Either Rudy or...
...McCoy's got a half a million bucks.
-Put out the word.
-What about Jack?
Just dump him down a dry well,
if you can find one.
No, he ought to be buried proper.
You just do what I tell you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Wendy, sit down.
Two day-coach tickets to El Paso.
Leaves in 45 minutes. Gate three.
Thank you, ma'am.
Kind of tricky, isn't it?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Come over here.
You don't always have to
take your gun out.
I'll do anything you want.
Really.
I will.
Get rid of that nail polish.
Okay.
I don't like it.
And get rid of that, too.
What is that?
Don't get any blood on me. I hate blood.
Say, you wouldn't happen to be
a Mormon, would you?
No, I'm afraid not.
I'd like another one.
Me, neither.
I'm from Orem. That's right near Salt Lake.
There's about 12 people in the state who
aren't Mormons, and I'm one of them.
I guess that makes you kind of special.
-Yeah, I guess it does.
-Thank you.
Hey, baby.
You wouldn't be taking the train
to Salt Lake, would you?
No, I'm afraid not!
That's just my luck.
Listen, I hope you have a really nice trip.
Thanks. I hope yours is okay, too.
Where's the bag?
It's in the locker. I've got the key.
A man helped me open it.
How long ago?
Fifteen minutes ago.
It's the oldest con game in the world.
He switched keys with you.
He'll figure you for more time.
He's probably still in the station.
Find him.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org