[Man]
Let me get this straight.
You're saying you don't have a warrant?
[Man #2]
I'm saying I don't have it signed yet.
[Man #1]
Okay, how do we do this?
The informer's up there with 'em.
And don't worry. She'll do the intro.
[Man #1] They'll be armed for sure,
so don't be a pussy.
[Man #2]
Fuck you.
Go on now and talk to your friends.
[Knocking]
Lordy, Lordy, Lord. What?
You call that a knock?
Hands up, motherfucker!
Hands up! On the wall!
- [Shouting In Spanish]
- Get those paws on the wall!
We're clear.
Jesus Christ. Look at that.
Must be a couple of million there.
- [Static On Radio]
- Hold on, Roland.
- Kane-361. Shots fired.
- It's four.
It's code four.
Let's just get our thoughts together.
- We need backup.
- There's two million. Okay?
- Ain't nobody comin' to claim this.
- You're jokin', right, man?
The fuckin' informant must've skipped out.
She's not gonna tell anybody.
It's just you, me,
and these dead slingers here.
Motherfucker, I thought I knew you.
[Chuckles]
Relax, Roland.
- I'm just fuckin' around.
- I thought you was, man.
Jesus, Roland.
This could've been so much easier.
We could've taken the money,
and no one would've cared.
[Sighs]
Fuck goin' out on your knees, huh?
Any motherfucker can drop
from a heart attack...
take a pension, and move to Utah.
But not you, Roland.
You just became a hero.
[Grunts]
Come back and get you later.
This is D-63-Henry. I've got an officer down.
I need an ambulance stat.
[Man]
Yes, D-63. What is your present location?
Normandie and 107 th, southwest corner.
Copy that.
Ambulance and backup on its way.
Jesus, I think my partner's dying.
What's the E.T.A. On the ambulance?
I need it here now.
[Sighs]
Hell of a day, huh?
[Officer]
Are you sure you don't need ambulatory?
I'm fine.
I'm just trying to take it in.
I can't believe he's gone.
I mean, we were just talkin' about...
He had a pulse, Trevor.
- They're taking him to Harbor General.
- What?
- [Siren Wailing]
- The medics say it looks bad.
- But he ain't dead yet.
- No.
I saw him take his last breath.
He... He died.
Miracles happen, son.
Let's pray this is one of'em.
Look, I'm gonna have a couple guys
take you back to the station.
I want you to go in there and give your statement,
then take a couple days off.
- [Man] What do we have?
- [Man #2] Two shots to the chest.
B.P.'s dropping. Pulse, thready.
- Is O.R. 3 prepped?
- Yeah, it's all set.
- Team's prepped and ready.
- Watch the line. Watch the line.
Comin'through here!
Pupils nonresponsive.
- B.P. 's still dropping. Systolic... 75.
- [Continuous Beep]
- Charge the paddles. Clear.
- [Electrical Charge]
[Beeping]
Ten mics. Get it started.
Put a pad here.
[Beeping]
[Beeping Continues]
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Oh, Jesus.
It's hard to see him like this.
He's stable for right now.
There is brain activity.
But, unfortunately,
there's no way for us to tell...
when he'll regain consciousness.
He's my uncle. We work together.
- Give me a percentage.
- We can't estimate odds.
What we do know is ifhe doesn't
regain consciousness within the next 48 hours...
we'll have to run tests to determine whether
or not there's been some brain damage.
We'll need a statement if he becomes coherent.
The desk has my number.
Hold the elevator.
Roland. I gotta hand it to you.
You are one tough son of a bitch.
Shit. Damn it.
You see, here's the thing.
Your luck can only take you so far.
[Chuckles] I mean, hell.
You're the one that preached that.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
You'd thank me if you could, Roland.
I mean,
who wants to live like a vegetable anyway?
[Roland]
Fuck you!
[Gunshot]
Motherfucker.
You always got to have the last word.
[Gasps]
[Phone Ringing]
[Answering Machine Beeps]
[Roland On Machine]
I'm not available. Leave a message.
- [Beeps]
- [Woman] Hey, pick up. It's Regina.
Listen, I'm running late, but I'll swing by
this afternoon with the therapist.
I hear she's good. We can do this, Roland.
One day at a time, huh?
[Exhales Sharply]
I don't know why I can't
kick this stuff, man. I'm so tired of it.
Roland, you sustained injuries
that would kill most men.
The fact you're walking
is a miracle in itself.
With time,
you'll be able to throw those away.
I hope the time comes soon.
I've seen you do shit
that's beyond belief.
Hell, you're the inspiration for every guy
that ever applied for the SWAT team.
Well, you know what?
- I just wanna get back to work.
- You will.
[Knocks]
Hey. You ready for a walk?
Why not? A little bit of fresh air
would do me some good.
That's what I like to hear.
I'm proud of you, Roland.
So are a lot of others.
Texas? Isn't that a little out
of the neighborhood?
Not really. It's a great state, man.
I did some training there
and made some good friends.
- That chief of theirs... What's his name?
- Conner. Stand-up guy.
Good friend.
[Men Grunting]
What is up? How you doin'?
- I'm good. I'm good.
- Damn, girl, you are fine.
- [Clearing Throat]
- Uh, this is my dad, Conner Wells.
I'm tired of this shit, man.
[Exhales]
Oh, Lord.
[Yelling, Shouting]
- He's not supposed to be going that hard, Daddy.
- He looks great.
[Man]
That's it!
[Man #2]
Goodjob, Mason.
[Sighs]
##[House]
[Woman]
Mason! Mason!
- Oh, hey, baby.
- Hi.
[Indistinct]
- Come here, sweetheart.
- It's so exciting.
- You did all this for me?
- I did. I did it all for you.
- Huh?
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
- Well done, Mason. Nice to see you.
- Thank you, sir.
- [Chuckles]
- Let's toast to our success.
Cheers.
##[Continues]
[Mason]
Hey. Champagne over here.
Hey.
Mason.
Hey, baby.
You're drunk.
Yeah. So what, baby? What...
- What's happening? Hey, where...
- It's time to leave, Mason. Come on.
Leave? We just got here. What are you
talkin' about? Baby, we're just celebratin'.
- We're just celebratin'.
- Well, why don't you celebrate with me?
What made you mad?
I'm sorry, sweetheart. Hey.
- [Chuckles] Come here.
- [Chuckles]
Jorge, get the car. We're goin'.
It's too crowded. Let's take the elevator.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
[Bell Dings]
[Mason] Damn, you look good in
that little pink dress.
- You like that one I got you?
- [Chattering]
Watch your step there.
- [Giggles]
- Get in, baby. After you. After you.
- Okay.
- [Jorge] Here comes the paparazzi.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
- [Camera Shutters Clicking]
Mason, come on! Give us a photo!
Back away from the car.
[Moaning]
- Come on out and do it!
- Hey!
- [Shouting Continues]
- One picture outside, champ. Come on!
- Oh, baby. Oh, God.
- Oh, shit.
[Mason]
There's a lot of'em.
- [Groans]
- Just one minute.
No! Haven't you had enough?
Of course you haven't.
You boys have been following me all night.
Might as well give you a good shot.
Here you go, boys. Huh?
What, you want a shot? Not a mark on me.
- See that?
- [Man] That's it!
[Woman]
Jorge, I wanna go.
Back away from the car. Mason. Mason!
- Get back in the car. This is dangerous.
- Hey, just relax...
- Oh, God!
- [Yelling, Shouting]
[Screams]
No!
Mason!
- [Screaming] No!
- All right, let's move!
- Let's get out ofhere!
- No!
- Mason!
- Go, go, go!
Mason! Mason! No!
Stop the car! Stop...
[Breathing Heavily]
Help me!
[Birds Twittering]
- [Clears Throat]
- [Line Ringing]
[Phone Ringing]
[Answering Machine Beeps]
[Roland On Machine]
I'm not available. Leave a message.
When they officially closed
the investigation about Trevor...
I thought this was over, you know?
- That you'd be back the next morning.
- Yeah.
Well, you know, uh,
I guess that's what you get...
for 20 years of devotion and service.
You know,
no good deed goes unpunished.
It's like their special "Thank you" to me.
The medical board just won't approve
your rehab. They want you retired.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
- No. What?
- I'm gonna...
- [Phone Ringing]
- Hello?
- Roland.
[Chuckles]
Boy, it's good to hear your voice.
You know who this is?
I do. How you feeling, Connie?
Not bad for an old guy.
I take it life is treatin' you well?
Not bad. I'm off the force.
I just went out I.O.D.
- Everything's good, I guess.
- Well, I'll have to take your word for that.
I have a problem, Roland, and I think
you're the only man that can help me.
- What could I do for you, brother?
- It concerns Nikita.
- She all right?
- She's fine... for now.
But, uh... Look, it'd be best
if we could talk in person.
Well, if you'd like,
I'll head on out there tomorrow.
Oh, that's fantastic. I'll make all the arrangements.
My people will be in touch.
- Then I'll see you tomorrow.
- I'll send my plane for you.
- All right, brother.
- [Beeps]
[Sets Phone Down]
[Beeps]
- Mr. Sallinger?
- How you doin', sir?
Detective Simon. Good to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Welcome to town.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I make it a point...
to check the itineraries of all
the private charters that come in and out of here.
You know, with the dope problem
in this part of the world.
And, uh, your name popped up.
Well, I understand, uh,
you're an ex-cop, and in fact...
Yeah, back in the day. That's right.
I also understand you're retired.
Looks like you're, uh,
carrying quite a few firearms too.
You know,
I was a cop in L.A. For about 25 years.
I just came down to visit a friend.
Simple stuff.
Yeah, I understand that.
However, uh, I didn't call for any backup.
You're funny. No, you know how us cops are, man.
We can't go nowhere without our weapons.
- So that's how I roll.
- Yeah. See, this is my town.
So I hope there's no problem.
You just remember while you're here...
I'll be watching you.
Yes, sir.
Well, it's nice to have somebody on my back.
- Yeah, we'll see about that.
- All right.
- You have a good day.
- Thank you, sir.
[Car Door Closes]
- Roland Sallinger?
- Yeah.
Manuelo.
I'm the driver for Mr. Wells.
Oh, yeah?
[Spanish]
Mr. Wells apologizes for not being able
to pick you up personally.
He's at the mansion waiting for you.
Any, uh, wife? Kids? Future wife? Ex-wife?
Kids you don't know about, huh?
# [Whistling]
Yeah. Who... Who needs a radio...
with your kind of musical talents?
You like it? It's a Mexican folk song.
- Very popular. ##[Whistling]
- It's amazing.
Very nice.
[Woman Speaking Spanish]
What are you doing?
Hey, baby. You miss us?
- [Spits]
- Now, why you gotta do that, Allegra?
Men like girls who swallow,
not girls that spit.
Why don't you teach
your boyfriend how to swallow?
Did you hear that?
[Chuckles]
Why don't you tell me
where your brothers are?
Because frankly, um...
[Allegra Gasping]
[Manuelo]
Is that my cousin?
- I don't know where they're at.
- You don't know?
- I don't know.
- Why don't you just fuckin' know, okay?
It is my cousin. Allegra!
Oh, man.
No!
You don't have to protect 'em, baby.
Okay?
- Come on...
- That's my cousin, man!
- [Grunts] Get out of here!
- Stop! Leave him alone!
- What's up?
- We got a problem.
Her brothers owe us some money.
Yo, what's the problem?
- That's the problem, motherfucker.
- [Coughs]
Motherfucker, I'm gonna cut you up!
Listen to me, man.
When somebody pull a knife on me, I kill him.
But then, I got another rule.
I don't kill children.
Which rule you want me to follow?
Don't kill children.
Y'all, come on.
- Die, motherfucker!
- No. No, no, no.
You don't wanna kill me, do you?
All right, come on.
Motherfucker, you're gonna die!
[Bone Breaks]
Listen to me.
Listen to me. I told you.
- [Groaning]
- I don't like to kill children.
Don't make me kill you.
Let's go.
You're lucky.
You don't know who you're messing with!
- [Man #2] This ain't over, motherfucker!
- Hey!
Y'all forgot your knife, man.
Gracias.
[Spanish]
[Engine Starts]
- [Tires Screeching]
- Enrique. Gustavo.
- Take care of your sister.
- Gracias.
- [Spanish]
- You all right?
[Allegra]
Yeah, I'm okay.
[Spanish]
[Manuelo]
Senor Wells's office is right to the right.
Right there.
- [Both Speaking Spanish]
- [Conner] Well, I'll be!
[Laughs]
Roland, it's been too long.
[Spanish]
Now, I have to apologize
for the phone security.
What security?
Damn it, let's talk.
- This way.
- Yes, sir.
- Have a seat, Roland.
- Thank you.
Make yourself comfortable.
Good to see you, partner.
Good to see you too.
See the beast out there?
- You still drivin' that piece of shit?
- Yeah.
- What's that about?
- I'll tell you, it brings back a lot of memories.
[Chuckles]
Well, yeah, I know what that's like.
Now, I'll tell you one thing, Roland.
When you're in Texas,
you gotta look Texas.
Lord, that's beautiful.
Thank you so much, man.
- I'm glad you like it.
- You know, my daddy's family's from Texas...
so I still remember
a little bit about this.
Tell me, what's going on?
- Someone tried to kidnap Nikita.
- You have any idea who?
Well, not really.
You have any idea why?
My station in life has changed.
I'm a wealthy man once again.
See, after my father passed away,
the oil in his land started flowing.
Well, why can't you just call the police?
I mean...
In this part ofTexas, there are people
who feel that race determines a man's value.
These same men control everything...
- except me.
- All right.
What do you want me to do?
I need for you to take care
of Nikita personally.
I mean...
I'm not much of a babysitter, but, uh...
I need for you to be her bodyguard.
You know, buddy,
I kind of have a feeling...
there's just something you're not telling me
that's real important.
Someone inside my organization
may be an enemy.
Well, that changes things a little bit, man.
That changes the dynamics quite a bit.
Roland, you're the only one I can trust.
Uh, all right.
- Well, what... what can I do?
- Nikita's outside.
She hasn't been off the estate
since it happened.
- But, hell, I can't keep her locked up forever.
- Well, listen.
You got surveillance cameras here
that don't work.
You got direct line of sight
into your windows.
I don't know much about your staff.
If you let me set up your security
the way it's gotta be...
and you listen to everything I say...
So we have a deal?
I'll bodyguard Nikita for you.
I'll make sure nothing happens to her.
Thank you. I knew I could count on you.
- Yes, sir.
- Now, let's get you settled.
Could you take this for me?
Thank you.
Baby, there's somebody here to see you.
Who's this?
You don't remember Roland?
Um... Roland.
Oh, my God! How are you?
- How have you been?
- All right. How about you, baby?
- Good.
- Now, we need a replacement forJorge.
- Yeah.
- And, hell, Roland's practically family...
- and an expert at these types of things.
- Right.
What do you think?
If I say yes,
does that mean I get to leave the house?
- [Vehicle Approaching]
- Yeah?
- Yes, ma'am, you do.
- Okay.
Um...So, Roland,
would you get me a cup of coffee?
Oh, right away.
Would you like a massage too?
Nikita, he's not your servant. You need to
treat him with the respect he deserves.
L... I do respect him, Daddy.
It's just that, um, thatJorge
used to bring me everything I asked for.
I understand. Jorge was her bodyguard.
- We lost him in the ambush.
- I see.
- We were all very close to him.
- Mason.
- Hey, baby.
- Daddy hired a new head of security.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Roland, meet Mason.
- Hey, man.
I'm financing his boxing career.
And judging by the winnin' streak he's on,
it might just pay off.
- Guess what this means, baby.
- What?
- I get to go out again.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- Well, come on.
- I wanna show you something. It's a surprise.
- Okay.
It was nice to see you.
- [Laughing]
- [Roland] Gonna be a lot of work.
Well, if I'm gonna do this,
a few things are gonna have to change.
Of course. You have complete autonomy.
And Victor's very loyal.
- He'll do everything you ask. You're the boss.
- [Chattering, Laughing]
[Nikita]
Ooh, can we go out? Can we go out?
- Hey, listen, you're not gonna drive this car.
You understand?
- Can I drive it?
Roland, the inventory's arrived.
Is that everything?
- Looks perfect.
- Good.
- Thank you, man.
- Very well.
Hey, Niki,
I got a little something for ya.
Yeah. You see here?
I have plenty of necklaces.
Listen, you ain't got one like this.
You know why? It's a transponder.
It's kind of ugly.
Turn around. You know what that means?
That means wherever you go,
I can find you.
That tickles.
What's the matter? Don't you like women?
- I love women.
- Nikita.
- What?
- Come on. Get a move on. We're waitin' for ya.
- I'm coming.
- You're the boss's daughter.
[Mason]
Come on. Get a move on.
- You look good. Is he comin' too?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he's comin'.
[Beeping, Whirring]
##[House]
There you go, sweetheart. Keep it.
Who's that white guy over there?
Him?
Jason Cross.
Very powerful man. Very dangerous.
Very dangerous. Should I be scared?
You? Maybe not.
- You have a good time, all right?
- Come on, buddy.
I'll be up in a little bit.
Go easy on him.
Here. All right. Let me try that.
[Snorting]
[Exhales Sharply]
Get your som' bitch over here.
Aw, shit.
Y'all are gonna get me in trouble,
you know that?
##[Continues]
Mason. I need
to talk to you for a second.
- What, right now?
- Yeah, right now.
Hold that thought.
You son of a bitch, you.
- Oh, this guy.
- Mason.
You know I'd never ask you
to do anything you didn't wanna do.
But I'd like you
to consider something for me.
Think about your fight plan.
There's plenty of this for all of us,
if you know what I'm talking about.
Mmm. That's some good shit. Take it easy.
Watch the boy.
Don't let him get into any more trouble.
You know, I got kicked out of Boy Scouts
for eatin' brownies.
[Mock Laugh]
You are so drunk.
- What are you doin'?
- [Man] Aw, come on. Are you serious?
You guys are dressed
like loin cloth-wearing Vikings.
- But by all means...
- Right, and you love that.
- Oh, my God. What?
- I'm not ready to go.
- What do you wanna do?
- I wanna stay.
- You wanna stay?
- What, you didn't hear her?
Fuckin'stuck on stupid?
I'll tell you what. Why don't you go park
the car and meet us around back.
Matter of fact, go to the grocery store
and get some chips.
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Do what...
[Yelling]
Let him go!
- [Man] Better get security.
- Oh, God.
Hey! Hey, Nikita! Where you goin', man?
Hey, what'd you do, man?
Those are friends of mine. You know that?
- Those are friends of mine!
- Back off! Okay?
There's no excuse for the way they act.
None.
- Unbelievable. Where are you goin'? Huh?
- [Elevator Bell Dings]
- You're goin' with him now?
- Yeah. What are you gonna do about it?
- I'm leaving.
- That sounds great. You two have fun.
Fuck it, man. Let's go. Come on.
[Nikita] No, Daddy. Mason's getting
arrogant and out of control.
- And I'm just so sorry that
I wasted all this time with him.
- Nikita...
Daddy, he's in love with his fame, not me!
But he's no different
than any other guy his age.
Men who get too much too fast
always make idiots of themselves.
I wish that Roland would have
knocked him on his ass as well.
What?
Did you just smile?
Yeah. Looks good.
Where's the ex-cop?
- Always the detective.
- Yep. Where is he, Victor?
He's in town.
He needed some medicine from the pharmacy.
- You wanna talk to me about the fight at the bar?
- Fight?
People from L.A. What can I say?
Ballistic nylon. Advanced stuff.
He's a smart guy. Knows a lot.
You better watch him.
If he becomes a problem,
you and your boss will pay the price.
I'll let him know.
Yeah, you do that.
[Victor]
Escort him out.
- What, you think I forgot about you?
- I have some questions.
- About the kidnapping attempt.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Wells has a lot of enemies out this way,
most from past business dealings.
- Why else would he need you?
- Well, the thing of it is, we're just friends.
And, uh, I feel like
I can help him out a little bit.
You know, with security issues and stuff.
We both were cops together.
- Things like that.
- Well, he's not a cop anymore.
Well, neither am I.
[Chuckles]
Your friend's involved
with some rough people.
- Like Cross.
- Yep.
They've had dealings in the past
when Conner's father ran a business.
- He sees an opportunity.
- Let me ask you something.
What do you know about Cross?
He's organized,
and I believe he's a violent separatist.
You know, he believes
whites and Mexicans shouldn't mix.
[Chuckles]
Crazy.
We've been after him for years,
but, hell, nobody will talk to us about him.
Listen. You wanna help your friend...
and I want Cross.
I don't know.
Maybe we can help each other here.
Now, you see,
that's what I'm talkin' about.
Both cops tryin' to help each other.
Man, let me know what I can do.
- All right.
Hey, Nikita. Roland's back.
Is everything okay? You feel safe now?
I do.
- I like him, Daddy.
- You do?
- I do. I like him.
- Good.
He makes me feel safe.
I don't think I've ever felt that safe
with anybody before.
Except for you, Daddy.
But there's something about him though,
you know?
He's... He's lonely,
but he won't ever show it.
- Well, I think he's a good man.
- I know.
I never would've
entrusted you to him if I didn't.
I know.
Well, I think
I'll take him shopping tomorrow.
[Laughs]
Good.
Oh, my God. I'm so glad to see
you're back to your old self. Oh!
- After what you've been through, I'm proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Well, I gotta get back to some work.
- Okay.
- All right.
Thank you, darling.
Hi.
I'm hungry, and there's nothing to eat.
- Well, I'll give you half of this one.
- You would?
- I will give you half of this one.
- [Chuckles]
Okay. I'm gonna take it.
I miss Jorge.
Well, you know how it is.
It's, like, people become bodyguards...
and they know it's a risk.
Sometimes they have to pay the ultimate price.
And I guess he did.
But it seems like
the good news in this instance is that...
you give him the ultimate gratitude.
Did you know that, um...
that Manuelo and Jorge were half brothers?
- No.
- No?
He told me once. We kinda kept it quiet...
because there were, like,
two of them living here right now.
And they're from the same city in Mexico,
and they're really close-knit.
They don't really ever tell anybody...
their personal business
if they don't trust them.
It's kinda cool.
Well, I mean, you know,
folks like that, that's the way they are.
Every time I close my eyes,
I still see that man...
in the parking structure shooting him.
Well, that's a terrible thing
for a young girl like you to witness.
- It's a lot to bear.
- Yeah.
We thought they were paparazzi,
and that's why Mason made them stop the car.
Well, you see, here's the thing.
I'm here now.
So shit's gonna be different.
It's like a nightmare.
- It isn't over, is it?
- It's not over.
But I'm gonna make it over soon.
I promise you that.
Look, I, um...
I'm sorry if I act stupid sometimes.
I just... I just wanted to let you know...
that I really appreciate
what you're doing for me.
You're welcome.
Yeah. It was pretty cool
what you did to Mason's friends.
I didn't know people
could fight like that. It was awesome.
- Well, I kinda, you know... I faked it.
- [Chuckling]
You know what you're doing.
I got lucky.
- Do you always eat like that?
- No.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, what was I telling you?
Are you sure we can't have something
with a little more kick?
Crazy, man? We're working, boy.
Why not? You're the bodyguard.
I'm just a driver.
- How about we don't drink on the job?
- Okay. Okay.
- [Spanish]
- I'll just drink the water.
Sí.
- [Retching, Coughing]
- Lord.
- She do this often?
- Every Friday night.
- Man.
- And most Saturdays.
Sometimes Tuesdays. And Wednesdays.
That's no good, bubba.
- Are you okay?
- Just take me home, please.
- She okay. She okay.
- [Roland] Baby girl...
what is wrong with you?
[Sighs] Mason stayed at the club
with his friends...
and he won't answer his phone.
Well, you know what?
- I'm sure he'll call you soon.
- Yeah. He will.
There's... There's something you...
There's something you gave me
as a little girl.
- Baby, you're still little.
- [Chuckles]
- What's that?
- It was an ornate umbrella from Siam.
It's really, really beautiful, and...
it was handmade
and painted really distinctly.
I can't believe you remember that.
And you said you got it
in Northern Thailand.
And then you told me all these cool stories
about how they were made.
It was really awesome.
Daddy told me
that you lived in Asia for a while.
Right after... after, uh... after the army.
- Is that true?
- Yes, ma'am. Back in the day.
That's back when it was called Siam.
They don't call it Siam anymore.
[Chuckles]
I still have that umbrella in my room.
It's just as beautiful
as the day that you gave it to me.
I'm really moved about that.
Maybe you could take me there one day.
I would love to. I would really love to.
I mean, not as... you know, as my bodyguard.
- Be my guest.
- Okay. I'd like that.
- Can I get you home now?
- Yeah.
Come on.
[Truck Engine Starting]
[Engine Starting]
[Roland]
Okay. Let's see what you're up to.
Good, good. How are you?
- A little late, punchy.
- [Scoffs]
So what's up? What'd I come here for?
Hmm?
- Talk to us.
- Where's Mr. Cross?
- I'm here.
- All right. I understand.
Well, since you're here,
I'll tell you then.
Tell Mr. Cross thank you very much
for his offer, but no, thanks.
- [Man] What?
- [Man #2] No, thanks.
- Did you hear that?
- Yep.
You know, he is tough.
- What the...
- You know...
Well, listen, sweetie...
Get your fuckin' hands...
You know what these things are made of?
- Watch this.
- Oh!
What are you,
some kind of psychopath, man, or what?
- Get your...
- Relax!
Are you... Huh!
Goddamn it.
All right, man. All right, listen. Listen.
Listen. I know what you guys are after.
You want the girl, right? Nikita.
I know what's on that old man's land.
It don't bother me none what y'all do.
All right?
Just keep it between us,
and real quiet, we can do some business.
You want the girl, you can get her.
We'll be calling.
You have a good day, huh?
Take care, sweetie.
You're on my list, man.
Oh, shit.
[Truck Starting]
[Car Starting]
Victor, I ain't got time
for this shit, man.
[Victor]
We have to check everybody coming in. You too.
- Through in there?
- Standard procedure.
Go on. Get out of here.
[Beeping]
Roland's gonna be mad
when he finds out we left.
What do you care what he thinks?
What? Suddenly you two
are best buddies now, or what?
Why not? He is a good guy.
[Sighs]
Jesus Christ.
- Where are we going?
- Relax. Shortcut, babe.
Mason.
[Tires Screech]
Get out of the car now!
I said get out of the car now!
- Mason, do something. Do something!
- Just do what they say.
Get out of the car!
[Nikita]
Roland! Help me!
- [Grunting]
- [Shouting]
[Machine Gun Firing]
No!
[Air Hissing]
[Gunshots Continue]
Sit tight.
Kill him!
[Gunshots]
Her bodyguard's tailing me.
Get him off my ass!
We're headed north on Flores.
Sit back! Get out of the way!
- No!
- Aaah!
[Groaning]
[Nikita]
Roland! Roland!
No!
Get off the bike! Get on that damn bike!
[Sirens Approaching]
Don't move!
Hands where we can see 'em!
Come on now. Get down.
Get down on your knees!
These folks tried to kill me
and kidnap my friend.
- Get down on your knees.
- Yes, sir. [Sighs]
Cover me.
Suspect in custody. Call it in.
Don't start with me, Roland, okay?
There's a lot of folks around here...
think I oughta have you downstairs in
the interview room handcuffed to a steel chair.
But you're here out of professional courtesy.
And that's all I can do.
Man, I appreciate that.
I suggest you contact a lawyer.
This might be Texas, but it's not the Wild West.
You can't just shoot people
in the streets and get away with it.
Look, even a civilian,
if he saw a kidnapping in progress...
would have the obligation
to try to do something.
- That's all I did.
- That's for the courts to decide.
And let me tell you this.
They're dead, and you're not.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
There is no case. It was self-defense.
[Man On Phone] Self-defense? He shot
three people. He stabbed a guy in the neck.
We have no witnesses.
John, if you find that he was in the wrong,
he will appear.
I give you my word. That's right.
Thank you, John.
- We don't have time for this. They work for Cross.
- I know.
I seen 'em together.
Tory Harris.
He's one of Cross's lieutenants.
I know.
[Whispering, Indistinct]
Something's come up. I'll be back.
Please, you stay here.
You owe Wells. That's not right.
What about police work?
This guy killed three people in the street.
Now do something about this.
Excuse me. You're free to go.
Goddamn it!
I spoke to Allegra like you asked.
She'll be happy to meet us
at our church tonight.
[Man, Indistinct]
[Man #2]
Yeah, Frank's doing that.
Exactly what are you doing
about finding my daughter?
We can't find her
until we know why she was taken.
- You say there've been no ransom demands.
- None.
Three of the dead kidnappers
were associates ofJason Cross.
Forgive me for being blunt...
but we know you've had business dealings
with Mr. Cross in the past.
For your daughter's sake,
I urge you not to hide anything from us.
[No Audible Dialogue]
You know everything
you need to know, Detective. Find Nikita.
There's one other thing.
Roland Sallinger was released
from custody this afternoon...
with the help, I'm sure,
of a phone call from you.
You really think that was a wise move?
I helped see the chief was appointed.
He knows my word is my bond.
Now leave Roland Sallinger alone.
He's got nothing to do with this.
That's not what Mason Silver says.
So what? He can't be trusted.
If you have no idea who did this or why...
how can you be so sure he's innocent?
'Cause I trust him.
Now please leave.
It's late, and I got other business to attend to.
If the kidnappers contact you,
I want to know immediately.
[Phone Dialing]
[Phone Ringing]
- Hello.
- So are you ready to talk now?
- Where's my daughter?
- She's safe.
Thanks.
Whether she stays that way is up to you.
Look, it's gonna take more time.
There's paperwork that needs to be filed.
Twenty-four hours, Conner!
Not a minute more.
It won't take long after the news is
announced for people to figure this out.
Yeah. Well, you know,
intelligence equals power, Conner.
I know about the uranium now.
You want to see
your sweet little Nikita back...
you can transfer over the land...
and five million in cash and diamonds.
- I want to make sure she's alive.
- [Beeps]
- [Dial Tone]
- Do you hear me, Cross? Hello?
Let's go.
[Car Engine Starting]
- Are you in contact with Roland?
- Yes, sir. Manuelo is with him.
Find him.
- Are we late?
- I don't know where he is.
Just sit tight.
- I'll be right back, okay?
- Okay.
- [Speaking Spanish]
- Uh...
Victor said he wanted certain items along
with five million in 24 hours.
- [Chuckling] Pendejo, no.
- Sí.
You, uh, have an address on Mason yet?
Yeah, I got an address. And...
I thought you might need these.
You wanna give me this in a church?
You are sacrilegious.
I don't know where else
to give 'em to you.
Look, I'm a little nervous, okay?
[Laughing]
[Spanish]
Okay.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Sí. Sí.
You're fine. You know that?
Sit right here on this couch.
Right here.
Let me see now.
- Wanna see this?
- Yeah.
Shit.
Sit like that. Stay still now.
This is good shit here. Hold on. [Sniffs]
[Woman Moans]
What the fuck are you two looking at?
Play your cards, man.
Come here.
Roland, I did not have a choice.
They asked me to throw the fight.
I said I would not do it.
They...
I let my pride get in the way.
I fucked up.
Listen. Let me ask you a question.
Did your pride get in the way...
when you set up her getting kidnapped?
Look, man, they said they were gonna kill me.
I don't... l-l...
l-I know you're not gonna believe me, man,
but I love Nikita.
I wouldn't want to hurt her in any way.
They told me they wouldn't harm her.
- It was her or me. You understand?
- Uh-huh.
You're supposed to be
protecting her if you love her.
You understand? Now where is she?
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
You see these two
dead motherfuckers right here?
That's how you gonna look in about five minutes.
You hear me?
All right. I was supposed to meet them
at Hermano's Restaurant.
It's over on the other side of town.
Let me ask you another question.
This is kind of a deep, esoteric question.
Come here, baby.
Sit up here.
- Manuelo.
- Sí.
- What's wrong with this picture?
- She's in his lap?
Uh-huh.
You know what's wrong with this picture?
Niki's out there
in all kinds of jeopardy right now...
and you're in here fucking around
with some stanky ho...
tryin' to have a good time.
Now I'm gonna put you
in the same jeopardy she's in.
You understand? Let's go.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Chattering In Spanish]
- [Phone Ringing]
- See when that property's transferred.
- Yeah, let's do it. Let's telephone the area.
- I have the file right here.
- Hello?
- [Cross] Conner.
Hey, buddy. Time's runnin' out.
- I'm workin' on it.
- Good, good. Are we on schedule?
Yes.
- What?
- I want to speak to my daughter.
Well, she's not available right now.
But don't worry. You'll see her soon.
- When?
- Tomorrow. 8:00.
When I have those property deeds.
- [Chattering]
- [Beeps]
[Sighs]
Ma'am?
Do you think Nikita's here?
No, I don't. That man Cross is not stupid.
- [Indistinct]
- There's a lot at stake, whatever it is.
- They know the police have been here.
- For sure.
- What are you gonna do?
- When they leave, we will follow.
[No Audible Dialogue]
You sure he's got no guns?
Okay. They've got Mason in the car.
[Sighs]
Thank you very much.
Y'all have a good evening.
- Man, I already did everything y'all asked me to do.
- Get.
- [Engine Starting]
- We got a problem.
- That's him.
- Get down over there right now.
[Grunts]
Roland, I'm shot!
Manuelo, out of the way. You guys, go.
You're okay.
Stay down. Stay down and stay out of it.
[Man On TV] And it looks like another
beautiful day tomorrow in San Antonio.
We're gonna have sunny skies
with highs in the mid 70s.
And the lows are gonna be in the high 50s.
Uh, now, next with sports...
[Roland]
I think we need to talk.
- Roland, how'd you get in here?
- [Sighs]
You know, I did design the security system.
I think you know that.
Of course. So what'd you find out?
Well, I found out that Mason set you up.
But I think you know that.
[Exhales]
I suspected as much.
My daughter trusted him with information
that he now uses against us.
What kind of information might that be?
And what does he want for it?
Five million dollars in cash and diamonds.
I thought Manuelo told you that.
Well, you know,
somehow I kind of feel like...
there's a little bit more than that.
You see, five million to a guy like that
ain't much compared to what's at stake here.
- So tell me what's going on.
- I don't know what you mean.
I feel like you're not leveling with me.
We're friends.
I'm sorry. You're right.
I'm sorry.
Cross and I grew up together.
He chose a life of crime,
and I became a cop.
- Do you know my family owns a lot of property?
- Yes, sir, I do.
One of the properties we own
was a tapped-out oil field.
He wasn't interested in the property.
What he's interested in is this.
We went in to re-tap the oil wells...
and we've discovered something
much more valuable.
Uranium.
Make a long story short...
I found one of the richest deposits
of uranium in the history of North America.
And that's what you're pulling up now.
Some. Got a lot more work to do.
That makes sense.
I knew there was something.
If I sign those papers tomorrow night,
everything I have...
everything I have worked for
will be torn away.
And I don't give a damn.
I just want Nikita back.
But I don't have a choice.
Let me tell you something. You do have a choice.
You're not gonna sign those papers.
Where's the drop?
Up in the hills.
He's built a new hacienda.
I know it well. I have the plans.
I'm gonna get your daughter back.
You don't worry about nothin'.
I give you my word. You hear?
[Groans]
Man.
[Roland Speaks Spanish]
Thank you for coming.
Mmm. They don't talk much, those two.
- Yeah? Well, can they shoot?
- Yeah.
They can shoot.
[Engine Starts]
So you know how many guys
are gonna be there?
Enough to make it interesting.
[Spanish]
Thank you, Tory.
[Sighs]
Just a few more hours, sweetheart,
and this will all be over.
- I want to see my father.
- Oh, you will. You will.
I promise.
[Sobbing]
- Mason?
- I risked a lot for this, Cross.
I just want to know
when I'm gonna get paid.
You'll get your money tonight as promised.
Now, Mason, please, get outta here.
Mason, what's he talking about?
Mason, answer me!
And I want that bodyguard dead too, Cross.
We're lookin' for him.
Don't worry about it.
He'll be dead before dawn.
- Now let's go.
- [Nikita] You son of a bitch.
- You son of a bitch! I hope you die!
- [Cross] Stay calm.
Emotions get you nothing.
[Sobbing]
No!
Let's do it. Come on.
- [Knocking]
- [Simon] Yeah, come in.
What the hell is this?
Shit!
[Phone Beeping]
All right, fellas. This is it. Let's go.
Goin' to see your daddy.
Mason, when we get there...
keep your eyes open, okay?
Just look around.
I'm sure he won't be alone.
- He's not comin' alone.
- You keep your eyes open.
Come on. Let's go. Move it.
Come on. Let's go.
[Engine Starting]
- What's the plan?
- Stay out of sight, and I'll let you know.
- All right.
- [Sniffles]
You know, um, those rifles,
they look like they're from the Civil War.
Do you think they'll work?
- They'll do fine. I promise.
- Okay.
All right.
Daddy!
Go, go, go, go!
Cross!
No need to shout.
- You Judas son of a bitch.
- [Scoffs]
Should've shown me
some more respect, old man.
Boy, you can kiss my ass.
- Where's Nikita?
- First things first. Let's see those documents.
- [Man] Exchange is goin'down.
- [Tory] You keep your eyes open
for that bodyguard.
Looks like you upheld
your end of the bargain for once.
What about the money, Cross?
Satisfied?
[Whistles]
- Daddy.
- It's okay, baby.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You got what you wanted. Now let her go.
You'll get your daughter.
This is Lucien.
- Lucien, say again.
- [Gagging]
What's goin' on?
- Got a problem.
- You're right about that, Tory.
- Who is this?
- Now tell your bitches to drop their guns.
- [Gasps]
- Or we'll kill every fuckin' one of you.
Fuckin' bodyguard. He's here.
What a waste. What a sad, pathetic waste.
- Mr. Cross, pages are missing.
These contracts are useless!
- You're a fool.
- Kill her, Tory!
- Daddy!
Wait!
[Nikita Screaming]
- Nikita!
- [Indistinct]
[Nikita Screaming]
Son of a...
[Nikita Groans]
[Both Groaning]
Kill you.
No! Roland! Roland!
[Clicking]
[Sirens Approaching]
There they are. Let's go.
[Cross Chortling]
Conner, you pull that trigger,
you'll never see your daughter again.
This is the police. Put the gun down.
I know what you're feeling.
But you have to let us handle this.
I can't.
[Simon]
No, you're wrong.
[Nikita Groaning]
Keep moving or I'll kill you right here.
Behind me. Take him out.
- [Nikita] Let me go.
- [Tory] Shut up!
Let me go!
Stay down!
[Groans]
[Clicking]
[Stammers]
Okay, I give up.
Yeah. Well, after you're dead maybe.
Fuck it.
Mi casa tu casa, motherfucker!
[Groaning]
Get the fuck off me!
Roland.
[Panting, Gasping]
- Okay. You all right?
- [Crying] Yeah.
- I knew you'd save me.
- Yeah.
Conner, we have plenty
of evidence to convict him.
Now put the gun down.
Come on, Conner. We're all cops together.
Listen to me. Put it down.
[Cross Groaning]
[Grunting]
Simon, you're a pig!
Your mother's a whore!
Mason, don't tell 'em anything.
Get that son of a bitch in the van.
Carry on.
Yeah.
[Spanish]
Nikita, you okay? Oh!
[Crying]
I'm so sorry.
- I owe you my life.
- Well, brother, let's go.
[Sighs]