Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Come in.
Vanessa, please have a seat.
Allison has been telling me an
interesting story that I'd like you to verify.
A story about what?
About a visit you made with her
and Miyuki Nazawa to a certain house.
I'm sorry, Miss Dale,
but I don't know what she told you.
Please, Vanessa,
no one is in trouble here.
I just need to find out exactly
what happened in that house.
Miyuki is missing.
We just got the call.
Apparently she never came home
last night.
She said she was going to be
with her boyfriend, Michael.
Yes, we've spoken with him.
He said she disappeared.
Now you can understand, Vanessa,
how important it is that we hear the truth.
Why did you do this to me?
Why did you take me to that place?
You wanted to come.
What did I ever do to you?
Allison, wait!
Wait here.
Miyuki?
Miyuki... is that you?
- Wait here.
- No, II... want --
Please. Just stay here.
Eason...
Aubrey...
please don't go in that house.
Aubrey! What are you doing in here?
Something pulled me in.
- I told you to stay outside.
- I didn't know...
We have to go. Now.
Kayako kept this journal her whole life.
She was only eight
when she wrote this part.
I don't understand it,
but it looks creepy as hell.
It's not creepy. It's sad.
Apparently, her mother was an Itako.
Itako? What is that?
It's a kind of channeler.
People believe they can talk with
deceased loved ones through them.
But... I don't understand this part.
I have a friend. He's really into folklore.
I think he can help us.
This is not Itako.
Wait.
This person who is written in diary
did channeler, but...
I can't say
this is channeler exactly.
I mean, something...
He says what Kayako wrote was about
the rituaIs her mother performed...
and how they were somewhat abnormal.
I can't explain it in English.
Shaman...
Exorcist.
It must be named Exorcist.
There's no real word to
describe it in English, but...
the closest thing would be 'exorcist'.
She did this to her daugter.
Take demon away from
people's mind or body.
- What is it?
- She let daugter eat
- Eason...?
- demon everyday.
Eason!
I've never heard bout it.
It... it sounds like her mother
was able to cure people
through extracting evil spirits...
out of their bodies...
and feeding them to her daughter.
What?
First thing tomorrow
morning we have to go see her.
See who?
Kayako's mother.
I've tried everything.
I even went back to the house. I...
Look...
if she can really take evil spirits
out of people, maybe she can help us.
I don't know what to believe any more.
We don't have a choice.
It's our only hope.
Okay.
This is the research
I was doing for the story.
I've got her childhood address...
right here.
It's a small village.
The train will only take us haIfway.
We'lI have to switch to a bus.
Last time I saw Karen,
we got into this huge fight.
It was really stupid.
She took me out to lunch and she
dropped this college application on me...
and I... I was just...
I was so pissed.
I thought she was trying to be
just like my mother.
I screamed at her to stop trying
to change my life and leave me alone.
She did.
We never spoke again until last night.
I always, I always blamed Karen for
my mother's indifference towards me.
But I know that wasn't true,
and I really...
I really regret...
Well, you know, it's strange.
Back in Hong Kong, my brother lived
a few blocks away from me for four years.
We never even tried to see each other.
I'll make some tea.
Yeah, thanks.
Eason?
Eason? Are you in here?
Eason...
Eason... Eason!
Eason!
Jeez, you sick or something?
So... what do you think?
Sally, are you okay?
Jake?
No, it's okay.
I'll be right there.
I have to go.
Jake?
God!
Jake. What are you doing in here?
I... I was scared.
What were you scared of?
Trish.
And Dad.
They were fighting, Lacey.
Where are they?
I... I don't know...
But I wish Mom was here.
Jake...
Mr. Fleming?
Hi...
What's wrong, Jake?
I went next door and I...
- You went where?
- Next door.
I saw something in the window -- eyes.
It's all right, Jake. It's okay.
Something is really wrong, Lacey.
Tomorrow l promise
I'll go there with you. Okay?
Just try and get some sleep now.
Dammit!
You got home late last night.
Where were you?
Come in.
Allison...
Allison, are you all right?
Maybe we should go see the nurse.
I want to go home.
Take a breath.
Tell me what's going on.
You can talk to me.
It was that house.
There was something there
when I was there.
I...
I just want to go home.
Allison, Listen...
I've been to that house with the police.
There's nothing there.
It's just an abandoned house.
You... went there?
Yes, I did.
She's going to come for you.
She got Miyuki and Vanessa...
and now she's after me.
Allison...
I don't know what you're talking about.
- What?
- They are right here.
Hello?
I need to speak to you about
your daughter Kayako.
I saw the journal.
I know you can get rid of evil spirits.
She is dead.
You did this.
You made her what she was.
Now, I need you to help me
help me end this.
Wait...!
People came looking for me.
Full of pain and suffering...
I took the dark spirits from them.
And so did my daughter.
You poisoned her.
Look what she has become.
I didnot create this evil.
Kayako was killed by her
husband because she was foolish.
That is where the curse started.
I didnot make her what she is now.
My sister tried to burn down
the house where Kayako was killed.
She thought if she burned down
the house that it would stop?
This is not about a house.
You are just making things worse.
This is rage.
She wants us to suffer the way
she has suffered.
- No. We have to make it stop.
- No, it will not stop.
It will grow
and destroy everything it touches.
It will spread beyond the house.
There can be no end to what has started.
You brought her here.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Something bad.
What?
Something bad lives there.
That is what's making
everything eIse bad here.
Come on, Jake.
Let's go.
Dad...?
Trish?
Just wait here.
Dad? Trish?
Hello?
Hi, Mom, it's me.
I've been waiting for you.
Where have you been?
How is Karen?
She's gone, mom.
- I'm sorry.
- She's gone?
I know how much you loved her. I...
I know she was everything to you.
Why have you done this? You were...
You were supposed to bring her back!
You could never do anything
on your own
I love you so much...
but you can't talk to me
like this any more.
This has to end.
Aubrey...!
- Aubrey!
- I love you, Mom. Goodbye.
My sister is dead.
You killed her...
just like you killed the others.
You won't stop. Why?
What do you want?
Doug?
Wait... Karen!
Karen?
Karen, no!
Lacey!
Lacey! Lacey!
No. no
Lacey!
- No!
- Jake.
It's time for your bath.
Karen?
They say this is one of the most
haunted houses...
in all of Japan.
Yeah.
And that anyone who goes
inside gets the curse.
All the other girIs
have been too afraid to try.
Only me and Miyuki
have been able to do it so far.
Help me!
Please, you have to help me!
He killed her.
He snapped her neck.
If you close your eyes
and count to ten...
when you open them again,
you'll see her.
It's all your fauIt!
What did you do?
What did you bring here?
It followed me here.
They followed me here.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org