Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I believe you.
Your child will need a father.
I will declare him as my own.
People, they will not look at you the same.
They will not look at us the same.
You are my wife.
I am your husband.
That is all anyone need know.
And after this...
there shall arise a star from Jacob.
And a man shall arise like the sun...
walking with the sons of men
in gentleness and righteousness.
This is the shoot of God most high.
This is the fountain of life,
of all humanity.
You see, Gaspar...
that's why we follow the star.
Rome is requesting a census.
Each man to return
to the place of his birth.
Such an order will lead to unrest.
The people whisper
of rebellion even now.
It is the will of Caesar.
My father lost his life...
because he failed to see the threat...
that was mounting against him.
From his own people.
Now, all it will take is one man.
One man to convince the people
he is their Messiah.
The prophet said this man will rise
from the house of David.
This census
would bring him back home.
Have your soldiers and your spies...
keep watch for a man
returning to Bethlehem.
A man of power.
A man the people will follow.
Town of Nazareth...
in the name of King Herod
and the almighty Caesar...
you are ordered to participate
in a census of all people.
Each man will return
to the land of his ancestors...
along with each member of his family.
And what if it's a four-day journey?
Then you would be wise to leave soon.
You have one month!
And any resistance will be dealt with.
A census can only mean one thing.
More taxes for Herod.
- Does that surprise you?
- Ha ha!
I cannot register here.
The order was for each man...
to travel to the place of his ancestors.
I must go to Bethlehem.
But the journey to Bethlehem
is more than a hundred miles.
I know.
For me and for each member of my family.
They will allow her to stay.
- They cannot expect you...
- They will allow nothing.
Mother...
the days before my child comes...
are greater than those of this journey.
There is time.
That is a question
for God to decide, not you.
I'm going with my husband.
Then you must leave in the morning.
Take the animal.
No. No.
Take it, Joseph.
Thank you.
I will protect
your daughter and the child...
with all that I am, I promise you.
There is no well
before the Sea of Galilee.
Here.
Mary.
You're a strong young woman.
- Thank you, Father.
- Go.
Ha ha!
They're going to miss us.
Yes.
Yes, come.
For you.
He's moving.
You've never really told me of your dream.
My dream?
No.
No, please.
Tell me.
The angel came to me...
and he told me the child within you...
had been conceived by the Holy Spirit.
And that I should not be afraid.
Are you afraid?
Yes. Are you?
Yes.
Do you ever wonder when we'll know?
Know? Know what?
When he's more than just a child.
Will it be something he says?
A look in his eye?
I wonder if...
I will even be able
to teach him anything.
I have a snake.
It was good we brought one more camel...
or that might be your dinner.
Perhaps we should have brought another.
The journey would be more bearable.
Tell me, Gaspar...
how many days has it been
since we departed?
One hundred and four.
And how many of those days...
have you spoken with regret
for having journeyed with us?
One hundred and five.
Huh?
I'm counting tomorrow.
Aha.
Stop.
Where are you headed?
From Nazareth to Bethlehem.
Bethlehem?
Search him.
Go.
He's not the one.
Goats!
Shout in triumph,
O daughter of Judea.
Behold, your king is coming to you.
He is just and endowed with salvation...
and his dominion
will be from sea to sea...
and from the river
to the ends of the earth.
And he shall speak peace
unto the heathens.
Almonds! I have almonds!
Olives!
Yes, yes, lovely...
- For you.
- No.
No, no. For you.
For your child.
- Thank you.
You carry him like a son.
To see yourself in a young face,
there is no greater joy.
Behold, your king
is coming to you. He is...
- Help, help! Soldiers!
- Soldiers!
And his dominion will be...
- From sea to sea...
- Silence!
In the name of King Herod...
And from the river
to the ends of the Earth.
Aaaaaaaah!
I will end this threat to my rule,
as I will all threats.
Pass your sins onto the animal.
Aaaaaaaah!
Their animal is weak.
For the first time in 3,000 years...
all 3 will appear to touch.
Mm.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Shh-shh.
What? More?
No, no, no.
I am the hungry one, not you.
If I am doing your will,
I pray you'll give me a sign.
Hm. Come on.
Come.
Come on. Come.
Come on.
- Aaah!
- Aah!
Uhh!
- Joseph!
- Mary!
Joseph!
Mary!
Joseph.
My child, you will have
a good and decent man to raise you.
A man who will give of himself
before anyone else.
Ha ha ha!
Jerusalem.
The holy city.
Almonds here!
Fresh-picked almonds!
Some jewelry for your beautiful wife.
That's a good animal.
Would your husband
be willing to sell him?
No.
What belongs to us stays with us.
Almonds. Almonds.
For sacrifice.
Doves! Golden doves!
No blemishes.
For you. Good for sacrifice.
- Herod, Herod!
- Herod's here!
It is the king!
The king. The king is here!
- Shh. It is him.
- The king.
No, no. No.
Pigeons. Pigeons for sacrifice.
Good pigeons!
- Pigeons!
- Pigeons for sacrifice.
No blemishes!
No. Enough! No.
This was meant to be a holy place.
Bethlehem. This way.
These shepherds...
they live alone most of their lives.
Your woman looks cold.
Just for a moment.
I will tell our child about you.
About your kindness.
My father told me a long time ago...
that we are all given something.
A gift.
Your gift is what you carry inside.
What was your gift?
Nothing.
Nothing but the hope of waiting for one.
We must go if we're to reach
Bethlehem by dark.
We thank you.
- Good for sacrifice.
- Good pigeons.
- Good pigeons for sacrifice.
- One half shekel.
One half shekel!
What brings you here?
We are visitors from the East.
We follow the star.
The star of the prophecy.
The prophecy of the Messiah?
- The Messiah!
- Messiah!
Come. All of you.
Magi. The wisest of the wise.
Tell me what they claim.
They believe that a new king
awaits them now in Judea.
Father, we must send
your soldiers to follow them...
until they find the man we seek.
And raise their suspicions?
Then we risk not finding this king at all.
Invite them to dine with us.
Your arrival
is by the hand of Providence.
For years I have studied
the words of the prophets.
"Out of Bethlehem shall come a ruler...
"who shall shepherd my people, Israel."
Your Excellency, I, too,
have studied these words.
I have waited a lifetime
for the signs I now see.
As have many.
This star, the one
that you have followed...
tell me, what does it mean?
The prophecy speaks of a child...
Heralded by the star we have followed
these many months.
What do you mean, a child?
Are you not here seeking a man?
A man ready
to proclaim himself Messiah?
No.
A child.
A Messiah for the lowest of men
to the highest of kings.
We, too, have been waiting
for God's king.
For years.
When you find him...
please return to us so that
we may come worship him as well.
Joseph, the child is pressing.
The child...
- Now?
- Now.
Yes. We're very close.
Bethlehem.
We're here.
We will find a place.
I promise.
God be with you.
Is there a place
for my wife and me to stay?
I'm sorry, there is no room here.
Please. Please!
Is there an inn?
Is there a place for us?
My wife, she's in pain.
- Is there a place for us?
- No!
- Open the door!
- Go away!
Help!
Please, Lord,
will you not provide for us?
Is there someone? Help us!
Leave us alone!
Joseph! Joseph!
Mary! Mary!
Uhh.
Help!
I beg you!
I ask not your home,
but any place you have!
It's all I can do.
Melchior, Gaspar.
A star shall come forth.
Oh.
- Oh!
- Aaaaah!
Aaah!
Sorry.
Aaaah!
Aaaah! Aah!
Aaah! Aah! Aaaah!
- Oh, Mary!
- Aaaah!
Oh! Oh!
Ha ha ha!
Oh, Mary! Ha ha ha!
How is your faith now?
Rejoice.
I bring you good tidings of great joy.
For unto you is born this day...
in the city of David,
a savior who is Christ the Lord.
You will find a child wrapped
in cloths and lying in a manger.
Are you well?
I have been given the strength I prayed for.
Strength from God.
And from you.
He is for all mankind.
We are each given a gift.
The greatest of kings,
born in the most humble of places.
God...
made into flesh.
Gold for the king of kings.
Frankincense for the priest of all priests.
A gift of myrrh to honor thy sacrifice.
If I am right, and I usually am...
perhaps we should keep
what we have seen to ourselves.
We shall not return to Herod.
What if your soldiers
were to go to Bethlehem...
and find every young boy there
under two years?
What would happen
to their new Messiah then?
The prophecy will end tonight, Father.
The sons of Bethlehem shall be no more.
A child for the lowest of men
to the highest of kings.
Arise, Joseph.
Huh?
Look over there!
Take the child and his mother...
and flee to Egypt...
and remain there until I bring you word.
The Almighty has done great things.
And holy is his name.
He has shown strength with his arm.
He has scattered the proud.
He has filled
the hungry with good things.
And the rich,
he has sent away empty.
He has brought down rulers
from their thrones...
...and has exalted
those who were humble.
~... Hallelujah ~
~ Christus natus est ~
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org