Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Mr. Gorbatschow,
tear down this war!
Bring to an end the Soviet empire...
and its 70 year experiment of comunism...
continuing stife in... regions, along with widespread corruption
and economic misery
resulting in a virtual tidal wave of crime....
the Russian maffia has involved into a world class
organized crime network,
with profits in billions including substantial US operations.
announcingthe unprecedented opening
of the FBI legal attache office in Moscow
along with the first ever joint US
and Russian cooperation. They insist....
Ghazzi is in the Club. He is in position.
O.k. Up to go. MVD only!
What is this?
An Amerikan.
Who the fuck are you?
Deputy Director Carter Preston,
FBl.
You fuck Americans now?
You ugly milicia whore.
And you,
go fuck yourself!
This is not Chicago.
This is Russia.
So take your bitch and get the fuck out of here!
Do you think I am afraid of the MVD?
I swear I will kill you...
and your fucking whore mothers, if you don't get...
I repeat...
Fuck you, fuck you!
You scumface cunt! Fuck you!
All right, that's enough!
It's never easy taking a life...
but you saved one, too.
Mine. Thank you.
If you had my warning...
they must have ambushed our men outside...
before we knew it, there were militia with their gunns
out in every corner of the room.
They just opened fire and killed him.
It happened so fast...
it was over before it started.
Good. My poor brother...
How many militia did you kill?
Terek please,we didn't have a chance.
There were 30 of them.
Plus the American.
Yes, yes. But how many did you kill?
None.
None? Not even one?
Terek please. I did what I could...
You did what you could!
You let those militia pigs and that American scum kill my brother.
Without killing one in return?
O.k. That's what you could do.
Here is what I can do!
I loved this man like a brother.
He was a dear friend and partner to me.
So I took no joy in that.
But just think...
if I could do this to one I love...
what could I do to someone I hate?
So... the american FBI...
declare war with us.
And war it is.
Unlike other...
The hiena takes no chances.
Never atacking under sure of a kill.
Though a consument killer,
he is clearly no gentelman.
I apologise for keeping you waiting.
I had some other buisiness to dispose off.
So much wasted time,
confusing motion with acomplishment.
Another drink ?
The MVD killed my brother.
For that, I will see them drown in blood.
But their allies in America...
I wish to send them a message,
and very bad public (bad).
I want to strike fear into the marrow of their bones.
Can you kill this person?
Yes.
If I take this job I have to dissapear.
Forever.
So if you want me to do this, you're going to have to pay me.
How much?
American dollars.
All cash, of course.
A half now, a half on completion.
70 million.
Why not?
Done.
How many people know about this?
You and I.
Keep it that way.
Don't refere to our arrangement by telephone or fax, ever.
You should find a place outside Russia to hide,
untill the mission is completed.
If are leaks it will be my choice weather to continue the mission or not.
I've had a way I keep the initial payment.
Agreed?
O.k.
Informants tell us Terek has put bounties on all MVD and FBI personel.
Deputy Director Preston and Ihave special bounties on our lives.
In two weeks seven MVD operatives have been killed.
At least we know we are getting into.
Informants say it is just a start.
Terek has planned something more dramatic.
8 days ago...
Terek and his two top lieutenats were spotted in the town of Porvoo,
60 kilometres West of Helsinki.
They have been there ever since...
taking the entire thoughtful of for themselves and their bodyguards.
All for Specnaz, nine in all
but one has left the building in five days.
Their only contact with the outside is this man,
Victor Politovsky.
Goes to the Porvoo post office twice a day for Terek's mail which arrives general delivery.
Contact Interpol and get everything you can on Politovsky.
Yes sir.
Terek's men are notoriously hard to turn out.
Should we get the opportunity, we must be prepared to conduct the interrogation
with the at most efficiency.
Good day to you, Mr Preston.
Sir.
I don't think I wanna know what that means.
The new contamination is a tricky part.
They got to use ethyl acetylene.
Nasty stuff.
Gives you a liver cancer.
And I used a disk drive to erease the magnetic strip.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
You really did a beautiful work.
What do I owe you?
I think your ballance is about...
375 pounds.
This is 500 pounds.
Ooo...thank you!
Luck with it baby.
See you next time.
How do you want the accounts handled?
Split the deposit equally between
the Macao and the Panama accounts.
And the balance?
Live it here in dollars.
I need you to open me a Luxemburg account.
And get me some credit cards
use an American bank.
I'll sign you the names this week.
I'll live the creditcards in your box in Montreal.
Oh..this also came in the draught.
I need to use your computer, Clive.
Of course, everything is ready for you.
Good afternoon.
How may we help you?
I'm interrested in intermediate range system,
high cyclic rate.
Man portable?
Compact, vehicle mounted unit.
What caliber?
Not smaller than 7,62.
Available.
7,62 millimeter,M- 134 electric gatling gun.
I prefer non US equipment. Single parallel system.
Available.
Jugoslavian 20-millimeter 19/55 cannon.
Too heavy.
Available.
Polisch ZSU-33, elektric,
14,5 millimeter.
cyclic rate1.400 round per minute.
Interested.
Effective combat range 3.500 Meter.
middle velocity is 1.700 meter per second.
I'll take it.
Cost will be $200.000 US.
Transfer funds in a usual manner,
half now, half on delivery.
To the following address:
"Letterham Shipping",
Montreal, Quebec, Canada.
GIH 876.
Client name: Murdock, Charles C.
What are they planning?
Why is Terek in Finnland?
The Americans... Killed. Example.
Jackal? What Jackal ?
It doesn't make sense.
What are they planning for?
Who are you?
You fucken Jackal!
Why are you hanging around?
Revive him.
Jesus...
Drug assistance interrogation is perfectly legal,
when the matter is a state security.
Unfortunately Mr Politovsky had an undiagnozed heart condition.
He said...
Jackal?
Does this mean something to you, Mr Preston?
He is supposedly a killer for hire, who uses that name.
Several assasinations was acredited to him,
but we have never been able to prove if he even exists.
From time to time he was KGB assert.
Do you have a name?
No name.
Payments were made to the contracting organizations
or a Hong-Kong bank account.
no KGB member has ever seen him.
Do we know, if he ever operated in the US?
No.
But...
Politovsky's briefcase contained bigraphical material...
on your Donald Brown,
Director of the FBl.
Jesus Christ. These guys are going for the gold.
Get her on the phone for me.
Good morning. Purpose of your visit to Canada?
Steel...
Fishing.
Enjoy your stay Mr...Hayslip.
Thank you. I will.
Man, I give you a really good deal on this minivan, you know...
It's brand new, it's fully loaded.
We have got 60 CD changer for you.
Now, the only thing I need right now is your driving licence,
your credit card and I'll check this with the credit manager.
I think everything should be okay Mr Murdock.
Oh. Make it Charlie, allright?
Allright Charlie, see you in a second.
Take your time.
I want this...close hold.
No publicity.
For the working group together,
Staat, CIA, Secret Service,
Russian Emabassy.
I'll have daily progress reports 9 p.m. at this office.
Major Koslova, anything else?
Since 1983...
KGB provided founding for fight direct action missions.
One bombing and 4 assasinations...
The Jackal was the operative used.
Not giving me much to work with, Preston.
We don't have much, Sir.
Major Koslova's informers can't finger.
They don't know who he is.
The CIA can't track him.
Then what?
Using KGB files I've identified 6 operatives we belive,
they have actually seen him.
4 are dead, one is in Lybia,
but the last one is belived to be here in the United States.
A bask Separatist named lsabella Celia Zancona.
She maight at least know how he looks like.
But we have no idea about where she is.
Now, someone must tell...
Interpol says...
in the 80's she was involved with one...Declan Joseph Mulqueen,
IRA sharpshooter.
so they decided to get him out of Irland
and shipped him over here.
In 1989 he picked up twice 25 years
for weapon...
He is curently serving time in
a maximum security state camp in Massachusetts.
I say he does know where she is.
What makes you think he'll talk to you?
I'm hoping he will cooperate for a reduced sentence.
But don't promise too much.
After all...he's a terrorist.
You have got some visitors, Mulqueen.
What do you want from lsabella ?
She has done nothing here.
She entered the country illegaly.
What?
The FBI sent Deputy Directors
out after illegal aliens?
Give over, Preston,
What you're really looking for?
A pro.
Calls himself "The Jackal".
The "Mystery-Man".
We think she maight have seen him,
and may be able to help us find him.
If so, we will arrange a pardon for her
signed by the President of the United States.
And garantee - no extradition,
and also garantee, the Spanish government will never know about her.
They don't know now, do they?
Neither do you.
Let's keep it that way.
Would it matter that you maight be saving a human life?
Human life, whatever, say again
...would it be important enough for all of this?
Mr Donald Brown, Director of the FBI.
It can not be truth.
Look, we know that certain elements in this prison want you dead.
The entire government wants me dead, Mister.
Yet, here I am.
Oh you smart ass, let's cut the bullshit.
You cooperate, and you'll be to transfer to a minimum security facility.
That's our deal.
And that's your chance
to walk out this god damn place in one piece.
That's a one-time offer.
Take it or leave it.
Stuff a time, waste of fucken time...
Pardon my language, I've been in prison...
Alright, what would it take for you to help us?
First I'd have to be convinced that Isabella would be kept safe.
Done.
Then you would have to let me go,
back to Ireland. Free man.
Out of the question.
Besides gunnery, you are a known killer by the British government...
Not to mention all the women and children you've probably blew out.
It's not my war!.
I was never a bomber.
I don't see the distinction!
You steal human lives.
A distinction is a killer at war.
I wanna go home. As simple as that.
Simple for you, perhaps.
Same as in Russia, soldiers go home when the truce is signed yet?
Well, that's not gonna happen. Sorry
Alright, just the chance.
Your best effort is to give me freedom.
I'll sell her for your word on it.
I'm sorry.
So the Jackal is after your Director, is he?
Just tell him to get his affairs in order,
Nobody can save him now.
Nobody, except me!
Because I've met him!
Oh yeah, didn't I mentioned that?
I can identify him, by his face. Give me the opportunity.
But more importantly..by his methods.
So you can leave Isabella out of this.
Did you work with him?
With him? No. No way.
Did you have a problem with this man?
That's between him and me.
Isabella Zancona is the only confirmed contact we have.
And we will find her.
With or without your help.
O.k., o.k.
I want 3 things.
One: get me out of here.
No use to here
What will keep you from trying to escape?
Nothing. Simply, I give you my word.
Two:
I go with you to meet lsabella.
Why?
To see her. That's all.
And the third thing?
Decent razor.
Here is how it's gonna go:
You will be searched...
and if we find as much as a paperclip, that hasn't been authorized
I send you right back to prison.
The same goes for using the telephone.
you don't trust me? As far as I can throw you...
But I have a little choice.
And if you have got any thoughts about the IRA snatch
we will shoot to kill...them and you.
And not necesserily on their arm
Understand ?
I heard you.
Go along and we will get along.
I will keep a real good eye on you.
Miss Koslova, is it?
And what your first name be, then?
Major. Major Koslova.
We're a bit rusty, that's all.
Sub assembly of titanium, so light as stresses will allow.
The arms are gonna traverse 270 degrees.
...drive mechanism with two time servos.
All things are gonna run at 12 Volt DC.
Okay. Well, it's car batteries, that's cool.
How much weight is the arm gonna support?
55 kilograms.
Hehe...bigfucker, yea?
Hey, you want one?
No.
You know, I want this in 8 days.
I can do that.
O.k. How much?
Well, titanium is gonna be a problem.
It's a listed material, so it's gonna take time
and a little more money.
50 grand?
I mean... well... 40...
40 grand.
Alright.
Half now, half on delivery.
This suckers definietly are gonna kick some ass, yea?.
It is straight:
When you finish this unit, your gonna turn over the plans
and all the scrap material
You're gonna forget about Charlie Murdock and his plans
Yea, sure man, I'm cool.
Relax.
Alright.
Are you nervous?
8 years.
It's a life time, isn't it?
Hello! Mr Decker, is it?
Yes.
Hello there, I'm Declan Mulqueen.
And this is Major Koslova.
How do you do?
We would like to speak to your wife.
Iss. Someone to see you!
I'll take the kids out there.
My beautiful Irish.
They have let me out to ask you something.
Sir, I was thinking, maybe we could use
the woman as insurance....
However he plays, we play it straight:
Isabella Zanconas environment remains classified
That means: nothing in the report.
No name, no location. Nothing. Got it?
Yes sir.
I've never known his name, but was definietly an American
He had some kind of a...
special military training and he learnt Spanish
in EI Salvador, I think...
I didn't like talking to him
I suppose, we were all dangerous people,
but he was...different.
I mean, Declan was fire, all passionate...
But this man was ice.
no feelings, nothing.
O.k. Thank you Mrs Decker.
You've been very helpfull.
Incidentaly, it would be best
if you'd keep our conversation
confidential even for your husband.
Don't worry about George.
he doesn't know anything about my pass,
and he doesn't want to.
All he needs to know is...that I love him.
I see. Well, I thank you again.
I'll wait for you in the car.
This opens a lock at Norfolk bus station
Inside is a clean passport and 10000 dollars cash.
Your friends left it with me
in case you have shown up
Take it, and go back to Ireland.
I cannot.
You gave your word?
Go now!
You know, after he kills whoever he's after
they'll send you back to prison.
When I believed that, I'd use the key.
Are you happy at least?
Yes.
I love my children...
and my husband.
In my way, I mean..
Still at night I can close my eyes...
and sleep...
and no dead faces come to wake me.
That is more than I ever had..
You wouldn't have me give that up, would you?
Give me some credit babe...
She is Bask, isn't she?
They say, Bask live by the vendetta.
If they hate someone, it's to the death.
It's the same way, when they love...
My first name is Valentina.
Do you have family in Russia?
My parents. My brother in the Navy.
Husband? Kids?
No. I have not found the time.
In truth...
it's never been a conflict for me.
This is not a quality a man looks for in the woman.
By the way,
Whatever lsabella gave you, after I left
I trust you won't use that after our buissiness is concluded.
You don't miss a thing, do you?
No, Mr Mulqueen,
I see everything.
Maybe we should start by canceling you public appearances?
No, no. I don't thing that's necessary. I mean not yet.
Those fellows are gonna do same preparations
and they need time.
Mr Mulqueen, something you'd like to share with us?
He's likely to be using full of false identities
Three would be on him,
and one reserve in a dropbag somewhere
This is how he used to operate.
What matter if he has 40? It's still one man!
We maight be creating a storm in a tea cup.
Yea, yea... exactly...
Direktor Bolitonov,
Terek has always made doing his own killing a point of honour...
usually very bloody and very public.
A "Statement", if you wish.
So, if he's hiding outside there
obviously this is something he takes very seriously.
Untill this Jackal is captured or killed,
I don't think we can afford to do the less.
Ah come on, let's get real...
Hey, I mean - it's one guy.
It's just one guy. Bolitonov's right!
But with the assets in this room, the guy is good as god.
As if he does stick his dick in a ring...
like a lot of this clowns...
What's that Mr Mulqueen ?
Sorry, Mr Brown.This man is not a clown.
He knows all your moves back to front.
You have a name. That's all you're at!
So the Jackal has got a target.
You!
He's got the timetable.
And as to making mistakes, he spent 20 years
in a trade that doesn't forgive error!
Do you think he's vulnerable up against us?
Set the way round.
Hi. Can I buy you a drink?
Yea.
Maybe you should come home with me?
I'd love to.
But I can't.
I have to go back to Atlanta...
Does she know?
She does now.
So, how am I gonna see you again?
You can give me one of your cards.
You're not gonna call.
You just have to have a little faith in people, thats all.
Like I do.
Open your shirt.
Easy...
Now!
Open your shirt...
Souvenires... British hospitality.
I apologize
No problem.
Oslo travel came up with James William Hayslip,
he flew from Toronto on August 25th.
Two days before meeting with Terek.
We checked the social-security number on his passport,
and guess what.
They belonged to an inmate commited to a mental institution in Virginia
twelve years ago.
Now, Canadian travels says
he flew to Montreal.
Nine days ago.
Charlie Murdock.
I think I have a delivery yet.
Yes, yes.
Hi! I need to use one of your computers.
Sure. Anyone.
Can I get online with this?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you. Hayslip has dissapeared.
A border patrol has his passport photo,
but nothing has shown up yet.
He's moved on. I told you.
One moment.
Only place for sure he has been is Montreal.
What if he started the next identity there?
I'm not following you.
Hayslip's dissapeared, but that doesn't mean the Jackal though.
Perhaps something has happened.
Witherspoon,
Have the Montreal Police
goes through their logs for the last 48 hours.
If he signed to the next name, because it's in the plan?
Man like this doesn't make mistakes.
No. They always make one. Somewhere.
Isn't that how you were caught?
What's our story...?
Major Koslova...
ends the debate about women in combat.
As far as I'm concerned.
How is that?
When she saved my life and took out Terek's brother.
She did it knowing she would be drawing
a death sentence down there...
But when we offered
settle her up at some place elswhere,
when this is over...
You know what she said?
The good guys don't hide.
Fearless woman.
In that country... under that system...
staggering.
Oh shit, you know what? I couldn't get titanium,
so I had a friend of mine mould the base
at carbon fibres instead.
It came at 23 kilos down of the weight you wanted.
Is that cool?
Yes, it's great.
But I still want the planes,
the mould and the scratch material.
Yeah... maybe we...are to talk about that once more.
You see, this rig...
I figure it's to support something really heavy.
Like a... gatling gun maybe?
Or a... 20 millimetre cannon?
So, you gotta be sure
that it's really something big, right?
Armoured car, maybe?
I don't know! You know, you gotta be sure the fucken...
But a.... the point is... a job like this can atract a lot of attention.
I don't want an attention...
Right, right... and that's what I'm saying,
I think the plans and the mould were a little bonus.
How much?
I don't know...
100 grand?
Come on man, you know it's worth it.
You've got a serious piece of equipement there.
Alright. I'll give you 50 grand tomorrow.
I need a place to test it, though.
Some place that won't draw any attention.
We have place like that, we have place just like that.
Target's at place.
You know, I should have brought some beer.
Motherfucker...
That motherfucker
is a state of the art!
I knew it's gonna be big,
but I didn't know it's gonna be
the fucken prototype cannon!
It's a fucken monstrum!
Man, look at the rounds.
Made from the uranium.
Once they get inside, they just spatter.
Yeah?
They get in there and...
That rocks!
Look at the phreacking lens on that thing.
Don't touch that!
They're like 2.000 mile-zoom-lense.
Is this thing a prototype, or what?
I bet it has cost you a shit load! That rocks!
You know, what I'm saying? It kicks ass.
I can't wait to see...
Lamont!
Close your mouth.
O.k.?
Well, at least...
you took out the target.
No, it's off.
By at least 3 millimeters.
No, that's precision craftsmanship.
So Lamont, tell me how to set this thing automatically.
You just...
touch a wind-correction and elevation, and hit enter.
So you just a... estimate it, huh?
And hit enter?
I give up!
I guess the automatic siding works.
is about to sprawl...
Well Lamont,
Let's speed-test it now.
Speed-test.
So... run!
What do you mean?
I mean run.
Now!
Run to your right!
Get up!
Just stop there!
Hold that pack of cigarettes. Don't be afraid!
Stand very still!
Stand still !
I told you, that was off.
Move over by the car!
Quick!
Here it goes Sir..
Eleven days ago Charles C. Murdock...
bought himself a brand new Dodge Minivan.
Now! That was a big surprise for Mr. Murdock,
whose passport and wallet
were stolen 16 days ago at the Helsinki-Airport.
Anything from the border?
We have sent the description of the van to every crossing...
I have something. Uphall Station.
It is a small town outside Ottawa.
I think your man has been there.
Let's go.
The owner is lan Lamont...
Hello! I think I got something here.
What is it?
This is a remote firing station.
It manoeuvres a weapon,
the servo is on of a... remote control.
Like a... like a model aeroplane.
We used that things for models or a...
But nothing like... this size!
He needs a van, just to move around.
What would something of this size be used for?
Antiaircraft?
No! You can buy them...
Missiles are best for the aircraft.
This was something else...
Something with one hell of a range!
Not just a range, though.
See, this is a gun, It's a cyclic rate.
It sends out a hundred bullets,
before the first one reaches the target.
The thing about boats like this, is it sells itself.
It has a lot for the money.
It's got radar, GPS, autopilot, autotackle...
This has even a cellular phone.
You can call your wife if you want to...
So, what you think?
Deja vu. She is perfect.
Jackal.
They know you were in Canada,
and have an Irish who is helping them.
The Irishman's name?
Mulqueen.
Declan Mulqueen? Declan Mulqueen.
The operation still at go.
Declan.
The crossing points and airports have his photograph
but R.M.C.P. has nothing.
On our side the boarder patrol and I.N.S.
are both in a highest alert.
Again. Nothing.
But let's face it. Don't be Houdini to make a cross from Canada.
Probably walking cross for Christ sake.
He won't be walking, I can tell you that.
He's got a weapon to move.
What kind of patrol do you have on this?
the Great Lakes?
Not a lot. No need. People either fly or drive.
There are a few ferry services,
but we checked those, as well
What about people with boats?
What kind of emigration controls they have?
Arriving vessels have to check at the harbour.
Hmm...voluntarily?
Yeah. No active enforcement.
Say he does use a boat
he still wanna..mix with others.
Are there any gatherings to speak of?
Yeah, the Mackinaw-Regatta is going on.
It's the biggest regatta on Lake Michigan.
From where to were?
It starts in Mackinaw and it ends in Chicago.
Witherspoon, take Waveland.
Declan, Valentina, Chicago-Yachtklub.
I'll take the locals.
And remember, he would be on Ontario registered boat.
So look at everything and stay on your radios.
If you do find something, call in back.
I want an arrest, not a firefight.
Alright, lets get to it.
Preston,what about let me have a gun?
Are you crazy?
a fucking gun...
So many people.
So many rich people.
Shall we dance?
Would you give me a gun?
Hi, want some chmpagne?
Come on, join us.
Maybe later...
Get out of the way!
Preston, canI talk to you?
Look, he saw me. He wasn't surprised!
Like he was expecting me!
One of your team is playing for the other side!
Impossible! I can trust every man on tis team.
I'm telling you...
This is not the IRA, we don't get into...
Somebody got to...
Look. This is a manhunt, not your Cause.
Don't make it personal.
What do you fucken know...
I'll tell you, what I know...
I know the Jackal set you up
in an arms deal in Lybia.
I know Isabella was wounded,
when you walked into the trap.
I also know, it was the buissiness...
Do you also know, that Isabella was pregnant?
That our child didn't survived!
Don't tell me it's not personal!
I can't let you jeopardize us! In a vendetta.
There's no Vendetta.
I hope for a fresh start, you know...
maybe it will happen...
This was recorded at 1 a.m. this morning.
It's a call to a number in Brighton Beach, New York.
Item 4: at 1:05 p.m. Direktor Brown is scheduled
to meet the First Lady.
diplomatic reception at the White House,
regarding to a New Hope Hospital opening.
That information came out of this room.
Who? Whos voice is it? On the tape?
Mine.
Mr ambassador
we have arranged the 9 p.m. Aeroflot flight to Moscow.
A car is waiting to drive Colonel Bolitonov to the airport.
how did you know, whose phone to tape?
I didn't, so I taped everybidies.
But I... I have diplomatic immunity.
Who authorized you to tape my telephone?
I did, ambassador.
We are currently examining
documents taken from Direktor Bolitonovs Apartment.
Jackal.
Direktor Bolitonov is no longer contactable at this number.
All inquiries should be forwarded to...
This is only a precaution for a short while
untill we get this man.
You and your family would be safer in Washington.
You don't really think you'll find him,
because you won't. Belive me, you can't.
It's my job to try.
Waste your time and maybe get killed for nothing?
I began this. I have to do what I can.
So please, get your family away.
Everything o.k.?
Valentina is evacuating Isabella family
in case the Jackal knows, where she lives.
Look, the Director doesn't even know
where Isabella lives.
I ordered Witherspoon to keep it out of the report.
No way the Jackal knows.
Well, our Russian black heart
passed everything else, didn't he?
Hier, look.
That's your phone number,
that's Valentina's.
Are you still at the bottom?
The first one is a Russian Embassy.
The second one is... son of a bitch!
This is an FBI access code!
This is Special Agent Carter Preston.
Mine authorisation number is: 223578k
I need a voice transcriptions
of field report November-Alpha...
from 915 this year
Agent Witherspoon.
And I'm in a hurry, operator.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
Field report November-Alpha,
File 0900 hours
Scroll
interviewed subject lsabella Zancona,
at the following address...
Witherspoon,you fool ashole!
I' gonna check upstairs.
Witherspoon !
Come out!
Please don't shoot me.
I'm just taking out the garbage.
I've got to do one more trip.
Hurry!
I meet you at the front.
Yes Madame.
Were is Witherspoon?
He's in the backyard, taking out the trash.
It's comming from the back!
Where is that commieng from?
I don't know!
It said to go of 2 minutes ago.
What the hell...
Where is McMurphy?
Press here.
Hard. It's a load of bleeding.
You see, that's bad...
Blood is almost black, that means the bullet is in your liver.
You have got about 20 minutes to live...
Paining is too much, you can take your hand away.
And you'll be...
dead in five minutes.
When Declan kills you,
you think of me, ok?
Ok.... I'll make it...
If you see Declan befor you die...
you tell him...
that you can't pick up this woman.
It will be fine.
...Declan...
You're gonna be fine.
I tried...
help Isabella...
Oh I know. You did fine. Shh....
He said to tell you,
You...
cannot protect your woman.
No Valentina!
No don't Valentina... don't go!
Stay with me!
Oh, Declan...it was him, wasn't it?
I thought, it was all behind us...
Oh... is this ever gonna end?
Yes.
I promise you, it will end.
And I will end it.
Do you have a gun?
Fallowing a lot of helicopter searching...
the team can infiltrate the weapon to a point here...
covering the Northern approaches in "Route One".
If your weapon has needed range and cyclic rate...
you can engage any ground vehicle
and aircraft approaching the place.
He doesn't have a helicopter
or a team to help him set off.
He is alone.
What do you say, Mulqueen?
...the only way you can make the killer escape from a distance.
So, we'll make sure you're always secure, indoors...
with the cordon of men outside your location.
Exactly.
tieing a knot, if you like.
If he make his move,
we'll tie the knot and we'll hang him.
Not exactly foolproof, I know...
But it's the best regard.
Best regard?
You have a call on line 6.
Thank you.
this is Doug.
I told you I'd call...
Oh... how are you?
You just have got to have
a little faith in people, Douglas.
O.k., noe, that I have a faith...
Are you busy tonight? Are you here? You're in town, yes?
Hello! I am home!
I see you have found the keys.
Where are you?
In the garage!
You changed your hair.
Yeah, like it?
Yes, sure.
Do you like Korean food?
Oh, sure, yeah.
Take it.
I... I thought we're gonna...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought we were gonna go out.
Yea...maybe later.
We are covering tonight Top-Story:
Police is asking your help on locating this man.
He is wanted in several states
for a serie of brutal murders.
The Police belive he is in Washington area, tonight.
The man is supposed to be armed and extremaly dangerous.
If you see him, please do not approach him.
And notify authorities, immediately.
Donald Kennedy said once, that if somebody want's to kill...
a public official...
it's impossible to provide a 100% safety.
Would you agree?
Certainly!
but hopefully there aren't many people willing to do that...
Preston!
What?
You remember Valentina said:
"A statement, public and brutal".
It has always bothered me, why does he keep comming?
Well, he knew... he knew we can protect the director,
as long as I get involved.
But he didn't abort!
Why?
It didn't come together, untill I remembered
what he said to Valentina...
"tell Declan, he can't protect his women"
Wasn't he refering to lsabella?
Any woman. All women!
but remember:
"public and brutal".
We're garding the wrong person.
He's after the First Lady.
Ladies and Gentelman...
Welcome! I am sure you...
She is already on the stage!
The Secret Service wants to know,
what is going on.
Tell them!
No!
They'll try to get her of the stage.
He will shoot in the crowd!
We are looking for a dark brown minivan..
The only one here is red...
I checked that about 15 minutes ago. There are local parked...
I will check that out again, if you want.
No. It's probably one of the safe and sorry circle jerk...
Yeah...
The Secret Service said,
the search came at nothing.
They're on alert,
but she's going to the podium!
I guess it's all on us!
You'll need a gun!
Forget the laser!
Got to work with the optic...at this range.
Get out!
I am going for the First Lady.
It's going to be hard to shoot on the weapon on the system.
Ladies and Gentalmen, it's a great pleasure to introduce
the First Lady of the United States...
It's a beautiful day for the beginning of the new hope...
Give me the gun!
It's that how he plans to get out.
The phone, give me the phone!
And also right now...
there are Police officers, risking their very lifes
to help kids stay out of troubles...
Red minivan,
There by the trees.
One o'clock!
Jesus!
Range it...
750...
762 meter!
Right, I am after him!
You check up the minivan!
Get out! Get out of here!
Say: "Help me Declan"!
Please, help me Declan!
Loud!
Help me, Declan!
Please! Declan, help me!
What you gonna do, Declan?
You just can't protect any of your women!
Let her go!
She has nothing to do with this!
Now, you can save this girl!
What's your name?
Maggie.
You can save Maggie, you see?
You can save her right now!
You just have to put down your little gun!
Okay?
Declan!?
Oh..you did so good, you did so good!
You slip it, Declan.
Now, let her go.
You step away from the gun.
Step away from the gun!
Maggie,
you're so brave.
You'll remember this for the rest of your life.
Get down.
Kneel down.
I'm sorry, Declan.
It's alright, it's okay.
I wonder if we'll ever know
who the hell he really was.
We know what we need to.
He was evil.
he is dead, and he is gone.
Nothing more about it.
Sorry I didn't give you an apartament.
You will get the minimum security. Just like a Country Club.
By the way...
Direktor Brown sends his warmest thanks.
Oh... that's nice.
I look forward to play tennis with him.
Did I tell you I'm going back to Russia?
And I'm going to stay untills Terek Murad
rocks in prison...
or in the grave!
She'd appreciate that..
I think so.
And lsabella ?
Back safe, with the family.
For good.
I know about that key she gave you...
I know you could use it any time you wanted to...
Do you have one of those drop-boxes, too?
Like the Jackal?
Did you read the paper today?
I'm quite a hero, because of you.
The agent, who saved the First Lady.
I could screw everything else up for the rest of my life...
and I'd still be...untouchable.
Is that a fact, then?
Going back to the drop-box...
An operative, with your experience...
with a clean passport...
and a lot of cash.
I bet, if you had taken off...
we never would have found you.
Do you drink coffe?
Oh no, that's right.
They drink Guinness in lrland.
I'll... ask across the street, if they've got any...
coffe, I mean...
I'll be back in...
30 minutes?
Okay.
Thanks Declan, for everything.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org