Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
There's only two ways
this can go now, Lepi.
We either have an all-out fucking war
or we find a nice quiet spot
so that my cousin Moby
- and that fucking shithouse...
- Fuck you!
So that my cousin Moby and that
fucking shithouse can have a one-on-one.
- The choice is yours.
- One-on-one, huh?
It's called a straightener. It's what
we fucking do in this city, Lepi.
Although it's probably a bit too
fucking civilised for the likes of you!
Like a duel, huh? How suave.
Be there tomorrow morning, 8am.
No crew. No fucking tools.
- No problem.
- You'd fucking hope so, wouldn't you?
[yells in Serbian]
All fucking Brennans are fucking crazy!
- £900! You do this to me for £900!
- Have we... Lepi, have we got a...
Have we got a fucking...
Have we got a fucking deal?!
- Don't you fucking touch me.
- The meeting is over.
- I need to speak to Lepi now.
- Motherfucker.
I'm not going out the front.
Where's the fucking back door?
The meeting's over.
Get the fuck out of here.
Just fucking... Fuck off!
# I'm just a bad boy
# La, la, la, la, la, la
# Boy
# All dressed up in fancy clothes
# I'm taking the trouble
# To blow my bubbles away... #
- All right.
- Gerard.
Francis.
- Your dad sends his regards.
- Does he, now?
You should go and see him.
- I don't think so.
- How's tricks?
Can't complain, Francis. How about you?
Yeah, not too bad. Heard you had
a bit of trouble with a blag.
Yeah, it was nothing, really, mate.
Right. Let's have a proper drink
and a chat later.
- That'd be nice.
- Thanks for coming.
[taps glass]
I'd just like to thank yous all
for coming here today
and for helping make it a nice day
for Leo's family.
We all know Leo was no angel,
but he wasn't a bad man.
He had respect. He was loyal.
Honest. Old school.
He was a fucking good businessman.
Made me a lot of money, didn't he?
You see, the problem is,
these young crews today,
they've got no respect.
They think the flash cars
and the fancy clothes
make them real men.
And when I catch who's done this,
and I will fucking catch them...
...then we'll see who the real men are.
Now, if you'd all like to stand
and raise your glasses.
And join me in a toast.
- To Leo.
- [all] To Leo.
Safe journey.
There's a little bit of
adult entertainment for you here, boys.
So enjoy yourselves.
Feel free to tip the girls.
You all know where the slots are.
Here's your drinks.
Don't give him a drink, all right?
- Not for him. No drinks for him.
- I've only had one beer.
You've got a straightener
in the morning, soft shite.
- You're making a cunt out of me.
- You're all right.
- I'll not have a drink.
- You're fucking right.
So do me a favour. Fuck off home! Now!
You'll thank me in the morning
when you're not nursing a hangover.
I'll pick you up at seven o'clock. Maybe
next time you'll fucking listen to me!
- [indistinct]
- Do you wanna take his place?
All right, Moby.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I spoke to the Irishman about the thing.
- Two whiskies, Joe.
- Coming up, Franner.
- You heard anything about Leo?
- Serbs. That's all I've heard.
- That's what we got told.
- That's why I wanna make this tender.
Big step up for you, lad.
- I'm good for it.
- Leo had a good network.
Solid custom guaranteed.
Whoever takes it on has gotta be able to
maintain that. Think you can handle it?
- Sorted.
- Should have come to me first.
The normal scheme of things,
that's exactly what I would have done.
Things are not normal, Franner.
I had to move quick on this.
I take it your Gerard
knows fuck all about this.
I'd like to keep it like that.
It's not his scene.
He's got his own things happening.
I just wanted to get myself set up,
have my own little thing going.
You good for the money?
Don't fuck them boys about.
It's sweet.
All right.
Keep in touch.
Come on.
- You are one dirty bastard.
- More right.
More right.
Whoa. Back up.
More.
Back. Whoa, whoa.
OK. Go.
Go.
- Push.
- I'm pushing, you dirty fuck.
It's coming.
I see it.
Push!
[smashing glass]
Look at me.
Good night, was it?
No.
Wanna tell me about it?
- No.
[Ged] You ever thought
of doing anything different?
You know, if we didn't do what we do.
[Moby] What do you mean?
I don't know, Moby. Just...
A business or something.
Something different.
There has to be something different.
Years ago
I thought of getting a pet shop.
Exotic pets, snakes, iguanas,
that sort of thing.
- You in a shop?
- Yeah.
Why? What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
- So what stopped you?
- I don't know.
Things come up. You get sidetracked.
Years go by and then it's too late.
Do you regret that?
I sometimes think about it.
Well, it's not too late, you know.
Yeah. Maybe. Why?
After this next job, I'm out.
- I've got the fear.
- Come on.
I keep feeling my luck's running out,
and if it does... I can't do the time.
Not with my little one.
Kid needs a father.
Your Fitzy's getting to that age.
Don't you feel the same way?
- I've never really thought about it.
- You should.
Aren't you tired?
Constantly pulling blags
and knocking skulls together.
I quite like it, actually,
especially the last bit.
- Morning!
- Here we go.
You think about it.
Now go and knock his fucking head off.
Shall we get on with it, then?
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
I'm so tired.
You know after you left the other night?
I lay there for hours.
- Really?
- I kept thinking about you.
Yeah. Me too.
Thanks for everything, Pam.
I'm having the most amazing time.
- You're welcome.
- You've been brilliant.
I'll pop round as soon as I can.
No problem. Bye.
- Nice to see you ladies working hard.
- Darling. Join us for breakfast.
I'd love to, but I just dropped in
to see Ged. Is he around?
He left early this morning.
I've been told that we'll be signing
for the land tomorrow.
- Four o'clock at our house.
- Brilliant.
Everything's been approved, so we're on.
It's just today is the final chance
to get everyone's commitment.
- Sorry, Debs.
- Oh, no, listen. I'll give him a call.
- I'm sure he won't be long.
- I need to get going.
It's no problem.
- [mutters]
- Tighter.
[phone rings]
Ged, can you call me, please?
It's gone to voice mail.
Oh, bollocks. Um... I'm not sure
I'm going to be able to get back.
What time does the money
have to be in by?
- Noon.
- Can't you pay Ged's part now?
- He'll pay you later.
- It's a lot of money.
Keith, don't be so rude.
Ged's got the money.
- Debs, I'm really sorry.
- Hang on. How much is outstanding?
- 140,000. But we can take care of it.
- No, stay... Wait there.
Fucking cunt!
[yelling]
Moby. Moby.
I think the lad's had enough.
This ends now.
I think you know what I mean.
- 82... Come on, lad. 83...
- [phone jingle]
84... Go on.
Keep going, lad. Keep going.
Yeah. Lepi?
Your proposition regarding your brother?
You have yourself a deal, matey.
We're on. We're fucking on, lad.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[Ged, muffled] Deb?
Deb, are you OK? Are you OK?
- Debbie, are you OK? Are you OK?
- What?
- Where is the fucking money, Debbie?!
- Where is the fucking money, Debbie?
- I gave it to Keith.
- Keith came round here for it?
- For the land sale.
He had to get the money today.
- So why didn't you call me?
- I did. You didn't answer the phone.
How much did you give him?
It wasn't all there.
- Some in the safe and I had some...
- How much?!
108,000.
Don't worry about it.
I'll make up the rest.
Thank you, darling.
Tell Ged he can pay me back
when he's got it.
- Are you drunk?
- What?
We have been celebrating.
Is it because I gave it to him?
Ged, get off!
- Phone Pamela.
- I'm not phoning Pamela.
- Stop panicking. Everything is fine.
- I'm going round there.
- What for?
- Because I wanna see him!
OK, let me have a shower.
I'm coming with you.
I'm going now, Debbie.
All right, lads?
Richie. You wanted to see me.
His sister's been seeing one of them
fucking Lepi's boys, hasn't she?
Told him they're planning on robbing
thousands of them new PlayStations.
Well, the Brennans
have planned the same job.
It's gonna fucking kick off
big time, kidda.
- You want a ton for that?
- Yeah, of course.
Why would she say that?
I'll be in touch.
Keep your eye on him.
Are you all right?
[smashing glass]
You have got to be fucking kidding me.
Fuck!
[Pamela] Vamos a quedar aquí in casa
por un poco de tiempo.
[Keith] Check it out with him.
Tell him to stop dicking me around.
Y, Monica, estaremos aquíí esta noche.
[Keith] Hang on a second. Monica.
Monica, get me a beer or something.
Yeah, I need you to do something for me.
Yeah. Cayman Islands account.
I need you to transfer
the money for me. Yeah.
It's 003-795-160.
No, it went like a dream.
Don't worry about it. Don't worry about
it. I left them a bottle of champagne.
I'll catch you later. I'm a happy man.
Are you?
No!
- I love you.
- I love you too.
See you. Congratulations.
- See you later.
- Bye.
- We should celebrate.
- Definitely.
I don't fucking believe this.
I must be losing my fucking touch.
What a fucking mess.
But they were our friends.
Excuse me?
Friends? They weren't our friends.
They were never our fucking friends.
- They've been planning this for months.
- God.
I just can't believe
she'd do this to me.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
What the fuck are you talking?
What the fuck are you talk?
Oh, you... Look at me!
Look at me! Look at me.
Look at your husband. Look at me.
Mm? Open your eyes, Debbie.
Fucking open your eyes.
Little fucking pretty cokehead,
was she, eh?
Little fucking pretty cokehead?
Reeled you in, didn't she?
Well, she fucking
ripped you off, Debbie!
- They've fucked off with the money!
- No! She wouldn't do it to me!
She wouldn't do it to me!
Fuck!
Jimmy? I'm coming over
to your place right now.
No, right fucking now, Jimmy!
- What's up?
- Get in.
There's a change of plan.
We're doing the first truck.
What? That's in two days' time.
It's too soon. Anyway, I'm not driving
that one. I'm driving the third...
Jimmy, we're doing
the first fucking truck.
You make sure you're fucking driving it.
Fuck.
Ged, it's gonna cost you.
Fucking say that to me again.
Fucking!
Tell me you're not fucking
taking the piss!
- All right.
- You're getting enough out of this.
Just fucking make sure
you're on that fucking truck!
Go on, fuck off!
Fucking...
[Ged]... be prepared, and we're now
doing it on the 20th. OK?
[Moby] Does it have to be that day?
Can't we do the second one?
Anthony, I'll get you back in time
for your communion. Stop worrying.
- You're late.
- What's the panic?
Changed the date, lad.
We're doing the first one on the 20th.
- Same day as the communion.
- He says we'll be finished before that.
Since when do you give a fuck
about a communion?
- 20th a problem for you?
- No, it's sound.
It's not a problem, Ged.
[phone rings]
Francis.
- Are you up for going to the communion?
- [Ratter] Course I am.
What, now?
Well, yeah. I'm kind of in the middle
of something. Can't it wait?
- [Ratter] What are you wearing?
- [Moby] A suit, I think.
George, I'll see you later.
Right, guys, see yous all on the 20th.
- Get a good rest, eh?
- So that's it?
I was fucking called here for that?
Are we finished?
- He's changed the plans?
- Don't worry about that.
Tell Lepi it's the same job,
details, route, just a different date.
Got you.
Don't make it sound as if it's anything
to panic about. Don't flap.
Flap? What do you mean? I don't flap.
- What the fuck are you doing now?
- I don't fucking flap!
For fuck's sake, Paul!
Get out the car.
You get in the car.
Just get out the car, will you?
[yelling]
- A picture.
- Please, no!
- Richie, you piece of shit. Smile.
- You fucking cunt!
- Did you get that?
- Yeah, got that one.
All right, lads.
Get me down. Please.
Please.
Stop.
No, please, no more.
Tell him. Tell him what you told me.
Tell him. Tell him, Richie. Tell him.
- Fucking...
- Francis.
Fucking take him down, will you?
- Tell him.
- Ratter.
- Who?
- [yells] It was Ratter.
- Fucking hell.
- Tell him. Tell him.
Tell him what you told me.
- Who?
- Ratter.
Who?! Who told you?
Francis...
Who told you?
Ratter! Fucking Ratter!
Ratter told me.
- What did he tell you to do?
- To kill Leo.
- What?
Just shut him up now.
- Kill Leo!
- Shut him up now.
- Fucking why?
- To take over his patch.
Ratter told us to do it.
- That's enough now.
- What the fuck are you doing?
Shut the boy up. You know
I've got fuck all to do with this.
- Do I?
- Yes, you fucking do.
You see, he would have had
to have had the nod from you, Francis.
You fucking did,
cos I watched you do it.
Tell me you fucking gave him the nod.
You gave him the nod.
Yeah, to take over Leo's patch,
but not to fucking kill him.
I can't believe you'd do that to me!
I can't fucking believe you're making
little land deals behind my back
without cutting me in on it.
But we do things, Gerard.
It's what we do.
All right.
This... This PlayStation thing.
- You're gonna have to drop it.
- Fucking no chance.
I'm fucking doing it.
I fucking am. I'm doing it, Franner.
I've heard the Serbs
are gonna be involved.
Be a fucking blood bath.
You wanna watch yourself.
That is a fucking chance I'm gonna take.
Understand me?
Because I'm fucking doing that job.
Besides, that little fucking land deal
has gone fucking tits up.
[Richie groans]
Fucked off with my money.
Are you telling me you got shafted?
Yeah. I'm losing my fucking touch.
- Who was it?
- Slick little fucker.
Called himself Keith Thompson.
Fucking little husband and wife team.
I checked him out. He seemed kosher.
I fucking hold my hands up.
They fucking took me for a ride.
That is why I am fucking doing this job!
Do you fucking understand me?!
I fucking need it!
Don't fuck... Don't fucking stop me!
- Gerard...
- Don't fucking stop me.
I'm not asking.
I'm telling you. For your own good.
You're not doing it.
[Richie] Please...
Maybe you're right.
See? Wasn't that hard, was it?
No.
Are you your brother's keeper?
Don't worry about your kid.
I'll take care of that. For you.
OK?
You just clean this mess up.
Fuck off.
[Richie sobs] Please don't. Please.
- See you, Richie.
- Just get me down. Please.
Please, Ged. Please.
Please.
- Shh.
- Please. Please.
Don't...
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes. Close your eyes.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh. Richie.
- Close your eyes.
- Please.
- Ged, please.
- Close your fucking eyes!
[cocks gun]
- Don't be late for that service, you.
- I'll be there.
We've fucking done it. We've done it!
After this,
no one will be fucking with us.
We're fucking gonna be untouchable.
It's just the fucking start, mate.
We'll be making much bigger fucking
deals than this, I promise you, lad.
Come on!
Listen, I'm gonna have to go, mate.
See you later. All right?
Oi, Jimmy.
You have to finish that before you get
in. There's no food or drink allowed.
- It's the rules.
- Jimmy! Jimmy! You haven't signed.
Oh, shit.
- Sorry, mate.
- OK, don't worry about it.
- All right. Don't panic.
- Yeah, all right.
- Ged.
- All right, boss.
All right.
Everyone's here,
but I can't fucking get hold of Rats.
He's not coming.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
It's gonna be
the year of the fucking Rat, mate.
And the year of the fucking Hom.
Gerard? Gerard fucking who?
Shut the fuck up, will you, Paul, lad?
Fuck's sake.
- Can I have some more?
- Easy with that!
Checking in. One, two. Hear me?
All good this end.
Richie, it's Paul.
Get back to me, you little prick.
What's the story with Rats,
then, George? Why isn't he here?
Rats isn't coming. Simple as that.
End of story. So just forget
about the fucker, will you?
- The fucker should be here.
- Well, he's not, is he?
So just fucking shut up, will you?!
This isn't like Ged. Last-minute job.
Well, sometimes
plans have gotta change, haven't they?
That way, you stay ahead of the game,
don't you?
- If this is a dud, we're off.
- Fucking behave, will you?!
If Ged says it's gonna be a big one,
it's gonna be fucking big, all right?!
Eh, Tony, what if
these fucking Brennans show up, mate?
Fuck them. They won't turn up.
Don't worry about them.
We'll have to go right through
these cunts if theys turn up.
Shut the fuck up. Let's get this job
done and get the fuck out of here.
[Ratter] You've forgotten who you are.
Trying to be the big fucking "I am".
- [Franner] I will catch them.
- [Richie] Fucking Ratter!
[Ged] Trust me.
- Here we go, gents.
- 60 seconds to go.
Get out! Get the fuck out!
Fucking get out! Come on!
[yelling]
Ten minutes, boys! Ten minutes!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Just in case.
Are you fucking stupid? It's Franner.
You can't carry a gun. Put it back.
I fucking mean it, lad. Put it back.
Fuck's sake.
What's got into you?
Now, look, let me do the talking.
Ahoy, shipmates.
All right, Franner. Didn't expect to see
you here, but it's always a pleasure.
- You have the cash, I presume?
- Yeah, it's all there.
And... Where are the goods?
There's a bit of a problem
on that score, boys.
Yeah, we've had a few developments
concerning a fat friend of ours.
Fuck!
[gunshots]
Paul!
Franner, mate, I can explain this.
We go fucking way back, don't we, now?
All right, go on.
- What else?
- We're running the old decoy system.
So they send out a dummy truck
on a different route.
I'm the dummy truck. The dummy truck.
I want all the information
on that decoy truck. All the routes.
What's the point?
They're all empty, aren't they?
- Just get it.
- Fucking hell.
Here you are. That's for your trouble.
- Make sure you drop them two far out.
- Not a bother.
See you later.
[phone rings]
All right. So? How'd you get on?
What, totally empty?
I tried. I'll drive myself.
I've got a nice new car there.
See you in a bit.
Make it look good, eh?
I already have, Jimmy.
I already have.
[# Candi Staton: Young Hearts Run Free]
# What's the sense in sharing
this one and only life
# Ending up
just another lost and lonely wife?
# You count up the years
and they will be filled with tears
# Love only breaks up
to start over again
# You'll get the babies
but you won't have your man
# While he is busy
loving every woman that he can
# Say I wanna leave
a thousand times a day
# It's easier said than done
when you just can't break away
# When you just can't break away
# Young hearts, run free
# Never be hung up
Hung up like my man and me
# My man and me
# Young hearts, to yourself be true
# Don't be no fool
when love really don't love you
# Don't love you
# It's high time now
Just one crack at life
# Who wants to live it
in trouble and strife?
# My mind must be free
to learn all I can about me
# I'm gonna love me
for the rest of my days...
So you've had a good day?
You?
So-so.
# Say I'm gonna turn loose
a thousand times a day
# But how can I turn loose
when I just can't break away?
# When I just can't break away
# Young hearts, run free
# You'll never be hung up
Hung up like my man and me
# You and me
# Young hearts...
Got something for you.
# Don't be no fool
when love really don't love you
# Don't love you
# Young hearts, run free
# You'll never be hung up
Hung up like my man and me...
Take care.
# Young hearts, to yourself be true
# Don't be no fool
when love really don't love you
# Don't love you
# Young hearts, run free
# You'll never be hung up
Hung up like my man and me #
[# Feeder: We Are The People]
# What do you say?
# What do you think about miracles?
# Miracles are something you dream about
# We're looking for a new way out
# Slipping away
# Losing all sense of reality
# Sacrifice, love and democracy
# We burn it all down
# Cos all our lives
# We're waiting for something new
# Waiting for someone like you
# We are the people
# Who let this whole thing go
# Just like the people you know
# We are the reason
# We're blinded by the goal
# We are the people, you know
# Burning away, light in the sky
# So you can bring us home
# Further, further down an open road
# We've torn it all down
# Why do we pray?
# Why do we talk about angels?
# Flying with their golden wings
# We've burned it all down
# Cos all our lives
# We're waiting for something new
# Waiting for someone like you
# We are the people
# Who let this whole thing go
# Just like the people you know
# We are the reason
# We're blinded by the goal
# We are the people, you know
# Step it up, step it up
Step it up again
# We can be silenced, we can be brave
# We can be broken, all can be saved
# It's the rest of our lives
It's the rest of our lives
# One
# We are one
# We are family
# One
# We are one
# We are family #
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org