Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Y'all come and eat!
Let us pray.
Dear Lord...
...we thank you for this meal...
...and for bringing me these friends
and our daily bread...
...and all the animals
and all the beast in the field.
Amen.
You live alone?
l've got a son that comes and sees me
every month and brings me food.
But it's been six months
since he was here.
What do you live on?
l got some things stored away.
Thank you.
-l'd like to ask you a favor.
-Anything you want.
l wanted to ask you...
...if you can shoot me.
My son ain't coming back.
Oh, he'll come back.
No, he told me he had cancer.
And he told me to
go back to town with him.
But l don't wanna go,
because l've always lived here.
Well, we can't do it.
l don't wanna offend God
by killing myself.
lt's a problem.
We don't wanna offend God either.
lt would be the best thing to do.
You're good people.
You need to go ahead
and shoot me.
You know, l'm innocent actually.
l didn't mean
to kill your friend, man.
He shot at me, all right?
And l swear to God,
really, if l could....
You let me go and l promise--
l swear.
l promise l will not press charges.
Where's that son of a bitch at?
l don't know.
You ought to,
you've been fucking him.
We don't talk a lot.
God almighty.
Get this horse off of me.
Get up, Bill, get up.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on. Up.
Goddamn, Bill, get up.
Whoa, Bill.
Fucking motherfuck!
Shit!
Help!
-Good afternoon, sir.
-How do you do?
Sir, have you seen anyone
coming through this area...
...or in this general area
on horseback?
Like, maybe two men? Horseback?
Maybe with a couple
pack horses or mules?
l ain't seen anybody in 30 years.
All right. l am sorry, sir.
Have you heard anyone come this way
in the past few days or hours?
Are y'all cops?
No, sir, we're actually
with the Border Patrol.
Ain't no Mexicans
come through here.
We're not looking for Mexicans.
-No one come through.
-Are you sure?
Hell, no, l'm not sure.
But l don't think so.
Okay. Do you need anything?
No.
All right, we're moving out.
This way, hurry up!
Watch out.
That's a rattlesnake.
He's not gonna bite anybody.
A dead guy!
He's still breathing.
-l think that snake bit him.
-He sure did.
-ls he a gringo?
-He looks too fucked up to be a gringo.
Has he got money?
l think it's too late.
Take it easy. l'm a friend.
-We didn't do nothing, mister.
-l know it.
-What happened to him?
-He was bite by a snake.
He's dying.
You know where
we can get some help?
l know a girl who is good with herbs.
Maybe she can cure him.
But she lives across the border.
ls it far?
The border is not far.
But la Migra is all around.
They are looking for a gringo
who kidnap a Migra agent.
You're the gringo.
Yes.
Can you help me get him across?
l don't want him to die.
Tomas, keep going with them.
l'll take the gringo to get cured.
l'm leaving.
You're leaving.
Yes.
l hate this place.
Maybe he'll come back.
l don't care.
He'll come back, honey.
The son of a bitch
is beyond redemption.
l'm leaving him.
-Can you get us across?
-Yes.
But l've never crossed people
from this side to that side.
-Much less on horses.
-Okay, take us.
-What about the price?
-What price?
The price to cross you.
lt's 1 000 a person.
l don't have $ 1 000.
Three-thousand dollars.
A thousand for you.
And 1 000 for the gringo.
And 1 000 for the dead guy.
Shit.
l'll find a way to get across.
Okay, let's make a deal.
Give me your rifle...
...and your horse.
No.
All right, l'll give you the horse.
But not my horse.
-The other horse.
-And the rifle.
Just the horse.
Okay, done deal.
Okay.
This is where we cross.
-ls the water deep?
-A little.
No! No, goddamn it! No!
Fucking gringo bit me.
Sonofabitch.
Fuck you!
Fuck you, sons of bitches!
What the hell is this on me?
You sons of bitches!
Fuck you!
l don't need this bullshit!
l mean it! l'm serious--
Fuck you!
Fuck!
-Dona Adriana, is Mariana at home?
-Yes, she is.
What's going on?
ls this the one that got snakebit?
Get this gringo out of here.
He's the one that broke my nose.
You sure?
Hell yes,
he's got a face like a white rat.
-He'll probably die.
-Let him die.
Please...
...heal him.
Why?
Because...
...l need him alive.
Will he get well?
From the poison, yes.
But if he gets gangrene,
we'll have to cut his foot off.
Your call is ready.
Sands Restaurant, how may
l help you? This is Rachel.
Rachel.
Pete?
Where are you?
I'm in Mexico.
You know the Border Patrol
is on your ass?
What's Belmont doing?
He went on vacation. He said he
had nothing to do with this.
Said it's between you and the Border
Patrol, and he wanna go to SeaWorld.
Rachel...
...l want you to come to Mexico.
What for?
Marry me.
Be my wife.
Are you crazy? l can't do that.
Why not?
Because l love Bob, Pete.
You said l was the only you loved.
Pete, you don't understand.
l have to go. Take care.
We'll get you home pretty soon,
Melquiades.
Any day now.
You look like hell, son.
Good morning.
Where am l?
Mexico. Shit.
-Who are you, man?
-Your private 91 1 , dude.
The gringo asshole woke up.
She's gonna check you up.
Easy. Easy.
Drink.
-ls there hot coffee?
-Fresh made.
Bring me the pot.
Now we're even, asshole.
You want to help us?
We'll have to walk it from here.
Shit.
Come here.
You try to run away again, l'll kill you.
l guess you know that by now.
Yes, sir.
Do you even know how much
new tires cost?
Do you even know what the mileage
on your little foreign car is?
Do you know when the oil change
is due? Tell me. I want you to tell me.
Johnny, is there someone else?
What do you mean?
Someone else what?
Someone else putting
a roof over your head?
-Someone paying the bills--?
-Johnny.
You've been so distant,
so far away. I cook. I clean house.
I wonder what your mother
would say. I do.
My mother has no say.
Do you think she cares about me?
You think she cares about you?
No, it's not.
She is addicted to vodka
and Valium, and she is....
-You want some coffee?
-Yes, sir. Please.
No, she is not. She is not.
Oh, yes, I do care.
Sit down.
I gave up a scholarship
to State University to take this job--
Can you sell us some food?
l'll give it to you.
We have fresh meat.
Take what you want.
We had to kill him.
This fucking bear was killing
too many goats.
No, it's not.
It's that girl from the....
-ls this Coahuila?
-Yes, you're right here in Coahuila.
Do you know how to get to El Toston?
Twenty kilometers that way.
I'm not stupid, Johnny.
I've got eyes in my head.
When you hit the sierra,
head south and you'll get there.
You're throwing your life away,
Johnny.
Don't do it. Please don't do it.
l've seen that. l know this one.
Please. Please. Please.
You see, that's it.
That's exactly it, right there.
That's what I'm talking about. It's
always the same, always the same.
Johnny.
What'd the guy on TV say?
We used to be so happy.
Let's go.
Take it...
...for your troubles.
We were happy then.
And we'll be happy again.
I know it.
Please, don't cry.
There will always be
a River Valley for us.
I hope so, Johnny.
I hope so.
-Yes, it's $2.
-You speak English.
Yeah, everyone here speak English.
We were worked on the other side.
-What are you doing here?
-Looking for a town called Jiménez.
Jiménez?
No, there's no place like that here.
Do you know of a place
called Jimenez?
Manuel...
...you ever hear of Jimenez?
Jiménez?
No, not around here.
They said it was a little village
about 1 0 kilometers away.
No, the only village around
here is called Los Chilicotes.
Do you know this woman?
Her name is Evelia Camargo.
Yeah, l know her.
But her name's not Evelia.
lt's Rosa.
Do you know that man?
He's the one lived in Jiménez.
His name is Melquiades Estrada.
No, we don't him.
What's he doing with that woman?
l don't know.
Why you don't ask her?
She lives around the corner.
You speak English?
Well, señora...
...Melquiades was a good friend.
l'm sorry to tell you he's passed away.
Who is Melquiades?
Melquiades, your husband.
He's passed away and l've brought
his body back from Texas.
l don't know anyone
named Melquiades.
Well, this is you and that's him.
What are you doing
with a photo of me and my kids?
Melquiades gave it to me.
Please, señora,
you can tell me the truth.
He was a good friend of mine.
You were married to him,
weren't you?
Don't talk foolishness.
Because you'll get me in trouble
with my husband, Javier Martinez...
...and we don't know any Melquiades.
Excuse me, ma'am.
l didn't want to offend you.
But Melquiades was my friend.
Go see Don Casimiro.
He knows everybody
that comes through town.
Maybe he can help you.
No.
l don't know him.
You know anything about
a little town called Jiménez?
No.
lt doesn't exist around here.
l know for sure.
lt doesn't exist.
Why?
Your friend lied to you.
-No, he didn't.
-Sure he did.
There's no Jiménez, man.
Wake up.
-That place doesn't exist.
-Yes, it does.
There is no fucking Jiménez, man!
Don't you see? There's no Jiménez!
lt exists.
Jimenez is a beautiful fucking place.
lt sits between two hills.
The air is so clear there...
...you feel like you can hug
the mountains with your arms.
A stream of clear clean fresh water
bubbles up right out of the rocks there.
lf you go to Jimenez...
...l swear to you your heart will break
with so much beauty.
This is Jimenez.
lt's just like Mel said it was.
Got good water.
And...
...that's the house.
Store's right over yonder.
Graveyard.
Garden.
Right there.
See?
Just like that right there.
Yeah.
This is it.
You found it, Pete.
Well...
...get down.
You got a grave to dig.
Ask Melquiades for forgiveness.
-What?
-Ask for forgiveness.
Ask for forgiveness right now
or go to hell right now.
l don't believe in hell.
l'm sorry!
l swear to God, l'm sorry.
l swear to God. l swear to God.
l did not mean to kill him.
lt was a mistake.
l didn't want it to happen.
lt hurts me, and l regret it...
...every single day.
Forgive me.
Forgive me...
...Melquiades...
...for taking your life. Forgive me.
Forgive me.
You can go now.
Where?
To your wife.
Wherever.
l always. . . .
l always thought that
you'd end up killing me.
You can keep the horse...
...son.
You gonna be all right?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org