Yeah, I like animals
better than people sometimes.
Especially dogs. Dogs are the best.
Every time you come home, they act
like they haven't seen you in a year.
And the good thing about dogs...
...is they got different dogs
for different people.
Like pit bulls.
The dog of dogs.
Pit bull can be the right man's
best friend...
...and the wrong man's worst enemy.
You going to give me a dog for a pet,
give me a pit bull. Give me...
...Raoul. Right, Omar?
Give me Raoul.
I fucking hate Raoul!
Shut the fuck up, asshole!
Sonofabitch won't shut up!
Hates Raoul.
Farley fucked up the list.
I can dig it, Omar.
I had a dog like that.
A poodle.
She didn't bark, though.
She pissed on the floor.
I hated that dog.
But if I was ever depressed...
...she'd lay her head in my lap, look up
at me with those big old eyes.
Even though I thought
I hated that dog...
...I loved her.
It's like that, ain't it?
That love-hate thing.
No more goddamned talk!
I can't wait anymore.
I want my wife!
I want her up here.
Or I'll do our daughter.
- Listen to me...
- No more talking.
I want that bitch or
I'll do the girl.
Omar, I'm doing the
best I can here, man.
I'm not going to hurt her. I just want
her to see me blow my brains out.
I want her to think about that when
she's sucking that fat prick's cock.
Roman's losing him.
If this guy goes, he takes
the girl with him. Let's go in.
I'll give Danny another minute.
He's pulled out of worse.
Another minute, that girl
will be dead.
Unit One, prepare entry.
All units stand by for full breach.
You lost him. Make entry.
Beck thinks you lost him.
Frost gave him the go-ahead.
That's not the play. Omar's tight.
He can get a shot off if they breach.
I can still talk to him.
I just need time.
HBT 1. Negotiator requests time.
Negative. Team's in position.
Fuck it. I'm going in.
Don't do it.
You'll give him another hostage.
Know another way to get the gun
off her head?
Negotiator entering kill zone.
Keep him out. Our men will lose
objectivity if he's in there.
This is Frost. Stand down.
Omar was a Marine, right?
- We have a shot?
- Bedroom, but he's nowhere near.
He will be.
Get Eagle and Palermo to that window.
Tell them to wait for my signal.
Put that motherfucker on his back.
Hellman, Allen, Argento.
When I'm clear, come get that girl.
I just got word your wife's here.
Wife?
Shut the fuck up.
I've been authorized to make the trade.
But I got to come in...
...look around, make sure there's
no other hostages or surprises.
Fuck you!
I want to see her first.
Omar, I got to come look.
Then I can bring in your wife,
get the girl.
What if you're lying?
Then shoot me!
Fair enough!
Nice and slow!
You look around...
...then I get my wife.
Or you fucking die.
Ready.
Move real slow.
This ain't about me or you...
...but I'll take you out just the same.
He's in.
We got to play it out now.
Unit 1, hold position.
Lock it.
Nice breeze.
Great day to be out, you know?
Not cold. Cool, kind of brisk.
Too bad we're stuck here.
You've seen there's no surprise.
Let's do this.
I got to look in those rooms down there.
Make sure there's nobody there.
All right, move.
Football, huh?
Perfect day for it.
Ain't missed a Bears game
since I left the Corps.
The Corps was a winning team.
Oh, yeah? You were in?
- Did a tour in '73.
- Semper fi, motherfucker.
I did 2 tours.
'68 and '69.
Well, hoo-fucking-rah, Omar. Hoorah!
Don't meet many Marines these days.
Everybody joins the Navy.
I have a visual on the suspect.
See? Nothing here, Lieutenant.
So now we make the trade.
Stay cool.
We got a one count.
Like I said,
got to check out everything.
A Marine and a sailor
are taking a piss.
The Marine goes to leave
without washing up.
Sailor says, "In the Navy...
...they teach us to wash our hands."
The Marine turns to him and says:
"In the Marines, they teach us
not to piss on our hands."
Move! Move!
H.T.'s down!
Copy.
You all right?
You okay?
Thanks.
Here, boy!
Get down, get funky, get loose!
Do it, do it, do it!
You're a hoedown guy.
Now I've seen everything.
Which one is the most
pathetic out there?
How you feeling?
Not great. I want to talk to you.
All right, cool.
Cut the music!
Take a wild guess
who's on the news again.
After 6 hours, hostage negotiator
Danny Roman risked his own life...
... disarming the hostage-taker
to end the standoff.
It looks like you saved the day again.
No, it was a team effort.
I just talked the guy out.
Did he say anything in there?
He just wanted to hog the spotlight!
I came close to busting your ass today
because of that shit you pulled.
But because it'll never happen again,
I'll let it go.
All right, he's all talk.
Off the record, that was one hell of a
gutsy job. Again! Congratulations.
Thanks. Congratulations to you.
Great party.
You really in the Marines?
No, I was in the Army and
I fucking hate dogs.
Though things worked out you put
these guys in jeopardy.
If you were taken hostage,
you would've fucked up everything.
Everybody lived, Beck.
Even you.
Party!
20,000 cops in Chicago.
Can't you take turns?
I was going to let Nate go in...
...but I knew Linda would be
pissed at me.
Nate's much smarter than that.
I'm too smart.
Too smart for my own good sometimes.
I got to talk to you. It's important.
A minute, I promise.
Just a minute.
Go on, tell your secrets.
Someone approached me recently.
He knows who took money
from the disability fund.
Almost 2 million is missing.
I know.
According to him, we know the guys
who took it.
Cops.
Guys in our precinct, guys we
might call our friends...
...stealing our own money.
I would've told you sooner,
but this is my first chance.
Who told you this?
I can't say.
But he knows. He's been on
the job since '74.
He's been around.
He knows his shit.
Why didn't he go to Internal Affairs?
Because he thinks Internal Affairs
is involved.
Niebaum's name was mentioned.
He doesn't know what to do.
They offered to buy him out.
- And?
- And he said he'd think about it.
We were at the academy, worked Area 6
together, so he trusts me.
But this guy...
This guy is really scared.
When did you find out?
Most of it last night.
But I've been working on it
for a couple of weeks.
But you're on the board,
You might've heard something.
I didn't hear a thing.
They did do an audit,
but we didn't prove anything.
If somebody's stealing our money,
we got to find out who.
Tell this informant...
Shit!
Jesus Christ!
Officer Bald!
You girls blowing each other?
I was about to get one
till you showed.
I know you're partners,
but everyone's looking for you.
Don't shine the light in here, officer.
Can't a guy hold his partner's hand?
All right, I'll let you girls be.
Wipe your mouth.
Yeah, order me a drink, big guy.
We'll finish this later.
Don't tell Linda.
Shit!
I don't care to fix up this house alone.
And with what you're doing...
Darling...
...that's the job.
It's not the job.
The job I can deal with.
It's how you do the job.
- Like what you did today.
- I'm fine.
This time.
I love that you do these crazy things.
I just wish you'd start differentiating
between crazy and just plain stupid.
I know this marriage thing
is new to you...
...but coming home every night
is a big part of it.
Every night.
I promise...
...I will come home every night.
No matter what I have to do.
Every night.
What are you trying to negotiate?
You forget I know you lie for a living.
Not right now.
Listen, listen.
Danny Roman is a married man now.
No more crazy shit, all right?
See that?
That's the bus.
The bus is going down the street.
"Crazy" is on the bus.
What's vibrating, baby?
Nate's vibrating.
Go. Tell Nate I said hello.
And that I expect him to keep you
out of trouble.
Hey, how you doing? Caught me.
Danny beeped me earlier.
What's going on?
Freeze!
Get your hands up!
Police officer! Officer down!
He talked to his
informant last night.
Some guy he was at academy with
and knew from Area 6.
This guy said he knew what was
going down with the pension fund.
The informant didn't come to
you guys...
...because he thought someone in
Internal Affairs was involved.
One of us?
Exactly who was this informant?
He didn't tell me his name.
It's obvious somebody found out
Nate was investigating...
...off this informant's tip
and they took him out.
Let's go back to the very beginning.
I just found my partner with his
head blown off.
I don't want to do this!
You have to.
Fuck this!
Just back off, Niebaum.
We'll do this some other time.
Is that the door?
You get it.
Shit!
They found the gun that killed Nathan.
It's in the lake. No fingerprints.
- I have a search warrant...
- Hold it. The gun's serial number.
It was 1 of 3 guns stolen from a dealer.
Two of the guns were recovered by you.
Remember? The third gun
was not found until now.
You're must be kidding.
- You serious?
- There's nothing we can do.
We came as soon as we heard
about the search warrant.
- Guys, go easy. He's one of ours.
- In here.
I'm sorry about this, Karen.
We know all know it's bullshit.
Just let them do their work.
They can get the hell out of here.
He's standing over a dead cop,
he had access to the gun...
...and he's on the fund's board.
He had motive and opportunity.
Who the fuck are you, Niebaum?
Nate mentioned your name when he said
Internal Affairs was involved.
Now it's my name, huh?
We've got an investigation too and
your name keeps coming up. Wonder why.
Maybe because Nathan found you
stealing money from the fund.
Inspector!
I think I got something in here.
Looks like offshore accounts.
That shit's not mine.
You planted this shit.
Put it away.
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you think you'll be charged
for the murder of Officer Roenick?
Make a hole here!
Come on, back up!
Give the guy a break!
Thanks.
How could you show your face?
I knew you'd get somebody killed.
Nobody really knows
what happened, okay?
Come on, seriously.
What's going on, Danny?
We're hearing a lot of shit.
What?
Come on inside.
All right, everybody, get back to work.
Sit down.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't know what to think.
But I don't have any choice until...
...this investigation is complete.
So your gun and your badge.
You know me.
I'm being set up.
Nate told me his informant
knows who's involved.
Help me find this informant
and all this goes away.
We should keep going.
Mrs. Roenick, we should go.
I didn't do what they say I did.
Fuck you, Danny.
Fuck Niebaum.
Fuck all of you.
You all killed him.
Don't you stand here in my face.
Don't say one more fucking word to me.
You took him away from me.
God help you, Danny.
You took him away from Jeremy.
Now you stand here...
...and you just live with that.
Mrs. Roenick, please.
Please, let's go home.
Danny, we need to go.
Come on, this way.
The papers found in your house...
Can you come up with an explanation
as to why you had that kind of money?
You have no proof the money was from
the fund or that he opened the accounts.
The money was well-laundered...
...but the last deposit matched
the last amount stolen.
I don't have any offshore accounts.
The statements were in your home.
You stood over the body.
Are you charging my client?
All of this is very circumstantial.
We have a gun linked to you...
...and a pair of gloves from the water.
Which explains why your client had
no powder on his hands.
You know how this city feels
about corrupt cops.
I'll get a conviction
with my eyes closed.
Tell us where the rest of the money is,
who your partners were and maybe...
I need to speak to my client.
I'll give you one day to make a deal.
You hear me?
One day.
After that, there'll be no deal
to negotiate.
We will arrest you and you will face
the maximum penalty. I'll see to it.
Be here tomorrow and have
a decision made.
What?!
Understand that they have a case
that a jury will convict on.
I can't do any more for you.
Cut a deal.
Wait in the car.
Don't worry.
Everything's going to be fine.
Please don't do anything crazy.
Crazy's on the bus, remember?
I love you.
I love you too.
Be right back.
- Danny Roman.
- I'm going to see Niebaum.
Could you wait a minute?
I'll buzz him.
Wait, sir!
Hold on.
Roman. What can I do for you?
Man's got a right to face his accusers,
doesn't he?
- We need to talk.
- Go ahead, talk.
What's going on?
You killed your partner.
And you're about to be
formally indicted.
You're not answering my question.
Nate told me you were involved. How?
Look me in the eye and say
you weren't involved.
- Look me in the eye!
- For what?
Why don't you just tell it to the judge?
We're finished.
Get him out of here.
You're not doing this!
Lock the door. Lock it!
Don't make things worse than they are.
Put the gun down.
You, sit your ass down.
Sit!
This is my life here, Niebaum.
I want answers.
I don't have answers!
Put the gun down and leave!
Don't feel like talking?!
We're going to stay here until you do!
It's your choice.
Because I'm not going to jail today.
Go!
Drop your weapon.
Drop it, Danny.
Guns down! Down!
That was no accident! And neither will
the next one that goes in your head!
Get down here, now!
Come on!
Everybody in here, march over
to that desk over there.
Put your guns, cuffs, keys,
everything...
...on this desk and get out!
Let's go! Move! Move it!
Why are you here?
The call is out on the city-wide.
- See what they're making me do?!
- Danny, you just got married!
Think about Karen!
I am thinking about Karen.
And now that I think of it,
I'm glad you're here.
You just raised the ante.
Join the party.
God, Danny, this is crazy.
Take your guns off.
Put them on this table now!
I know you heard me say both of them.
Listen to me.
It's not too late to stop.
Are you trying to talk me down?
This is crazy. This isn't helping you.
Me and him have nothing to do with this.
I've known you 20 years.
What are you doing?
I know I made you stay, Frost, but you
cannot monopolize the conversation.
You're not the scene commander here.
I am.
You're Niebaum's secretary?
What's your name?
My name's Maggie and I'm his assistant.
Well, Maggie, don't be scared.
I'm familiar with situations like this.
I'm not scared. I've been mugged twice.
Once at gunpoint.
Guns are not new to me.
But I'd rather avoid them
if I get the chance.
You won't have that chance this time.
If you're his assistant...
...you have everything to do with this.
But not me, bro.
I don't work for this pig.
- I'm not a cop.
- You're Rudy Timmons.
You're a rat for the rat squad.
You don't remember me?
I arrested you in '92 for
credit card fraud.
Yeah, I remember you.
I remember you. Hey, man!
Last time I saw you, you were
a clean-cut boy in blue.
What happened to you?
That's what we're here to find out.
I wonder if they're out there.
Your partners, Niebaum.
The guilty ones.
My guys.
They'll come...
...scared shitless
I'll get the truth out of you.
And if they can't get me...
...they'll kill you.
Clear the perimeter and start evac.
Nothing moves on that fucking river!
Locate the phone panel. Lock down
the elevator. Clear the stairwell.
Have Unit 2 hold outside
Internal Affairs.
Christ, they're here already.
Set up command on that barge over there
so the press can't get to us.
What do you got?
Elevators locked
from the 20th floor down.
I got a real concern.
He knows our tactics, we got a big area
to lock down. Do we have the manpower?
We got personnel from
6 different districts.
But he'll still try and control
the environment.
We'll see who wins the race.
Perpetrator is an expert marksman.
He's an expert in explosives
and tactics.
Gentlemen, play this by the numbers.
Maintain your fields of fire.
Elevators.
Fucking Roman's up there, man.
He's got Frost inside.
We see a chance to end this,
we take him out.
We're blind and he's seeing 20/20.
I want visuals and audio
set up from 19 and 21.
Farley, you're negotiating.
He'll eat Farley up.
Commander...
...if you want to talk to him...
I may not have a choice.
Get him locked down first! In the
meantime get on the fucking phone.
Someone locate the building engineer.
Right away.
Chief Travis.
Special Agent Grey.
This is Moran.
We're the FBI negotiators.
It's a federal building.
It's our jurisdiction.
He's one of ours. We got this.
Fine with us. For now.
We got eyes.
Son of a bitch! Go to camera 2.
He got all 6. We got nothing.
We got to see in that room.
No eyes, no ears.
We're running out of options.
- I want status reports now.
- Give me an update.
Give me status. Somebody give
me status. Tell me what you see.
All shafts are locked down, sir.
Blind's closed.
Visibility zero, sir.
We contained him.
We have not contained him.
He's contained himself and cut us off.
Try the phone again.
Let's see what he wants.
Talk.
I'm Rudy, so don't shoot me
thinking I'm him. Please.
Rudy, my name is Farley.
Please get Danny on the line.
Farley would like to talk to you.
I only want to talk to Chris Sabian.
He'll only talk to Chris Sabian.
If Sabian's not here in 20 minutes...
...you die.
I don't want to talk to anyone else
but Chris Sabian.
Okay, we heard you.
He said they heard you.
Who is Chris Sabian?
- I heard of him.
- He's from the Westside.
Once he talked 55 hours.
Never forces tactical action.
I don't know how Danny knows him.
So find Sabian.
911 Chris Sabian.
Come on...
...talk to me.
I'm right here.
I'm not going anywhere,
so please come out.
You don't want me to.
I want to kill her.
I do want you to come out,
so we can discuss this.
You're not even listening to me.
Yes, I am listening to you.
You promised that you'd come out.
So come on out, all right?
I don't want to do this
through the door.
Look, I want to do something
without arguing. Let's get on the road.
Your clothes look fine.
They do.
According to some people
I look fat in ski clothes.
That's not the word she used.
She used...
...a much worse word.
Honey, get off the phone!
Get off the phone.
I'm your father and I'm very
upset with you right now!
Try your sweater.
Honey, get off the phone.
And I want you to apologize to your
mother for saying she looks...
..."wide."
That is not a good word to use. "Wide."
How'd you like to be called wide?
Do you hear me?! I am very serious!
I'm very angry with you!
Get off the phone! Get off the phone.
Don't you make me...
I talked a man out of
blowing up the Sears Tower...
...but I can't talk my wife out
of a bedroom or my kid off a phone.
That's because no one's standing
behind you with a big gun.
Yeah, well, that's debatable.
Hold on.
Yeah, he's right here.
It's for you.
Sabian's 20 minutes out.
And we only got 15.
Call Danny again.
Get him to change that deadline.
Tell him Sabian's on his way.
Sabian?
It's Farley.
I told you I don't want to talk
to anyone but Chris Sabian.
He's on his way. He's going to be here
real soon. We just need more time.
But you don't have more time, Farley.
What are you doing here?
This is pretty serious.
It is serious!
So why don't you take me seriously?
Well, we are. We are. We just...
I just want to talk to you, okay?
Wait, wait.
You think you can talk me down?
I need to...
Tell me what you want.
You want a shot?
I'll give you a shot.
We got some time before Sabian gets
here.
What do I want? Let's see.
How about, can I see a priest?
No, you can't see a priest.
That's good, Farley.
You shouldn't let me see a priest.
A priest is associated with death and
you don't want me thinking about death.
But you told me "no," Farley.
You can't say "no."
Never use "no" in a hostage situation.
- Danny, would you relax a little bit?
- I'm relaxed!
But here's some advice.
Never say "no" to a hostage-taker.
It's in the manual.
Will you to tell me "no" again?
No.
Wrong answer!
Shut up!
Never use "no," "don't," "won't"
or "can't." All right?
It eliminates options. The option that
leaves is to shoot someone. Understand?
Yes.
Yes! Good! See, "yes" is good.
You say "no" again, I'll kill somebody.
Let's practice. Can I see a priest?
You know what? Can we just
talk about this right now?
You wanted to talk! We are talking!
Now, can I see a priest?
I'll see what I can do?
That's good, Farley.
Now you're learning.
I'd like a submachine gun
to blow everyone away.
I'll look into that.
You're doing good.
You ever cheat on your wife?
- No.
- Watch yourself.
I'll kill someone.
You ever cheat on your wife? Answer!
I'll see what I can do.
I'll have to think about that.
I'll look into that.
You ever...
...dress up like a schoolgirl and
get your ass spanked?
Look, all I want to do is talk to you.
I am talking!
Did you or did you not dress up like a
schoolgirl and get your ass spanked?
Have to look into that, Danny.
Nothing against you dressing up
like a girl...
... but I didn't know that
about you, Farley.
This is really, really unproductive.
Unproductive?!
You're right. It is.
So tell me a joke, Farley.
You know any jokes?
No?! You just cost someone
their life, Farley! Game over!!
Shot fired!
Can anyone see?
Don't let him go.
You can't talk me down!
You can't make me change the deadline!
Now get me Sabian!
You got 6 minutes, 42, 41...
Listen, Danny, is anybody hurt?!
Is anybody hurt?
We're okay, just don't be saying "no"
no more, motherfucker!
- Everybody calm down.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
Give me status. Someone give me status.
Tell me what you see.
Visibility zero, sir.
Just a few moments ago...
... a single shot was fired inside
the city administration building.
We got the whole city of Chicago
watching this.
This could turn into a press nightmare.
What do we do if Sabian can't make it?
We got to remember that's
Danny Roman upstairs.
We work with him and we don't
really know what he's done.
We know what he's doing now.
I don't want this to get personal
for us either.
He's obviously over...
Do you mind?!
He's obviously gone over the edge.
This is not personal.
If I thought sending my team in there
would put more people in jeopardy...
...I wouldn't consider it.
I don't want to go in there.
But it's our best option.
He can't be talked down.
They'll get us out.
Don't worry about Danny.
He won't hurt anybody.
Bullshit. No one knows what this
crazy fucker is going to do.
This has nothing to do with me
and Maggie. You get him to let us go.
"Because once you familiarize yourself
with the chains of bondage...
...you prepare your own
limbs to wear them."
Abraham Lincoln said that
and I believe it.
So you have got to get me
the fuck out! Now!
Do yourself a favor and keep quiet.
We'll handle this.
Don't tell me to be quiet.
Don't say you'll handle it. None of you
been in a situation like this before.
Just shut the fuck up.
Fuck you!
- Prick.
- That's enough!
He's going to hear you.
He's got the gun, so he's in charge.
Both of you pipe down now.
Let Maggie go. She's not involved.
And she's a woman...
I didn't ask to be let go because
I'm a woman. I hate that crap.
Me and him should be let go because
we had nothing to do with this.
It's between you cops.
We have nothing to do with this.
Look, I'm not just some dirt merchant
loose in the street anymore.
I'm not. I got a nice new lady friend
that I'd like to get back to.
And she has got this kid, Albert.
Super kid, Dan.
Great kid.
What do you think you can do?
Take a look at that screen.
They think you're a killer.
They're going to try to take you out.
What do you think Sabian can do?
He can't stop this.
What about you, Frosty?
You think I'm a killer too?
Come on!
You've known me for 20 years.
You think I killed Nate?
I don't know what to think.
I'll tell you this:
What you're doing is not helping.
Hey, schoolgirl.
You still sweating that ugly display
you gave us all a few minutes ago?
Stop kicking yourself in the ass.
We all have our bad days.
Stop trying to get in here.
I'm pretty well bunkered.
Palermo...
...take that toothpick out.
I don't want you to swallow it
if something goes down.
That's right, sports fans...
...it's me, Danny Roman.
The man upstairs.
Just wanted to say hello before the
curtain goes up on this little drama.
I guess you're all wondering
why we're here.
Well, it's simple.
We're here to find out
who took our money...
...and who killed Nate...
...because it wasn't me.
There's some bad cops among us...
... and today we're going to
find out who they are.
I know how that sounds.
I know what you're thinking:
"He's gone. He's a murderer."
But I'm that same son of a bitch
you trusted your lives with...
...played softball with,
went drinking with.
The same guy you invited to your house
to celebrate...
... your kid's baptism, Tonray.
The same guy who saved Palermo's ass...
... when that sniper had a bead
on him at the stadium gig.
This is good.
Danny's trying to get us to Stockholm
so we think twice about taking him out.
Now, I want...
No, I need you guys...
... to understand that I had
no choice here.
My life was being stripped away from me.
First, they kill Nate.
Then they took my badge.
Then you guys.
Next...
...they were going to take away my wife
by sending me to prison. And that...
...I cannot take.
I can't live without...
Put yourself in my position.
What else could I do?
Gaines, get word out to our team. We're
switching to frequency 3 now.
I tried to tell everyone I was being
set up, but no one wanted to listen.
Well, now you have no choice.
You got to listen,
because we're not leaving here...
...until I find out who set me up.
Let me warn you:
Whoever killed Nate is frightened that
Niebaum might know something.
They're going to try and
end this quickly.
Another warning:
I know the rules of engagement...
... so don't test me.
You got 4 minutes to get Sabian here...
...or you'll find out just how serious
I really am.
Look me in the eye.
Right here.
Now, tell me...
...when did you find out Nate
was investigating the fund?
I first found that Nathan was
conducting the investigation...
...after I spoke with you
after he was killed.
You're lying. And I know you're lying.
You know it, huh?
You can read my mind, Roman?
No, I'm not. I'm reading your eyes.
The eyes can't lie.
Didn't you know?!
A quick lesson in lying. See, this is
what us real cops do.
We study liars.
Example:
If I ask you a question about something
visual, like your favorite color...
...your eyes go up and to the left.
Neurophysiology tells us your eyes
go in that direction...
...because you're accessing
the visual cortex.
So you're telling the truth.
If your eyes go up and right...
...you're accessing the brain's creative
centers and we know you're full of shit.
Now, let's try this again.
Your favorite television show?
I'm not going to play your stupid
fucking game, okay?
Why, Niebaum? You afraid we'll
catch you in a lie?
When did you find out
Nate was investigating the fund?
After I spoke with you.
That's a lie if I've ever seen one!
- Fuck you! I never blinked my eyes!
- You didn't have to blink.
Your body language says you're lying.
He's nervous.
What do you expect from him?
Shut up! You know how this works!
It's not just your eyes.
It's everything.
If you cough, sneeze, cross your legs,
scratch your ass...
...they're all tell-tale signs.
You can stare at me with those
dead-ass eyes all you want.
You can't beat the system.
One last question:
Do you know who killed Nate?
You.
I don't know. I couldn't tell.
Up, down, right, left...
So what now? Card tricks?
Shut the fuck up!
You knew Nate was investigating
the fund and you killed him.
You could've ended this.
I guess you don't want to.
That's too bad.
That's really too bad.
Because Danny Roman was just
starting to like you.
Tell Danny Roman to hold the fuck on.
You don't want to do this.
How do you know?
If you think I could kill Nate, how do
you know I don't want to do this?
Danny Roman?
This is Chris Sabian here.
Good timing, Chris.
You made it just in time.
I got lucky. Traffic was light.
Glad you accepted my invitation.
I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
What's it been? 2 years?
Not since we both...
...showed for that North Side gig.
You pulled rank and ran my boys out.
Two negotiators on the same site...
... never work.
So what's this, then? The exception
that disproves the rule?
You do your job, I do mine, maybe we
both walk out of here in one piece.
Here's the million-dollar question.
Why you?
Exactly.
I don't want to go into that now.
We'll talk about that later.
This is our first date.
The courting period.
So what do guys like you do when
they're not talking guys like me down?
I'm pretty much of a homebody.
I spend a lot of time with my family.
My kid.
I read a lot of books.
I watch a lot of old movies. AMC.
You got a satellite?
They show all those old westerns.
Westerns?
I like comedies, myself.
I did like Shane though.
Shane, now that's a good one.
I would have picked one where
the hero lives at the end.
Like a Rio Bravo...
...or a Red River.
I think that's the wrong movie.
Shane lives. At the end of it,
he's riding off and that kid...
- Brandon...
- De Wilde.
Brandon de Wilde's calling his name:
"Shane, come back! Shane!"
I'm sorry to be the one to
tell you this but Shane died.
That's an assumption.
It's a common mistake.
In the final shot,
he slumps over his horse.
He doesn't look back because he can't.
Shane's dead.
He slumps because he's shot.
Don't mean he's dead.
You think Butch and Sundance live too?
You never see them dead either,
but they're surrounded.
Now you're a history buff?
I generally read
histories and biographies.
Don't believe everything you read.
I didn't say I read just one book.
I try to read all books on a subject.
You know, try to get all the facts...
...and then decide for myself
what really happened.
Get all the facts, huh? That's smart.
You're much better at this than Farley.
All right, before we start to bore
everyone, let's get back to business.
First, my list of demands.
One: I want my badge brought down here.
Two: If I die, I want a
departmental funeral.
No one's dying here.
Three: I want the informant found.
He's the only one who
can clear my name...
...and knows who's running
this conspiracy.
Four: I want to know
who killed my partner.
If neither the informant or killer
is found in 8 hours...
...I will kill one hostage an hour
until they're all dead.
Five:
I want to talk to you face to face now.
- Scene commander's upstairs?
- You can talk to me.
You're the chief?
Pleased to meet you.
You're Beck?
You're...?
All right. Vest.
You're going up?
Yes.
- Why didn't you try and talk him down?
- He would've expected it. His sheet.
Why'd he ask for me?
We were hoping you could answer that.
Psych evaluation, who's on it?
He thinks he's innocent.
We'll probably have to go tactical.
We've put a plan together.
If we can distract him long enough,
we can send in an infiltration team.
- Let's wait on that.
- Wife's here!
God! How is he? Has he hurt anyone?
Who's talking to him?
Karen, he's okay.
He asked for Chris Sabian.
I'm Chris Sabian.
Do you know Danny?
He didn't do those things they say.
You have to help him.
I have no idea about Danny's
guilt or innocence.
I'm here to get him out safely.
If you want to help...
...answer Tonray's questions
and then go home.
No! No! I'm not going home.
You bring tension and emotion to a scene
that already has too much of both.
I am not...
...leaving my husband.
All right, fine. But if you want
to help him, help me.
I have to get up there now.
Go with Tonray, answer his questions
and then stay in case we need you.
Just come with me and talk, okay?
It's going to be all right.
How do I get up?
Freight elevator to 18,
and walk the rest of the way.
All right. What is this? This is a
shaft off Internal Affairs?
That's access to the steam pipes.
It's unusable.
First, get his badge.
Second, shut off the heat.
He might deal a hostage to get it back.
What channel?
Three.
I want to show you something.
Danny, take me.
Take him. Come on.
I got the asthma.
You know?
You can't put me in bad situations, man.
For chrissakes.
Why you always pick on me?
I mean, who am I?
Charlie Brown?
You know what Nietzsche says:
"Even the strongest have their
moments of fatigue."
And I'm fatigued, Dan.
I'm fucking fatigued. Oh, God.
You okay?
Do I look okay? I got a gun
pointed at the back of my head.
Nice fucking pants.
Shut up, Mr. Blackwell. Get over here.
- You working?
- Sort of.
I was negotiating a truce between
my wife and daughter.
That might prove easy by comparison.
It wouldn't surprise me in the least.
You shut off the heat.
You know how this works.
Yeah, I do.
Next time you try and bluff,
make sure you charge your cell phone.
Now, you want to tell me
what I'm doing up here?
I wanted to tell you face to face
I'm not crazy.
I'm just doing this to
prove my innocence.
I believe you.
Anything I can do to help you get out...
Don't fucking patronize me!
You don't think I'm innocent!
Don't tell me "I want to do everything
I can to help you."
Like I'm some second-rate HT.
You're right. I'm sorry. My mistake.
You are sorry. Get out. Lock the door.
Call when you want to talk.
I'm ready to talk.
You're right.
I don't know if you're innocent or not.
You could've done everything they say
you've done. I don't care.
There are ways to prove your innocence.
This isn't one of them.
And now you got hostages.
So let me tell you:
You hurt one of them, you'll burn up
whatever currency you got to deal with.
They're all I care about. You leaving
here walking is a distant second.