Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yuki! Hey, girl, time to eat.
Oh, Yuki's my cat.
Well, I don't understand.
If you don't want to go out with him,
why did you say you would?
I mean, you don't want to give him
the wrong idea, do you?
Where is she?
Yuki!
Well, listen, you need
to make up your mind.
Where is she?
I'm starting to worry about my cat.
She never misses a meal.
Yuki?
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Yuki!
We haven't seen her anywhere today,
but we'll be sure to tell you if we do.
- Ice cream!
- She's wearing a bell like this one.
- I don't know where your cat is.
- Me either.
I know. She's at the old haunted house.
Hey, look!
There's a rainbow over there again.
I don't get it. She likes to stay home.
What is she doing over there?
You know, you're not supposed
to go in there...
...but we don't really care about that.
You wanna go?
- Are we going?
- It's probably raining there again.
Let's go!
Nice moves, man.
Come on!
- Hey, it's over here.
- Wait, I'm coming with you.
You sure it's okay to show her?
Hello? Where are you?
Guys? Where'd you go?
Where'd they go?
- Come on, boy.
- Whoa, cool truck!
Settle down!
Hold still!
Sit! Sit!
Hello?
Where is everyone?
Yuki?
Stupid cat.
What's happening?
What's going on here?
- I got it!
- Yeah!
Yuki? Is that you?
There you are, Yuki.
Come here.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Bad cat.
Bet you're hungry, huh?
I figured this out yesterday.
Your cat's okay.
Yeah, thanks.
It's those boys.
- Ready!
- There he goes.
Banzai! Yes!
May I have your attention, please.
And you are the winner!
No fair. He hit the ground.
His nose is bleeding. Look!
I think he's right.
He hit the ground.
- Hey, who told her?
- Don't look at me.
- I don't know.
- I didn't tell her.
So this house is haunted.
- No way. Wow, this is too much!
- This never happened before.
That, that was...
What was that?
Hi.
Anybody home?
Yeah, they're gonna tear it down.
Come on, come on, come on!
Hey, light as a feather.
- I wanna try! I wanna try!
- Come on, we could help her.
Hey, hey! Come on.
Get away from there. Move along!
Yuki, wait!
Clear the area.
Clear the area immediately.
Get out of here!
Yuki!
Where are you?
Yuki.
If you don 't want to go out with him,
why did you say you would?
I mean, you don 't wanna give him
the wrong idea.
Where is she?
Yuki!
You need to make up your mind.
Where is she?
I'm starting to worry.
Yuki!
Hey, you! We've got one over here.
You don't belong here.
Move along, folks.
Nothing to see here.
Come on, folks, out of the way.
Go about your business.
Let go of me, let go!
- Tell me you have all of them.
- Yes, sir. The last one's over there.
- Examine her. Then let her go.
- Yes, sir.
Let go! Listen to me! There's no bugs
in there! It's just some kids!
Let go!
- Listen!
- Seal the area off now.
I'm going, I'll see you guys later.
- Nothing.
- Yeah, nothing.
Work!
It's not working.
Forget it. Come on, let's go.
A case to end all cases.
You know what I mean, Dinah?
I used to think being
a private detective was cool.
Like Sam Spade
or Phillip Marlowe, right?
But there's nothing cool left to it.
On top of that, both my fridge
and my bank account are empty.
Wait.
Okay, Dinah, let's bet.
If it's another suspicious husband,
I'm out of this business forever.
- Hello?
- Mr. Ash, I have a job for you.
And you need me
to check on your wife, right?
I'm looking for a computer hacker.
This hacker goes by the alias Trinity.
That's all we know.
Well, it looks like we're still
in business, Dinah.
Fine. And who will I be working for?
- I can 't say.
- You can't say.
Call me back when you can say.
That's not the way I do business.
It was a pleasure chatting with you.
Before you hang up, take a look
at your bank account balance.
I didn't get a good feeling
about the case.
But I had no good reason
to turn the guy down now.
This Trinity was well-known
in hacker circles.
A real artist by the sound of it.
The cops were always
one step behind him.
So I knew I could get that close.
Question was, could I get closer?
I had a few tricks up my sleeve
for getting to hackers.
While I was searching,
I found something strange.
Other detectives had been
on the case too.
And their investigations had all been,
shall we say, troubled.
One of the guys killed himself.
Another had disappeared.
Another went crazy.
So I paid the one
who was left a visit.
The crazy one.
Trinity doesn't exist, man.
He's not real.
He's a figment. A cipher.
A jabberwocky.
And who am I? Who the hell am I?
Did I mention he was crazy?
Chessboards, jabberwocky,
Red Queen...
I started searching
all the usual hacker hangouts...
... for someone with
an Alice in Wonderland m.o.
Hacker bulletin boards,
anonymous mailboxes, chat rooms.
And it was in one of those
that I picked up Trinity's trail.
"Six brooks."
"I'll be there at 2005."
Of course!
Crossing the second brook
takes her into the woods.
Alice jumps the first brook...
...and...
And then she boards a train.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Hey!
I knew this was some kind of trap.
There's a difference, Mr. Ash,
between a trap and a test.
You were testing me?
You made it. I'm impressed.
Flattery will get you everywhere.
I'm not here to flatter you,
I'm here to save you.
What just happened?
Mr. Ash, dream of having
an eye exam lately?
Yeah, how'd you know?
You've stepped
to the edge of the looking glass.
So then, that means I wasn't dreaming.
They hired me as a way
of getting to you, didn't they?
Go!
What the hell is going on here?
This is really crazy.
Now I understand what happened
to those other detectives.
They went nuts.
Well, I've gotten out
of worse jams than this.
I am not gonna let them get you.
What's happening to me?
I'm sorry.
You didn't make it, Mr. Ash.
I wish...
...I could go with you.
I don't blame you, you know.
Everything that happened, Trinity,
it was all my fault.
All that Through the Looking Glass stuff.
Can't get my head around it.
I'm old-fashioned.
There's a difference between
a test and a choice.
For what it's worth,
I think you could've handled the truth.
It was just a job.
Goodbye, Trinity.
Goodbye.
A case to end all cases.
Wake up. Baby's spotted
two machines heading in fast.
I see them.
They're runners.
Think you can handle them?
Watch me.
Okay. I'm in.
That runner's smarter
than we've seen so far.
- It's quite a catch.
- Thanks.
Will it..?
Do you think it'll convert?
To convert is its choice to make.
Do you think maybe
we ought to reprogram it?
No. We can't make slaves of them.
Because that would be simpler.
We won't beat the machines
by making them our slaves.
Better to let them join us by choice.
Make them believe the right choice
is the one we want them to make.
All right. Yes, machines are tools.
They're made to be used.
- It's their nature.
- To be slaves.
That's why we can show them
a better world, why they convert.
- But that world we show them isn't real.
- It doesn't matter.
I'm afraid they'll figure out that
we've made up the thing in our heads.
They can't tell the difference.
To an artificial mind, all reality is virtual.
How do they know that the real world
isn't just another simulation?
How do you?
I know I'm not dreaming now because
I know what it's like being in a dream.
So dreaming lets you know
reality exists.
No. Just that my mind exists.
I don't know about the rest.
Okay, he's good to go.
Looks like we are too.
Dreaming already?
He's had a rough day.
You poor baby.
Would you mind?
Not at all.
Hello there.
What's happening?
Sentinels.
Let's go!
Come on, damn it, help me!
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org