Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Ok, everybody.
Ready?
Let's settle down.
Today I'm going to
show you a story.
Let's all tune in together.
A long time ago...
...the soul of our planet was sick.
People had become isolated...
...and warlike.
Our world was frightened.
It was dying.
But a great scientist...
...was trying to save us.
He had tried many times...
...and he knew
he could only try once more.
This was the last mimzy.
It's gotta be my new braces.
I'm not a terrorist, ok?
Ah, you sure about that?
Let's see in your pockets.
That's the third time she's done that.
We're gonna be late for the test.
Have you studied?
All night. I'm freaked out.
C'mere.
Check your messages.
Whoa. Gee, thanks, man.
Courtesy of my cousin Bob.
Took the test last week. Cool.
Listen up. All right?
Now, just a reminder...
Science fair projects are
due one week after vacation.
Oh, come on!
It's gonna be a great fair this year.
There's lots of great exhibits.
Um, you have tests
sitting in front of you.
Noah, you're not an ameba.
You have a spine.
Use it, sit up straight.
That goes for all of you.
Come on, you guys.
Let's get focused here.
You have 30 minutes...
...and begin.
So, how d'you do?
Total choke.
You didn't use the text I sent you.
Mr. White coughed. I think he saw.
You're such a wuss. Hey, look at this.
Whoa. I'm in the front...
I have times four.
Hey, dude,
d'you wanna come over?
Can't. Leaving for whidbey in an hour.
Whidbey?
For easter vacation?
- How lame!
- Tell me about it.
Hey!
Oh, hey, sweetheart, how's it going?
I packed up the car already.
You were supposed to be home.
Listen, we're gonna leave
first thing in the morning.
I promise. But you gotta tell the kids
there was nothing I could do about it.
- Oh, sweetheart.
- I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get home late
so eat without me, ok?
Emma, where are you?
We're eating.
- Coming, mom!
- Ok.
Know what? It snapped.
Oh, honey, sit down,
we can fix it later.
Please.
No, you're the sensitive little genius.
Why don't you do it?
I can't do it.
I don't have dexterity.
Dexterity? What kind of mutant are you?
Noah. Fine.
Where's the stupid string?
It's in my stupid hand.
Why couldn't I have a normal sister
like everyone else?
Come on, sit down...
So that we can eat like a family, ok?
Yuck!
They killed it!
How else would you eat it?
- Mommy, I don't understand.
- What?
Why did they have to kill it?
He didn't do anything to anyone.
What about that chopped-up cow
you're eating?
What chopped-up cow?
What do you think hamburger is?
Did you have to?
You there?
- Dad!
- Heh!
- You're home.
- Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry about tonight, ok?
Ok?
Oh, you're in a bad mood, are you?
Is it 'cause i'm late?
Hm? What is it?
Your sister or school, what is it?
School! School sucks!
Ok.
What else? Ahhh.
What else?
- Life sucks.
- I suck.
- You suck.
All right. Well, just put
it on pause for a second...
...because I wanna tell you,
you're probably right.
Because sometimes life does suck...
...and sometimes school sucks, but...
...you're completely wrong
on the Noah Wilder front.
I should know, I mean
I've lived with him for...
How old are you? 10?
10 years.
And, uh, I will put it in writing...
...money-back guarantee, full warranty...
...whatever you want, to tell you...
...that noah wilder does not suck.
In fact...
...he's the greatest kid I know.
Y- Yeah? Yeah?
Sorry, hope I didn't wake you up.
No, no.
Ah, no, no, listen...
If he accepts the motion, we're done.
Don't you dare,
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Oh!
Sorry, Jo. Take the kids
to Whidbey, I'll be there later.
Come on, get out.
Come on, sweetie. Get out!
Isn't it pretty?
Oh, look at it, it is so beautiful!
I'll get the keys.
Oh, look at it!
I love this place.
Oh, careful. You ok?
The magic staircase.
- Up you go.
- Magic?
Well, kinda.
Noah, no!
Mommy said you have to wait!
Man, it's cold.
Oh, it's really cold.
Cold water.
What's that?
I don't know. I'll go see.
Let me.
No, don't.
I wonder if it opens.
What's that?
I don't know.
Read the directions.
Do you see any directions?
Come on in, guys.
Keep it a secret.
Dinner's almost on,
you coming down?
Yeah, in a sec.
- What is that?
- Oh, it... I don't know.
Em and I found it on the beach.
Let me see.
Look at all those triangles.
Make a nice paperweight.
Mim... Mimzy.
Mimzy.
Mimzy?
What are you doing, Em?
Get out of my stuff.
What's that new stuff?
And what's that bunny rabbit?
Where'd they come from?
She was on the side.
No she wasn't.
I think she's the easter bunny.
Ya-Da-Da da-Da.
Give me that.
Give this to me. No.
- Give it...
- No.
Now look what you did.
Give me those.
What are they for?
It's like she's talking to me.
Yeah, right.
Like this?
It's a spinner, Noah.
Uh...
What...
How did you do that?
I did like this.
No, smooth.
Close your eyes.
What is this stuff?
Wow!
Whoa!
Oh, sheesh.
No, don't!
Are you crazy?
Do you even know what
just happened to your hand?
Is it ok?
This stuff could be dangerous.
Maybe we should tell someone.
I showed the green glass thing to mom.
She thought it was a paperweight.
Maybe other people
don't see what we see.
Maybe you can use these
for your science proje ct.
I'm not even gonna do
a science project.
And I bet Mr. White couldn't care less.
- Morning, Mr. Willpower.
- Morning.
I thought you were dieting.
I thought you were meditating.
Aren't you supposed to be in Nirvana?
I am.
Larry, are you seriously eating that?
I haven't had anything
to eat in 8 hours.
Oh, really?
That's called sleeping.
Here. Come on.
Oh, my goodness.
- Ha! No.
- Yes.
I am not so easily tempted.
- What about him?
- Hey, stop it!
Ah, let me focus.
I had another one of
those dreams last night.
Were there any lotto numbers?
No, no numbers. Just that...
That same light and that...
Spinning mandala shape...
- Coming down at me.
- Oh, are you sure?
Because sometimes you forget.
Historically, you've been...
No, no numbers. Just, god,
ever since we left nepal...
It's that same dream.
I don't get it.
It's like the shape is...
...sucking me into it.
It's... It...
Don't talk.
Just... Just try not to lose it.
Just...
See if it can...
Come back to you, then...
you can remember...
You're trying to get numbers out of me.
- No, I'm not...
- There were no numbers.
It's so sad.
Oh, we could've been so rich.
Could you imagine how many
people we could've helped...
...with that money?
Naomi, let it go, ok?
It was a year and a half
a go, it just happened once.
It was a total fluke.
Larry, you dreamt all six numbers
of a winning lottery ticket.
- We could've won 18 million dollars.
- Million dollars, I know.
How was that a fluke, larry?
Come on, I'm sorry. I know.
Oh, really?
Is this what's going on right now?
It is, mm-Hm.
You think you can just...
...kiss your way back...
- I do.
You know what?
It's easter vacation, let's celebrate.
- You're not allowed to...
- Got you.
I tagged you.
- You're it.
- Oh...
You're not gonna get me,
you can't get me.
You can't get me.
I'm gonna get you.
Em!
Oh. Man, that feels good.
You got some pretty
intact sand dollars there.
They're nice.
Reminds me of Mr. White.
Try it. This is mimzy's shell.
We'll find a shortwave frequency
The wave connecting you and me
Hello, I love you
Sweet!
Wasn't that just
the most beautiful day, huh?
The beach...
Sweetie, come here, I'm cold,
I need a cuddle.
Yeah, let's...
Aww.
That's good.
Now I'm nice and warm.
God, look at it.
It's so beautiful.
- I love this.
- Me too.
- Look at all the stars, mommy.
- Yeah.
It's so big.
Are we the only people
in the universe?
That is a very big question...
And, um, nobody really knows, honey.
I don't think we are.
I think you're probably right.
So what do you say, guys?
Uh, how about we make
some s'mores, hm?
Well, actually, I'm not hungry.
I'm full too.
My tummy's so full
I'm gonna go upstairs.
M- Me too, I'm...
I'm kinda tired, em.
We can do s'mores tomorrow,
ok, mom?
I have a girlfriend named Marcie.
But she doesn't always like me.
She thinks I'm too smart.
And the girls in my class...
...don't talk to me.
Because I like astronomy...
...and I play the violin.
- Mimzy.
- I know, I'm your friend too.
Tea, ladies?
What's in there?
What did I just do?
How did you do that, Noah?
I don't know, with my brain?
I just looked
at it and it...
Disappeared.
It's not funny!
It is to me.
You better clean that up.
You're not the boss of me, ok?
Hey, Noah, Mimzy knows things.
Oh, yeah? What kind of things?
I think she reads minds.
She knows all about us.
Like what?
She knows our names...
...where we were born...
...and what kind of french fries I like.
That's nice.
And you know what else?
She said dad's gonna call.
That's daddy.
Come on, Mimz.
- Hey, guess what?
- I know. Daddy's coming.
Well, how do you know that?
He just called me from the car.
- Mimzy told me.
- Yeah, mimzy told her.
Daddy! Daddy's here!
Daddy! Yay!
- Daddy, daddy, daddy!
- That's dad, all right.
- Daddy's coming!
- Come on, let's go.
- Hey, guys!
- Daddy, yay!
- Daddy's here!
- C'mere, Em.
Hey, bud.
How are ya? Huh?
Oh, I'm happy to see you guys!
- Hi!
- Hey, you!
Home at last.
And they said
we're just looking for carrots...
...and there was no carrots there.
Mom, can you tell a joke? Oh.
And they were really
dreaming of carrots.
Come on, come on, tell a joke!
- Hey, did you...
- Come on.
I don't know what's got into them.
You know, Emma, she just
hangs onto that rabbit...
Day and night.
And Noah, it's just like
he's on another planet...
You know?
They're not my babies any more.
Aww. No, it's true.
You know, we haven't
played one board game...
...since we've been here.
Not one.
- Yeah?
- You know, we've barely talked...
Apart from at dinner...
And then they run off
before they're done, I...
It's really different, I...
They're growing up.
They'll always be your babies, Jo.
Our babies.
- All right.
- Thanks, Mike.
Grab the bucket, ok.
All right, here we go.
This one's for you.
Why are you giving me a club?
Dad, I'm not gonna play golf, am i?
Ah, come on,
we're gonna give it a try.
All right.
Noah...
Come give it a try.
No, dad, you know I suck at sports.
Oh, now this is not a sport...
This is an obsession. Come on.
Come on, you're gonna like this.
Ok.
Now, you wanna line up, right?
There you go.
Just get in position.
Now, you don't wanna kill it.
You don't wanna kill it, all right?
You just wanna let the gravity...
...just glide the club
right down to the ball.
All right, now then,
it's not about strength...
...it's about control.
Ok?
You ready? Ho-Ho-Ho.
Hold on. Hold on.
Just want to see right
where you are here.
Ok.
Whoa, baby!
I think we've found your sport.
And this, ladies and gentlemen...
...is a basic outline
of the story of DNA...
And of the doctors Watson and Crick...
...who cracked the genetic code
that controls all living things.
And we now believe...
...that genes don't just
control the way we look.
But also how we think
and how we act...
...and how we feel.
So, when people mess
with mother nature...
Look out.
Because pollutants can change us.
And not just chemical
and biological ones...
Cultural ones as well.
Perfectly good DNA
becomes a bunch of useless junk...
...carried from
generation to generation.
And, uh, as a case in point
I'd like you to meet...
...a very special friend of mine.
This is Charlie.
He'd like to say hello,
he's a little shy.
How you doin'?
You don't wanna come out?
No, I think you should.
Gotcha!
Ew! Gross!
Oh, yes...
Gross, oh, that's right.
This is what happens when
you screw with the code.
And don't tell your parents
i said the word "screw".
Please.
This is what happens
when pollutants...
...contaminate DNA.
Let Charlie be a warning.
This could happen to us.
You wanna end up with two heads?
I don't think so.
This can happen to all living things...
And in fact, it may be
happening right now.
Then why don't they do something?
Why don't they stop it?
Excellent question, Wendy.
"Why don't they do something?"
"Why don't they stop it"?
Who is this "they" that
wendy's referring to...
I wonder, huh?
What do you think?
"They" is all of us.
Right?
Ok, thank you.
We'll see you on wednesday.
Keep working on your
science fair projects.
You play golf?
No. What's goin' on?
Nothing's going on, I mean...
I was bored out of my mind.
Noah! Noah, do you have a sec?
I need to talk to you about this.
Yeah.
I'm outta here, dude.
Just relax, Noah, it's ok.
It's not about the test...
It's about this.
Um... Hey, did you, uh,
did you draw this?
Yeah.
Ok. Uh, what was your inspiration?
I mean, where did you
come up with this design?
I was just scribbling.
I do it all the time.
And I've got a whole bookful.
May I?
Here are a few of 'em.
That is incredible.
My favorite one...
There's a few.
Beautiful.
Do you know what these are called?
No.
They're actually called mandalas.
- Have you ever seen one before?
- Mandalas.
No. Never...
Heard of one or seen.
Noah, would it be all right...
If I borrowed these for a little while?
Borrow all you want.
Trade you for an A.
Only kiddin'. See ya.
Sure it's not in one of the other books?
No, it's in here,
it's one of the old ones.
I know I've seen it.
There it is.
I knew it.
It's 12th century,
it's one of the oldest known.
Oh, my god...
That is incredible.
It's almost an exact match.
And you know something else?
This is the same image...
...from my dream.
Larry...
Hey, Noah...
You know what time it is?
Yeah, I know, it's late, but...
You gotta see this.
What is this? I mean
it's way past your bedtime, bud.
It's... Uh...
What is that?
It's part of my exhibit
for the science fair at school.
It's amazing, how did you do that?
It was easy.
First i discovered that spiders
are sensitive to sound waves...
...and seem to move when they
hear various frequencies.
Then I experimented
with the frequencies...
...to make them move in
specific patterns.
I calculated their movements
with my computer...
...and I re-programmed them.
Their circular webs started changing
into something more elongated.
I call it...
...the structured bridge.
This geometric design is
extraordinarily strong...
...and would be equal to
a beam that could hold...
...1,000 pounds per square inch.
Did he do this on his own?
Did you help him?
No, he's done it all by himself.
He's just, sort of,
taken off all of a sudden.
You know,
in the last month or so.
His sister is highly gifted too.
Mm. No, no, no, no.
This is more than highly gifted.
This is genius.
He's gonna win the
national science fair.
...that exist today,
a bridge of this type...
...could span
the entire solar system.
Are there any questions?
"It was brillig and the slithy toves...
"Did gyre and gimble in the wabe...
"All mimzy were the borogoves...
"And the mome raths outgrabe."
Wait, did that say mimzy?
Uh, yep.
Let me see.
Look, she's got mimzy too.
- With the white rabbit?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
- And this is mimzy.
She came here to find me.
I don't know why.
White rabbit, just like in the book.
You know, he was the one
who was always late...
...for a very important date.
Where did you get it?
We found her on the beach.
Noah thinks she's from outer space...
But he doesn't really know.
Outer space.
Do you believe in aliens?
Aliens? Like flying saucers
and things like that?
Yeah, I guess I do, sort of.
Noah does too.
Oh, well... boys.
Do you think aliens
would ever come here?
Some people think they
might be here right now...
...and we don't even know it.
Really?
But what do they want?
I don't know.
Noah doesn't know
if they're good or bad...
They might help us or kill us...
...or maybe steal our brains.
Steal our brains?
If I show you something
promise you won't tell?
Oh. Like... a secret?
Really? Cool!
What kind of secret?
I can do a magic trick
with my hand.
Really? Yeah. Show me.
Ok.
Whoop... Thank you.
That's, um... That's...
That's a really great magic trick, Em.
Honey, c'mere.
Sweetheart, please, come here!
Come here, ok? No!
- Oh, my god.
- It's ok.
It doesn't hurt.
Watch.
Oh, my god! No! No! No! Uh!
Julie! Julie! Wait up! What's
wrong? Don't you wanna get pai d?
I... I gotta go!
I gotta go home!
- Julie, what's wrong?
- Honey, are you ok?
- What happened?
- Nothing.
What happened?
What did you do?
Nothing, daddy.
I just showed her a magic trick.
You know what?
I'll call Julie in the morning.
I'm sure it was nothing.
It's not just Julie...
It's everything.
I mean what about
Noah's science project, huh?
How did he do that
all by himself?
I mean, usually he struggles,
he needs my help...
...and suddenly he's in
a league of his own.
I mean, something is just not right.
What's not right? Look,
we got two special kids...
...with great minds,
imaginations, it's...
No, you're not getting it!
You know, I'm scared. I...
That... It's... It's
just not normal.
Don't talk like that.
Look, you're overreacting
to this whole...
David, stop it. Open your eyes.
I think we need to do something.
We have to get help.
Yeah, well, all right,
we'll get help. Um...
What kinda help?
No! Uh!
What was that?
Hey, George! What's goin' on?
Stop messin' around, this isn't funny.
Whoa, I just lost power in sector 4.
Keith, see if you can't rerout
power through substation 5.
Sector 3's offline.
Homeland security?
Yeah, no kidding.
Oh, my gosh.
- Hey, Noah, you all right?
- Daddy, what's happening?
Hey, sweetie. It's...
It's a blackout.
The whole neighborhood's dark.
Did you guys hear that sound?
They're saying that it's
blacked out half the state.
Unbelievable.
They don't know what's caused it.
No, well, they...
They will.
They always know exactly
how these things start.
- They do?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah!
- That didn't last long.
Are you ok?
I'm goin' down there now.
Oh, man, it's been a crazy morning.
The FBI, the Pentagon's been calling.
Look, I can't talk right now, Bill.
Well, somebody has to have the keys.
Look, Bill, just get
everybody down there now.
- It's Lorna.
- Who?
Your daughter, Nate.
She wants to know what's happening.
Tell her so does the president,
he wants to know too.
Hey, baby, you know where
my computer codes are?
He'll call you back, honey.
Did you try your dresser,
under your underwear?
Ahh, got it.
I knew you should
never have agreed to this.
You had a perfectly good job
at the justice department...
And now, all of a sudden,
you're a terrorism expert.
Look, baby,
the national director appointed me.
What do you want me to do,
call in sick?
But no one ever
actually thought you'd...
I mean, this is Seattle, Nate.
Why would terrorists attack Seattle?
I don't know, Sheila.
Look, we got the Boeing plant...
We got Microsoft...
We got the music experience.
I don't know, babe.
I gotta go.
I'll call you later, baby.
- Nate...
- Huh?
- Your fly.
- Who?
Zip up your fly.
Oh, oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
I love you, baby.
It grew right in front of my eyes.
I moved stuff inside the crystal...
And then... then whoosh.
Half of the state blacked out.
What do you think it is, noah?
I don't know...
But we have to throw it out.
All of them, all of the toys.
Everything, it's just too dangerous.
No!
Em, what if something
terrible's about to happen?
- That won't happen.
- How do you know?
Mimzy told me.
Mimzy, she's one of them.
She came with them.
...tesseract.
Acute, hexagon. Rhomboid...
Acute, tesseract, pyramidal, octahedron...
Acute, helix...
Whoa!
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone.
- Morning.
- Morning, sir.
For those of you who don't know,
I'm regional director Nathaniel Broadman.
And this is briefing one of alert 22d.
I think this is the day we've
been training for, everybody.
Training? Nate, we’ve only had
two meetings.
And thank god for those.
Look, we're gonna do this right,
we're gonna do it by the book.
Stu, you're up first.
What do you got?
This is from NSA, uh...
Global positioning has zeroed in...
On the Queen Anne section of Seattle.
No suspicious net chatter.
How could a surge like that originate
from a residential neighborhood?
That's what we wanna find out.
I got a very bad feeling about this one.
This is important.
No, I'm not taking them
to the emergency room.
Look, uh, I know Dr. Sherman very well.
Please get him to call me.
Eat up, guys.
Can you get me some orange juice?
Can you "please" get me
some orange juice?
I had a strange dream last night.
I dreamed about a bridge.
- What kind of bridge?
- I don't know what kind.
I dreamed that they were
gonna build a really big one.
Across the whole universe.
And you know what?
It's gonna come right to our house.
- Hello, Noah.
- Mr. White.
- Who is it, Noah?
- Is your mother ar...
Oh, hello, Mrs. Wilder.
I'm so sorry to barge in
on you like this.
I was gonna call
but I thought it would be better...
...if I came by in person.
This is my fiance Naomi.
- Hello.
- Do you have a minute?
- Uh, sure, come on in.
- Great.
Ok, thank you.
Uh, please, sit down.
Uh, Noah, do you think your mother and I
could have a moment or two alone, please?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org