Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Mr Ernest Worthing? B4, The Albany?
- Yes, that is my address.
Very sorry, sir,
but I have a writ against you
at the suit of the Savoy Hotel Company
Limited for 762 pounds, 14 shillings.
I never dine at the Savoy
at my own expense.
We have no option but to take out
an order for committal of your person.
- Committal of my person?
- For six months.
- Six months?
- You'll prefer to pay the bill.
How on earth can I do that?
No gentleman ever has any money.
In my experience,
it is usually relations who pay.
Quite right. Brother Jack?
762 pounds 14 shillings and tuppence
since last October.
I'm bound to say I never saw
such reckless extravagance in all my life.
My dear fellow, you have your debts
and I have mine.
This bill is yours.
- Mine?
- Yes, and you know it!
- If this is a jest, it is out of place.
- It is not!
Gross effrontery! Just what I expected!
And it is ingratitude. I didn't expect that.
Next, he'll be denying
he's Ernest Worthing in the first place.
Sorry to have disturbed so pleasant
a family meeting, but time presses.
We have to be at Holloway not later than
4 o'clock or one cannot obtain admission.
Holloway? Get off me!
It is at Holloway that detentions
are made.
I will not be imprisoned in the suburbs
for having dined in the West End!
Jack!
I agree to settle my brother's accounts...
...on the condition that he makes his way
to the bedside of the bedridden Bunbury,
whose health, I have been informed,
is rapidly declining.
Well... Ernest?
Mr Worthing, I would ask you
not to interrupt Miss Cardew's studies.
Miss Prism, Dr Chasuble
is expecting you in the vestry.
In the vestry? Dr Chasuble?
Expecting you, yes.
That sounds serious. I do not think
it would be right to keep him waiting.
It would be very wrong. The vestry is,
I am told, excessively damp.
This parting is very painful.
You cannot desert Mr Bunbury
in his hour of need.
I don't care about Bunbury any more.
I don't seem to care about anything.
I only care for you. I love you, Cecily.
Will you marry me, Cecily?
Of course. Why, we have been
engaged for the last three months.
- For the last three months?
- Exactly three months on Thursday.
Darling!
So when was the engagement
actually settled?
On the 14th February last.
After a long struggle with myself,
I accepted you under this tree.
This is the box
in which I keep your letters.
Letters? But I have never
written you any letters.
You need hardly remind me. I was
forced to write your letters for you.
I wrote always three times a week.
- Do let me look.
- No, I couldn't possibly.
They would make you far too conceited.
The three you wrote after I broke it off
are so beautiful and so badly spelled.
I can hardly read them without crying.
- Was our engagement broken off?
- Yes. On the 22nd of last March.
You can see the entry if you like.
"I broke off my engagement with Ernest."
- "The weather continues charming."
- What had I done? Nothing at all!
I am hurt you broke it off, particularly
when the weather was so charming.
It'd hardly be a serious engagement
if I hadn't broken it off at least once.
But I forgave you
before the week was out.
You're a perfect angel.
You dear romantic boy.
I never really thought of myself
as the marrying kind until now.
You mustn't break it off again.
I don't think I could break it off
now that I've actually met you.
Besides, there is the question
of your name.
Yes, of course.
It's always been a girlish dream of mine
to love someone named Ernest.
There's something in that name
that seems to inspire confidence.
Do you mean you couldn't love me
if I had another name?
But what name?
Algy, for instance.
I might respect you, Ernest,
I might admire your character,
but I fear that I would never be able
to give you my undivided attention.
The dog cart is ready for you, sir.
And now you must go, my love,
for sooner then shall you return.
What a charming boy.
I like his hair so much.
You wanted to see me, Dr Chasuble?
I didn't.
You didn't?
I'm sorry, but merely for the purposes
of clarification,
when you said you didn't, did you mean
you didn't say you wanted to see me
or you didn't, in fact, want to see me?
Isn't language a curious thing?
Will you excuse me? I have a double
baptism and I have to top up the font.
Bless you.
A Miss Fairfax has called
to see Mr Worthing.
On very important business,
Miss Fairfax states.
He is sure to be out soon.
Kindly bring some tea.
Yes, Miss.
- Miss Cardew.
- Thank you.
Miss Fairfax, let me introduce myself.
My name is Cecily Cardew.
Cecily Cardew. What a very sweet name.
Something tells me we're going
to be great friends. I like you already.
My first impressions are never wrong.
- You are here on a short visit?
- No, I live here.
Your mother or some female relative
of advanced years resides here also?
I have no mother nor any relations.
My guardian has the task
of looking after me.
- Your guardian?
- Yes, I'm Mr Worthing's ward.
Strange, he never mentioned it.
How secretive of him.
He grows more interesting hourly.
But I am bound to state that now that
I know you are Mr Worthing's ward,
I cannot help expressing a wish
that you were, well,
a little older than you seem to be
and not so alluring in appearance.
In fact, if I may speak candidly...
I think, whenever one has anything
unpleasant to say, one should be candid.
To speak with perfect candour, Cecily,
I wish you were fully 42
and more than usually plain for your age.
Ernest has a strong, upright nature.
He's the soul of truth and honour.
I think Jack, for instance. Jack.
Jack, for instance, a charming name.
It is not Mr Ernest Worthing
who is my guardian.
It is his brother, his elder brother.
That accounts for it. You've lifted a load
from my mind. I was growing anxious.
You're quite sure it's not Mr Ernest
Worthing who is your guardian?
Quite sure.
In fact... I am going to be his.
- I beg your pardon?
- Mr Ernest Worthing and I are engaged.
My darling Cecily,
I think there must be some slight error.
Mr Ernest Worthing is engaged to me.
The announcement will appear
in "The Morning Post" on Saturday.
You must be under some misconception.
Ernest proposed to me 10 minutes ago.
Very curious. For he asked me to be
his wife yesterday afternoon at 5.30.
If you would care to verify the incident,
pray do so.
I never travel without my diary
so I have something sensational to read.
I'm so sorry, dear Cecily,
but I'm afraid I have the prior claim.
May I offer you some tea, Miss Fairfax?
Thank you, Miss Cardew.
Sugar?
No, thank you.
Sugar is not fashionable any more.
- Cake or bread and butter?
- Bread and butter, please.
Cake is rarely seen
in the best houses nowadays.
From the moment I saw you,
I felt you were false and deceitful.
It seems to me that I am trespassing
on your valuable time.
No doubt you have other calls
of a similar character to make.
Ernest!
- You're back so soon.
- My own love.
May I ask, are you engaged
to be married to this young lady?
What young lady?
- Good heavens, Gwendolen!
- Yes, to good heavens Gwendolen.
No. What put such an idea
into your pretty little head?
- Thank you. You may.
- I thought there must be some error.
The gentleman who is embracing you
is my cousin, Mr Algernon Moncrieff.
Algernon... Moncrieff?
- Yes.
- Algy!
Here is Ernest.
- My own Ernest!
- Gwendolen, my darling!
I knew there must be
some misunderstanding.
The gentleman whose arm is round your
waist is my guardian, Mr John Worthing.
- I beg your pardon?
- This is Uncle Jack.
Jack?
- Are you called Algy?
- I cannot deny it.
Is your name really John?
I could deny it if I liked,
but it certainly is John.
- It has been for years.
- We have been grossly deceived.
- My poor wounded Cecily.
- My sweet, wronged Gwendolen.
- You will call me sister, will you not?
- Of course.
Let us go into the house.
They won't venture to come after us.
No. Men are so cowardly, aren't they?
How you can calmly eat muffins,
I can't make out.
You seem to be perfectly heartless.
I can hardly eat muffins
in an agitated manner, can I?
- Butter would probably get on my cuffs.
- It's heartless your eating muffins at all!
When I'm in trouble,
eating is my only consolation.
When I'm in really great trouble,
I refuse everything except food and drink.
At present, I am eating muffins
because I am unhappy.
Besides, I'm particularly fond of muffins.
There's no reason why you should
eat them all in that greedy way.
Would you like some teacake?
I don't like teacake.
A man may eat his own muffins
in his own garden!
They seem to be eating muffins.
You said it was perfectly heartless
to eat muffins!
I said it was perfectly heartless of you.
That is a very different thing.
Maybe, but the muffins are the same!
I certainly don't rate your chances
with my ward, Algernon!
There isn't much likelihood of you and
Miss Fairfax being united, Jackety Jack!
But is there any particular infant
in whom you are interested?
The fact is, Doctor,
I would like to be christened myself.
This afternoon,
if you have nothing better to do.
Surely, Mr Worthing,
you've been christened already?
I don't remember anything about it.
I don't know if the thing would bother you
or if you think that I'm a little too old now.
No, no. Not at all, not at all.
The sprinkling,
and indeed immersion, of adults
is a perfectly canonical practice.
When would you wish the ceremony
to be performed?
At about six if that would suit you.
- Perfectly, perfectly.
- Thank you.
- We cannot both be christened Ernest.
- I have a right to be christened if I like.
- You've been christened already!
- Not for years!
- But you have been christened.
- I know my constitution can stand it.
If you've never been christened, it's
dangerous your venturing on it now.
That is nonsense.
You're always talking nonsense.
- Let us preserve a dignified silence.
- Certainly. It's the only thing to do now.
The western wind is blowing fair
Across the dark Aegean Sea
And at the secret marble stair
My Tyrian galley waits for thee
Come down! The purple sail is spread
The watchman sleeps within the town
This dignified silence
produces an unpleasant effect.
Most distasteful.
Lady mine, come down
Come down
Lady, come down
She will not come, I know her well
Of lover's vows she hath no care
A little good a man can tell
Of one so cruel and so fair
True love is but a woman's toy
They never know the lover's pain
And I who loved as loves a boy
Must love in vain, must love in vain
Come down
Lady, come down
- We will not be the first to speak.
- Certainly not.
I have something to ask you.
Much depends on your reply.
Your common sense is invaluable.
Kindly answer me this question. Why did
you pretend to be my guardian's brother?
In order that I might meet you.
- That seems a satisfactory explanation.
- Yes, dear, if you can believe him.
I don't, but that doesn't affect
the beauty of his answer.
True. In matters of grave importance,
style, not sincerity, is the vital thing.
What explanation can you offer me
for pretending to have a brother?
Was it in order that you might come up
to town to see me as often as possible?
Can you doubt it, Miss Fairfax?
I have the gravest doubts on the subject,
but I intend to crush them.
Their explanations appear to be
quite satisfactory.
Mr Worthing's seems to have
the stamp of truth upon it.
I am content
with what Mr Moncrieff said.
His voice alone seemed to inspire
absolute credulity.
- Do you think we should forgive them?
- Yes...
- I mean, no.
- There are principles at stake
that one cannot surrender!
Your Christian names are still
an insuperable barrier. That is all.
- Our Christian names?
- Is that all?
We're going to be christened
this afternoon.
- You're prepared to do this terrible thing?
- I am.
You're ready to face this fearful ordeal?
On questions of self-sacrifice,
men are infinitely beyond us!
- We are.
- Darling!
- Lady Bracknell.
- Gwendolen!
What does this mean?
Merely that I am engaged to be married
to Mr Worthing, Mama.
Come here. Sit down.
Sit down immediately!
All communication between yourself
and my daughter must cease at once.
On this point, I am firm.
- I'm engaged to Gwendolen.
- You are nothing of the kind, sir.
And now, as regards Algy.
- Algy...
- Yes, Aunt Augusta.
Is it here that your invalid friend
Mr Bunbury resides?
No, Bunbury doesn't live here.
Bunbury's somewhere else at present.
In fact... Bunbury is dead.
- Dead?
- Dead.
When did he die?
His death must have been sudden.
He died this afternoon.
- What did he die of?
- Bunbury?
- He was quite exploded.
- Exploded?
Was he the victim
of a revolutionary outrage?
I was not aware
he was interested in social legislation.
My dear Aunt Augusta,
I mean he was found out.
The doctors found out that Bunbury
could not live, so Bunbury died.
He had great confidence
in the opinion of his physicians.
I'm glad he made up his mind
to some definite course of action
and acted under proper medical advice.
And now that we have finally
got rid of this Mr Bunbury,
may I ask, who is that young person
who's hand Algernon is now holding
in what seems to me to be
a peculiarly unnecessary manner?
- She is Miss Cecily Cardew, my ward.
- I am engaged to be married to Cecily.
- I beg your pardon?
- Mr Moncrieff and I are engaged.
I do not know if there is anything peculiar
about the air in this part of Hertfordshire,
but the number of engagements seem
to be considerably above the average
that statistics have laid down
for our guidance.
Is Miss Cardew connected with any of
the larger railway stations in London?
I merely desire information.
Until recently, I was not aware there were
anyone whose origin was a terminus.
Gwendolen, the time approaches
for our departure.
I'd better ask if Miss Cardew
has any fortune.
About £130,000 in the funds, that is all.
Goodbye. So pleased to have seen you.
A moment, Mr Worthing.
£130,000... and in the funds?
Miss Cardew seems to me to be a most
attractive young lady now I look at her.
Come over here, dear.
The chin a little higher dear.
Style largely depends on the way the chin
is worn. They are worn high at present.
Algy, there are distinct social possibilities
in Miss Cardew's profile.
Cecily is the sweetest, dearest girl. I don't
give tuppence for her social possibilities.
Never speak disrespectfully of society.
Only people who can't get into it do that.
You know that Algy has nothing
but his debts to depend upon.
I do not approve of mercenary marriages.
Indeed, when I married Lord Bracknell,
I had no fortune of any kind.
But I never dreamed for a moment
of allowing that to stand in my way.
- I suppose I must give my consent.
- Thank you, Aunt Augusta.
I beg your pardon for interrupting,
but I am Miss Cardew's guardian.
She can't marry without my consent until
she comes of age and I decline to give it.
Upon what grounds, may I ask?
I suspect him of being untruthful.
Untruthful? My nephew Algy?
I fear there can be no possible doubt
about the matter.
During my temporary absence in London
on an important question of romance,
he obtained admission to my house
by the pretence of being my brother.
He won over the affections of my ward,
and his intentions were purely financial.
Deny it if you dare!
He subsequently stayed to tea
and devoured every single muffin.
What makes his behaviour
even more heartless
is that he was aware I have no brother
and I don't intend to have a brother.
- Please!
- Come here, sweet child.
- How old are you, dear?
- 18, Aunt Augusta.
It will not be long before you are of age,
free from the restraints of your guardian.
According to the terms
of her grandfather's will,
she does not come legally of age
until she is 35.
That does not seem to be
a grave objection.
35 is a very attractive age.
London society is full of women
of the highest birth
who have, of their own free choice,
remained 35 for years.
- Could you wait for me till I was 35?
- You know I could.
I felt it instinctively,
but I couldn't wait all that time.
- What is to be done, Cecily?
- I don't know, Mr Moncrieff.
My dear Mr Worthing,
as Miss Cardew states quite positively
that she cannot wait until she is 35,
a remark which, I am bound to say,
shows a somewhat impatient nature,
I beg you to reconsider your decision.
My dear Lady Bracknell, the moment you
consent to my marriage with Gwendolen,
your nephew can form an alliance
with my ward.
You must be aware that
what you propose is out of the question.
Then a passionate celibacy
is all any of us can look forward to.
Come, dear.
We've missed five, if not six trains.
To miss more might expose us
to comment on the platform.
Everything is quite ready
for the christenings.
The christenings, sir?
Is not that somewhat premature?
Both of these gentlemen have expressed
a desire for immediate baptism.
At their age?
The idea is grotesque and irreligious.
Algy, I forbid you to be baptised.
I will not hear of such excesses.
- I'm sorry to interrupt, Dr Chasuble.
- Yes, yes?
Miss Prism has asked me to tell you
she's waiting for you in the vestry.
She's been waiting for some time.
Miss Prism... in the vestry.
Waiting for you, yes.
Miss Prism?
- Did I hear you mention a Miss Prism?
- Yes, madam...
- Bless you.
- Yes, I'm on my way to join her.
Is she a female of repellent aspect
remotely connected with education?
She is the most cultivated of ladies
and the picture of respectability.
It is obviously the same person.
Take me to the vestry at once.
I've been expecting you, dear Doctor.
Prism!
Prism.
Where is that baby?
34 years ago, you left Lord Bracknell's
house - 104 Upper Grosvenor Street -
in charge of a perambulator that
contained a baby of the male sex.
You never returned.
A few weeks later, through the elaborate
investigations of the Metropolitan Police,
the perambulator was discovered
at midnight
standing by itself
in a remote corner of Bayswater.
It contained the manuscript
of a three-volume novel
of more than usually revolting
sentimentality.
But the baby was not there.
Prism, where is that baby?
Lady Bracknell, I admit with shame
that I do not know.
The facts of the case are these.
On the morning of the day in question,
a day for ever branded on my memory,
I prepared, as usual, to take the baby
out in its perambulator.
I had also with me a somewhat old,
but capacious handbag,
in which I had intended to place
a work of fiction
that I had written
during my few unoccupied hours.
In a moment of mental abstraction,
for which I never can forgive myself,
I deposited the manuscript
in the bassinet
and placed the baby in the handbag.
Where did you deposit the handbag?
- Do not ask me, Mr Worthing.
- This is a matter of importance to me.
I insist on knowing where you deposited
the handbag that contained that infant.
I left it in the cloakroom of one of
London's larger railway stations.
- What railway station?
- Victoria. The Brighton Line.
Uncle Jack seems strangely agitated.
Is this the handbag, Miss Prism?
Examine it carefully before you speak.
The happiness of more than one life
depends on your answer.
That is undoubtedly mine. I am delighted
to have it so unexpectedly restored to me.
It has been a great inconvenience
being without it.
More is restored to you
than this handbag. I was the baby.
You?
- Mother!
- Mr Worthing, I am unmarried.
Unmarried? I cannot deny
that is a serious blow.
But who has the right to cast a stone
against one who has suffered?
Cannot repentance wipe out
an act of folly?
- I forgive you!
- No, Mr Worthing, there is some error.
There is the lady who can tell you
who you really are.
Lady Bracknell, I hate to seem inquisitive,
but would you inform me who I am?
You are the son of my poor sister,
Mrs Moncrieff,
and, consequently,
Algy's younger brother.
Algy's younger brother?
So I have a brother, after all.
Yes.
I knew I had a brother!
I always said I had a brother.
How could you ever have doubted
I had a brother?
Dr Chasuble, my unfortunate brother.
Miss Prism, my unfortunate brother.
Gwendolen, my unfortunate brother.
Lady Bracknell, my brother!
Under these strange and unforeseen
circumstances, Mr Moncrieff,
you may kiss your Aunt Augusta.
Mr Moncrieff...
...after all that has occurred
and any inconvenience I may have
caused you in your infancy,
it is my duty to resign my position
in this household.
That is absurd. I won't hear of it.
Sir, it is my duty to leave.
I have really nothing more
to teach dear Cecily.
In the very difficult accomplishment
of getting married,
I fear my sweet and clever pupil
has far outstripped her teacher.
A moment, Miss Prism.
Dr Chasuble.
I have come to the conclusion
that the Primitive Church
is in error on certain points
on the question of matrimony.
Corrupt readings seem to have
crept into the text.
In consequence...
...I beg to solicit the honour of your hand.
- Frederick!
- Laetitia!
- My dear Cecily!
- My dearest Algernon!
- My own Gwendolen.
- My own... But wait, who are you?
I mean, what is your Christian name
now you have become someone else?
I'd forgotten that point. The question
had better be cleared up at once.
At the time when Miss Prism left me
in the handbag, had I been christened?
I think you were christened
after your father.
What was my father's Christian name?
I cannot now recall what the General's
name was. I've no doubt he had one.
Can't you recollect what his name was?
We were hardly on speaking terms.
He died when I was three.
His name would appear on the army lists.
The General was a man of peace,
except in his domestic life.
But his name would appear
on any military directory.
Army lists of the last 40 years are here.
They should've been my constant study.
Lieutenants... captains... colonels...
...colonels... generals!
M.
Maxbolm, Magley,
Markby, Migsby, Mobbs, Moncrieff!
Lieutenant, 1860. Christian names.
I always told you, Gwendolen,
that my name was Ernest, didn't I?
Well, it is Ernest, after all.
It naturally is Ernest.
My own Ernest, I felt from the first
that you could have no other name.
My nephew...
...you seem to be displaying signs
of triviality.
On the contrary, Aunt Augusta,
I've realised for the first time
the vital importance of being earnest.
The western wind is blowing fair
Across the dark Aegean Sea
And at the secret marble stair
My Tyrian galley waits for thee
Come down! The purple sail is spread
The watchman sleeps within the town
Leave thy lily-flowered bed
O lady mine, come down
Come down
Lady, come down
O, lady, come down
She will not come, I know her well
Of lover's vows she hath no care
A little good a man can tell
Of one so cruel and so fair
True love is but a woman's toy
They never know the lover's pain
And I who loved as loves a boy
Must love in vain, must love in vain
Come down
Lady, come down
I think your high notes
may have damaged our chances.
- You're completely out of tune!
- How dare you!
- I'll take this bit.
- Leave this to me!
- I'm coming through!
- Go easy, my dear fellow.
- Come down! Come down!
- Lady, come down
- Overdoing it. Less is more.
Come down
Lady, come down
That wasn't so bad, was it?
Maybe they're not going to come down.
Maybe we should go up.
- Algy, you're always talking nonsense.
- Well, it's better than listening to it.
Lady, come down
Did you hear what
I was playing, Lane?
I didn't think it polite to listen, sir.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org