Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You stepped over the line.
- Huh?
- You stepped over the line, miss.
Uh, it's Ms.
Sorry, Ms., but, um-
I meant to.
You're not supposed to do that.
Or the photos.
- That's why I tried it.
- Why?
To see what would happen.
Well, uh,
I mean,
I'm what happens.
I-I ha-- I have to walk over, like I've
done, and ask you to take a step back.
And if someone doesn't,
what then?
I'm not sure.
I've never had anyone
not step back.
I've only said it, like, four times,
and every time they've done it.
What if I'm your first?
Non-stepper, I mean. Then what?
Look, I'm off in 10 minutes. I'd probably just
stand here, make sure you didn't touch anything.
Really?
Pretty much.
Yeah-- No, I'd let the next shift talk
to you, kick you out, or whatever.
You wouldn't grab me or anything?
You're not gonna mess up
my weekend with this, are you?
I wasn't planning on it, but I'm
not completely against it either.
See, if you get all crazy, then I gotta
write up a report and stuff.
I'm here till 5:00, 5:30 easy, and I have
a second job to get to- the video store.
Oh, that's where I--
I've seen you in there.
you helped me once, I think.
Yeah? With what?
The Picture of Dorian Gray.
You found it in " Drama,"
not "Classics."
Right!
I remember that!
Somebody misplaced it. Yes!
Yeah, behind Cabaret.
Mmm.
That's funny.
Anyway, you helped me.
That was... nice.
Thanks.
But you're not gonna
return the favor, right?
You mean, step back over-
- No, I-I'm- I'm sorry. I can't.
- Why is that?
It's a pretty good-sized sculpture.
You could see it just fine from here.
Truthfully?
I'm gonna deface the statue.
Oh.
Uh, is that paint?
Yes, it is.
Great.
Hey, uh, paint's not really a great
thing to bring into a museum.
Why do you have that?
I'm gonna do something to the nude.
What, like, color it?
I'm thinking more of
painting a big dick on it.
And would "Why?" be completely
out of the question here?
- Because I don't like art that isn't true.
- True?
This sculpture, it's fake, it's not real.
Therefore, false art.
No, it's a Fornicelli.
It definitely is.
I read the little thing there one time.
- Yes, but the leaf isn't.
- It's not?
Well, what is it? A paste or something,
like strippers have?
It's plaster...
that was added by a committee who had
complaints from local townspeople.
Really?
I didn't know that.
They took issue with his thing-
you know, the shape of it.
Said it was too lifelike.
It's supposed to be God. You know,
that's what pisses them off.
Look.
See, it's right behind
the leaf there.
You can just see his-
Yeah, but they didn't even cover it properly.
It's shoddy craftsmanship.
I mean, if you're gonna do it, at least do it--
Exactly. Do it right.
So, you're a student, then,
or is this just basic anarchy?
Student.
Me too.
What's your emphasis?
Taking out school loans, mostly.
But I do sit in on
a few English classes.
You're in art?
Mm-hmm. MFA.
Oh.
Applied Theory and Crit.
So, is this, like, a project,
then, or--
No, I am just getting started
on my thesis project now.
It's a big sort of
installation... thing.
That's a good word, huh?
"Thing."
It is.
Anyway, this is just...
an idea I had.
You're cute.
I don't like your hair.
Thanks... I think.
No, you're definitely cute,
but you should-
You should do something
with it, your hair.
Okay.
I-I'll try that.
Your relief's late.
Yeah. Typical.
Yeah, so do you have to stay
at your station until they spell you, or-
Oh, no, no. At punch-out time I'm
supposed to get down there and do it.
They can really be pricks
about that.
Oh, you should go, then.
Yeah.
Can I call you?
What do you want to call me?
Um...just up...
for right now.
I mean, talk.
Maybe get crazy.
Um, take you to dinner?
Okay.
Uh, sure.
Do they... allow you
to do that here?
What, eat dinner?
I meant, hit on the patrons.
Uh, no.
They've got a pretty strict policy
about that too actually.
But--
Ah. The great equalizer.
" But."
Exactly.
I'll take the risk.
Good answer, Grasshopper.
What?
Kung Fu. On TV?
Remember when he was a kid, there was
an old guy with fake contact lenses-
Right!
Grasshopper.
I don't really watch
much television.
Yeah.
So, do you want
a number?
Hmm? Oh, God.
Absolutely.
Oh, dang it.
I don't have a pen.
Me either.
Here.
What?
Give me the jacket.
Hmm? Oh.
Uh-- Uh--
That's my own.
That's not part of the uniform.
That's mine.
Good. Now you'll
always have it on you.
3-3-0--
Great.
Yeah.
- So, I'll call you?
- Yeah.
It was nice
to meet you... again.
You too.
You can definitely tell.
you can.
- Really.
- I bet your friends say something.
Twenty bucks.
Okay.
- I mean, I can't tell, so I figured-
- That's because you see you every day,
shower, getting dressed-
- So do you.
- I don't see you shower or getting dressed.
I meant everyday.
So far, anyways.
I know. I'm kidding.
Oh.
I'd like that, though,
if... you would.
What?
Showering and...
getting dressed, you know-
Both, if you want.
Either. Anything.
Any moment I can get with you.
That's what I'd like.
Ask and you shall receive.
So I'm asking, then.
So you shall be
receiving, then.
PDA.
What?
Public display of affection.
Oh.
I'm not used to that.
No?
I don't mind.
Really?
Nah. Whose business is it?
Ours, right?
Kiss if we want to. Make love
in a bathroom stall. Who cares?
I'd start with
the administration.
Why should they? We're two adults.
We know what we're doing.
I think this is a bigger discussion
than before Jenny and Philip get here.
Whatever.
Oh, no, I mean--
I'd love to have it with you-
uh, the discussion.
And I agree... somewhat.
I understand.
No, another time
we'll definitely discuss it.
"Another time."
I'd rather do it.
We'll, let me go
check the men's room.
You amaze me.
And you amaze me.
You do. Look at you.
It's just a little jogging.
I'm very proud of you.
Thank you...
Henry Higgins.
What's that?
That's from a book.
Well, it's a play actually.
Not the one we're seeing,
though, is it?
No, we're... seeing Medea.
Oh, yeah, right.
I read this as an undergrad.
I like it.
- Should I be nervous?
- No, not too much.
I mean, unless we have kids.
Now, what about you?
What about me?
- I don't know anything about you.
- Yes, you do.
I don't. Not really.
- Where am I from?
- Illinois, near Chicago.
- Sign.
- Gemini, I think.
- The twins, yes.
- Does that mean that you have a split personality?
- No, it means I was born in June.
- Ah. Okay.
Anything else you wanna know?
Why do you like me?
- What?
- Why would you like me?
I'm not anything. I mean-
Don't do that, okay? That's the
only thing about you I don't like.
What you see in yourself
or don't see.
Fuckin' insecurities.
Sorry.
Do you like me?
Of course.
- And do I appear to like you? Huh?
- Yeah.
I mean, it seems like it, yes.
I do like you.
Do I seem to know my own mind?
No question.
So don't you trust me, then, to know how I feel?
Yeah- No, you're right-
I mean,
don't worry about "why..."
when... "what"
is right in front of you.
Those are very wise words...
from someone
with such a great ass.
Kiss me...
Grasshopper.
Ah-ah-ah!
PDA.
I don't think anybody wants
to watch you kiss, Adam.
Hi, guys.
- Hey, Phil.
- Hello.
Hi.
Hey!
Evelyn, this is Philip.
- Hello.
- Hi.
And his fiancee, Jenny.
- Hey.
So, should we grab our tickets?
Adam, what's up with you?
Did you lose weight?
Um... a little, maybe.
No, it's--
He cut his hair or something.
- That's it, right?
- Right.
Yeah, well, uh, both, sort of.
Huh.
Okay, so, let's, uh-
Come on.
Oh.
- So tell me this again. You guys are gonna-
- Underwater.
We're gonna get married underwater.
You gotta be kidding me. Like in those
Life magazine photos you see, or whatever.
Is that, like,
a... California thing?
No. We wanted to try something bold.
That oughta do it.
That is crazy. Really.
So if we want to attend,
we have to--
Get in the tank with us.
you bet.
- No. Honey, I thought we said the guests-
- U h, we haven't--
We haven't settled
that part completely.
- That is nuts.
- No, I applaud you. I think it is very bold.
Yeah, well, don't expect my buddy
here to follow in our footsteps.
- He's the least adventurous
person I know. - Really?
Absolutely.
Oh, and the marriage thing?
Uh-uh.
It's not gonna happen. Sorry.
I don't know how many nights
I listened to this guy say,
" Not me, man. I'm never
gettin' hooked. No way, man."
Well, well!
Listen, don't encourage him.
My room doesn't need
any more encouragement.
Former roommate.
You're gonna look stupid
in one of it hose wet suits.
Hey, let's not be
a party pooper, my friend.
This could have been yours.
Oh, Phil, stop being-
Adam and I had a class together, and he
never got up the nerve to ask me out.
I'm borrowing his pen, like, all the time--
hint, hint--
and he's this total monk
the whole semester.
Anyway, Phil picks him up
from class one day, sees me,
and we went to mini golf
that same night.
I cannot tell a lie.
I got the moves, God help me.
Whoo!
God help all of us.
Well, like I said,
I think it's great.
It's really amazing- it is-
to find anybody willing
to take a risk these days,
to look a little silly
or different or anything.
Bravo.
To people with balls.
To balls.
Long may they wave.
I'll tell you
what took some balls.
That museum thing a few
weeks back, with the balls.
Did you guys
read about that?
Oh, Adam, of course you did.
you were supposed to be guarding it.
But, uh--
Evelyn, did you hear about it?
- The penis.
- Yes, I did.
Why are we whispering?
Because you don't say "penis"
in Jenny's house.
But we're at my place now,
so we sing it from the eaves.
# Penis, penis #
Bar's closed.
Last call.
- # Penis, penis #
- Nice.
Seriously, though,
can you believe that shit?
Somebody with the gall to pull that kind
of bullshit on our campus? Fuckin' burns me up.
Shh.
I'm an artist, so...
Maybe we should-
I don't really have the same reaction as--
I mean, this isn't Berkeley. What does
that mean anyway- " I'm an artist"?
Mmm, nothing.
It means nothing really.
Just that
I understand the impulse.
You what?
Um, Evelyn, we should probably-
No, no. Wait, Adam.
I wanna hear.
What impulse?
It's called vandalism.
Uh, does anybody want dessert?
Holdon.
This is rich. Go ahead.
Just that, um, I don't think
it was just kids playing.
I think it was
a sort of statement, a kind of--
- Statement?
- Yeah, I do.
What kind of statement would that be?
It was pornography.
- Oh, no, it wasn't.
- Yes, it was.
No. Pornography is meant
to titillate, to excite you.
- Did you see a picture of what happened?
- We did, yeah.
And does a penis excite you?
I mean, just any old penis?
Uh, you're funny,
and that's not the point.
It's totally the point!
How about you, Jenn? Did you like
what you saw? Did it get you hot?
This is, like,
uncalled for, okay?
- All she said was--
- I know what she said. Why don't you let her speak?
Did you wanna say
anything else? Huh?
Okay.
Then, look, all I'm--
I'm saying is that, in my opinion,
it wasn't pornography,
it was a statement.
Wow.
The postgraduate mind at work.
You know, I still don't see
how that makes it a statement.
- What do you mean?
- It's graffiti.
It would be a huge statement,
especially for a town like this.
Which "Take Back the Night" rally
did you find her at, Adam?
You're really the obnoxious type.
You know that?
- I mean, how long did you have
to stomach this guy? - Evelyn-
Anyhow, who knows what the person
was saying by it. We don't.
But I think it was a gesture,
a kind of manifesto, if you will-
W-W-Wait. I don't think a person's
dick can be a manifesto. Uh-uh.
You can write a manifesto
on your thing,
but your thing can't be one.
I'm sure I read that somewhere.
See, you're just trying to be really-
Hey, I'm not trying to be anything.
Who the hell do you think you are?
A few double dates, and telling me
anything about who I am.
- Un-fucking-believable!
- Okay, this is getting a little-
Adam, you can really pick 'em.
Let's just forget the whole-
- You are not gonna take his side in this, are you?
- No.
Jesus! I'm just trying to get out of here
with a touch of dignity.
I've got a test tomorrow anyway.
"Statement."
Just shut the fuck up!
Fuck right off.
How would you know?
I think she was making one.
So, that's my opinion.
Jenny,
thanks for everything.
Yeah, how'd you know
it was a girl?
I don't.
I just said.
It's a guess-
what it was, where it was placed.
An educated guess.
Oh, you're not-
She's not trying to take a poke
at my being an undergrad, is she?
Okay, can we just stop this now, please?
Adam, tell me she didn't just-
Hey, artiste, how did you know it was
a woman who painted the cock?
Very, very suspicious there.
You're such a prick.
Man, how do you go on
day after day?
Let's go.
Adam,
are you coming?
Yeah.
I'll meet you out front?
I just wanna-
Okay.
You're very sweet.
Good luck.
"Good luck"?
Hey, fuck you!
Oh, come on, m-man!
Where in hell did you meet that bitch?
At the museum.
What, did she give you a haircut
and a blowjob, now you're her puppy?
Phil!
I'm not her puppy!
The wedding sounds great.
Really, it sounds- Yeah.
You don't have to leave.
Were you...
always like this before?
So...
You know.
Shy?
Mm-hmm.
Just about the fact that no one
would ever sleep with me. That's all.
Come on!
No, seriously.
I mean, you're, like,
I don't know,
only the third person
I've ever--
Really?
Yeah.
I mean it.
And they were both young.
I mean, I was too.
I wasn't, like, hanging out
by a day care or anything.
It was during high school, mostly.
So you're sort of
in uncharted waters here.
I don't wanna
blow your cover, but...
I could kinda tell.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, that's okay.
Nobody here at school?
Well, nothing serious.
Dates.
Some close calls.
But not anyone,
you know-
Like Jenny?
No, no.
Are you sorry
you didn't ask her out?
Hmm? I mean, if--
if I wasn't in the equation.
Not really.
Hmm.
We just never got the right-
What--
I sort of blew that one.
Anyway, it's kinda weird
talking about it now that-
That's okay.
You know, it's nice to see,
every so often, someone... gallant.
So, did you enjoy tonight?
Uh-huh.
Dinner was great.
The trip into the city-
that was fun. I like your car.
I meant the performance.
Oh, right, that.
Um--
Not really.
Well...
that's all right.
- That's fine.
- Oh, no, it's not that I didn't enjoy it. It was okay.
You didn't think it was amazing?
I thought it was amazing that the cops
didn't bust in and stop her.
Oh, come on!
- How could you not find that moving,
what she was doing? - Easy.
I mean, granted, I usually love it when
a woman removes her tampon in front of me.
- Very sexy.
- It's not supposed to be sexy.
I was joking. You know that.
I mean, Jesus, it's an expression
of herself as an artist, as a woman,
a person.
I couldn't believe what I was seeing.
Me either. You didn't get it.
That's all.
No, that's not true.
We just don't agree. That's all.
- I wanted to like it.
- Then why didn't you?
Maybe because she was finger painting
portraits of her daddy using menstrual blood.
She... is completely influential,
totally vanguard.
To me, it was nasty, it was private, and I felt like
it was something I wasn't supposed to be seeing.
She allowed you to though.
She allowed you into her world,
into her work,
but in a highly theatrical way.
Exactly my point.
It's called theater, not therapy.
No, it's called performance art!
- It's called her period!
- It's called your taste up your ass!
Did we just have our first fight?
I think so.
Yeah, we did.
Cool.
Better mark it down in our diaries.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
We can do that- fight.
That's good.
- Why good?
- 'Cause, um,
now we get to make up.
Were you nervous before?
I mean, about us with the video.
Oh, not really.
- A bit.
- Sure.
Yeah. It's just, let's not watch it. Okay?
Do we have to do that?
- Not if you don't want to.
- Good.
'Cause I don't think I could get into
that actually. See, I'm totally different.
I think everyone should
see themselves doing it,
and their friends
should see it too.
That's why the tape's going back to my place.
Don't be so frightened of everything.
I'm not.
I'm not frightened anyway.
I just don't think that's a thing other
people need to see, ever- my ass.
People like who? Philip?
No, that's fine.
you can show him.
Are you crazy?
Why is he your friend?
Oh, God, you don't wanna go over all that.
I just don't think you need
that kind of person in your life.
I mean, no one does.
It- It may be a touch early to start
dictating who my friends are.
Yeah... I suppose.
Boy, he really got under
your skin, didn't he?
Under, over, around.
I hate that kind of guy.
What kind?
That kind.
Whatever he is, that's what I hate.
I'll let him know.
No! God, no.
Don't give him the satisfaction.
And he'd take it too. Believe me.
I don't know.
Maybe it would help him,
you know, be better or something.
The only thing that would help him
is a fuckin' knife through his throat.
Okay, I'm glad I don't have
a pet rabbit or anything.
You know what I mean.
Um... no, not really.
I've just been around his type,
that's all, and I don't like him.
Yeah, I got that part.
No big deal.
Right. No, it was the "knife through the throat"
part that was the big deal, I thought.
Oh, that's just an expression.
From where?
Transylvania?
No.
From the Scorned Girl's Handbook.
Oh, yeah, page 333.
You've been peeking.
You know what happens
to peekers, don't you?
Well, if they're deejays, they usually get asked
to play " Misty" on the radio all the time.
Close.
No, I'll show you.
But you have to do me a favor.
What's that?
Just... smile.
Smile into the camera...
for as...
long as you can.
Jenny!
Adam! Hi!
Hey.
Hi.
Oh!
So--
Thanks for coming.
I appreciate it.
Of course.
How's it going?
You know... okay.
Right.
Lots to do for a wedding.
I bet.
Yeah. Invitations to get out,
arrangements to make.
Air tanks to fill.
That too.
So you guys are still
going through with that, huh?
That's what we're saying.
- What do you mean, "saying"?
- No, no, no. We are.
It's what we're doing.
I just-
-Jenny, what?
- I don't know.
- I'm just, you know, worried.
- Why?
About what?
What do you think? Philip.
He's just, I don't know, being funny.
- Funny how?
-Just kinda funny odd.
Like nice.
- Nice?
- Yeah. You know, sweet?
Now, I love him and all.
I do. You know that.
But that is not the way I would describe him
to people- sweet. Would you?
I wouldn't exactly use his name
and "sweet" in the same...
short story.
And that's
what's bugging me.
I mean, he's only been like this
once before, maybe twice.
But definitely once, when we were first
going out and he was seeing somebody else.
- You remember that?
- Yeah. I do. The other one.
The other Jenny. Exactly.
I'd call and I could hear him
freeze up, you know,
get all sort of... sweet,
fish around slowly until he
figured out if it was her or me.
God, I used to hate that.
Maybe I'm just
making it all up, you know?
I mean, my own insecurities
and looking for a reason to not-
Dive in?
- Take the plunge?
- Oh, God!
Jump off the deep end?
Stop me before I-
Cute, but yes.
That might be it,
but I don't think so.
I mean, I wanna get married.
I do.
Even if it is underwater.
And I love the guy,
whether he's sweet or not.
It's just, I don't believe him
now that he is.
Well, you got me.
Really? I mean, you don't know anything?
Haven't felt that?
I only see him, like, once a week in our survey
course, so it's not like I'm in the inner circle anymore.
I know. I just thought that maybe you'd
tell me if you knew something.
But I would tell you, Jenny.
I would. Seriously.
Really?
I think so.
I mean-- Oh, look, that's a lousy thing
to pass on to a person.
And if I did, you know, know something
and then told you,
You'd more likely hate me forever
than be grateful.
Yeah,
that's probably true.
Um, you could lie.
Feel free.
No, you're probably right. So that doesn't
exactly make me want to come clean here.
Which I have nothing to come
clean about, okay? Honestly.
It's just-
I-I just feel that I would.
I-I do.
Because I think you're pretty amazing...
if the, uh, truth be known.
And you're almost married,
so why shouldn't it be?
Uh, the truth, I mean.
Thank you.
Not a problem.
Anyway, that's all I know.
Which is nothing.
Okay!
Hwah!
I'm just being stupid.
Hey.
If you feel it, it's not stupid.
God!
You're a lovely person.
You know that?
" Lovely"?
Jesus, why don't you just
call me gay and get it over with?
Hey! Lovely is nice.
No, I wish there were a few more
lovely people in the world.
I mean it. You are.
And getting cuter by the day.
What is that girl doing to you?
Lots.
She's amazing. Really.
What happened to your glasses?
- Are you wearing-
- No! Adam!
- Are those contacts?
- Yep.
Contacts.
Oh, my God.
This from the former
tape-around-the-nose-thing champion.
That was only for, like, a week!
That one time!
I know, but still, you gotta admit-
I do. It's great.
I feel better.
" Better."
I mean, you're, like, this totally hot guy now.
No. No, I mean, I always thought
you were handsome before, but...
I didn't think you'd go in
for the makeover thing.
Me either.
Who knew?
Well, apparently she did.
You are still seeing her, aren't you?
Oh, yeah. She's-
You don't hold a grudge, do ya?
All she said that night-
Oh, God, I couldn't believe that!
No, it was great.
No, truthfully, it was. I mean, Phil needed
to hear every word of that.
He did, too.
Hear it, I mean.
You know, he even said something
after you guys left.
I mean, not an admittance
of guilt, exactly,
but as close to one as we're
likely to hear from the guy.
Really? What'd he say? I'm amazed.
As was I.
He put on quite the show.
I remember vaguely.
They both did.
Anyway, later on
he said something like,
" He could do worse."
Not exactly a seal of approval.
No, but a lot for him.
And after what she said?
You're right.
Huh.
Hey, her middle name's
not Jenny or anything, is it?
No such luck.
Whew!
No, it's Ann.
Evelyn Ann Thompson.
It's nice, right?
Eat?
What?
Eat.
Those are her initials.
The acronym of her name is E-A-T.
Hey, that's cute.
Oh, God, you're a goner.
I know.
It's pathetic, isn't it?
Somewhat.
But lovely.
No, not that again!
What the heck is this?
- What is this?
- What?
Did you stop biting your nails?
Yeah, for, like, a month now.
Don't tell me she--
It's true.
She gave me some kind of crap to put
on 'em, and that was it. I just stopped.
You have nails!
This is crazy!
It's no biggie.
The whole time I've known you-
three years now-
Your fingers have looked
like raw meat.
Anyway, awful.
And now you just quit.
This girl is the messiah.
I've quit before.
For, like, an hour.
I love this woman.
Me too.
Yeah, I can see that.
Wow.
And you'd really tell me
if you knew something?
I would, yes.
Okay.
Geez, when did you get so cute?
Whew.
Shit.
Yeah.
What was that all about?
I don't know.
Uh, I'm not sure.
Look, I'm sorry.
- No. Don't be.
- I am.
Uh, I'm the one with the ring on.
Yeah, it's...
my friend's ring.
Good point.
Thanks for reminding me.
You're welcome.
Aw, dang it!
Oh, no, listen,
it wasn't because of,
You know, my worries or whatever,
how I'm feeling about Philip right now.
It wasn't.
Okay.
It just-
Happened.
Right.
I've wanted to do that for a long time.
Three years.
Me too.
Now we take it down to the--
the beach and bury it.
Don't we?
Yeah, we do.
Of course.
Um...
don't you want to?
Bury it?
Yes. Or--
No. No, we can't talk about it.
Don't even say the-
God. Do you have
a shovel in your car?
Uh, I don't, no.
But... I have my car.
My bike's right over there.
Then it...
should be fine if we were to...
go to the beach.
I suppose so.
Good.
Oh, come on.
We should go bury this.
On the beach.
What time did they say?
10:30.
It's 10:50 now.
No big deal. You always wait
at the doctor's office.
I know. I just had to be
at work by 12:00.
Today?
Yeah, I told you that.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did.
I always work Wednesdays.
Really?
Yeah. Every Wednesday.
It's okay.
I can be late if I have to.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I mean, they hate it,
but I'll come up with something.
Or we can go.
No.
I wanna do this. I do.
I mean, w-who wouldn't want to pay a lot
of money to get their nose chopped off?
Well, you're only talking to them
anyway. That's all.
It's just weird to think-
People do it all the time.
Especially out here.
Right.
No, you're right. You're right.
- I just never imagined myself to be one of those people.
- I'm one of those people.
What? you are not.
Take a look.
Where?
I don't see anything.
Exactly.
You got your nose done?
Honestly?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org