Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
In 1941.
The Japanese bombed Pearl Harbor.
The US fleet was crippled.
Ten hours later. Across the Pacific.
They attacked the Philippines.
Clearing the way for
an overwhelming invasion of the islands.
Japan has undertaken
a surprise offense...
US forces.
Including 10.000 Americans
and 60.000 Filipinos.
Pull back to the Bataan Peninsula.
Without a navy to rescue them
and with their backs to the sea.
They're trapped.
Despite promises to the contrary.
President Roosevelt
and his military high command
decide to focus first on Europe.
And on stopping Hitler.
This strategy effectively
seals the fate of the Philippines
and the men trapped on Bataan.
Under orders and against his wishes.
General MacArthur escapes to Australia.
Vowing to return.
After four months
of fighting without supplies.
Starving American and Filipino troops
surrender to the Japanese Imperial Army.
It is the largest single defeat
in the history of the American military.
Unequipped to house or feed
70.000 prisoners of war.
The Japanese take the weakened soldiers
on a brutal 60-mile forced march.
Men who fall out of line
are bayoneted or shot.
15.000 perish on what would become
known as the Bataan Death March.
The surviving POWs
are herded into various camps
at O'Donnell.
Cabanatuan and Palawan.
The Japanese guards.
Who view surrender as a disgrace.
Treat them viciously.
Thousands die from disease.
Starvation and abuse.
By 1944. however.
The tide of battle changes.
With each new victory.
American forces advance on Japan.
And with each new defeat. The
Japanese army becomes more desperate.
Fueled by propaganda. They believe
that the Americans will show no mercy.
The government in Tokyo
encourages these fears.
Convincing its people they must prepare
to defend their country to the death.
On August 1. 1944.
The Tokyo war ministry
releases a memo
dictating the Japanese army's policy
toward prisoners of war.
It reads:
"It is the aim not to allow the escape
of a single one.
"To annihilate them all.
And not leave any traces. "
Go! Go, go!
The landing at Lingayen Gulf
was the largest naval operation
ever undertaken in the Pacific.
Over a quarter million troops
came ashore.
Ready for the final push
into the Philippines.
I was a Stanford graduate who'd
entered the service through the R. O. T. C.
I wasn't interested
in being a career soldier.
I just wanted to do my part
and go home to my wife.
I was a captain
with the 6th Ranger battalion.
My commanding officer
was Lieutenant Colonel Henry Mucci.
- You in this hand, Lieutenant?
- Thinking about it, Colonel.
Well, if you're thinking about it,
you already lost.
- Want me to give you a better look?
- No, Colonel, I don't want you...
A West Point graduate. Mucci was
one of the most driven men I'd ever met.
He took on what seemed to many
like a hopeless task -
the job of turning a group of raw.
Untested recruits
into a new unit of elite soldiers.
Originally assigned to handle livestock.
They were mostly farm hands
from small towns in rural areas
with little or no combat experience.
First Sergeant, overlays are ready.
Have you seen Colonel Mucci?
Yes, sir.
He's in the Waldorf, playing poker.
Wouldn't interrupt him right now.
I think he's losing.
Ah, for cryin' out loud. Lieutenant Foley,
get me a new deck. This one's unlucky.
When you stick that pipe in your mouth,
I know you're in trouble.
Just you wait,
you smug son of a bitch.
Colonel, overlays.
Any idea who that is?
- No, sir.
- Corporal of the guard.
- Yes, sir.
- Aliteri, find out who the cowboy is.
Sir.
We'd spent months training
and had seen very little action.
As far as the army was concerned.
We were nothing more
than the colonel's personal experiment.
Mucci was determined
to prove them wrong.
- General.
- Henry.
You know Colonel White,
and this is Major Lapham.
Major, this is Lieutenant Colonel
Henry Mucci, CO, 6th Ranger battalion.
Major Lapham is a stay-behind
from the Bataan campaign.
He runs guerrilla units here
in north-central Luzon.
Philippine guerrillas have
been the primary source
of intel for MacArthur
since the fall.
- It's an honor, Major.
- Thank you.
Major Lapham,
tell Colonel Mucci what you told us.
Five miles east
of Cabanatuan City here,
there's a Japanese POW camp holding
about 500 survivors of the death march.
As we advance on this area,
I believe the Japanese will murder
the prisoners rather than release them.
Major Lapham is probably right. There
was an incident in a camp on Palawan.
150 American POWs were herded
into air-raid shelters and burnt alive
on the news that MacArthur had invaded.
Our axis of advance
is headed right for that camp.
Unless we run into
something unexpected,
we're gonna be in Cabanatuan at the
end of the week, and that may be too late.
Horton, what's G2 got to say about this?
Because of our advances, Jap movements
have become increasingly fluid -
retreating at night, hiding during the day
to avoid our aircraft.
What that means is we can't be sure
where the enemy is.
They're only 30 miles
from our front lines.
There's over 30,000 Japanese troops
in that area alone, Colonel.
Henry, you develop a plan
and get it to the G3 by the morning.
- Sir.
- I'll make my decision then.
Henry, I'll be
honest with you.
his mission appeals more
to my heart than to my head.
Three years ago
we ordered these men to surrender.
The way I see it, we owe them a great debt.
But... I need you
to be a hard-headed pragmatist.
If it doesn't feel right,
you call it off. Understand?
Yes, sir.
- Who will you assign it to?
- I'll lead it myself.
Let the rest of your
battalion worry about it.
I trained these Rangers. Everything
I've asked them to do, I've done myself.
I feel like they deserve a shot at this.
And so do I.
All right, Henry.
You show me a plan that works.
Sir.
General Krueger
hasn't made up his mind yet,
so I need you to come up
with a hell of a plan.
The Alamo Scouts are briefing us in five.
After that, you've got till the morning.
Yes, sir.
Sir, when you said
you were going to accompany us...
Don't worry, Captain.
You'll be leading the raid, not me.
How many guards
in the compound?
- Could be as many as 200.
- Any tanks?
This building with the metal roof
looks like it's protecting something.
If the camp is here, what is the Japanese
strength inside Cabanatuan City?
- 9,000 troops, sir.
- Not to worry. That's over 4 miles away.
What's enemy traffic like on this road?
The Japanese are moving their troops
from south to north.
So this is one of their main routes.
Looks like this bridge
is a mile away from the camp.
Half a mile, sir.
We believe it's heavily fortified. We're
not sure how many troops are guarding it.
Sir, it's hard to determine the number of
men we'll need without more specific intel.
Unfortunately, we don't have that luxury,
Bob. I selected you for your flexibility.
Now, you've got
a 24-hour jump on us, Lieutenant.
Is that enough time to get Captain Prince
all the dope he needs?
We'll be ready to report to you at 0800
hours on the morning of the 29th, sir.
- Get it done.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, the tough nut is the final approach.
No cover for over 800 yards.
It's as flat as a pancake.
Hey. Hey!
How far do you think
Hewitt's got by now?
What difference does it make?
The Japs are gonna catch him
sooner or later.
You couldn't have got me
something easier to chew?
A mango, banana?
Duke's selling graveyard rats,
but I thought...
I thought that'd be overindulging.
Is it your gums
or your teeth hurting?
Starts at the gums, works its way
around the back of my head
and then ends up
in my neck somewhere.
Don't worry.
It's not malaria.
- Sir.
- Take a knee, Lieutenant.
We've just translated
a telegram to Colonel Mori.
MacArthur's conquered the southern
islands. He's landed here on Luzon.
Good ol' Dugout Doug.
He can take in the sun for a few days,
then head on back to Australia
like he did the first time.
The information's good, Major.
I'm in that office every day.
We don't know how close MacArthur is
or when he'll reach Cabanatuan.
Tell the men the best thing to do is sit
tight and stay calm till we find out more.
Yes, sir.
- Make sure McMahon gets that.
- Yes, sir.
Come on, get up!
- They caught Hewitt.
- Who was watchin' him?
Poor dumb bastard
couldn't even wait till it got dark.
You are responsible for this.
You surrender like cowards,
then you run away like dogs.
He'll die, because none of you
had the courage to stop him!
Redding.
I need food.
Colvin, watch his back.
- How much?
- Five.
- You should not have come.
- Neither should you.
The guards are getting
harder to bribe.
What we really need is more medicine.
Carlos and my father were questioned
by the Japanese last week.
They are watching us.
Then tell Margaret
not to take any more risks.
You think she'll listen?
Is there anything else
you want me to tell her?
Just to take care.
There is some quinine in the peanuts.
Take some yourself, huh?
You don't look well.
Who's Margaret, Red?
She's an American nurse who was married
to his commanding officer.
He died of malaria about a year ago
in one of the other camps.
- Is the major involved with her?
- What makes you ask?
Nothing.
He just sounded concerned.
Well, he wasn't involved with her,
but he should have been.
Her husband
didn't give a damn about her,
and Gibby couldn't give a damn
about anyone else but her.
- Why didn't he do something about it?
- 'Cause he's a gentleman.
He'd never fool around
with another man's wife.
I, on the other hand, might.
Where is she now?
She's still in Manila.
Who do you think smuggles
all the medicine into the camp?
In 1941. Manila was considered
the pearl of the Orient.
An international city where people
from all over the world lived and worked.
That all changed
when the Japanese took over.
They believed
that as a conquered people.
The Filipinos should do
as they were told.
Those who disobeyed were jailed.
Tortured or executed.
This made the bond between the Filipinos
and the Americans even stronger.
Resistance grew throughout the country.
By 1945. hundreds of ordinary people
had joined the underground.
It's like they have been
watching me for weeks.
The Japanese
have questioned our people before.
It doesn't necessarily mean anything.
They know
that the Americans are closing in,
and they know that we have evidence
of their war crimes.
Don Antonio is right. This...
This wasn't like before, Margaret.
Now they know of things
only an informer could have told them.
Then why'd they let you go?
I'm sorry, Carlos,
but if you're worried, you're free to go.
I won't hold it against you.
I won't hold it against any of you.
I wouldn't leave unless we all go.
You know that.
I can't leave, not as long as there is
a single prisoner left in Cabanatuan.
...Margaret.
I saw Daniel.
How is he?
He did not look well.
I think he has malaria again.
I know my father said to wait, but if we
do that, it may be too late for Daniel.
No, your father's right.
It's too dangerous. Don't listen to me.
No. I will meet you outside the hospital
in the usual place, OK?
I should go.
Company... atten-hut!
At ease.
I'm here to tell you men
the latrine rumors are true.
We've finally got a mission
worthy of Rangers.
We're going to push right through
our front lines into the Japs' backyard
and rescue 500 American prisoners of war.
It's going to be a rough son of a bitch.
A textbook-style raid
that can only succeed
through speed, surprise
and overwhelming firepower.
That's why you've been chosen.
Before you start congratulating yourselves,
remember that you haven't achieved
a damn thing yet.
You're the best-trained,
least-proven battalion in this whole army.
This is your one chance
to do something about it.
And I mean one chance.
How you acquit yourselves
over the next 48 hours
will determine how you are judged
for the rest of your lives.
Men worthy of serving in this army,
or an embarrassment that history and time
will eventually forget.
It's up to you.
Now, I happen to think it's the former.
That's why I'm accompanying you
on this raid.
There's not another
group of men in this
or any other army I'd
sooner trust my life with.
You're the finest, best-prepared soldiers
this country's ever sent to war,
and I expect you to prove it.
One final thing:
I wanna see every last one of you
in the chapel after this formation's over.
I do not want any damned atheists
on this raid.
And no fakers either.
I want you to get down on your knees
and swear before Almighty God
that you'll give your lives
before you let any of those prisoners die.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, sir!
- Are you sure?
Carry on.
Company... atten-hut!
The general liked your plan.
... and build an enduring peace
founded upon thy holy laws,
and upon that unselfish goodwill
to all those who love justice and peace
which thou hast given unto us through
Jesus Christ, thine only son, our Lord.
- Amen.
Take charge of your platoon!
Can't believe the colonel said
don't wear no insignia.
He's got that pencil mustache. Even
the Nips are gonna know he's an officer.
- Shut up.
- I mean, I can wear my helmet.
Come on. I use it to cook,
to clean, to wash.
Yeah, the helmets,
they make too much noise,
out in the field.
- Sorry, I didn't hear that, Aldrige. You?
- I heard him.
Aldrige, you're the best shot
in the company. Ever fire one of these?
No.
- No, sir. I like my M-1.
- Choose yourself a loader.
Lucas.
- Sure about that?
- Yeah.
Rookies.
... Japanese planes have struck
at six different points in the Philippines.
Manila is 13 hours ahead
of Eastern Standard Time.
It is reported that Japanese bombs...
First Sergeant.
- So you really are going.
- Someone told me you had the same idea.
Yeah.
Look, Jim,
I'm already taking four of your men.
All fine combat medics, Henry.
But if we get hit hard, you're gonna need
someone who can operate.
I can't miss this, Henry.
It's why I'm here.
Besides, sometimes a young field medic
needs his surgeon around.
Just like a young company commander
needs his colonel.
You win.
Captain, you got a minute for me?
Sure, Top.
I was going over the personnel roster,
and I ain't on it.
Colonel Mucci said he preferred
unmarried men on this trip,
so I had to take you off.
Well, with respect, sir, you're married.
And I imagine your wife would miss you
a hell of a lot more than mine'd miss me.
I'm the one planning this raid, Top.
Don't make me go against my instructions.
I'm not, sir. I'm asking you
to be a smart company commander.
We got Rangers out there that ain't heard
the first round go downrange in combat yet.
You need me on this mission.
Just think you need something
on that jungle rot.
Top, when I was in R.O.T.C., I was four
weeks away from being shipped to Bataan.
I was held back
by an impacted wisdom tooth.
Guys I knew ended up in those camps.
I think I can live with defeat.
That may be, but you're gonna find it
a lot harder to live without me.
All right, I'll talk to the colonel.
- Anything else, First Sergeant?
- No, sir.
Thank you. Good night, sir.
We left 6th Army Headquarters
with very little information.
The only advantage we had
was the element of surprise.
We faced a two-day walk through
open terrain patrolled by the enemy.
All it would take
is a single Japanese scout to spot us
and our mission would be over.
Let's go! Riley, load 'em up!
Pack 'em up! Let's move!
Move 'em out!
We all knew the idealistic notion
of rescuing POWs
far outweighted its strategic value.
We didn't spent much time
thinking about it.
As far as we were concerned.
We were going to rescue them
or die trying.
- They're gonna just leave us, sir?
- I have no idea what they're doing.
Get this quinine to the doctors.
You know the drill - worst cases first.
They must be retreating.
Even the brass is leaving.
Hey, Major, Mori's leaving too.
Looks like you were right.
General MacArthur's got 'em on the run.
They're not on the run. They've got orders
to fight to the last man.
It's a trap.
A goddamn elaborate one.
We walk out those gates, it'll give
'em the perfect excuse to kill us.
Since when did they need an excuse?
I don't know about you, but I'm getting
out of here before they change their minds.
How far do you think you'll get, Captain?
Even if the Japs are retreating,
the jungle's gonna be crawling with 'em.
What's wrong with that?
We're still soldiers, ain't we?
Major's right, Red. Where we gonna go
when most of us can't walk?
I don't recall inviting you, kid.
What happens
to the ones we leave behind?
I never said we'd all make it,
but at least some of us might.
If we sit tight, all of us will make it.
Our troops can't be far now.
Looks like you got yourself
a disciple, Gibby.
It might do you some good
to listen to him.
They're out there, Red.
Don't make it any easier for 'em.
Don't worry, I won't escape
without your permission.
Get the padre, Duke.
Poor son of a bitch still believed in God.
Well, if we can't escape,
we might as well eat.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Ghost.
Where do you think Mori sits?
I'll take a shit on his plate.
- Where'd you learn to do that?
- I wasn't always this sane.
- What's the matter?
- These food parcels were meant for us.
The bastards
were starving us deliberately.
Make sure you get some
to the men in the hospital ward.
Easy, Red.
Your stomach ain't used to it.
What do I care? Feels like
I'm sucking on Rita Hayworth's tits.
I was thinking more Mae West.
- What is it, Top?
- Japs. Only left a few hours ago.
Must have been hiding from our planes.
There's no telling where they are now. We
might wanna look around before we go on.
They're retreating, Captain.
That's all we need to know.
- Let's go.
- Move out.
- Platoons, let's go.
- Charlie Two, to the left.
Let's go, Charlie One. Follow me.
Damn it.
They're Kempei Tai.
I think they're heading towards the camp.
The river branches out
about a half mile to the east of us.
It's not marked. There might be a bridge
that can get us around this convoy.
The Japanese will be guarding
a major artery at a chokepoint like that.
I think we ought to check it out.
This traffic isn't getting any thinner.
Go.
It was thanks to me
you met Margaret in the first place.
Sure it was.
When I look up at the sky like this,
I could be anywhere in the world.
- Where are you now?
- Halfway across the jungle.
I disobeyed your orders, and now
I'm only a few miles from civilization.
Well, have a drink for me
when you get there.
What do you want me
to tell Margaret?
Assuming she's still interested.
Well, if she's not, I'll propose
to her myself, and you know what?
I'll make you best man,
'cause I know you won't run off with her.
If I had someone like that waiting for me
on the other side of an open gate...
- That's not regular army.
- They're Kempei Tai.
Military secret police.
Don't...
give them the satisfaction.
They'll be dead soon.
You fought in Bataan, Major?
You commanded a battalion of the 31 st
Infantry in operations near Mamala River?
I can give you my name,
rank and serial number.
We found these in your barracks.
I assume they were smuggled in
by the Filipino resistance.
They say, "Take hope.
"MacArthur is coming."
We've lived off rumors like that
for three years.
Only this time they are true.
Your forces will recapture the Philippines
within a few weeks.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because it isn't long to wait.
You are the senior officer.
If you help me keep order,
I can make the rest
of your time here tolerable.
But if any of the prisoners try to escape,
I will kill ten others in his place.
Are you married, Major?
- No.
- You have a reason to survive this war?
I'd like to be here for your surrender.
Then you had better stay in good health.
You look feverish.
Some quinine would help.
Will that be all?
You were delirious.
- Wittinghill thinks it's malignant malaria.
- How long is he giving me?
Three or four days
unless we get you more quinine.
He tried to convince me
to send you to St. Peter's ward.
Oh, you're my next of kin now?
Hey, it's no joke. You die on me,
what's to stop me leaving this place?
I told you what Nagai said.
- Stay out of trouble. It will soon be over.
- The problem is I don't believe Nagai.
Which part don't you believe?
Ten of us getting killed
for every one that escapes?
That's the reason I didn't want to make
any friends here - in case I let 'em down.
Unfortunately, you
I was stuck with from before.
You gotta pull through this, pal.
Just think of everything
you got to look forward to.
Think of Margaret in a see-through
cheongsam walking on your back.
- You ever gonna stop?
- No.
Come on, you bastard.
Pull out of it.
20mls of iodine, please.
Thanks.
They murdered Cora.
I'm being followed.
Behind us in the... the brown vest.
- Is it just him?
- I think so.
Mina, I have to get you out of here.
The quinine's in the bag.
Pack your things and leave.
- No, I'm not leaving...
- Mina, leave!
Try to get the medicine to Cabanatuan.
If you can't, head for the mountains.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about me.
Go.
What are you doing?
- Balincarin?
- Yes, sir.
Let's get some people in there.
Top?
- All clear.
- What is it, Top?
Tanks.
You better go get the colonel.
Yeah, Top.
Bob, hang back a little.
Let me walk ahead.
- Captain Juan Pajota.
- Lieutenant Colonel Henry Mucci,
CO, 6th Ranger battalion.
Sir.
What happened here?
The Japanese came into the village
yesterday, with tanks,
to punish these people
for helping my men.
Over a hundred were killed.
Captain, I guarantee you,
this will not go unpunished.
Alamo Scouts. Hold your fire.
- Charlie Company CO.
- This way. Follow me.
The camp is divided into quarters.
We only spotted POWs
in the southeast quadrant here.
The Jap guard barracks
are here in this area.
There are sentries
in each guard tower,
two at the gates,
five in the guardhouses.
We couldn't get precise numbers. Could
be anything between 50 and 100 of 'em.
This isn't enough, sir.
- Enough of what?
- There's too many unknowns.
There's a big difference
between 50 and 100 men.
It isn't always about the arithmetic.
Some things you gotta take on faith.
We get into firefight
inside that compound,
and a lot of those men we're trying
to rescue are liable to get killed.
Lieutenant Able, you've got 12
hours till this raid kicks off.
Can you get in there
and bring back more detailed intel?
It's dicey, sir. All that open terrain
in broad daylight.
We need more time.
Give them a chance to work in closer.
No more delays now, goddammit.
Those poor bastards have had three years
of delays. We'll stick to your plan, Bob.
With respect, sir,
you said you chose me
for my flexibility.
Under present circumstances, I cannot
guarantee the safety of those prisoners.
Sir, you may be forced to delay.
Why, Captain?
There's a Japanese convoy
traveling north, division strength.
They will pass
directly in front of the camp tonight.
How is it you came by this information,
Captain Pajota?
From our spies in Cabanatuan City.
Are we talking hard facts
or the bamboo telegraph?
The bamboo telegraph told me you
and your men are coming here today, sir.
Lieutenant Able, get some of our own
people on this. As of now we leave tonight.
Sir.
Captain?
You heard the colonel.
Do what you can.
Yes, sir.
Captain?
You have a minute? I wanted
to discuss this plan with you.
My men have been watching
this camp for three years.
We planned to raid it
many times ourselves.
- Why didn't you?
- Most of your POWs can't walk.
They're either sick or crippled.
The healthy ones were shipped
to labor camps in Japan.
If we rescued them,
how would we care for them?
Well, how did you plan
to move them from the camp?
In carabao carts.
You have enough carts
for 500 prisoners?
If you give me 24 hours, I will.
But... you have to convince your colonel
to move to another village.
It isn't safe to bring them here.
What village do you suggest?
Platero.
Sir.
Sorry if I was out of line before.
- I spoke to Captain Pajota...
- We'll delay 24 hours.
Get a message to General Krueger.
That'll be all.
Yes, sir.
Margaret Utinsky?
Yes.
You work at the Manila hospital?
Why?
I am with the Japanese Military Police.
Please come with me.
Utinsky is a German name?
Lithuanian.
- You were born in Lithuania?
- Kovno.
You speak good English.
I was raised in Canada.
You have a passport
to prove you are Lithuanian?
My papers are back at the apartment.
May I have your keys?
- I can go get them for you.
- Your keys.
Why did you stay in Manila
when the war started?
I'm a nurse. I wanted to help people.
You think the people of this country
want American help?
I'm Lithuanian, not American.
Your passport is forged.
I've traveled everywhere
on that passport.
Do you know a woman
called Mina Corcurea?
No.
This morning,
you assaulted a man
who was following her in the street.
I was assaulted myself,
if that's what you're talking about.
Mina Corcurea
is a member
of the Filipino underground.
She and her father
are responsible for stealing medicine
from wounded Japanese soldiers
and smuggling it
to American prisoners of war.
I'm a citizen of a neutral country.
I have no dealings whatsoever
with any underground
or any American prisoners of war.
- Is this your Bible?
- I don't know.
Did you take it from my apartment?
You were married to an American officer
before the war?
I've never been married.
Then...
who is this man?
Your husband?
Your lover?
No.
But you keep a picture of him
in your Bible.
From Manila, sir.
Would you like to sit, Major?
You know her?
I knew her briefly.
Why?
She claims she knew you well.
She claims she stayed behind
in the Philippines to be near you.
I find that hard to believe.
I didn't make much
of an impression on her.
She clearly left an impression on you.
Would you like to see her again?
What's that to you?
We know this woman
is the head
of an underground movement in Manila...
responsible for smuggling stolen medicine
into this camp.
If you convince her to confess
and give us
the names of her accomplices,
I guarantee the two of you
will be free to leave
the Philippines together.
And if I don't?
You'll be returned
to your hospital ward to die.
I assume your colleagues
made her the same offer?
I wouldn't know.
She must've turned 'em down.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here now.
I'm offering you your future, Major.
My future isn't in your hands.
- Aw, honey, you look great.
- So do you.
Pity there ain't
a Cabanatuan beauty contest.
Shucks.
I got you something.
- I hoped it would be quinine.
- Gettin' fussy now, huh?
Sure am.
It didn't get through.
Your friend Nagai stopped
all work details to Cabanatuan City.
He's got us digging
air-raid shelters instead.
They'll find some other way
to smuggle it in.
It'll be too late for you by then, old pal.
You ain't thinking of leaving me.
I don't think Nagai's men
want me here.
I can think of ten of us that do.
Like I said, you're the only one
I give a damn about.
You and the kid sometimes.
Don't try it, Red.
I'll see you, Gibby.
Tell Duke and Pitt
to keep an eye on him.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org