I've come back.
Give me a drink, Brother Kipling.
Don't you know me?
No. I don't know you.
Who are you?
What can I do for you?
I told you. Give me a drink.
It was all settled.
Right here, in this office.
Remember?
Danny and me signed the contract
and you witnessed it.
You...
...stood over there.
I stood there.
And Daniel stood here.
Remember?
Carnehan!
Peachy Taliaferro Carnehan.
Of course.
Keep looking at me. It helps
to keep my soul from flying off.
Carnehan!
The same, and not the same,
who sat beside you...
...in a first-class carriage
on the train to Marwar Junction...
...three summers
and a thousand years ago.
Jodhpur, please.
Blast!
All aboard!
May I?
Riding in this ashcart is like being
kicked by a mule every 10 minutes!
Mr. Clutterbury Das.
Failed entrance examination,
Calcutta University, 1863.
Writer of correspondence
for the illiterate general public.
Shut up!
Thank you, sir.
- Out of the window, Babu!
- Thank you, sir.
Outside, you inky-fingered thief!
- I hope you break your neck!
- Thank you, sir.
- You might have killed him!
- Serves him right if I had!
- We're not making five miles an hour.
- But why?
- I caught him stealing your watch.
- My watch?
I say, it is my watch!
Well!
I'm very much obliged to you, Mr...?
Carnehan. Former gunnery sergeant
in Her Majesty's Forces.
Mine's Kipling.
- May I offer you a drink?
- I don't mind if I do.
You've knocked about India a bit,
I take it.
You can say that twice!
On foot, on horseback and on camel.
- You don't look green, either.
- I was born in India.
Great country, or was till bureaucrats
took over and ruined everything.
- I hope you're not one of them!
- No.
I didn't think so.
They usually have long noses
for looking down at you.
And I've yet to have
one of them offer me a drink!
- Glenlivet, 12 years old.
- You've an educated taste.
I have an educated taste in whiskey,
women, waistcoats and bills of fare.
But I've had few chances
to exercise it.
Because them that governs
make up laws...
...to stop men like us
from getting anywhere.
Whose loss is it?
England's, of course!
If we were unrestrained, she wouldn't
get 70 millions in revenue...
- ... it would be 700 millions! Right?
- I quite agree, yes.
- Where are you heading for?
- Jodhpur.
- Will you return on this line?
- In 10 days.
Can you make it eight?
I have a message for a man...
...travelling through Marwar Junction
on the 24th.
He expects to meet
but I have urgent business.
I'm sorry, I can't help you there.
Supposing I was to ask you...
...as a stranger going to the West
to seek for that which was lost.
What would you say then?
I should answer,
where do you come from?
From the East.
I am hoping that you will give
my message on the square...
...for the sake of the widow's son.
- Which lodge do you hail from?
- Travelling Lodge 3276, Fore and Fit.
The Queen's Own Royal Loyal Light
Infantry, Regimental District 329A.
- To whom is the message?
- Daniel Dravot.
- Dravot.
- A big man with long gray sideboards.
A great swell.
You'll find him
in a first-class compartment.
Don't be afraid.
Slip the window down and say,
" Peachy's gone south for the week. "
- " Peachy's gone south for the week. "
- Yes, and he'll tumble.
Well, I'll be getting off now
before we reach the station.
By the way, Brother Carnehan...
I missed my watch
in the station at Lahore...
...before boarding the train.
How was I to know you were a Mason?
What's this?
God's holy trousers!
Tickets again?
Is your name Dravot, sir?
I'm to say that Peachy
has gone south for the week.
He's gone south for the week.
Did he say I'd give anything for this?
I won't.
- No, he didn't.
- Then why did you do it?
For the sake of the widow's son.
- He said south, did he?
- Yes.
Then that'll be Degumber.
Since you're Peachy's pal,
I'll tell you.
We're gonna put the screw on the rajah
for what he did to his mother-in-law.
Filled her with peppers
and flogged her to death.
You mean you intend to blackmail him?
You wouldn't get out alive! If they
don't cut your throat, they'll poison you.
Both's been tried.
Peachy and me don't kill easy!
The rajah's an independent ruler.
He answers to nobody.
How will you put the screw on him?
By telling him we're correspondents
for The Northern Star.
You can't! You can't do that!
Because I am the correspondent
of The Northern Star!
- You what?
- I'm the correspondent!
Eh? What did you say, brother?
As you know,
we took them at the Degumber border...
...so there's a question
of jurisdiction.
But a charge of conspiracy
to blackmail might be brought.
I didn't lay this information before
you as a criminal prosecution.
Only to save their lives.
May I ask what particular interest
you have in these scoundrels?
Well, they happen to be...
...Freemasons. Like myself.
Freemasons? Them? I'd think
you'd strike them off your roll!
Oh, once a Mason, always a Mason.
Never could understand how
pukka chaps like you can go about...
...wearing aprons and sashes
and shaking hands with strangers.
What is Masonry, Kipling?
It's an ancient order...
...dedicated to the brotherhood
of man, under the eye of God.
We should have left that behind
in England. It can never work here.
There are tales that it did work here,
before we came.
Some audacious scholars
can trace it...
...to the builders
of Solomon's Temple.
- Old wives' tales, I suspect.
- Yes, in all likelihood, sir.
Well, let's have a look
at your lodge brothers.
Right turn.
Halt.
Hats off!
You men are not under arrest...
...thanks to Mr. Kipling, who's a real
correspondent for The Northern Star.
But both of you richly deserve
to be in jail.
I have your records before me.
There's everything
from smuggling to swindling...
...receiving stolen goods
and barefaced blackmail!
I resent the accusation.
It is blackmail to threaten
to publish information.
What blackmail is there in accepting
a retainer to keep it out?
How did you propose to do that?
Telling the editor what I know
about his sister...
...and a certain government official.
Let him put that in his paper
if he has need of news!
You should have gone home
after your army service.
To what? A porter's uniform
outside a restaurant?
Tips for closing cab doors
on civilians and their blowzy women?
Not for us, after watching
Afghans take command...
- ... when the officers had copped it!
- Well said!
There may be no criminal charges, but
I'll see these files reach Calcutta...
...with the advice you be
deported as political undesirables.
Detriments to the empire and the raj.
Detriments you call us? Detriments?
Detriments like us built this bloody
empire and the izzat of the raj!
Hats on!
About turn!
By the left, quick march!
Left turn!
There's no need to let any of this
get into the Star, I take it, Kipling?
No, no, no.
Copy.
My God! You two!
What do you want this time?
- We want to ask you a favour.
- Another favour?
Calm down, we've never taken
advantage of a fellow in the craft.
We don't want money,
just a little time...
...a look at a book or two,
a study of your maps.
We'll take a drink, but if not,
we won't mind.
Peachy is as sober as I am.
It's important you have no doubts.
So we'll take one of your cigars
apiece, and you shall watch us...
...light up.
And now, sir...
...let me introduce you to Brother
Peachy Carnehan, which is him...
...and Brother Daniel Dravot,
which is I.
The less said about our jobs,
the better. We've been most things.
We've been all over India. We know
her cities, jungles, jails and passes.
We have decided
she isn't big enough for us.
The commissioner said that.
We're going to another place...
...where a man isn't crowded
and can come into his own.
We're not little men,
so we're going away to be kings.
- Kings of Kafiristan.
- Oh, Kafiristan.
We hear they have two and 30 idols
there. So we'll be the 33rd and 34th.
It's a place of warring tribes,
meaning a land of opportunity...
...for such who can train
and lead men in battle.
We'll go there
and say to any chief we find:
"Want to vanquish your foes?"
He'll say, "Of course, do it. "
We'll fight for him, make him king
and then subvert him.
We'll seize his royal throne
and loot the country.
How's that for a plan?
You're both out of your minds!
To start with...
...the only way to get there
is through Afghanistan.
Kafiristan? No, no, no.
Two white men would be cut to pieces
five miles into the Khyber Pass.
Just suppose we managed it.
Just suppose.
And suppose we got across
the Afghan plains, then what?
There's the Hindu Kush,
a frozen sea of peaks and glaciers.
A party of geographers tried several
years ago and vanished into thin air.
No white man has ever been there
and come out since Alexander.
Alexander who?
Alexander the Great, king of Greece.
300 years before Christ.
If a Greek can do it, we can do it.
Right.
I can only repeat,
you're a pair of lunatics!
Would a pair of lunatics
draw up a contract like this?
"This contract between us, pursuing
and witnesseth in the name of God.
One: We will settle this together,
i. e., to be kings of Kafiristan.
Two: We will not, while this
is being settled, look at liquor...
...or any woman, so as to get mixed
up with one or the other harmful.
Three: We act
with dignity and discretion.
If one is in trouble, the other stays
by him. Signed by us this day. "
There's no need for the last article,
but it's got a ring to it.
Daniel.
Now, you witness it and it's legal.
Well, gentlemen,
it's 4 in the morning.
Don't stand on politeness. If you want
to go to bed, we won't steal anything.
Thank you.
We'll send word when we're ready
to go, if you want to say goodbye.
Yes. Well, try not to burn
the place down.
Here we are.
" Kafiristan. 10,000 square miles.
Mountainous terrain.
Religion unknown. Population unknown.
Conquered by Alexander in 328 B.C.
According to Herodotus,
he defeated King Oxyartes...
...whose daughter Roxanne
he subsequently took to wife. "
You buy from me,
I give you good price.
Very cheap, very nice things for you,
especially for you, sir.
Our forward continuance is impeded
by this fellow, who is begging...
...you will accompany him that he may
show you a rare and wonderful thing.
- What thing?
- He would not say what thing.
Therefore, I suspect
his bad intentions...
...to entice you into
a house of disreputation...
...where he will take you,
kill you, murder you...
...cut your throat and rob the money
from your pockets also.
Crikey!
- Wait at the office!
- Sir, please!
Myself, I will take you
to a loving house.
You will be very happy
and delightful...
Morning to you, brother.
Glad you caught the performance.
What do you think?
It's convincing,
but what are you rascals up to now?
Last week it was kings
you were to be, of Kafiristan.
- We've gotta get there first.
- Madness is a trick.
Who'd hurt some poor crazy priest
and his servant?
Peachy worked this out.
We've used it before.
He talks, while I act dumb.
I can clown pretty good now.
I can twitch to put the fear
into any good Muslim.
I can froth at the mouth.
Want to see?
- I can imagine.
- All right, some other time perhaps.
Come over here.
Give it a touch-up down here.
- Rifles?
- Twenty Martinis, and ammunition.
Cost us every sou we got
out of the rajah of Degumber.
Good heavens!
You mean you went back there?
Of course, Brother Kipling.
God help you
if you're caught with those!
Gunrunning isn't exactly new to us.
Well, Brother Kipling,
goodbye and many thanks.
Man, don't do it!
The odds are too great.
Wish us luck. We met upon the level.
And we're parting on the square.
Good luck, indeed.
Come along, you ugly beast.
Wait!
Here. Take this.
Last time Danny and me came through
the Khyber Pass, we fought our way...
...yard by bloody yard...
...and General Bobbs
called us heroes afterwards.
But that was years ago.
Times have changed.
- Blast! Look who's on sentry!
- Mulvaney!
That loudmouthed mick
from the Black Tyrone!
Private Mulvaney! Come to attention
when I am addressing you!
Slope arms!
Present! March!
Mark time!
At the double!
Corporal of the guard!
Take three men and put
Private Mulvaney under arrest!
Bloody man's drunk again!
We came through the Khyber
with that caravan...
...doing all sorts of antics
to amuse the people.
At night, he told them their fortunes
in a tongue of his own...
...and I translated.
And all concerned were happy...
...because I promised them
all their wishes would come true.
Then at Jaedallak we turned off
towards Kafiristan.
They were sad to see us leave
the caravan. We'd brought it good luck.
Two she-camels had foaled and there
was no sniping at us from the hills.
They waved goodbye to the mad priest
and his servant.
And Danny danced them out of sight.
The country was deserty.
The inhabitants were dispersed, solitary.
We travelled by night
and kept away from villages.
We didn't want to waste ammunition
in idle fighting with Afghans.
The Pushtukan.
A wavy blue line on the map, but we
couldn't hope to get camels across.
So Peachy says,
"It doesn't matter what they cost...
...we'll trade them for goats.
We're playing for high stakes. "
Major McCrimmon bet me 10 bob he could
blow up a goat skin in one breath.
He did. Though he'd sat down
on an anthill in his kilt unknowing.
Ten shillings was ten shillings
to McCrimmon!
Mules.
Now, the problem is...
...how to divide five Afghans
from three mules...
- ... and have two Englishmen left over.
- Shoot them.
No. The mules would bolt.
Sit over there, Danny.
So we starts forward into those
bitter cold mountainous parts...
...and never a path broader
than the back of your hand.
The mountains was tall and white...
...like wild rams,
they was always fighting...
...so you couldn't sleep
for the din of their fighting.
For God's sake, Danny, pipe down.
- Why? Who's going to hear us?
- These mountains, that's who.
- You wanna start an avalanche?
- You don't believe that, I hope.
If a king can't sing,
it ain't worth being king.
The country was mountainous...
...and the mules was most contrary.
They all died but one.
And she died later on.
Danny went snow-blind
and clung to jenny's tail.
Up and up we went,
and down and down.
Through defiles and over snowy saddles
till all at once...
...two giants stood in our way.
God's holy trousers.
What's the matter?
Blokes twice our size standing
guarding the snow, like. Two of them.
Give them a round apiece.
Not a move out of them.
Stay put.
I'll reconnoitre.
They're not real, thank God.
They're horrible.
Put there by the Kafiris
to frighten the neighbours.
Peachy, that means
we're in Kafiristan. Or almost.
So it does.
- What was that?
- Our bridges have been burned.
What do you mean?
The bridge we crossed by
ain't there no longer.
God.
Now what?
- Tell me.
- A crevasse.
We've had it, Danny.
Coming and going!
- Wide?
- Wide enough!
It drops into nothing below,
straight as a beggar can spit!
That's the last of them, Peachy.
No more gods to burn.
It looks like last post, Danny.
I don't fancy dying by inches.
Feeling the cold creeping up my limbs.
- Getting all numb.
- I'll do the necessary...
- ... when the fire goes out.
- Fair enough.
Bloody shame.
Getting this close and not making it.
A stone's throw away, our kingdom.
I'd have liked to seen you, Danny,
with a gold crown on your head.
If you could've found one
that fitted it.
Peachy, in your opinion...
...have our lives been misspent?
Well, that depends
on how you look at it.
The world's not a better
place because of us.
No, hardly that.
- Nobody's gonna weep at our demise.
- And who'd want them to?
And we haven't many good deeds
to our credit.
None. None to brag about.
But how many have been
where we've been...
- ... and seen what we've seen?
- Bloody few. And that's a fact.
Even now, I wouldn't change places
with the viceroy himself...
- ... if it meant giving up my memories.
- Me neither.
Remember the time the Highlanders
was retreating down the hill...
...at Ali Masjit and Pipe Major
McCrimmon got his sporran shot off?
Half a crown was in it, right?
So he goes after it without checking
to see if that was all he'd lost!
And then he got the Victoria Cross...
...because the Highlanders
followed him up the hill!
Danny, we can get on!
Kafiristan.
The promised land.
Must be their Halloween.
Upsadaisy, lad.
Brass band and all.
Hail the conquering heroes.
Bloody cheek. Where's their gratitude?
I say! I say there!
Are you Englishmen, please?
Stone the bleeding crows!
Yes, mate.
- And who might you be?
- You just wait one jiffy.
Peachy, it's a Gurkha.
Rifleman Machendra Gurung.
Known to my regiment as Billy Fish.
Is that right? Well, report, rifleman.
What are you doing here?
Wherever here is.
- I come with Colonel Robertson, sir.
- The geographer?
Oh, dear me, alas, by Jove.
Party not reaching Er-Heb
for very misfortunate reasons.
Large mountain is falling on everyone.
Everybody buried alive
except your servant.
What about them up there
banging drums...
...and then shooting arrows at us?
Big noise to scare away devils!
- Many devils here these days.
- They thought we was devils?
Kafiristan peoples very ignorant.
I say to head man Ootah, I say,
"Oh, no, by Jove, they're not devils...
...they're Gorasahibs.
British soldiers. "
Good man, Billy Fish.
And now, if you'll take us
to this Ootah bloke...
...we will begin his education.
People of Er-Heb, do not fear.
They are our friends, not our enemies.
Do you understand?
Do not fear.
There is no need to fear.
They're our friends.
Why are you so afraid?
People of Er-Heb, do not fear!
They're from England!
British soldiers!
White men.
Do not be afraid.
Ootah!
Come on down.
No need to be afraid.
They're white men. Ootah!
Come down!
Don't be afraid.
Tell him we won't hurt him,
not to worry.
He wants to know where you come from.
Tell him we tumbled from the skies.
He wants to know, are you gods?
Not gods, Englishmen,
which is the next best thing.
I ofttimes tell Ootah
about Englishmans.
How they name dogs,
take off hats to womans...
...and march left, right
with rifles on their shoulders.
Bringing enlightenment
to the darker regions of the earth.
He wants to know how rifle works.
Show him, Peachy.
We are not gods, exactly,
but we are heaven-sent...
...to deliver you from your enemies.
Enemies all around.
The Bashkai are the worst.
All town comes out and pisses
downstream when we go bathing.
Shocking!
They are always stealing our womans.
Putting on masks.
And so our head chap
is thinking them devils...
- ... and running like bloody hell away.
- War! Red war we'll give them.
He give you two goats for each
Bashkai man you're killing.
One goat for each womans and childs.
Rather than knock them over
one at a time...
...we'd like to do it
in one fell swoop.
Serve him up a proper victory.
Storm Bashkai, take the city.
He says, " How much?"
Only the honour of leading
the brave men of Er-Heb into battle.
And what we fancy in souvenirs.
- A bauble here and a bangle there.
- Bashkai is only the beginning.
We hope to go on from victory to
victory until he runs out of enemies.
And a monarch of all you survey.
- All he surveys?
- From the highest place in the valley.
The mountains will echo your name.
Ootah the Great!
Oh, he says he prefers
"Ootah the Terrible. "
Then Ootah the Terrible it shall be.
And take him in token of our earnest.
And now the womans of Er-Heb
will cut his bollocks off!
Couldn't happen in a better cause.
- Contract.
Ootah say, "You, you no like?"
Tell him we've given up strong drink
until we've conquered all his enemies.
Boil them once or twice in hot water...
...and they'll come out
like chicken and ham.
You wouldn't know them from the
Gaiety Chorus.
- Ootah says, "Take your pick. "
- He does?
Oh, tell His Majesty one's prettier
than another. I couldn't choose.
Take as many as you like.
There are more where they came from.
He has 27 daughters.
They're his daughters?
His own daughters?
- Dirty old brute!
- Different countries, different customs.
Mustn't be prejudiced, Peachy.
Tell His Majesty we've also taken
a vow not to dally with females...
...till all his enemies
are vanquished.
He has 32 sons if you're liking boys.
Tell him he makes my gorge rise!
Hold on, Peachy, he's only being
hospitable according to his likes.
Polo!
Everything's the same.
The ball's bigger.
- Is the ball always that big?
- Depends on size of head.
Big head, big ball.
This here Bashkai man. Big damn head.
The bloody heathens.
Different countries, different customs.
Mustn't be prejudiced.
Now, listen to me,
you benighted muckers.
We're gonna teach you soldiering,
the noblest profession.
When we're done, you'll be able to
slaughter enemies like civilized men!
But first, you'll have to learn
to march in step...
...do the manual of arms
without having to think.
Good soldiers don't think,
they just obey.
You think if a man thought twice,
he'd die for his country?
Not bloody likely!
He wouldn't go near the battlefield!
One look at your foolish faces...
...tells me you're going to be
crack troops.
Him there with a 51/2 hat size
has the makings of a bloody hero.
Timing in the British Army
has always been: "One, two, three. "
One, two, three.
Say after me, "One, two, three. "
Wait. Ready, steady, go.
One, two, three.
Say it at the same time as the others.
Tell him to say it at the same time!
Right. Go!
One, two, three.
Billy, tell him to say it
with the others!
One, two, three. Right.
Now ready, steady, go.
One, two, three.
No! He's saying it
before the others, Billy.
Not before them, not after them,
with them!
Right. Attention!
No. You, look...
That one goes to there! Say that one
goes to there! That's it!
Down there, like that.
There. There we are.
Okay? Right.
Come on, smarten up,
you horrible lot!
Attention!
That's better.
Troops, march!
By the left. Quick. March!
Left. Left. Left, right, left.
Wait. You're a handsome piece,
that I don't deny...
...but the contract states the party
of the first part, Danny...
...and the party of the second part,
which is me...
...shall nowise compromise ourselves...
...with parties of the third part,
which is you.
All binding, properly sworn to...
...witnessed and attested.
- Danny!
- So!
Thank God you arrived.
Let's go seek safety in battle.
Trumpeter, sound your trumpet!
Billy Fish.
Blood is what we want.
The bloodier, the better.
So it shall be!
Like old times, Peachy.
Reminds me of Ali Majid.
It's a good job the odds
are only 10 to 1.
Halt!
Line up in a straight line here.
Present!
Aim!
Who are they?
What's happening?
Very holy men.
They walk through Kafiristan
collecting offerings for Holy City.
Battle is postponed
until priests have passed.
- Why are their eyes closed?
- They don't wish to see any badness...
...so keep eyes closed until they
return to beauties of Sikandergul.
Fire!
Aim! Fire!
Charge! Come on.
Oh, that great bloody showoff!
Rifle section, form line!
Fix bayonets!
Advance!
Volley fire! Commence!
Charge!
What did you think you were
playing at charging single-handed?
- I got carried away. Blood was up.
- Acting like a green lieutenant...
...hoping to be mentioned
in dispatches!
- You ought to be ashamed!
- Sorry.
Supposing you got killed.
Where would I be at?
- Won't happen again.
- See it don't!
- Why are you carrying that arrow?
- No particular reason.
Hold on!
What's he up to?
He say he win this big battle.
According to custom...
- ... he lop off their heads.
- Great warrior?
I never saw him in the
thick of the fray.
There's no prisoner executions
in this army.
Tell him to put that sword away.
He says once sword unsheathed,
it must taste blood.
Just as I thought.
He hasn't had it out until now!
He says watch out or he get very angry
and lop your head off.
All right. Up you get.
Off your hunkers.
No more grovelling.
We aren't gonna torch your city...
...or hang you in chains,
nor rape your daughters.
Tell them to divide their goods in half
and we will choose which half we want.
Henceforth, let the men of Er-Heb
and the men of Bashkai be as brothers.
Brothers in arms.
Let them march under one banner
and share in the victories to come.
Have the Bashkai any enemies
to speak of?
Oh, enemies all around!
Bhardoks, Ghundaras, Shus, Khawaks.
The Bhardoks piss downstream
on Bashkai people when they bathe.
Shocking!
We'll strike them
and grind them into dust!
Silver bracelet, 10 shillings.
A good heavy necklace of the same,
worth a fiver at least.
Earring with bangles.
One pig sticker with plain handle.
A gold coin worn pretty thin.
A rosy red ring
and a few other ones, plain.
All this should fetch
10 or 15 quid in a London shop.
Not too bad for the back of beyond.
Sikander!
They're calling for you.
For me?
Sikander. Sikander.
What does Sikander mean, Billy?
Sikander a god. Come here
long ago from the West.
That's the bloke Kipling told us about.
Alexander?
Alexander. Sikander.
Here.
- Alexander.
- He builded great city.
Sikandergul, high in mountains.
Sit on throne.
All people worship him.
Then one day, time comes,
he say he must go to East.
People pull their hair out,
tear clothes.
So Sikander promised to send back son.
328 B.C., encyclopaedia said.
They saw arrow go into Danny's chest,
him pluck it out, and not bleeding.
So?
So, son of Sikander.
They think I'm a god?
A god! Put your foot out
that I may kiss your big toe.
- You may kiss my royal arse.
- Not royal, holy!
- You're a deity, remember?
- Peachy.
- Yes, Billy?
- Is Danny not son of Sikander?
No, he's a man like us. He can
break wind at both ends simultaneous.
Which I bet is more
than any god can do!
But the arrow.
The arrow stuck in the bandolier.
No miracle.
You better tell them. And my dad's
name was Herbert Dravot, Esquire...
...and he was a bar steward in Durham!
Hang on, Danny.
- Maybe we're missing a bet.
- What do you mean?
Supposing you was an ignorant Kafiri...
...who would you rather follow,
a god or a man?
Now, we're here to conquer
this country, ain't we?
Well, with you as a god, it would take
half the time and half the trouble.
The idea is a bit blasphemous like.
No, Danny...
...blaspheming is when
you take his name in vain...
...God Almighty's.
What if they found out
we was having them on?
Why should they?
We won't tell them.
- You won't tell them, will you, Billy?
- Oh, no. Indeed, by Jove, no.
Polo.