Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
[# My Morning Jacket: One Big Holiday]
[Man] It only happens
once a year, and then they die.
It's like a mating ritual or something.
Isn't that romantic?
[Chuckles] Yeah. Yeah, it is.
- [Woman] Chris!
- Dude, what the fuck?
- [Woman 2] That's so not cool.
- [Woman 1] God! You scared me.
- Sorry.
- What happened?
- Shit. They're gone.
- You hit a deer or something?
- They're usually right here.
- Sit down.
- The party's that way.
- The party's this way.
- Danny.
- Come on, it's prom night.
- [Engine rewing]
- [Tires screech]
Whoo!
[Danny] Yeah!
Class of '03, kiss my ass!
Now look.
My God. They're so beautiful.
Look, look. You can grab the light.
[Screeching]
- Jesus!
- It's not funny.
- You can turn the lights back on.
- Come on.
- They were so beautiful.
- Told you, right?
- Please. You're freaking me out.
- There's more up there.
- Now!
- Hang on.
- Turn on the goddamn lights!
- Chris...
All right.
[Alarm beeping]
[Chris] I wake up.
Turn off the alarm.
I look outside
so that I know what to wear.
I take a shower...
... with soap.
And then I shave.
Sometimes I cry for no reason.
But I'm getting a handle on it.
[Alarm beeping]
I wake up.
I get dressed.
I take my meds.
When Lewis is gone,
I make the coffee, which can be tricky.
I eat breakfast,
but I don't read the paper.
It confuses me, which makes me mad.
[Alarm beeping]
I wake up.
I put on my coat and go to class.
[Man] Ten more seconds.
We're just doing one day, OK?
No big deal.
And time.
It's OK, chief. It's not a test.
[Honking]
[Children laughing]
[Beeping]
- Hey.
That's a nice hug.
Want anything?
[Man] Hi.
- What are you having?
- Hot chocolate.
- I'll have that. Thanks.
- OK.
- Any problems this week?
- Nope.
Swearing? Crying?
- Sequencing or memory issues?
- No.
Taking your meds?
- So all's good.
- Why? What's Lewis say?
You're the only one who can talk about
what's going on with you.
Well, in that case, I'm great.
There you go.
- Careful. It's hot.
- I know.
Have you spoken to Mr. Tuttle yet?
- No. I will.
- When?
- You were a model before.
- Chris...
I was just wondering how you go from
being a model to being a case manager.
After my head injury I realized there
were more people in the world than me.
Wanna go to a movie with me sometime?
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- Come on. It's just a movie.
We should talk about the women
in your life.
- You mean besides you?
- Yeah. Is there anybody?
Think you should do something
about that?
I think about fucking you all the time.
I don't think they heard that
over by the door.
- I didn't mean it like that. I meant...
- I know what you meant.
Would you have said that
before your injury?
So now you're gonna bring up
the frontal lobe bullshit?
Disinhibition. That might be getting
in the way of your meeting someone.
Asking a stranger for sex isn't
the best way to start a relationship.
- Not a good one.
- You're not a stranger.
- I have a relationship with you.
- I'm paid to work with you.
- Why are you here?
- You tell me.
I know why I'm here.
I'm here to help you get what you want.
What you really want.
But you've gotta know
what that is first.
I just wanna be who I was.
[Machine beeps]
[Man] Hey, kid, your mom called
to remind you about Thanksgiving.
I told her you had a hooker in your room
but that I'd be sure
to pass on the message.
OK, so the menu for tonight
is spaghetti amatriciana.
That's that pasta that's got
the bacon in it that you like.
The tomatoes are on the counter, so
open up the cans and put them in a pot.
Garlic press, asshole.
[Screams]
Fuck!
[Man 2] Hello, 1-800-Flowers.
Ma'am, if I can send them to my own
mother, anyone can send them to anybody.
And it just so happens to be
our featured special. Uh-huh.
Let's see. It's got roses and lilies
and snapdragons and fuji mums.
Australiums, which smell awesome,
unlike tulips, which don't smell at all.
[Chris] Lewis, I can't find
the motherfucking can opener!
They should last
about a week or two. That's right.
Terrific. And your name?
Kathy. Is that with a C or a K?
K. Kathy with a K.
That's a beautiful name, Kathy.
Chris?
I don't smell dinner.
I'm sorry, Lewis.
- Feel better?
- Yeah, thanks.
Chop some lettuce, cucumber, whatever
else you might want for your salad.
- Let's talk about your afternoon.
- We had to write again.
Oh, yeah? Let me guess.
Topic A, "Why am I all fucked up?"
Or topic B,
"Living with being all fucked up."
Reggie had us list a typical day,
and I kept getting stuck on "I wake up."
- I couldn't think of just a list.
- Well, don't think of it as a list.
Think of it as a story instead.
A story like what?
Like, you know,
"Once upon a time I woke up,
took a piss, beat off in the shower..."
- How is that gonna help me?
- I don't know.
Stories are what help us
make sense of the world.
- I can't tell stories.
- Use one you already know.
OK. How about War and fucking Peace?
That's a story.
I'd start a little simpler, though.
How about Goldilocks
and the Three fucking Bears?
Where's the cucumber?
- Come on. Let's hear it.
- You want me to tell you Goldilocks?
Entertain me.
OK. Once upon a time, there was
a little girl named Goldilocks.
- And then?
- And then...
I don't know, man.
She got eaten by a wolf.
Fucking hit by a truck. This is stupid.
Start at the end. Can't tell a story
if you don't know where it's going.
And lose the wolf.
That's Little Red Riding Hood.
The three bears find Goldilocks
asleep in their beds.
And then, um, she takes off.
Exactly. All right, now, that's the end.
What happened before that?
Um, one goes, "Someone's been sleeping
in my bed, and she's still there."
And before that it was,
"Someone is sitting in my chair."
Yeah, and then the bear kid's chair's
all jacked up.
Then it goes all the way back
to her walking in the door.
- First she walks in the forest.
- You sequence just fine.
You just gotta start at the end,
work backwards. Write that down.
- Hi, Mrs. Lange.
- Hi, Chris.
- He's in a good mood.
- Oh, OK.
- Good night.
The harvest checks go out
in a week or so.
That means we're going to be very busy
the next few weeks.
Which is why I want you to write down
"bank extra clean"
in your little notebook.
Good night.
Mr. Tuttle?
I'd like to apply to the executive
training program in Wichita,
but before I can, I have to have worked
100 hours as a teller at the branch.
- Take that up with Mrs. Lange.
- I have already.
We've been practicing.
She gave me some money.
She what?
See?
You said you'd think about
giving me some hours at a window.
You have to be able
to keep track of the debits.
A good teller is primarily
a good counter.
A teller keeps track of money
all day long,
taking care to keep the corners on bills
facing the same way.
At the end...
Um... The end...
Ends...
At the end... At the end of the day,
the teller balances the cash
against the payout tickets.
A good teller can go for years
without being out of balance.
Mrs. Lange has never been
out of balance yet.
But the real key
is a friendly personality.
The motto of a teller is,
"Be friendly and accurate."
- "But mostly be accurate."
- Very good, Chris.
Mrs. Lange also says the women's
bathroom fixture needs a new bulb.
Good night.
[Announcer] He'll scoop the puck
into the right corner.
Hartigan will center it
to the far boards.
Defense pushed it back to the line
to Lidstrom into the corner for Lang.
Lang floats it back to Lidstrom,
skating on the blue line with it.
Now fires a rising shot. Kicked aside.
But a goal pass by Pascal Leclaire.
[Raises volume] Trevor Letowski
carries it out to center ice.
A glove save. Now the puck bounces
away from Lidstrom out to center.
In pursuit Manny Malhotra.
Detroit played better
in the first period.
Malhotra is all over Williams,
forcing the Red Wings to have
a power play in their own zone.
Here comes Lidstrom
over the Columbus line.
Drop pass. Samuelson with a shot.
Passed to Danny Stevens.
Stevens back to Pratt.
Lidstrom right down the center.
Fakes it left.
Pratt fakes a shot on the right
and dekes out the goalie.
- [Horn blaring]
- [Crowd cheering]
I think Mark...
Game is tied...
And there's Holmstrom,
Johnny-on-the-spot, to fire it in...
You cannot be serious.
That is pathetic.
That's Chris Pratt.
Put that fucking thing out.
[# 78 Saab: No Illusions]
- Can I get you something?
- Yeah, an O'Doul's, please.
Yep.
This lady calls me over and she's, like,
"How many Dorothys live in Kansas?"
Hey.
Can you break a fifty?
Like, tens and fives?
Damn. And I thought I was good-looking.
- You having a good time?
- So far.
Well, that's all that matters, right?
Enjoy yourself.
Hey, Chris Pratt, right?
Gary Spargo. We know each other.
I was a couple of years ahead
in your sister's class.
We went out a couple of times,
but never took.
How's she doing, anyway? Alison, right?
Yeah, she's good, man.
She's married. She has a baby.
- Just my luck.
- [phone ringing]
- Well, it was nice seeing you, anyway.
- Yeah.
- You say hello to Alison for me.
- OK.
- Yeah. Where are you?
- It's 2.50, chief.
Ten, twenty, thirty, five, forty...
You were supposed to be here
an hour ago.
- Sorry, how much?
- 2.50.
That's not my problem.
I guess I'll see you later. OK, bye.
- Do you need any change with that?
- No, keep it.
- Thanks, chief.
- Whoa. Excuse me, uh... T.J.
You must be one hell of a bartender,
$17 tip for a $3 beer.
- What can I say?
- You can say, "It's on the house."
- It's not a problem.
- No, no, no, no.
He insists. Don't you, chief?
Yeah. Whatever.
Prick. Shit, I apologize
for that guy, Chris.
[Chris] No, it's OK.
You know, I find myself apologizing
for people pretty often these days.
I heard something happened to you.
So, what was it? Motorcycle accident?
If you don't mind me asking.
I'm just curious.
It was a car accident.
I was driving at night
and I hit a combine that was stalled
in the middle of the road, old Route 24.
Well, how does a thing like that happen?
- I had the lights off.
- Really?
They say I got thrown 90 feet.
Wait, I'm sorry. "They" say?
Well, no, I can't remember any of it.
Well, thank God for that.
I remember, uh, right before it
and right after it
and one moment where I thought
the medevac was gonna land on top of me.
Anybody die?
Yeah, two friends.
- You do any time?
- No.
But you're doing your time right now,
though, right?
So, you drink near beer and what else?
It's like I can pick up a glass
with this hand,
can't always drink from it.
I fall asleep a lot, just nod off
in the middle of things.
- Yeah, me, too.
- [Chuckles] Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Well, I call tomatoes "lemons."
I know that's wrong.
And sometimes certain colors
have certain smells.
- That's weird.
- [Inhaler hisses]
Well, we all got our problems, right?
There's an expression: "God closes
a door, but he opens a window."
Or he closes the window
and he opens the door.
My point is...
...sometimes something good
comes from an accident, you know?
Sometimes you're out there and you...
Man, she really wears that sweater,
doesn't she?
Fuck.
Anyway, it was a pleasure, Chris.
- Yeah.
- Take it easy.
[Chris] Once upon a time, I woke up.
I took a shower with soap.
I had breakfast.
I didn't read the paper.
I put on my coat.
I had Thanksgiving dinner
with my family.
[Chris] Coming around to you.
- Got your key?
- Yeah, I got my key.
- I smell money.
- Shut up.
Barb, did you make any of this?
- No, I'm afraid not.
- You used the thin ones, right?
- Not the thick nighttime ones?
- Yes, Alison, I used the thin ones.
You look great.
Lots of color in your cheeks.
- Not sure about this coat, though.
- Where's that from? Tenth grade?
- Well, I like this coat.
- I bumped into Marilyn Hess last week.
She had Charlotte with her.
Wasn't she in your class?
She was in my class.
Conrad was in Chris's.
Charlotte said for you to call her.
She looks fantastic.
- Lost quite a bit of weight.
- I love mushrooms.
What do you call a mushroom who goes
into the bar, buys everybody a drink?
- I don't know. What?
- A fungi.
This is all very good.
The relish in particular is nice.
- Not too tart, not too sweet.
- It was my grandmother's recipe.
Any other old family recipes?
We can use them for the restaurant.
- Restaurant?
- Chris didn't tell you?
No. He didn't tell us.
What exactly would you do
at a restaurant, Chris?
- Well, I'd help Lewis.
- We found a space, but it needs work.
- [Barbara] Where?
- Waverly, near Overland.
- Where is that?
- Southside. It's a gas station.
A gas station? Really?
We'd keep the door open during summer
for an al fresco kind of thing.
If it's a gas station,
you'd have to do some work...
We're just fucking talking about it, OK?
Excuse me.
- There are some steps.
- Oh.
Well, then, you better carry me.
Really?
- [Knock on door]
- Chris?
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
We gotta go. If I don't get her
down soon, she'll never sleep.
You should come by sometime.
We'll hang out.
And Dad's waiting down in the war room.
Hey, uh, you remember a Gary Spargo?
- Who?
- Gary Spargo.
He said he went out with you
a couple of times.
Well, he probably did.
- You look good. It's great to see you.
- Thanks.
Alison, right?
Say goodbye to Uncle Chris.
All right, we'll see you later.
In the last three years, we opened two
Jaguar stores and one Land Rover store.
So we're all about Ford now. But a
PorschelAudi franchise, that'd be tight.
What do you do
for the company, Cameron?
As little as possible.
Boy, you got me on the run here.
- There's a comforting sound.
- This new?
It was a gift from Charlie.
Whitehall, my partner.
Yeah, I know who Charlie Whitehall is.
- It's a nice gun.
- It's your move.
Check, by the way.
What'd you do?
- Sure you wanna do that?
- I think so.
You're gonna lose your queen, right?
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm gonna take her.
Check. In fact, checkmate.
- I didn't see that.
- I got lucky.
- Good game, Dad.
- We got time for another quick one.
I think we should go. Lewis, wanna go?
Would you rather I let you win?
Dad, I can't play chess anymore.
I'm sorry.
- Well, it's good seeing you.
- Good seeing you.
Happy Thanksgiving, son.
Can I say something?
You won't get upset?
[Chris] What?
I don't think
you should go home anymore.
[Knocking]
- Jesus, Ted, you snuck up on me.
- I'm supposed to sneak up on you.
They didn't have no more jellies,
so I got you a custard.
- Thanks. You got a cold, Ted?
- [Sneezes]
No wonder I don't got pneumonia, given
the house is cold enough to hang meat.
How come?
Sherry won't have the heat on
after nine.
Because of the baby.
We don't refer to it
as "the baby" no more.
- We don't?
- Sherry calls it "the little engine."
- It makes her hot all the time.
- Right.
Doctor told her she's got
three times more blood in her
and that's why she can't cool off.
Kid's not even born yet,
I'm already awake all night.
You're lucky you don't ever
have to worry about that stuff.
I gotta go.
Remember, lock the back door.
I will.
- You left your door open again.
- Oh, shit.
[# Black Rebel Motorcycle Club:
Shuffle Your Feet]
I thought I was good-looking.
- Excuse me?
- I thought I was good-looking.
Well, maybe you were.
- Chris Pratt?
- Yeah.
My friend would like to buy you a drink.
I used to dance at Wet Willy's.
You know that place in Raytown?
It got closed down
on account of debts,
so right now I'm working with Maura
at the chamber of commerce.
I'm answering phones.
What do you do?
Oh, I, um...
- Sorry, I forgot your name.
- Again?
It's Luvlee. L-U-V-L-E-E.
Luvlee.
Now you'll remember me.
Anything about Kansas City,
I can tell you.
- Yeah? Like what?
- Did you know Teflon was invented here?
And Eskimo Pies.
And McDonald's Happy Meals.
And "Melts in your mouth,
not in your hands," M&M candy coating.
You guys are so interesting.
Why don't we go somewhere quiet where
we can hear what you two have to say?
- Why don't we do that?
- You wanna come?
[Soft music playing]
[Moaning]
That's better.
I've seen you play hockey, you know.
Me and Alice Watts used to
watch you play all the time.
I don't remember you.
I saw you play the night you beat
the Raytown Cougars
for the state championships.
It was your birthday.
Do you remember that?
- Yeah. Yeah, that was a good game.
- Yeah, it was.
You got your second five-minute major
right at the end of the game.
Next game you would have
sat on the bench.
But it was the last game of the season,
and you knew that it didn't matter.
So what do you do? You go and slash
the hell out of some shitty player
at the end of a game you already won.
And, still, the whole crowd sings
Happy Birthday to you.
Me and Alice Watts were, like, "Damn, it
must be pretty cool to be Chris Pratt."
Don't mind me.
And then I heard what happened to you
and Nina and Danny and...
What was the name of the pretty girl?
- Kelly.
- Kelly, that's right.
And everyone was talking about how you,
you know, you woke up this other guy.
I remember thinking,
"God, we're the same age.
That could be me that it happened to."
Anyways...
- Are you OK?
- I wanna see you naked.
- Shit. I'm sorry.
- No, don't be. I'm flattered.
- Oh, you got cold hands.
- Sorry. [chuckles]
I see something still works.
- You don't have to do this.
- I know. I want to.
[Gary] How does a titan like Robert
Pratt feel about you living here?
[Chris] He's never seen it.
Really?
Tomorrow a bunch of us are hanging
at this farm we're borrowing,
celebrate Thanksgiving dinner,
if you wanna come.
But wasn't that last week?
Yeah, well,
we're just getting around to it.
Luvlee wrote the address down
in your notebook.
Hey, you know something?
You're better than this.
A lot better.
- Chris?
- Yeah.
- Doc Watson's got nothing on me, man.
- Well, good night.
You get stoned?
With somebody wearing perfume?
- No.
- No, no, stop. Don't move.
- Were you with a lady tonight?
- [Sighs]
Son of a bitch, you got laid.
- I don't really wanna talk about it.
- Oh, but you are, my friend, you are.
Come here.
So, tell me... did you get a hummer?
- Jesus, Lewis.
- All right. At least tell me her name.
- Luvlee something.
- Lovely? That's a name?
Yes. L-U-V-L-E-E.
That's a new one. So what's this
Luvlee something look like, huh?
She's nice.
Here I am sitting at home alone
every night
while you're out getting blown and God
knows what else by Luvlee something,
who probably has a friend.
- Lemons. That's what it is.
- What what is?
- That's her last name.
- Luvlee Lemons? That's her name?
Well, it's her stage name.
She's a performer. Or she was.
And by stage, I'm assuming
you mean the kind with a pole?
- What do you mean?
- Let's move on.
- Where'd you meet her?
- Gary introduced me to her.
- Who's Gary? Gary who?
- Gary Spargo.
- Do I know this guy?
- I don't think so.
- I just met him down at the local.
- Huh.
- Well, I better get some sleep.
- Yeah. Yeah, you better.
You dog.
Gary Spargo.
[Groaning]
- [Sighs]
- [Urinating]
Whoa! You scared me.
- I'm Chris.
- Yeah, yeah. Aaron Cork.
Got a good grip. Come on in.
We've been waiting on you.
- Is turkey supposed to be rare?
- I don't think so.
I totally undercooked it. I've gotta
put it back in. You have to help me.
Hey. You made it.
Tortilla salad, pierogies, egg rolls.
We made too much food.
- There's nine of us.
- There's seven. You, me, Cork, Marty...
Never mind.
I'm the chef.
Go on. They're waiting for you.
You smoke a joint to relax,
but you won't let me rub your shoulders.
I will never let you touch me.
You're not comfortable
with your sexuality.
Don't move.
Everybody,
this is Chris "Slap Shot" Pratt.
Hey, Chris. How you doing?
- Here's the Corker. Avoid that guy.
- Too late. We're old pals.
This is Marty. Marty is the guy
you wanna teach you how to surf.
- He's the only boy in Kansas knows how.
- I went to Framington, man.
We played you guys in Division A.
- I didn't really do sports.
- Gare, we gotta jam.
Too bad.
How many of these things
you gonna need?
- I'm gonna take all of them. Thanks.
- Cool.
Good seeing you guys.
Marty, watch out. It's heavy.
- Hey, sit down. Sit down.
- This your farm?
My Uncle Bone found it
and kind of negotiated with the owner.
- Wanna try some wine?
- I can't.
Come on. Take it.
- Marty?
- Yes.
Nice. One for me.
And toast.
How about, uh... Fuck it. Family, right?
- Hey, yeah. Cheers, man.
- Family's good.
Family.
- Welcome.
- Who are all these people?
- Whose place is this?
- Friend of a friend. Bone?
- Dinner is served.
- It's about time.
- Can we get some water?
- Food.
- Why the hell we eating burritos?
- Get your own water.
- Want some gravy?
- What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just remembered why I came here.
- [Chattering]
- [Music playing]
I'm just saying...
[Gary] Check this out.
[Maura]... some old farmhouse.
I don't know where it is.
No, that's water.
Mommy's doing dishes.
Mommy's cleaning up
after a bunch of pigs.
I'll see you in three weeks.
Tell Grandma to put it on the calendar
this time. I love you, too.
[Gunfire on TV]
Hey, Gare.
Hey, man. Why don't you come on down?
Couldn't sleep, huh?
Well, that's the thing about good wine.
Doesn't make you sleepy.
But, then, it doesn't give you
a hangover either, so...
Unless your brain's all fucked up.
- You played for Framington, right?
- No, man.
Let me just clean up some of this mess.
[Groans]
What's this?
This? This is a project I've been
working on for very many months.
Probably not ready
for anyone to see yet, but such is life.
- These all banks?
- Mm-hmm. That's right, Chris.
They're all banks.
Why are you taking pictures of banks?
- Because I'm gonna rob one of them.
- [Both chuckling]
Well, we're gonna rob one of them.
Some nice little farm bank
in the ass-end of nowhere
where they get
all that winter harvest cash.
You know what I'm talking about?
- You wanna steal from farmers?
- No, Chris.
I'm gonna steal from the corporate
fuckers who rape the farmers.
Agribusiness fat cats
who give the American farmer
enough to grow his crop
but not enough to live.
- Fucking tragedy is what it is.
- Totally tragic.
So we gotta find a bank
in the middle of a lot of big farms
where one time a year,
i.e., right now,
they're gonna fill that vault with cash
so that Farmer John can pay
Juan or Ramon to pick his crops.
There's this quiet, empty place
with no security to speak of,
and this quiet, empty place
no one really knows exists.
I mean, isn't that why you drive an hour
and a half each way to work there?
What is this?
Chris, I will totally understand if
you feel betrayed, but I need your help.
You want me to rob the bank.
- I can't do that.
- Why not, huh? Because it's wrong?
I don't know, but if I had... If I had
my life ripped out from underneath me
the way you had your life
ripped out from underneath you,
I don't think I'd give even half a rat's
ass about what was right or wrong.
I'd just fucking want
my old life back, you know?
Look at this shit.
Mopping floors, man.
Don't you want your old life back?
- You can't give that to me.
- No, I can't.
But I can give you something
maybe even better.
I can give you the power.
- Power?
- Mm-hmm.
Power.
Why don't you sit down?
I'll tell you about it.
Please?
My old man used to say to me, probably
the only thing we ever really agreed on,
whoever has the money has the power.
You might wanna jot that down
in your book.
It's something
you're gonna need to remember.
Do you have the power right now
in your life, Chris? Huh?
- Do you?
- I don't know.
How many janitors you know
have any kind of power to speak of?
Here's a question.
Who pays for your life?
You go to the ATM,
what, two, three times a week?
- Three.
- Three times. Wow.
Where does that money come from?
You drive a car.
Who pays for that?
Who pays for the insurance?
Given your track history,
it must be more than the rent,
which gets paid on the first
of every month by who?
- Daddy.
- Bingo.
Your old man,
he'll pay money to take care of you,
but he won't give you enough money
to take care of yourself. Why not?
He doesn't think that you can,
so he just doles out enough money
so that you have to depend on him.
You're as stuck as the farmers, Chris.
You star in your own tragedy.
My father would give me money
if I asked.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's... That's bullshit.
I'm sorry. Let's call him up.
Call him up, ask him.
Ask him for ten grand
and see what he says.
Hell, ask him for one grand
Tell him you wanna start a business.
You can't.
I know. I mean, you know,
I went to prison for my sins, Chris,
so I don't have to carry them
around with me.
But you, your old man picked up the tab,
so now you drive out
Old Farm Road 24 once a week
to the spot just to remind yourself,
keep it fresh in your head,
just what a piece of shit
you think you are.
- I thought we were friends.
- We are friends.
Outside of some old blind guy
dressed like Larry Flynt,
I'm the best friend you got right now,
and I mean that.
You were Chris Pratt. I was three years
ahead of you and I looked up to you.
You were fucking beautiful.
But then...
Well, now... I'm gonna help you.
- How?
- I'll say it again.
Maybe you'll write it down this time.
Whoever has the money has the power.
Chris? Where are you going?
Are you leaving?
Come on, sweetie.
[Lewis] We figure it's 30,000
to convert to a restaurant,
another ten or so to get us up on
our feet, plus or minus a few thousand.
Show him the menu, kid.
Is there a separate dinner menu?
We're just gonna be open
for breakfast and lunch.
- That way we have our nights free.
- I see.
OK, we have the Abbie, the Huey.
- Who are these sandwiches named after?
- People I've admired.
- We could name one after you.
- I don't think that's necessary.
- Sure, sure. Why not?
- Well, that's very kind, but...
What's your first name?
- Reuben.
- What's your middle name?
- Lewis...
- 30,000 seems a little low, boys.
- This place is a gas station now?
- Yeah, but you make that work for you.
Keep the gas station theme, maybe
you park a VW bus at one of the pumps,
paint the name of the place on the side.
Yeah, the name of the place.
Uh... Yes. Lew's...
Lew's Your Lunch.
See, I'm Lewis, Lew.
The place is just gonna be open
for breakfast and...
It's very clever.
- But we don't have to call it that.
- Yeah, I got lots of ideas.
Aside from that Reuben hiccup,
I think it went pretty well.
I've got a good feeling about it.
Our man Hearn was jazzed.
I don't know if you noticed. I think
he was pretty excited, don't you think?
Chris?
- Chris?
- I'm right here, Lewis.
- I thought you left me.
- I didn't leave you.
Come on. I'll drive you back to work.
[Reggie] Who can tell me
our three organizational strategies?
- Ritual.
- [Writing on chalkboard]
Pattern.
And... repetition.
- [Chris] Shit.
- Very good.
Hey.
If you ever wanna stay late,
we could practice counting or...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org