Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The peace of God,
which passes all understanding.
Keep your hearts and minds
in the knowledge and love of God...
and of his Son, Jesus Christ, our Lord.
The blessing of God Almighty,
the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit...
be upon you and remain with you
this day and always.
Amen.
Will that do the trick, do you think?
We're about to find out.
Jimmy!
Ready?
Ready.
Mum, please. Lads, one-
Just get in the car.
I'll be back. Five minutes.
Let's get it over with.
Ah-ah. Give me a minute.
- Read it out. Fiona, just read it out!
- Let's see, let's see.
Three A's!
- I got three A's! Three A's!
- Chris, what'd you get?
Full house!
- Full house!
- Three A's! Three A's!
- Told you you would!
- Full house!
- Hey, what'd you get?
- "A" and two B's.
Fucking hell!
Hey! Hey, Dakin!
- Stu!
- Stu, what happened?
Yeah!
- Are you not gonna look?
- No, I got mine last night.
- I'll bet you did.
- You jammy sod!
- Lockwood.
- Felix.
- Sir?
- Why are you dressed as a milkman?
Working, sir, for the holidays.
As a milkman?
After the holidays, you'll be coming back
to try for Oxford and Cambridge.
Your A-level results
are the best we've ever had...
and they demand that you return for
an extra term to work for the examination...
to our ancient universities.
One more term, boys.
One more push.
In the meantime, try and do
something, oh, fitting.
- I'm in a book shop, sir.
- Good. Good.
- I'm on the bins, sir.
- I'm a bouncer, sir.
- Lavatory attendant, sir.
- Gigolo.
Congratulations, boys.
Oh.! Mrs. Lintott.!
Hey-hey-hey!
- Three A's! Three A's!
- Three A's! All right!
Mr. Hector!
So we shall be meeting again
after all.
- Yes!
At school you don't get parole.
Good behavior just brings a longer sentence.
Ah, you poor boys.
Hey, see you next term, sir!
Thank you, miss.
"The happiest youth,
viewing his progress through...
"what perils past,
what crosses to ensue...
would shut the book
and sit him down and die. "
Congratulations, Dorothy.
You must be very pleased.
Good morning!
You are entitled-
though only for five minutes, Dakin-
to feel pleased with yourselves.
No one has done as well,
not in English, not in science...
not even, dare I say it,
in media studies.
And you alone are up
for Oxford and Cambridge.
So, to work.
First essay this term will be the Church
on the eve of the Reformation.
- Not again, miss.
- This is Oxford and Cambridge.
You don't just need to know it.
You need to know it backwards, Timms.
Facts, facts, facts.
They're clever.
But they're crass.
And were it Bristol...
or York...
I'd have no worries.
But Oxford and Cambridge!
We need a strategy, Dorothy.
A game plan.
They know their stuff.
But they lack flair.
Culture they can get from Hector,
uh, history from you.
But-
I'm thinking aloud now.
Is there something else?
Think charm.
Think polish.
Think... renaissance man.
Leave it with me, Dorothy.
Leave it with me.
Yes, Headmaster.
Wilkes.
Ah, yes.
An innovation to the timetable.
- P.E.
- Yes, Headmaster.
For the Oxbridge set.
Surely not, you say.
But why not?
This is the biggest hurdle of their lives.
And I want them... galvanized.
Galvanized. Yes, Headmaster.
In the timetable...
our esteemed headmaster has given
these periods the dubious title...
of"General Studies. "
I will let you into a little secret, boys.
There is no such thing
as "general studies. "
General studies is a waste of time.
Knowledge is not general.
It is specific...
and nothing to do with getting on.
But remember-
open quotation marks-
"All knowledge is precious, whether or not
it serves the slightest human use. "
Close quotation marks.
Who said, Akhtar?
Timms? Lockwood? Dakin?
- "Loveliest of trees, the cherry now. "
- A.E. Houseman, sir!
A.E. Houseman, sir!
Wasn't he a nancy, sir?
Foul, festering,
grubby-minded little trollop!
- Do not use that word!
- But you use it, sir!
I do, sir, I know, but I am far gone
in age and decrepitude.
You're not supposed to hit us, sir,
or we could report you.
- I know, I know.
- You should treat us with more respect.
We're scholarship candidates now, sir.
We're all going in
for Oxford and Cambridge.
Oxford and Cambridge?
What for?
Old, sir! Tried and tested.
No, it's because other boys want to go there.
It's the hot ticket.
Standing room only.
- Where did you go, sir?
- I went to Sheffield.
I was happy.
"Happy is England,
sweet her artless daughters;
Enough her simple
loveliness for me. "
Keats.
We won't be examined
on that, though, will we, sir?
- Keats?
- Happiness.
- You are?
- Irwin.
- The temporary contract teacher?
Quite so.
The examinations
are at the end of term...
which gives us, uh,
three months at the outside.
- You were at Cambridge. You know the form.
- Oxford. Jesus.
Ah. Yes, I- I thought of going.
But this was the- the '50s.
Change was in the air...
a spirit of adventure.
So, where did you go?
I was a geographer.
I went to Hull.
They're a likely lot, the boys.
Um, they're all keen.
One oddity- Rudge.
Determined to try for Oxford...
and Christ Church, of all places.
No hope.
Might get into Loughborough
in a bad year.
Um, o-otherwise all bright.
But they need polish, edge.
Your job.
We are low in the league.
I want to see us up there
with Manchester Grammar School...
Haberdashers' Aske's,
Leighton Park.
Or is that an open prison?
No matter.
There is a vacancy in history.
That's very true.
In the school.
Ah.
Get me scholarships, Irwin.
Pull us up the table and it's yours.
I- I-I'm corseted by the curriculum.
But I can find you, uh,
three lessons a week.
- Not enough.
- No, I-I-Yes, I agree, I agree.
However, I think I know
where we can filch an hour.
Où voudriez-vous
travailler cet après-midi?
Je voudrais travailler
dans une maison de passe.
Ooh-la-la!
- Comment, "maison de passe"?
- Qu'est-ce que c'est?
A brothel. He'd like to work in a brothel.
Oui. Très bien.
Mais une maison de passe
où tous les clients...
utilisent le subjonctif,
ou le conditionnel.
- Oui?
- D'accord, monsieur.
Voilà. Voilà.!
Déjà un client.
- Bonjour, monsieur.
- Bonjour, chérie.
Entrez, si'I vous plaît.
Voilà. Votre lit.
Et voici votre prostituée.
- For fuck's sake!
- Ooh-la-la!
Je veux m'étendre sur le lit.
Je voudrais.!
"I would like to stretch out on the bed,"
in the conditional or the subjunctive.
Continuez, mes enfants.
Mais les chaussures, monsieur.
Pas sur le lit.
Oh, excusez-moi, mademoiselle.
Excusez-moi.
Et votre pantalon, s'il vous plaît.
- Fucking hell!
- Sir, come on!
Sir-
Oh.! Quelles belles jambes.
Et maintenant, Claudine.!
Oui. La prostituée,
si'I vous plaît.
Whoo-ooh!
A quel prix?
- Dix francs.
Pour dix francs, je peux vous montrer
ma prodigieuse poitrine.!
Non, non, non, non.
Ça vous coûterait quinze francs.
Non. Pour vingt francs-
- Un autre client.!
- Oh, my God.!
Ah! Cher Monsieur le directeur!
- Mr. Hector, what on earth is happening?
- Ah-ah-ah!
L 'anglais c'est interdit.
Ici, on ne parle que francais...
en accordant une importance
particulière au subjonctif.
Oh.
Um-
Et qu'est-ce qui se passe ici?
Pourquoi ce garçon-
- Um, Dakin, isn't it?
- Sir.
Est sans ses... trousers.
- Fuck's sakes.
- Oh, um-
Quelqu'un?
Oh, ne sois pas timide.
Dites à cher Monsieur le directeur
ce que nous faisons.
- Je suis un homme qui-
- Vous n'êtes pas un homme.!
Vous êtes un soldat.
Un soldat blessé.
Vous comprenez cher Monsieur le directeur.
Soldat blessé?
Wounded soldier?
Yes, yes, of course.
Ici c'est un hôpital en Belgique.
Belgique? Pourquoi Belgique?
- A Ypres, sir. Ypres.
- Ypres?
- Pendant la Guerre Mondiale Numéro Un.
- It's Ypres, sir.
- C'est ça.!
Dakin est un soldat blessé.
Un mutilé de guerre.
Et les autres sont
des médecins, infirmières...
et tout le personnel d'un grand établissement
médical et thérapeutique.
Continuez, mes enfants.
Qu'il souffre.!
- Ma mère.! Ma mère.!
- Il appelle sa mère.
- Mon père.! Mon père.!
- Il appelle son père.
Il est distrait. Il est distrait.
Il est commotionné, peut-être?
Comment?
Commotionné.
Shell-shocked.
C'est possible. Commotionné.
Oui. C'est le motjuste.
Permettez-moi d'introduire Monsieur Irwin,
notre nouveau professeur.
- Enchanté.
- Bonjour.
Enough of this silliness-
N- N-Not silliness.
Mr. Hector, you are aware these pupils
are Oxbridge candidates.
Are they? Are you sure?
Nobody's told me.
Mr. Irwin will be coaching them.
But it's a question of time.
- I've found him three lessons a week,
but I was wondering- - No, Headmaster.
No, purely on a temporary basis.
The last time. I promise.
The last time was the last time also.
- I'm thinking of the boys!
- I too. No. Absolutement. No. No, no, no.
C'est hors de question.
Et puis, si vous voulez m'excuser,
je dois continuer la leçon.
A tout à I'heure.
Fuck.
It's true, though, sir.
We don't have much time.
We don't even have to do French.
Now, who goes home?
Well, surely I can give somebody a lift.
Who's on pillion duty? Dakin!
Not me, sir.
I'm going into town.
- Crowther?
- No, I'm off for a run, sir.
- Akhtar.
- Computer club, sir.
Ah.
- I'll come, sir.
- Oh, no. Never mind.
I'll come, sir.
Oh. Scripps.
The things I do forJesus.
It's never me.
You're too young still.
It will happen,
now that you've achieved puberty.
If rather late in the day.
Mr. Hector is likely at some point
to try and put his hand on your knee.
This is because Mr. Hector
is a homosexual and a sad fuck.
The drill is to look at the hand and go...
"And what does Mr. Hector want?"
Well, he has no answer for this,
and so will desist.
Thrutch up.
I just think I should have been told.
Well, he comes highly recommended.
- So did Anne of Cleves.
- Who?
He's up to the minute, Dorothy.
More "now. "
"Now"?
I thought history was then.
Felix.
Anne of Cleves. Remind me.
- Fourth wife of Henry VIII, sir.
- Of course.
She was the one
they told him was Miss Dish.
Only when she turned up, she had a face
like the wrong end of a camel's turd.
Quite so.
What's the matter with you, lad?
Oh. I've got a note, sir.
How much for?
I don't do notes. Get changed.
- Sir-
- God doesn't do notes either.
Did Jesus say, "Can I be excused
the crucifixion?" No.
Actually, sir, I think he did.
Change!
One day it'll save your life.
Nothing saves anyone's life, sir.
It just postpones their death.
Jesus Christ will save your life, lad...
if you only let him into your heart.
I'm Jewish, sir.
I'm Muslim, sir.
Bloody good.
That was excellent.
Lad, lad, lad.
You're letting yourself down.
You're letting God down!
What's God got to do with it?
- Listen, boy, this isn't your body.
- No?
No. This body
is on loan to you from God.
Well, fuck me.
I heard that. Give me 20.
Twenty what? Hail Marys?
Do it.
You're late.
- Get your kit off.
- I'm on the staff.
Well, I've never seen you.
What's this?
- Do you need a hand with that, sir?
- Is it joined-up writing?
So, Mrs. Lintott's given me a view
of some of your latest essays.
The experience was interesting.
The essays, not.
Dull.
Dull. Abysmally dull.
A triumph- the dullest of the lot.
Well, I got all the points.
I didn't say it was wrong. I said it was dull.
Its sheer competence was staggering.
You've got crap handwriting, sir.
- It's your eyesight that's bad. We know what that's caused by.
- Sir!
Is that a coded reference
to the mythical dangers of self-abuse?
- Possibly. It might even be a joke.
- Ajoke, sir? Oh.
Are jokes gonna be a feature, sir?
We need to know, as it affects our mind-set.
You don't object to our using
the expression "mind-set,"do you, sir?
Mr. Hector doesn't care for it.
At the, uh-
At the time of the Reformation...
there were 14
foreskins of Christ preserved.
But it was thought the Church of St. John
Lateran in Rome had the authentic prepuce.
Don't think we're shocked by your mention
of the word "foreskin," sir.
No, sir.
Some of us even have them.
Not Posner, though, sir,
'cause he's, well, Jewish.
- It's one of several things he doesn't have.
- Fuck off.
- That's not racist, though, sir.
- Isn't it?
That's race-related, but not racist.
Has anybody been to Rome or Venice?
Or... Florence?
No. 'Cause the other candidates
will have been.
And they'll have done courses
on what they've seen there, most likely.
So they're gonna know, when they
come to do an essay like this...
on the Church at the time
of the Reformation that, ooh, look...
some silly nonsense on the foreskins
of Christ will come in handy...
so that their essays,
unlike yours, will not be dull.
They're not even bad.
They're just boring.
You haven't got a hope.
- So why are we bothering?
- I don't know.
You tell me. You want it?
Your parents want it.
The headmaster, he certainly wants it.
Me? I wouldn't waste the money.
I'd go to Newcastle and be happy.
Of course, there is another way.
Ooh! Wow!
Cheat!
Possibly.
Dakin.
- Sir?
- Don't take the piss. There isn't time.
- What a wanker.
- They all have to do it, don't they?
- Do what?
- Show you they're still in the game.
Foreskins and stuff.
"Oh, sir, you devil!"
Have a heart. He is only five minutes
older than we are.
What happened with Hector
on the bike?
As per.
Except I managed to get my bag down.
I think he thought he'd got me going.
In fact, it was my Tudor Economic
Documents Volume 2.
So, let's summarize.
The first world war.
- What points do we make?
- Trench warfare.
- Mountains of dead.
- On both sides.
- Generals stupid.
- Armistice. Germany humiliated.
- Keep it coming.
- Mass unemployment.
- Inflation.
Collapse of the Weimar Republic,
internal disorder and the rise of Hitler.
So, our overall conclusion
is that the origins of the second war...
lie in the unsatisfactory outcome
of the first.
Yes.
- Yes.
- First-class.
Bristol welcomes you with open arms.
Manchester longs to have you.
You can walk into Leeds.
But I'm a fellow
of Magdalen College, Oxford.
I've just read 70 papers, they're all saying
the same thing, and I'm asleep.
- But it's all true.
- What's truth got to do with it?
What's truth got to do with anything?
The new man seems clever.
He does. Depressingly so.
Didn't you try for Oxford?
Cambridge.
Cloisters.
Ancient libraries.
I was confusing learning
with the smell of cold stone.
If I had gone, I'd probably never
have worked out the difference.
Durham was very good for history.
It's where I had my first pizza.
Other things too, of course,
but it's the pizza that stands out.
Dakin's a good-looking boy,
though somehow sad.
You always think they're sad, Hector.
Every, every time.
Actually, I wouldn't have said he was sad.
I would've said he was cunt-struck.
Dorothy!
I'd have thought you'd have liked that.
It's a compound adjective.
- You like compound adjectives.
- Yeah.
Oh. Going walkabout.
Oh, yeah.
The truth was, in 1914
Germany doesn't want war.
Yeah, there's an arms race,
but it's Britain who's leading it.
So, why does no one admit this?
That's why- the dead.
The body count.
We still don't like to admit the war
was even partly our fault...
'cause so many of our people died.
And all the mournings
veiled the truth.
It's not "Lest we forget,"
it's "Lest we remember. "
That's what all this is about-
the memorials, the cenotaph,
the two-minute silence.
Because there is no better way of forgetting
something than by commemorating it.
And as for the truth, Scripps,
which you're worrying about, forget it.
In an examination,
truth's not an issue.
You really believe this, sir...
or are you just trying
to make us think?
You can't explain away
the poetry, sir.
- No, sir. Art wins in the end.
- What about this one, sir?
"Those long, uneven lines...
"standing as patiently as if they were
stretched outside The Oval or Villa Park...
"the crowns of hats...
"the sun on mustached, archaic faces...
grinning as if it were all
an August bank holiday lark. "
"Never such innocence,
never before or since...
as changed itself to past
without a word. "
"The men leaving the gardens tidy. "
"The thousands of marriages
lasting a little while longer. "
"Never such innocence again. "
How come you know all this by heart?
Not that it answers the question.
So much for our glorious dead.
Quite.
Actually, Fiona's my western front.
Well, last night, for instance.
I thought it might be the big push.
So, encountering
only token resistance...
I reconnoitered the ground
as far as the actual place.
- Shit!
- No, I mean, not onto it.
And certainly not into it.
- Up to it.
- Fuck.
And the metaphor really fits.
I mean...
moving up to the front...
troops presumably had to pass
the sites of previous battles.
Well, so it is with me.
Like, particularly her tits...
which only surrendered
about three weeks ago...
and which were indeed the start line
of a determined thrust southwards.
What's the matter?
No-man's-land.
Oh, fuck.
So, what do I do with this?
Carry out a controlled explosion?
Still, least I'm doing better than Felix.
- Felix?
- No!
Tries to.
Chases her around the desk.
Ooh!
Actually, the metaphor isn't exact...
because what Fiona is presumably
carrying out is a planned withdrawal.
You're not forcing her. She's not
being overwhelmed by superior forces.
- Does she like you?
- Of course she likes me.
Then you're not disputing the territory.
You're just negotiating
over the pace of the occupation.
Just let us know
when you get to Berlin.
I'm beginning to like him more.
Who? Me?
Irwin.
Though he hates me.
Jimmy.!
Wait for me.
Cheer up. Least he speaks to you.
Most guys wouldn't even speak to you.
Love can be very irritating.
How do you know?
That's what I always think about God.
Must get so pissed off,
everybody adoring him all the time.
Yes, only you don't catch God
poncing about in his underpants.
Well done, Posner.
And now for some poetry
of a more traditional sort.
Oh, God!
Uh, Timms, w-what is this?
Sir, I don't always understand poetry.
You don't always understand it?
Timms, I never understand it.
But learn it now, know it now...
and you will understand it...
whenever.
I don't see how we can
understand it.
Most of the stuff poetry's about
hasn't happened to us yet.
But it will, Timms. It will.
And when it does,
you'll have the antidote ready.
Grief, happiness.
Even when you're dying.
We're making your deathbeds here, boys.
- Fucking Ada.
- We've got an ending, sir!
Re- Oh! Goody goo-Yes!
Well, be sharp. Where's the kitty?
We have to smoke, sir.
And I happen to have some, sir.
Very well.
Jerry, please help me.
- Shall we just have a cigarette on it?
- Yes.
- May I sometimes come here?
- Whenever you like.
It's your home too.
There are people here who love you.
And will you be happy, Charlotte?
Oh, Jerry,
don't let's ask for the moon.
We have the stars!
Lovely!
Mmm!
Could it be Paul Henreid and Bette Davis
in Now, Voyager?
- Oh, fucking hell!
- It is famous, you ignorant little tarts!
- But we never heard of it, sir!
- Walt Whitman, Leaves of Grass.
"The untold want,
by life and land ne'er granted...
Now, voyager, sail thou forth
to seek and find. "
Fifty "p," please.
Ah, Rudge.
- There's nothing on the Carry On films.
- Why? Should there be?
The exam.
Mr. Irwin said the Carry Ons
would be good films to talk about.
How peculiar.
Does he like them, do you think?
Probably not.
You never know with him.
I'm now wondering if there's
something there that I've missed.
Well, Mr. Irwin says that...
"Whilst they have
no intrinsic artistic merit, they-
"they achieve
some of the permanence of art...
"simply by persisting...
and acquire incremental significance
if only as social history. "
Dear me.
What fun you must all have.
It's not like your stuff, miss.
It's cuttin' edge. It really is.
Where do you live, sir?
- Portsmouth.
- That's not far from Mr. Hector, sir.
He might even give you a lift
if you ask him.
It's not a loft, is it, sir?
Do you exist on an unhealthy diet
of take-away food, sir...
or do you whisk up
gourmet meals for one?
- Or is it a lonely pizza, sir?
- I manage.
- No questions from you, Dakin?
- What they want to know, sir, is, do you have a life?
Or are we it? Are we your life?
It's pretty dismal if you are,
'cause these are as dreary as ever.!
You get a question, you know the answer,
but then so does everybody else.
So say something different.
Say the opposite.
Okay, look, take Stalin.
He's generally agreed to be
a monster, and rightly.
So dissent.
Find something, anything,
and say it in his defense.
A question is about what you know.
It's not about what you don't know.
A question about Rembrandt,
for instance...
might prompt an answer on Degas.
Is Degas an old master?
About suffering, they were
never wrong, sir, the old masters.
How it takes place while someone's
eating or openin' a window.
- Have you done that with Mr. Hector?
- Done what, sir?
The poem. You're quoting somebody.
Auden, isn't it?
Was it, sir?
Sometimes it just flows out,
you know, brims over.
- Does he have a program, or is it just at random?
- It's just knowledge, sir.
The pursuit of it
for its own sake, sir.
Breaking bread with the dead, sir.
That's what we do.
- It's higher than your stuff. It's nobler.
- Only not useful.
- Mr. Hector's not as focused.
- No, he's blurred, sir.
And we know
what we're doing with you, sir.
Half the time with him
we don't know what we're doing at all.
- We're poor little sheep that have lost our way, sir.
- Sit down.
Where are we, sir?
You're very young, sir.
This isn't your gap year, is it, sir?
I wish it was.
Why, sir? Do you not like teaching us?
We're notjust a hiccup between the end
of university and the beginning oflife...
like Auden, are we, sir?
- Do you like Auden's poetry, sir?
- Some, yeah.
Mr. Hector does.
We know about Auden.
Oh, yes.
- He was a schoolmaster for a bit.
- I believe he was.
Yeah, he was.
Do you think he was more like you
or more like Mr. Hector?
I have no idea.
Why should he be like either of us?
Oh, I think he was more like Mr. Hector-
bit of a shambles.
He snogged his pupils.
Auden, sir. Not Mr. Hector.
So you could answer a question
on Auden then.
No, sir.!
Mr. Hector's stuff's not meant for the exam!
It's to make us
more rounded human beings.
Listen, this examination is going to be about
everything and anything you know and are.
If there's a question on Auden,
or whoever...
and you know about it, answer it!
We couldn't do that, sir.
That would be a betrayal of trust.
Yeah! Is nothing sacred, sir?
We're shocked!
I would, sir, and they would.
They're taking the piss.
"England, you've been here too long...
"and the songs you sing
are the songs you sung on a braver day.
Now they are wrong. "
- Who's that?
- Oh, Mr. Irwin!
Don't you know, sir? It's Stevie Smith
of"Not Waving but Drowning" fame.
Well, don't tell me
that's useless knowledge.
Listen, if you get an essay
on post-imperial decline...
losing an empire, finding a role,
all that kind of stuff...
a gobbet like that,
it's the perfect way to end it.
A what, sir?
A gobbet.
A quotation.
How much more stuff like this
have you got up your sleeves?
- We've got all sorts. Hey! The train, the train!
- Whoo!
I really meant to do it.
I stood there trembling,
right on the edge.
But I couldn't.
I wasn't brave enough.
I should like to be able to say it was the thought
of you and the children that prevented me...
but it wasn't.
I had no thoughts at all...
only an overwhelming desire not
to feel anything at all ever again...
not to be unhappy anymore.
I went back into the refreshment room.
That's when I nearly fainted.
- What is all
this? - Shh! - Shh.
Laura?
Yes, dear?
Whatever your dream was...
it wasn't a very happy one, was it?
No.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Fred, you always help.
You've been a long way away.
Thank you for coming back to me.
God knows why you've learned
Brief Encounter.
I think you ought to know this lesson's
been a complete waste of time.
Oh, a bit like
Mr. Hector's lessons then, sir.
They're a complete waste of time too.
Yeah, you little smart-ass, but he's not
trying to get you through an exam.
- French Kiss?
- I beg your pardon.
Newmarket, 3:00.
- Dorothy?
- Thank you, Stanley.
So, how are you finding them?
You've taught them too well.
They can't see it's a game.
- History? Is it a game?
- For an exam like this, yeah.
Dorothy.
Oh, fuck.
- Dorothy.
- Headmaster.
- I called him "the awful warning. "
- Who, Felix?
If you don't watch out,
he's what you turn into.
If this was a 1940s film...
he'd be played by Raymond Huntley.
Who? Uh-
He made a speciality of sour-faced judges
and vinegary schoolmasters.
Who would I be played by?
- Dirk Bogarde?
- I'm not sure I like that.
- Dorothy.
- Watch out.
Ah, Hector! The very man.
- Chin up, Rudge.
- Hello!
Mrs. Lintott.
Our lord and master having grudgingly
conceded that art may have its uses...
I gather I'm supposed to give your Oxford and
Cambridge boys a smattering of art history.
Not my bag, Hazel.
Irwin's your man.
It's really just the icing on the cake.
Is art ever anything else?
Michelangelo.
Well...
I suppose.
Who have you got?
- Both nancys.
- Are they?
These aren't women.
They're just men with tits.
And the tits look as if they've been
put on with an ice cream scoop.
Do you like Turner, then?
All right.
Well, choose someone you do like.
Art's meant to be enjoyed.
In the long term, miss, maybe...
but with us enjoyment
don't come into it.
We ain't got time to read the books,
we ain't got time to look at the pictures.
What we really need
is lessons in acting.
That's what this whole
scholarship thing is- an acting job.
- So, have the boys given you a nickname?
- Not that I'm aware of.
A nickname is an achievement...
both in the sense of something won...
and also in its armorial sense...
of a badge, a blazon.
Unsurprisingly, I am Tot.
Or Totty.
Some irony there, one feels.
- Hector has no nickname.
- Yes, he has- Hector.
- But he's called Hector.
- That's his nickname too.
He isn't called Hector.
His name's Douglas.
Though the only person
I've ever heard address him as such...
is his somewhat unexpected wife.
Posner came to see me yesterday.
He has a problem.
No nicknames.
At least you get their problems.
I seldom do.
Sir, I think I may be homosexual.
I love Dakin.
- Does Dakin know?
- Yes.
And doesn't think it's surprising.
Though Dakin likes girls, basically.
I sympathized.
Though not so much as to suggest
I might be in the same boat.
With Dakin?
With anybody.
That's sensible.
One of the hardest things for boys to learn
is that a teacher is human.
One of the hardest things for a teacher
to learn is not to try and tell them.
Is it a phase, sir?
Do you think it's a phase?
Some of the literature
says it will pass.
I'm not sure I want it to pass.
But I want to get into Oxford.
If I do, Dakin might love me.
Or I might stop caring.
Do you look at your life, sir?
I thought everybody did.
I'm a Jew...
I'm small...
I'm homosexual...
and I live in Sheffield.
I'm fucked.
So, with all this religion,
what do you do?
Go to church, pray.
Yes?
It's so time-consuming.
You've no idea.
Yeah? What else?
Well-
it's what you don't do.
You don't not wank.
- Jesus, you're headed for the bin.
- It's not forever.
Well, just tell me on the big day
and I'll stand well back.
See, what bothers me is,
the more you read...
the more you see that literature
is actually about losers.
- No!
- Yeah.
It's consolation.
All literature is consolation.
I don't care what Hector says.
I find literature really lowering.
This is Irwin, isn't it?
A line of stuff for the exam.
No.
Well, it isn't wholly my idea.
- I've been reading this book by "Kneeshaw. "
- Who?
Kneeshaw.
He's a philosopher.
Friedrich Kneeshaw.
I think that's pronounced Nietzsche.
Oh, shit.
- Shit.
- What's the matter?
I talked to Irwin about it.
He didn't correct me.
He let me call him Kneeshaw.
Think I'm a right fool. Shit!
- What have I done?
- Nothing.
You've done nothing.
The world doesn't revolve
around you, you know.
Ah, Irwin!
How are our young men doing?
Are they... on stream?
I think so.
Wh-You think so?
Are they or aren't they?
It must always be
something of a lottery.
A lottery? I don't like
the sound of that, Irwin.
I don't want you to fuck up. We've been
down that road too many times before.
Oi!
He's coming.
They took the lead off the roofs...
they used the timbers to melt it down,
and time did the rest.
And all thanks to Henry VIII.
If you want to learn about Stalin,
study Henry VIII.
If you want to learn about Mrs. Thatcher,
While you and Dorothy are taking them
through the history, I'll pitch camp here.
Though, Irwin,
I am constantly available...
for the provision
of useful quotations-
sorry- gobbets on request.
"Bare ruined choirs...
where late the sweet birds sang. "
Remember, boys...
festoon your answers with gobbets
and you won't go very far wrong.
Actually, singing was the least of it.
The monks were farmers,
clothiers, tanners, tailors.
They mined for lead.
They were captains of industry.
- This was a toilet, sir.
- One of them.
- A bit drafty on the bum.
- That was the drain down there.
And then they drank out of it.
- Fucking Christians.
- What about the Ganges? You're just as bad.
- I'm Muslim, knob.
- Ah, you all look alike to me anyway.
So, what was this then? Chapel?
No. It was a storeroom. A barn.
All the produce would come in here.
You know it all, don't you?
- It interests me.
- No, that's good.
It's good.
All-male community, was it, sir?
Of course. They were monks.
Bit of that, do you think?
- What?
- Same-sex stuff?
You've blushed, sir.
Have a fuck! "Blushed. "
- Sir! This is consecrated ground.
- Not to me, sir.
To me, it's a pagan temple.
Only you did blush a bit, sir.
So that's why Henry VllI put the boot in, sir?
'Cause of them bunking up?
- That's what he said.
- There was not much else for them to do, was there?
I mean, in their time off.
- Pray?
- Hey, Posner'd make a good monk.
'Cept he's Jewish.
- DoJews have monks?
- Yes. I'm one now.
In your own time, sir.!
Pass the parcel.
That's sometimes all you can do.
Take it...
feel it and pass it on.
Not for me. Not for you.
But for someone...
somewhere one day.
Pass it on, boys.
That's the game I want you to learn.
Pass it on.
Hector?
A word.
Uh, this is not the first time,
apparently.
But on this occasion, she managed
to make a note of the number.
Uh, f-for the moment,
I propose to say nothing about this.
But fortunately, it's not long
before you're due to retire.
In the circumstances, I propose
that we bring that forward.
I think we should be looking
at the end of term.
Have you nothing to say?
"The tree of man was never quiet:
Then 'twas the Roman, now 'tis I."
This is no time for poetry.
Um, I'm assuming
your wife doesn't know.
I've no idea.
What women know or don't know
has always been a mystery to me.
And are you going to tell her?
I don't know.
I'm not sure she'd be interested.
Well, um, there's another thing.
Strange how even
the most tragic turn of events...
generally resolve themselves
into questions about the timetable.
Irwin's been badgering me
for more lessons.
In the circumstances,
a concession might be in order.
- In future, I think you and he might share.
- Share?
Share!
In the meantime,
you must consider your position.
I do not want to sack you.
People talk.
And it's so... untidy.
It would be easier for all concerned...
if you retired early.
Look, nothing happened.
A hand on a boy's genitals
at 50 miles an hour...
and you call it nothing?
The transmission of knowledge
is, in itself, an erotic act.
- In the Renaissance, for instance-
- Fuck the Renaissance!
And fuck literature and Plato...
and Michelangelo
and Oscar Wilde...
and all the other shrunken violets...
you people line up!
This is a school...
and it isn't normal.
- Still here?
- It is Wednesday, sir.
Yes, but I thought with the day trip
to Fountains and, uh-
It's only half past 4:00.
Well, in that case, where's Dakin?
With Mr. Irwin, sir.
Ah.
Of course.
He's showing him
some old exam questions.
Ah. With all the appropriate
gobbets, no doubt.
Well, no matter.
We must keep up the fight
without him.
- What have we learned this week?
- "Drummer Hodge," sir. Hardy.
Ah. Nice.
"They throw in Drummer Hodge,
to rest...
"uncoffined, just as found:
"His landmark is a kopje-crest...
"which breaks the veld around;
"and foreign constellations west
each night above his mound.
"Young Hodge the Drummer
never knew-
"fresh from his Wessex home-
"the meaning of the broad Karoo...
"the Bush, the dusty loam...
"and why uprose to nightly view...
"strange stars amid the gloam.
"Yet portion of that unknown plain...
"will Hodge forever be;
"His homely Northern
breast and brain...
"grow to some Southern tree...
"and strange-eyed
constellations reign...
his stars eternally. "
Good.
Very good.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org