Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Come. Follow me.
Obey him!
- There may be a bit of a scar, Sam.
- I don't care.
Now it is your turn, Frodo.
I'm all right. What does it matter now?
It matters. We still have a long road,
and much to do.
Why? We've no hope without Gandalf.
You know that, Aragorn.
Then we must do without hope.
There is always vengeance.
Mithril shirt!
That's what saved you.
I have never seen one so beautiful.
- There!
- What is it?
The footsteps,
I heard them in Moria, following.
The Orcs will not come after us until dark.
It never sounds like an Orc.
They're bare feet and they flap.
Whatever creature it is,
it won't follow us where we're going.
Nothing evil passes through Lothlorien.
- That is not what we say in Gondor.
- Then you know nothing in Gondor.
Out of Moria into the Golden Wood.
Is there no way less perilous?
I would almost rather face
the Balrog again, than the Lady.
Lothlorien is a place of healing.
There is no evil in it...
...unless a man brings evil there with him.
Welcome to Lothlorien.
I am Galadriel
and this is my lord, Celeborn.
The forests have told us of your loss.
We sorrow for you,
and for all of Middle-earth.
Rest here now for a little,
until you are healed.
Your quest is known to us.
We will do what we can to aid you.
Frodo Baggins of the Shire?
'"Let the night never cease to call you
'"Let the day never more be the same'"
It is a song about Gandalf, isn't it?
Yes, Mithrandir
was the Elves' name for him.
It means, Grey Pilgrim.
We knew so little of him in the Shire,
Aragorn. He was just Gandalf, to us.
We never knew he had so many names.
I think he was fondest of Gandalf.
'"We 're still guided by your light
'"You're walking beside us
'"A prayer in the night
'"With the fear rushing thru the shadows
'"Like a star shining deep in his heart
'"You will know in your hearts forever
'"Never more
'"Will we stand
'"Alone'"
This is the mirror of Galadriel.
It shows things that were,
and things that are...
...and things that yet may be.
Do you wish to look?
I'd not mind a glimpse
of what's going on at home.
It seems a terrible long time
I've been away.
Come then, you shall look...
...and see what you may.
I got to go home!
They've dug up Bagshot Row...
...and thrown my poor old Gaffer
out in the street. I've got to go home.
The mirror shows many things, Sam,
and not all have yet come to pass.
Some never come to be,
unless those that behold the visions...
...turn aside from their path
to prevent them.
Do you wish to leave Frodo now,
and go home?
No.
Gandalf?
No, it must be Saruman.
Do not touch the water.
He is looking for you.
But he cannot find you, not here, not yet.
The door is closed.
Three Rings for the Elven-kings
under the sky.
Yes.
We hid those three from him,
and he has never touched them.
If your quest fails...
...then nothing can stand against him
and we are defenseless.
Yet, if you succeed,
if the One Ring is destroyed...
...all we built with the three will fade.
Time will come here,
and Lothlorien will fade.
You are the footstep of doom to us, Frodo.
Lady Galadriel, I will give you
the One Ring, if you ask for it.
It's too great a matter for me.
And I came to test your heart.
You will give me the Great Ring freely...
...and in place of the Dark Lord
you will set up a queen.
And I shall not be evil, but beautiful...
...and terrible as the morning
and the night.
Stronger than the foundations of the earth.
All shall love me and despair!
I pass the test.
I will diminish and go into the west
and remain Galadriel.
And you must depart in the morning.
For Gondor and the House of Isildur.
For Gondor and the city of Minas Tirith.
In a few days, we will have to choose:
Shall we turn west with Boromir
and go to the wars of Gondor...
...or turn east to Mordor and its Dark Lord?
Or shall we break our fellowship?
I'm going with Mr. Frodo.
I know that, Sam.
What a place. What a horrible place!
Behold the Argonath,
the pillars of the kings.
They are Isildur and Anarion,
my fathers of old.
If Gandalf were here...
The day has come at last, the day
of choice, which we have long delayed.
What shall now become of our company?
I am not Gandalf.
I have tried to guide you
as he would've done, but...
...if he had any plan for this moment,
he never told me.
Even if he had, if he had lived...
...I think the burden
would still have fallen on you, Frodo.
You alone can choose your way now.
The burden is heavy.
Give me an hour longer, and I will speak.
Let me be alone!
You shall have your hour.
And you shall be alone.
Who's there?
Boromir.
I was afraid for you, Frodo.
The Orcs may be on this side
of the river by now.
May I stay and talk to you, just for a while?
You're kind, but there's nothing to be said.
I know what I should do,
but I'm afraid of doing it, Boromir.
I wish I could help you.
Will you hear my counsel?
I know what your advice would be:
To go with you to Gondor
and use the Ring to defend Minas Tirith.
And is that such ill counsel?
Why should we fear to use the Ring
in a just cause?
Whatever is done with the Ring
turns to evil.
Gandalf and Elrond refused to touch it,
and Galadriel herself...
Yes, I know all that.
And for themselves, they may be right,
these Elves and half-Elves and Wizards!
But truehearted Men will not be corrupted.
We, of Minas Tirith, do not seek power.
Only the strength to defend ourselves.
Where is the evil in that, Frodo?
You cannot answer me, none of them can.
It's folly not using the Enemy's power
against him.
Think what Aragorn could do
with the Ring in this hour.
Or if he refuses, why not Boromir?
How I would drive the hosts of Mordor,
until I stood face to face with Sauron.
And they tell us to throw it away!
Come with me, Frodo.
My city is not far.
You can go to Mordor from there,
if you must.
Only, trust me, let me try my plan.
Lend me the Ring.
No, Boromir. No!
Fool, obstinate fool!
It is only yours by chance.
It might have been mine.
It should be mine. Give it to me!
Miserable trickster!
You'll sell us all to Sauron.
Traitor!
Curse you to death and darkness,
all you Halflings!
What have I done?
Frodo, come back!
A madness took me, but it has passed.
Come back!
This waiting's horrible.
Where have you been, Boromir?
Have you seen Frodo?
I tried to convince him
to come to Minas Tirith.
I grew angry and he vanished.
Is that all you have to say?
He put the Ring on.
But where did he go? Where is he?
Mr. Frodo!
Gimli, Legolas, stop them!
I don't know what part you've played
in this mischief, but help now!
Go after Merry and Pippin and guard them,
even if you cannot find Frodo. Go on!
Follow me, Sam. Stay close.
Sam Gamgee, your legs are too short,
so use your head.
The boats.
Coming, Mr. Frodo.
Coming!
It's only water, now.
I'm here, Sam.
Save me, Mr. Frodo.
Help, I'm drowning!
- Take my hand.
- Where's your hand?
Here. Here it is.
Of all the confounded nuisances
I ever knew.
Mr. Frodo, that's hard.
If I hadn't guessed right,
where would you be now?
Safely on my way.
"Safely"?
All alone and without me to help you?
But I am going to Mordor.
Well, of course you are,
Mr. Frodo, and I'm coming with you.
It's no good trying to escape you.
I'm glad, Sam.
May the others find a safe road.
Aragorn will look after them.
I don't suppose we shall see them again.
Yet we may, Mr. Frodo. We may.
This way!
Frodo!
Halfling.
Boromir.
I tried to take the Ring from Frodo.
I'm sorry. I have paid.
Aragorn, go to Minas Tirith.
Save my people.
Aragorn...
I will go...
...I promise you.
The Halflings, Orcs took them.
I think they are not dead.
Either we take the last boat
and follow Frodo...
...or we follow the Orcs on foot.
Pippin and Merry may be dead by now.
We don't know.
We cannot forsake them.
The fate of the Ring-bearer
is in my hands no longer.
The company of the Ring
has played its part.
We follow the Orcs.
Filth!
Maggots!
Can't run.
Hello, Pippin.
So you've come on this expedition, too?
When do we get bed and breakfast?
Bed and breakfast in Isengard, understand?
They are alive.
One of them, anyway.
Pippin, I think, by the footprints.
How far ahead of us are they, Aragorn?
Almost a day. Shall we rest by night,
or go on while our strength holds?
Do you think the Orcs will rest?
Yet, in the dark we may lose the trail,
or miss a sign, like that brooch.
There will be no more signs.
I cannot run all the way to Isengard.
Thank goodness for that rope
the Elves gave you.
We'd never have gotten down
that last cliff without it.
There's Mount Doom again, Mr. Frodo.
See it?
What a fix!
The one place
that we don't want to see any closer...
...and that's the one place
we're trying to get to.
We're plain lost, Mr. Frodo.
I'm tired, Sam.
I don't know what's to be done.
We must find a place to camp, I suppose.
Maybe there'll be a path tomorrow.
Cautious, my precious.
Don't turn!
It's him.
That Gollum?
That thing who had Mr. Bilbo's ring?
He's been following us since Moria.
My precious! More haste, less speed.
Well, he'll be sorry he found us again.
Be careful!
He's much more dangerous than he looks.
Where is it, my precious?
It's ours, it is, and we wants it.
Got you, you spying...
Let go, Gollum!
Let go, or I'll cut your throat!
Don't hurt us!
Don't let them hurt us, precious.
Cruel little Hobbitses.
Jumps on us
like cats on poor mices, Gollum.
We'll be nice to them if they'll be nice
to us, won't we, precious?
Pity Mr. Bilbo didn't kill the creature
when he had the chance.
I will not touch him.
Now that I see him, I do pity him.
Yes, Hobbits won't kill us,
not Hobbits, huh?
No, we won't.
But we won't let you go, either.
You will have to come with us
and help us, if you can.
Yes, indeed!
Nice Hobbits!
And where are they going in these cold,
hard lands, we wonder?
We are going to Mordor. You know that.
Lead us to the gates of his land.
No, precious.
Hobbits mustn't go there.
Gollum! Leave us alone!
Gotcha!
I think your rope might prove useful again.
Tie one end to his ankle.
We want him to walk.
Don't hurt us! No!
It burns! It bites!
It freezes!
Take it off us. It hurts us.
Don't you do it!
It hurts us.
What promise can you give me
that I can trust?
Smeagol will be very good.
Smeagol will swear
never to let him have it.
Smeagol will save it.
The precious is before you, Smeagol.
Speak your promise!
We promises, yes, I promise...
...I will serve the master of the precious.
Good master, good Smeagol.
Take the rope off, Sam.
Off we go. Follow Smeagol.
Smeagol knows a secret way, he does,
across the marshes.
Follow Smeagol.
I said, "No shooting."
You're wasting arrows, dunghill swine!
Snaga, Lugdush, stand guard.
Bind their legs.
White-skins break through. Understand?
You and your stinking Wizard.
You got us into this.
When I tell them in Mordor...
They are far, far away.
If stinking Wizard doesn't get you,
the white-skins will.
You won't get it that way.
It isn't easy to find.
Get it? Get what?
Nothing, my precious.
It's no good groping in the dark.
Ugluk will be back any minute.
Nothing for Mordor.
Nothing for poor Grishnakh and Gollum.
- Untie us, my precious.
- I said to be quiet!
Wait. You can't find it without our help.
You help me?
I don't know what to do now.
I don't even know where we are.
You should have studied maps more
and played less in Rivendell.
This is Fangorn Forest.
Then we're no safer
than we were with the Orcs.
We've no blankets and almost no food.
It looks like nothing to eat for 100 miles.
We don't even know
where we're trying to go.
Let's climb up there.
Maybe we can find out
where we are, at least.
It's nice here.
The forest looks so different
in the sunlight.
I know.
It's funny, but, well,
I almost feel I like the place.
Almost felt you liked the forest?
That's uncommonly kind of you.
The Orcs made us run here,
and when we tired...
...they carried us, cut our ropes, ran into
the forest and we came to your hill...
"Hill?"
A hasty word...
...for something that has stood here
since the world was shaped.
You may call me Treebeard.
We thought you were a tree,
standing there.
Not a tree, a tree herder.
Please, Treebeard...
...now that you know our story...
...whose side are you on?
I am not altogether on anybody's side...
...because nobody is altogether on my side.
But I am no friend of these...
...tree-killing Orcs and their masters.
They were here, no doubt of it.
- But where they went?
- I don't understand these other marks.
Look!
Your bow, Legolas! It's Saruman.
Shoot before he puts a spell on us, fast!
Elf...
...Man and Dwarf together?
A rare sight in these times.
Stop him, Legolas!
Gandalf?
Beyond all hope.
Gandalf!
Yes.
That was my name.
But where have you... Gandalf!
What happened?
A long time I fell.
Long I fell and he fell with me.
His fire was about me.
I was burned.
Ever he clutched me, and ever
I hewed him, far under the living earth...
...until at last, he fled back
up the secret ways of Moria.
There we fought,
above the mists of the world...
...and the mountain was wreathed
with lightning.
I threw down my enemy
and his fall broke the mountainside.
Then darkness took me...
...and I wandered far,
on roads that I will not tell.
Naked, I was sent back for a brief time...
...until my task was done.
And it is time I was about it.
You come with me to Edoras, my friends,
to the city of the Riders?
To Edoras, now?
But to leave Merry and Pippin?
They are in no danger, believe me.
The great danger is to Edoras.
Saruman's Orcs will attack there within
two days, and Theoden has need of us.
Theoden has grown old.
He shivers by his fire now...
...and leaves everything in the hands
of his new minister:
Grima Wormtongue.
Those Riders you followed,
who rescued Merry and Pippin...
...they were led by Theoden's nephew,
Eomer.
He is all but an outlaw
in Rohan these days.
He hunts the Orcs
wherever he finds them...
...defying Wormtongue's orders
to let them pass.
So Wormtongue calls him traitor
and renegade...
...and Theoden believes...
Gandalf, the Riders of Rohan
are the bravest fighters I've ever knew...
...but they were never many.
If Saruman strikes now,
he'll overrun Edoras in a single night.
Our time is at hand.
Theoden's hundreds will face
your tens of thousands.
When all of Rohan, your ancient oppressor,
lies vanquished...
...then shall we fly eastward...
...and sweep all of Middle-earth
beneath our feet.
We cannot be defeated!
Halfway between Edoras and Isengard,
there lies a fortress called Helm's Deep.
If we can decoy Saruman's Orcs there...
...the fortress will stop them longer
than the wooden halls of Edoras.
We are buying time, Aragorn.
Time? Time for what?
Perhaps for a miracle.
Perhaps only for Frodo
to get a little further on his way...
...while the armies
that should be hunting for the Ring...
...waste their own time destroying us.
I have returned.
The storm comes swiftly, and it is time
for all friends to gather together.
And do you...
...expect me to welcome you here...
...Master Gandalf?
Troubles follow you like crows.
Why should I welcome you,
Gandalf Stormcrow?
Justly spoken, Lord.
In the east, the Dark Lord is stirring...
...in Lorien, the Sorceress
of the Golden Wood weaves deceit.
And such is the hour
in which this wanderer chooses to return.
It is I who counsel the King now.
He hears you no longer.
No, Grima Wormtongue.
He hears nothing but your voice
telling him that he rules here...
...only because Saruman
is kind to old men...
...and that the best thing for a sickly,
feeble king...
...is to let Wizards and Orcs
do as they will in Rohan.
I am my own man, Gandalf...
...as I was.
It is true that...
...Grima advises me often
to leave Aruman in peace...
Hear, my Lord, you tire yourself.
You are still unwell.
And he does remind me
that it would be safest for Rohan...
...to seek their friendship...
...no matter how I may feel!
Dear Lord, let me deal with
these troublesome guests.
How long has it been, Grima Wormtongue?
How long since Saruman bought you?
For I saw you at Isengard.
Did I not counsel your doorkeeper
to forbid his staff?
Down, snake.
Down on your belly.
Grima is often...
...at Isengard.
I sent him there with messages.
And he returns with poison...
...Aruman's poison in your ears, Theoden.
Chilling your heart, making you old.
Take courage, Lord of Rohan!
Grima...
...is this so?
I will not harm you, Grima.
Is it so?
Let him go!
My sister-daughter, Eowyn.
My only loyal kin...
...since her brother has disobeyed
my commands.
Wormtongue's command, Theoden.
If Eomer had not defied him,
their cause might be already lost.
Tell me, Gandalf...
...what I must do now.
We cannot wait here for Saruman's attack.
Every man that can ride
must be sent immediately...
...to the old fortress of Helm's Deep.
When Saruman learns
that we have gone there...
...and he will...
...we will have the Riders of Rohan.
I will find Eomer and his Riders.
My armor!
Look for me at Helm's Deep.
That's all, Theoden.
And he's gone again...
...like a wind in the grass.
Stormcrow.
- Aragorn?
- My Lord?
Is there any hope for us?
Sam, you simpleminded...
You fell asleep.
Mr. Frodo, he's gone.
- Smeagol?
- He's gone. I didn't mean to sleep.
Well, he'll come back.
Promise will hold him a while yet.
He won't leave his precious, anyway.
Are we rested?
Ready to go on?
Nice Hobbitses.
Trust Smeagol now?
Stop!
Shivery light.
Nasty.
Look!
Wraiths!
Wraiths on wings!
The precious is calling them!
Gollum, wait, Mr. Frodo can't keep up!
Slow down, I tell you.
No time, no time.
The precious is heavy, yes.
Very heavy, Smeagol knows.
If it's too heavy for nice Master...
...little Smeagol will carry it.
Smeagol doesn't mind.
Give it to Smeagol.
Do not say that again.
Do not think it.
Before you touched the precious again,
Smeagol...
...I would put it on and have you
leap off a cliff, or into a fire...
...and you would do it, Smeagol.
Nice, Master.
Gollum!
Smeagol promised.
Yes, we promised to save our precious,
never to let him have it...
...but it's going to him...
...my precious is nearer every step.
I can't help it.
Smeagol promised to help nice Hobbit.
He took cruel rope off our leg.
He speaks nicely to me.
He's a Baggins, my precious.
A Baggins stoled it.
We hates Bagginses.
Must have the precious. Must have it.
We wants it.
But there's two of them.
Yes.
We needs help, precious.
She might help, yes.
She might help us...
...but Smeagol promised nice Hobbit.
Nice Hobbit.
Hey, you...
...what are you pawing at him for?
Where've you been anyway,
sneaking off and sneaking back?
"Sneaking?"
Hobbit's always so polite, yes.
Tired, thirsty Smeagol, he finds
a secret way through the mountain...
...a tunnel with no Orcses anywhere,
and they say "sneak."
"Sneak?"
Well, you startled me. I'm sorry.
Hello, Smeagol.
- Where have you been?
- Sneaking!
I like this place.
There is good rock here.
This country has tough bones.
Up on the ridge! They're coming!
There they are!
Fire of Isengard!
We're breached! Retreat to the caves!
The caves!
Theoden King.
I will not end here...
...taken like an old badger in a trap.
When dawn comes...
...I will bid men sound Helm's horn...
...and I will ride forth.
Will you ride with me then,
son of Arathorn?
At least, we may make such an end...
...as will be worth a song.
I will ride with you.
We're there, Sam.
Another day, maybe two.
When light comes tomorrow,
the mountains will be near.
Well, it's a good thing, Mr. Frodo,
because we're running awful low on food.
I reckon we've got enough left
to see us to this Mount Doom.
After that...
...I don't know.
Samwise Gamgee.
My dearest Hobbit...
...friend of friends...
..."after that," if the Ring goes
into the fire, and we are at hand?
"After that," dear Sam.
I wouldn't worry.
Just to get there.
The Ring is so heavy now, Sam.
We must go.
Mustn't rest here, silly Hobbits.
Orcs find us. Ring wraiths find us.
Must go on to safe, secret place.
Smeagol's secret way!
The straight stair...
...and the winding stair.
Up, up...
...through black, sharp mountains.
Follow good Smeagol.
Straight stair, winding stair?
What comes after that?
We shall see, yes...
...we shall see.
Gandalf!
The forces of darkness were driven
forever from the face of Middle-earth...
...by the valiant friends of Frodo.
As their gallant battle ended...
...so too ends the first great tale of...
...The Lord of the Rings.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org