Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Where you headed, little lady?
Nowhere with you, numb nuts.
Buzz off!
See you Thursday, gorgeous!
It's a pretty day to hitchhike.
I've got a little VW
at Stinson Beach with a cracked block.
You wouldn't be going
to Mill Valley, would you?
Aren't we going to Mill Valley?
Got a couple bottles of
ice-cold beer up there.
You son of a bitch.
Okay, pile in!
How long you been with
Western Gas and Electric?
I can't remember how long.
How long I been in this?
Turn in here.
Climb up this road here.
I'll be right with you.
Hang a left here, Harry,
there's a jam on Bay.
What's with the citizen?
-Police officer, what's the problem?
-Thank God! He's inside!
Come on, it's a heart attack!
Wait here.
Make some room! Move aside!
Move aside.
This is an emergency!
Please move over!
Please give us room.
He's a police officer.
-Where's the ambulance?
-He had a heart attack.
He's still breathing, though.
Come on, get up.
Get up!
Get up, get up!
I say!
-Party's over.
-Thanks a lot, Harry.
Why are you squawking?
You got the free meal.
But I always enjoy
the ride in the ambulance.
Get out of here.
Harry, it's an all-units.
Marvelous.
My old lady will kill me.
She's doing a novena tonight
and I said I'd be home for supper.
Suspects are armed.
Code 33.
Inspector 71 responding to your 406.
What's going on?
Bastards held up that liquor store.
One of our guys stumbled in
and they shot him.
They have four hostages.
They'll shoot them
unless we give them a car.
What're you waiting on?
Lieutenant Brannigan.
He said to stall until he gets here.
-Don't let them kill me!
-We want the goddamn car right now!
Okay, but you get nothing
till I come and talk.
Lay your piece on that car's hood!
What about me? I'm your partner.
I move fast. I don't need
extra linguini holding me back.
You got a lot of class, Harry.
You get cute, I blow this nice lady
all over you. Let's go.
On the floor, motherfucker.
For God's sake, do like he says!
-This is my best jacket.
-Get on the floor, you son of a bitch!
Spreadeagle! Move it!
Get down there.
San Francisco's finest.
Mitch.
Roll him over.
He's clean.
Here's the story.
First, we want all the pigs
out of here.
Second, we want a car...
...with a police radio.
Deliver it right out there in front.
We're taking two hostages.
Both the women.
You don't do what I tell you,
we blow their fucking heads off.
-You got the picture?
-Yeah.
What are you waiting for?
Run, you jive-ass bastard.
-What do they want?
-They want a car.
What are you going to do?
Give them one.
You son of a bitch!
Why's a man crazy enough
to join the cops?
If you find out, you let me know.
$14,379.
-How's that?
-Want an itemized account?
You took out two doors,
one window, 12 feet of counter...
...plus damages to the stock.
Plus one city vehicle totaled.
And three hostages in the hospital
who will probably sue the city.
-Why?
-Excessive use of force.
For your information, Callahan...
...the minority community
hates this kind of police work.
By "minority community"
you mean the hoods?
So happens they're
American citizens too.
-The lady with the gun by her ear?
-I'm not debating this.
I've spoken to the mayor twice!
He went through the ceiling!
You mention the meeting?
-What?
-The meeting two months ago...
...when you said priority was
to run the hoods out.
Not with violence!
Should I yell "trick-or-treat"?
Come on.
I expect you
and everyone on this force...
...to be restrained
or turn in his resignation.
You're on notice, Harry.
That wild west show of yours
is exactly what...
...this department's
not going to tolerate!
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
-lf that's all, I've work to do.
-Not in homicide.
What?
You're transferred to personnel.
To personnel? That's for assholes.
I was in personnel for ten years.
Yeah.
That's it!
Report tomorrow to the oral
examining board, 9:00!
No, you haven't got the picture.
I'm the robber, you're the cop.
Now, I'm in a market.
You've just caught me.
A 211 in the act.
I'm coming out with a hostage:
A kid with a gun at his head.
There's no way to take me alive.
You have ten seconds to decide.
What do you do?
One...
-... two, three...
-You're under arrest.
-... four, five...
-Do something!
...six, seven.
Don't just stand there,
goddamn it, do something!
Bang, you're dead.
-You're late, Callahan.
-Sorry.
-Hello, Krause.
-Hi.
Okay, Bustanoby,
you'll be given your grade.
You were told 9:00.
We have 50 officers to test.
-For how many vacancies?
-Eight.
Five men and three women
promoted to inspector in this group.
-Three women?
-Do you object, inspector?
Now who might you be?
Ms. Grey, from the mayor's staff.
She's to monitor the exams.
-This is Inspector Callahan.
-Yes, I know something of him.
And I'd like to tell you...
...the mayor's plan is to bring
this department into...
...the mainstream of
twentieth-century thought.
How does he figure to do that?
For one thing...
...His Honor intends to...
...broaden participation
for women in the police force.
Well, that sounds very stylish.
He also said something about...
...winnowing the Neanderthals
out of the department.
Well, we better move along.
Next applicant.
-Officer Moore?
-Yes, sir.
This is the final stage
in the examination.
It's an informal test to measure
your ability to think on your feet.
Your reaction to stress, pressure.
Your ability to use the law
in a hypothetical situation.
Yes, sir.
How long on the force?
-Nine years.
-What department?
Mainly Personnel and Records.
-Personnel and Records.
-Yes, sir.
Have you any questions
for the applicant?
Questions...
How fast do you run the hundred?
Come on, you know
how this board functions.
All right, I'm sorry.
You know...
...if you're inspector under
the new guidelines...
...you might be out
riding in a police car.
Yes, sir, that's what I hope for.
Officer Moore, tell us about...
...your greatest felony arrest.
I've never made a felony arrest.
Well, tell us about
your best misdemeanor arrest.
I've never made a
misdemeanor arrest either.
What gives you the right
to be an inspector...
...when men have been
working 15 years!
Women stay home,
is that what you're saying?
You think it's an encounter group?
What will she do
if someone points a gun...
...and says, "Hit the deck"?!
You're trying to fail
this candidate, aren't you?
If she fails there,
she gets her ass blown off!
It's my ass!
And my hard luck.
Out there you'll have a partner.
You get blown away, he does too!
That's some price to pay
for being stylish!
Are you finished with the questioning?
Hypothetical situation, huh?
I'm standing on a corner
and Mrs. Grey propositions me...
...saying for $5.00
she'll put on a show...
-... with a Shetland pony.
-lf this is your idea of humor...
All right, what are you doing here?
Seeing if you know
what law's being broken...
...besides cruelty to animals.
That's a conspiracy,
title 7-182-1...
...of the California penal code.
Conspiracy to commit a misdemeanor...
-... is a felony, and according to...
-Yes. Good answer.
Officer Moore,
you'll be given your grade.
After I get the guard's keys...
...we drive to the end,
warehouse 50-A. Lalo?
All right, now, that's...
...l drop you off at the small door
and go around...
...to the wharf side.
You open up the first big door.
I drive in and back up to
the compound on the right.
Karl and Tex?
Man, we grab
the M-16 automatic rifles.
Wanda?
Locate and take any explosives.
Dynamite, detonators, and plastics.
Right. Henry Lee?
I tote and load the ammo
for the M-16s, okay, man?
Miki?
Locate the L.A.W. rockets.
They'll be in the back.
It's the most important item.
You sure of the location?
I sweated there for five years!
They're there, I promise!
All right, you guys.
-This is for the people!
-Right on, for the people.
Jesus, spare me.
-What is it?
-Gas company.
-Why?
-Major gas leak in the area.
We'll check underground pipes.
Don't smoke until we say it's okay!
I won't, I won't.
It's seeping down in the earth.
This whole damn block could go!
-Got a phone I can use?
-Right this way.
Let's go.
Charlie left the gate open.
Better check it.
Tony, call backup.
-I'll check around.
-Frank, watch yourself.
L.A.W.S. rocket.
-Beautiful!
-Yes.
Lalo, get the rest of these loaded.
You'll blow us out of here!
You all right?
Let us get these.
Freeze.
Hold it right there!
Put those boxes down.
You back there.
Stand up so I can see you.
And drop that gun!
Put your hands over your head
and freeze!
-Now, wait a second.
-You shut up and listen.
You blink an eyelid
and I'll mail you home in a box!
All of you, against the fence!
Now!
You too, honey!
Oh, Jesus! Miki! Miki!
Oh, my God. Oh, Jesus.
Baby, I'll get you out.
I'll get you home.
Bobby, help get her up.
-You'll get us caught.
-No, we'll make it.
-She's dead.
-She's not dead!
The hell she isn't!
Come on, it's over.
Bobby.
Get it on there.
Lalo, get up in there! Come on!
Halt, police! Halt, or I'll fire!
I'll get this son of a bitch!
Goddamn it!
He said it looked like
a regular company truck.
I'm asking the
Marin County sheriff.
Might tie in with the two bodies
found there last week.
Yes, sir.
How's DiGeorgio?
Well, Irene's with him now.
Is that some kind of answer?
He's been given the last rites.
-Get what you can.
-l will.
Listen, I'm sorry.
Hello, Harry.
He's been asking for you.
How is he?
He's in and out.
I'll smoke a cigarette.
It's a war, isn't it?
I guess I never really
understood that.
Harry.
Frank, what happened?
I had them, dead bang. And then I...
Sorry.
Frank?
Something you want to tell him?
Harry, listen, the punk who cut me...
-... I seen him before.
-Where?
I just can't make the name.
Where do you know him from, Frank?
That homicide...
...young hooker...
...in the Fillmore area.
The summer of '71.
-What about it?
-He was one of the pimps questioned.
Liked him for it, Harry.
We liked him real good.
We liked everybody
north of Market on that one.
He had one of them cute,
little-boy names...
...Charlie something, or Bobby.
I'll check Records.
They'll have your notes.
Ten-to-one they blow it.
Not this time, Frank.
Maybe you better get some rest.
-Do you have to go just yet?
-Not if you don't want me to.
Thanks, Harry.
Get Irene.
-Talk to Records?
-Not yet. That was McKay.
We got a tape from the bastards.
I'll see you in 30 minutes.
Code Blue, Intensive Care.
30 minutes.
One million dollars
or we blow things up.
People's Revolutionary Strike Force.
Remember Fessenheim.
"Fessenheim"?
It's being checked.
People's Revolutionary Strike Force.
They on your list?
Nothing.
-Think it's legit?
-Probably not.
Lieutenant Bressler in Homicide.
What are you doing
about those records?
What do you mean?
I just talked to you about them!
Homicide! Fillmore District!
Inspectors Callahan and DiGeorgio.
What do you mean, "written request"?
Well, who's got the keys?
I'm coming down there
in five minutes...
...you get those files open,
you pencil-pushing son of a bitch!
-You don't have to make threats.
-I'm gonna nail the guy...
...who carved DiGeorgio
on my own time!
That's unnecessary...
...you're back in Homicide
since 9, didn't you know?
I've been down in Records
looking up a homicide.
Any luck?
Well, I've got eleven names
of known pimps.
-l think our man's one of them.
-Judson, Maddox, Skidmore.
Shall I tell you my instinct on this?
-Black Militants.
-No, it's all hookers.
The girl shot in the warehouse?
Miki Waleska.
A known prostitute.
What we've got is a
well-organized group of militants...
...with enough explosives to blow
San Francisco away...
-... including L.A.W.S. rockets.
-L.A.W.S. rockets?
The Army's giving a demonstration
at the firing range...
...in exactly 35 minutes.
I'd like everybody
on the case there...
...to see what you're against.
I've already been checked out
on the L.A.W.S. rocket.
Your partner hasn't.
My partner?
Shit!
You know Inspector Moore?
Inspector.
I'll see you at the firing range.
Inspector?
Inspector, I know you aren't
overjoyed by this assignment.
-You don't think I'm up to it, do you?
-Right.
All right...
...let's get one thing straight.
I'm a woman.
I consider that fact irrelevant...
...because I don't expect
any special consideration.
Marvelous.
The L.A.W.S. rocket: for all purposes...
...a one-shot disposable bazooka.
A fiberglass tube, 45 inches long...
...which fires a single projectile...
...designed to penetrate armor
three-quarters of an inch thick.
If you've all seen it,
I'll demonstrate how it works.
To fire the rocket, pull this pin...
...dropping the cover...
...then pull.
Front and rear sights spring up.
Got word from Pathology.
At noon they're posting the guard
that was killed. Check on it.
I'll be there.
-Captain?
-Go ahead.
Keep your eyes on that truck...
...l'll show how effective
this weapon can be.
Coming, inspector?
-lnspector?
-Yeah?
-13.5 in my gym shorts.
-What?
My time in the hundred.
You asked me before.
-Think I was picking on you?
-Yes.
-lt was nothing personal.
-Right.
I don't think you know
what Homicide does.
-I'll find out.
-l hope not the hard way.
How fast do you run the hundred?
Beats me.
I meant to say I'm sorry
about your partner.
He's not the first one.
Fanducci in '68 and Smith in '72,
but it wasn't your fault.
-How'd you know?
-Checked your records.
I don't want to get killed either.
What's the matter?
Black guy with the briefcase.
I know him.
-Tan suit?
-Yeah.
What did he do?
Can't remember. It's not important.
-Ever been to one of these before?
-No.
In that case, I'd suggest
you sit out here.
Don't concern yourself, inspector.
Hello, Harry.
Who's the pretty lady?
My partner, Inspector Moore.
-You missed most of it.
-We were at the firing range.
I have it on tape.
We finished the abdomen.
The wound matters.
The entry wound
was above the renal area...
...between ribs,
penetrating the chest cavity...
...piercing the lung.
There was also damage
to some other organs...
...pancreas, kidneys.
-What kind of knife?
-A long, heavy blade.
We're going in the skull now.
I'd say it was one of those
killing knives...
...a Marine Corps boy,
or Special Forces.
Bruises on the face?
The killer put his hand
over the mouth from behind.
-Professional?
-Textbook.
On first exam,
no exterior damage to the skull.
Subject brain shows no
contrecoup damage or clotting.
Jesus H. Christ, come look at this!
-lt's the damnedest thing I ever saw.
-What?
It says "Eat at Luigi's!"
Welcome to Homicide.
What are you doing?
Excuse me, I'm with him.
I was coming down the hall
to take a leak when it blew!
Anybody in there?
-l don't think so.
-Where you going?
A group of kids, some are missing.
-Help him out.
-Me?
Great, just step out here, will you?
Well, we were lucky this time.
It's getting so you can't
even pee in peace.
-We got them, they're okay.
-Good.
You didn't...
-... see anybody go in there, did you?
-No.
You sure? Black guy,
tan hat and suit, briefcase.
-l saw a guy like that.
-Short guy, about 5' 1 "?
No, this dude was six foot.
That's him.
It's a bomb. I saw who did it.
-Any idea?
-Looked familiar.
Just a minute.
You'd better check mug shots.
Honey, we're talking.
This is very important.
Better check mug shots,
we got another message.
They want two million.
-Two?
-l just saw him.
-Who?
-Tan suit, hat, and a briefcase.
-Where?
-Right down here.
-Why the hell didn't you tell me?
-Why the hell didn't you ask?
There he is, look!
Jesus!
Damn it.
What the hell's going on?
What are you doing here?
-Who are you?
-Police officer.
Speedy, you're under arrest.
God, this is a church!
What are you doing?
I'm a cop. He's under arrest.
Father, I did nothing!
This guy's rousting me!
Is it asking too much
to see a badge, officer?
He runs like a rabbit, I won't let go.
I'd like to see the badge now!
If you insist.
-Callahan, Inspector.
-Callahan...
...you're a disgrace to this city!
Okay! Nobody move!
Marvelous.
I think so.
Harry, wait, I'm talking to...
Jesus Christ!
Give him my best.
I'll call you back!
It's been disarmed
by the bomb squad.
It's the explosive from
the Hamilton Firearms works.
At times I can only
stand you as a human.
What about the punk?
-The suspect.
-"Suspect, " my ass!
He won't talk, but we have a make.
He's Henry Lee Caldwell.
Member of a Black Militant group
called Uhuru.
-Pusseau, shelve that.
-Uhuru?
It's run by a guy called
Big Ed Mustapha.
Mustapha, in the Mission District.
I thought he was familiar.
Where's my partner?
She's in the can.
Been there since she found out...
...she was packing this thing
all over San Francisco!
Do me a favor. Go easy on her.
It's her first day
and it's been a long one.
She wants to play lumberjack,
she has to handle her end of the log.
I give up. What's this?
The Fillmore chapter of the V.F.W.:
Very Few Whites.
Can I suggest you wait in the car,
inspector?
Don't concern yourself, inspector.
Well, if it ain't
Mighty Whitey and friend.
I'm looking for Big Ed Mustapha.
Sorry, honky, she can stay,
but you got to go.
Yeah, baby, we trying to keep up
standards, understand.
-You aren't making us welcome.
-You're welcome!
As welcome as a turd in a pool!
Well, look here, if it ain't the fuzz.
I'm looking for Ed Mustapha.
-You got a warrant, honky?
-What I got is Henry Lee Caldwell.
I never heard of him.
Let's see how fast you fuzz
can get your white asses out.
What is Henry Lee into now?
He's playing with dynamite.
You Mustapha?
Yeah, that's right.
Just come into my office here.
Just you.
Don't worry, pig,
she won't get lonesome.
That's mighty white of you.
Before we do anything uncalled-for...
...l'd like to point out
that I'm an officer.
Callahan.
Where do I know you from?
You don't.
I just know you.
Now, what's Henry Lee been up to?
Saying you don't know?
He don't come around here,
not for a long time.
Where is he?
He went white.
Why, he do something else foolish?
He and his friends helped
rip off the Hamilton Firearms.
I heard about that.
You wanna buy into that?
Four counts of murder,
aiding and abetting?
You got the wrong number, boy.
We don't deal in violence.
-What do you deal in?
-Waiting.
For what?
Waiting for all you honkies...
...to blow each other up
so we can move on in.
Talk about Henry Lee
and his friends.
Some dudes he met in Vietnam. Why?
Anybody on this list here grab you?
Hey, man, why should I help you?
I can talk to Robbery.
They'd be interested in this...
...elaborate furnishing.
What are you talking about?
"Room 401, Fairmont."
"Rest at the Holiday Inn."
Okay, okay, okay, so?
Maybe they're a little warm.
I tell you what...
...one of my boys got busted
on possession.
You get him off, and ignore
my interior decorator...
...and I'll see what I can do.
-That's a lot.
-You want a lot.
A thing like this can ruin my image.
I'll see what I can do.
What about the list?
Bobby Maxwell.
-He's the main man.
-You know him?
Stone waste of white.
Where can I find him?
I'll check around.
You do that. Much obliged.
Callahan, you're on the wrong side.
How do you figure that?
You put your ass on the line...
...for dudes who wouldn't
let you in the door any more...
...than they would me.
-lt's not for them.
-Who, then?
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org