Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Do you know the names
of any of her boyfriends?
What is it?
You can tell me.
Well,
I do remember,
before she split,
her and Lorna...
Mertz?
Yeah. Her and Lorna Mertz.
I mean I don't want to
tell any tales out of school
but I do remember them being
up on Hollywood Boulevard
speaking to this older woman.
And she,
she was wearing a mars suit
and had a mars short haircut.
But it was just that once.
Miss Saddon,
are you saying they
were talking to a lesbian?
(TRUCK HORN HONKING)
(WOMEN CHATTERING)
Your driver's here.
Yeah. I got to go.
We're not done yet.
Well, then,
how about you arrest me?
Because the truck don't wait!
Why don't we take
a look inside Lorna's bag,
and then maybe you can go.
SADDON: That's her.
Christ, she's 15.
Do you know what studios
Betty tested at?
They werert exactly studios.
MAN 1: Screen test,
Elizabeth Short.
MAN 2: So, where are you from?
Boston.
How long you've lived here?
Two years.
Lost your accent.
Yeah.
You know, when in Rome. Why?
Are you looking for a girl
with an accent?
No, no. That's all right.
Because I can just bring it
back like that.
Because I'm a whiz
with accents and I basically
do every accent in the world.
We don't really need
an accent, thank you.
'Cause I can be
from anywhere.
Okay.
Let's hear
that Boston accent.
Now?
Yes.
No, I can't do it now.
I would have to meet with
my dialect coach, Milton Perl,
who was introduced to me
by David Selznick.
You know
David O. Selznick?
I do.
He's been very,
very, very kind to me.
He's taken me out
to such beautiful dinners
in fancy restaurants.
And he's treated me
like a lady
and with respect
and guess what.
He was very, very,
very impressed
when I did my Scarlett
for him.
MAN 2: (LAUGHING)
You auditioned for
Scarlett O'Hara?
No, I didn't audition for
Gone With The Wind,
but, the thing is...
Gosh, I just love that movie
so much
that I decided
that I had to memorize
all of Scarlett's dialog.
Well...
And I want to do it for you
because I think
you're handsome.
No, no, I don't think
we need that...
But I think you're handsome
and I'm going to do it
for you right now.
"As God is my witness
"I will never go hungry again.
"Even if I have to lie
"or cheat
"or steal.
"I'll never go hungry again."
LEE: He hated her.
Bad, and he wanted
the whole world to know it.
Lee, you got to eat something.
Get this off the table!
God damn it!
Dwight,
you got to do something.
He's been like this
since last night.
Get some air.
I'll take care of him.
Bucky,
this ain't a random job.
He knew what he was doing
every single step of the way.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You learn anything
about our girl today?
Nothing won'th
you doing this to yourself.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
No, I'm staying here with her.
Come on.
Go learn something
about our girl!
(CARS HORNS HONKING)
WOMAN: Love
For sale
Advertising young love
for sale
Beverage Control?
LAPD Homicide.
Who got snuffed?
Seen either of them?
The Dahlia's a sister?
I don't know. You tell me.
Never seen her
except in the papers.
And the schoolgirl twist,
I've never seen.
We don't truck
with underage stuff, capisci?
Never seen her, man.
Don't fucking lie to me.
She's 15 fucking years old.
Come clean or I'll slap
a contributing beef on you
and you'll spend
the next five years
serving raisinjack
to bull dykes in Tehachapi.
A couple of times.
Two or three months ago.
She used to get drinks
off the sisters,
though, she liked boys.
I'm sure, man.
Not the Dahlia. Never.
For a trip to paradise
Love
For sale
Let the poets pipe of love
In their childish way
I know every type of love
Better far than they
If you want
the thrill of love
I've been through
Excuse me, ladies.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering
if you've seen this girl.
Have you?
No.
Everything but true love
Havert seen her.
This girl?
Advertising young love
For sale
If you want to try my wares
Come with me
and climb the stairs
Love
For sale
BUCKY: She wasrt the first
Dahlia wanna-be I'd seen
but she was the best.
Was she the les
that Betty and Lorna knew?
Or was she just some
rich bitch with a taste
for the low life?
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
I will not have these
in my house anymore.
No!
It is insane!
After everything
that's happened to us, Lee.
I will nail this guy, Kay!
LEE: I'll do this,
I will do this!
Talk to her, Bucky.
Reason with her.
Jesus.
Lee, she's right.
There's at least
three misdemeanors here.
You can't...
I promised him a week on this.
Four more days, and it's over.
Dwight, you can be
so gutless sometimes,
you know that?
BUCKY: Three days
since we killed four men.
Three days
until Bobby DeWitt got out.
I tried to tell myself
I was the sturdy leg
in our little triangle.
I was worried it was true.
Slumming, Miss Linscott?
I am now.
Daddy spying on me again?
"Maddy, girl,
you shouldn't
be congregating
"in such unsuitable places.' '
I'm a policeman.
That's a new one.
Homicide.
Let's try Elizabeth Short
and Lorna Mertz.
I know you knew them,
so don't jerk me off.
Otherwise, it's downtown
and a whole lot of publicity.
This is all a fluke.
I met them at LaVerne's
last fall.
Betty, maybe one time.
Lorna, a couple.
They'd come in
to cadge a drink
or a meal off a sister.
So why'd you rabbit
last night?
Mister,
my father is Emmett Linscott.
The Emmett Linscott?
He built half of Hollywood
and Long Beach.
Imagine the headlines,
"Construction Tycoors
Daughter Questioned
in Dahlia Case.
"Footsie
at Lesbian Nightclub.' '
Get the picture?
Technicolor.
So what'd you talk about?
When?
When you were playing footsie.
Lorna talked about her stupid
boyfriend back in Hicktown,
Nebraska, or wherever.
Betty talked about the latest
issue of Screen World.
Starlets, Hollywood dreams,
the whole sad nine yards.
So, did Betty ever tell you
about a movie she was in?
On a conversational level,
they were right up there
with you.
Cute. Answer the question.
Look, I'm tired.
Do you want my alibi
so I can go home?
Sure.
My family and I were in Laguna
from Sunday through Thursday,
along with the servants.
If you want verification,
call Daddy,
but please be discreet.
So,
what do I have to do to keep
my name out of the papers?
What do you mean?
That's not very convincing.
I don't need
your Daddy's money,
if that's what you're saying.
You know it's not
what I'm saying.
I might be convinced.
Tomorrow night, 8:00.
My address is 482
South Muirfield,
Hancock Park.
I know the address.
Not surprised.
Pick me up.
Like a gentleman,
not like a cop.
Oh, one more thing.
What's your name?
Bucky Bleichert.
Bucky?
I'll try to remember.
LEE: I can hear you just fine.
(PHONES RINGING)
Look, ma'am, you mind?
I've just learned to type.
Yes, I understand.
A werewolf and Red Sheridan.
What if the werewolf
is Red Sheridan?
Yes, that would be
more efficient.
I love tip duty.
How's Kay?
Not good.
You mind if I bunk out
at your pop's place
for a few days?
Sure.
Thanks.
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
DeWitt gets out tomorrow,
Lee.
I was thinking maybe
I should talk to him.
(RINGING)
Blanchard, Homicide.
Lee.
(RUMBLING)
MILLARD: All right, people,
let's get back to work here.
Yeah, it's an earthquake.
I heard it.
Look, I didn't know
you were a boxer.
Daddy's heard of you
and he insists
you stay for dinner.
I told him
we met at that art exhibit
at Stanley Rose's Book Shop.
So, if you have
to pump everybody
for my alibi, be subtle.
BUCKY: Who's this?
Balto.
The paper is the L.A. Times
for August 1, 1926.
Balto was bringing in
the paper
when Daddy found out
he made his first million.
He wanted to consecrate
the moment,
so he shot him.
Here we go.
Mother, Father,
this is my friend, Bucky.
Bucky, this is my mother,
Ramona Cathcan't Linscott.
BUCKY: Nice to meet you.
MADELEINE: My father,
Emmett Linscott.
BUCKY: Pleasure to meet you,
sir.
And my sister,
Martha McConville Linscott.
BUCKY: Hi.
Saw you fight Mondo Sanchez.
Boxed the pants off him.
Another Billy Conn
you might have been.
BUCKY: Thanks.
Can I get you something?
Sure.
I'll get it, Daddy.
Okay, darling.
Mondo gave a good show.
Whatever happened to him?
Heroin overdose.
Too bad.
He shamed his family.
And speaking of families,
Ramona, Martha.
That's our best Glenlivet,
laddie.
Madeleine says nice things
about you.
Daddy,
can we eat?
Bucky and I want
to catch a 9:30 show.
Of course, darling.
Dig in, lad.
Hearty fare breeds
hearty people.
Haute cuisine breeds
degenerates.
I want to draw
Mr. Bleichert, Daddy.
You're in for
a cruel caricaturing, Bucky.
Maddy's my pretty one,
but Martha's
my certified genius.
What kind of a name
is Bleichert? Dutch?
German.
A great people, the Germans.
Hitler was a bit excessive.
But mark my words
that someday we'll regret
not joining forces with him
to fight the Reds.
You know,
I killed a lot of your
countrymen during the war.
Mr. Bleichert, have you
met Balto in the hallway?
Yes. Very realistic.
EMMETT: An old friend
stuffed him.
We were in the Scots Regiment
together. Georgie Tilden.
He wanted to work
in the flickers.
When did you move here?
1920.
Hollywood was a cow pasture
but the silent flickers
were booming.
Georgie got work
as a lighting man,
me building houses.
Georgie introduced me
to Mack Sennett.
I helped him build
that housing project
he was putting up
underneath
that god-awful sign.
Hollywoodland.
I used to love
the Keystone Kops.
Me, too.
Old Mack knew how
to squeeze a dollar dry.
He had extras moonlighting
as laborers and vice versa.
Georgie and I used to drive
them over to Hollywoodland
after 12 hours
on a silent flicker.
Then put in another six hours
by torchlight.
He even gave us movie credits
a couple of times.
EMMETT: Mother.
Are you feeling well?
Would you like to contribute
to the conversation?
Did you know, Mr. Bleichert,
that Ramona Boulevard
is named after me?
I didn't.
When Emmett married me,
for my father's money,
he promised my family
that he would use
his influence
with the City Zoning Board
to have a street named
after me.
But all he could manage
was a dead-end block
in a red-light district
in Lincoln Heights.
Are you familiar with
the neighborhood,
Mr. Bleichert?
I grew up there.
Yes, well,
then you'll know
that Mexican prostitutes
expose themselves
in windows.
I hear many of them
know Mr. Linscott by name.
That's enough!
I will sing for my supper
when Mayor Bowron comes
to dinner,
but not
for Madeleine's male whores.
He's a common policeman.
My God, Emmett!
How little you think of me.
(THUDDING)
I'm sorry.
I'm really so sorry.
Mr. Bleichert.
(DOG BARKING)
BUCKY: You kept your name
out of the papers.
Until the wedding.
Your mother would love that.
She's a snob.
The kind who takes pills
the doctor gives her
so she doesn't have to admit
to being a hophead.
Do you want to know a secret?
Sure.
Daddy bought
rotten lumber
and old movie sets
from Mack Sennett
and built houses
out of them.
That's how he really made
his money.
He's got firetraps
all over LA.
His good friend Georgie,
maimed in a car crash,
while running Daddy
some errands.
And now he throws him scraps,
odd jobs, tending
Daddy's rental properties.
You don't have
to tell me this.
I like you, Bucky.
I didn't tell you
all about Betty.
You didn't?
Don't be mad at me.
Last summer, I heard about
a girl who looked like me.
I got curious.
I left notes
at a couple of places,
"Your look-alike
wants to meet you,"
things like that.
I left my number.
She called.
That's how I met her
at LaVerne's with Lorna.
And that's all of it?
Yes.
Tell me something.
Why'd you want to meet
Betty Short anyway?
I've worked hard to be loose
but the way people
described Betty
it was like she was a natural.
"Don't walk out on me,
Richard.
"Say you care.
Say that you..."
MAN: Miss Short.
There is a pause
after "care".
Are you familiar
with the English language?
I try to be.
Okay.
Let's try it again.
And remember,
go back to the beginning,
you're begging him.
Begging.
He's walking out on you.
You're begging him.
So, come on, let's do it.
We're running out of
film here. Let's go.
Richard,
don't walk out on me.
Please say that you care.
Say that you think
that I'm beautiful,
and that you love me.
Miss Short, you know,
this is a very sad scene.
Do you think you're capable
of playing sadness?
Sure.
I can do that.
(DUCKS QUACKING)
(DOG BARKING)
Miss!
MAN: Get your hands off her!
I'm an emancipated minor
and if you touch me
without a matron present
I'll sue you!
MAN: Leave her alone.
No!
I'm a policeman. Policeman.
You and Betty made
the casting rounds
together, right?
Did you ever get
any movie work?
No.
Well, then,
what about the film can?
It's a movie.
What kind of movie?
Something tells me
it's not David O. Selznick.
Now, you have to tell us
the whole thing, sweetheart,
so think it through.
I was cadging
at a bar in Gardena.
This man started
talking to me.
I thought I was pregnant
and I was desperate
wicked bad for money.
He said he'd give me $200
to act in a nudie film.
He said he needed another
girl, so I called Betty.
We made... Thank you.
...the movie at this big house
a couple of hours
outside town.
Then he drove us
back to LA.
Where was this house,
exactly?
I was pretty out of it,
if you know what I mean.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
What do you think, Russ?
This got anything to do
with the girl's murder?
Long shot, Chief.
What's that about, gentlemen?
Your boy can't hold his water?
I got you Warrants.
You're my men
and you made me
look like a fool
in front of
the most powerful
man in the department.
And you...
Yeah, you. Look at me.
Blanchard? Look at me!
If you werert Mr. Fire,
you would be suspended
from duty already.
You're a punch-drunk,
washed-up fighter...
Stay out of this, Bleichert!
You're back on Warrants
as of tomorrow.
I want you to report to me
at 0800
with a letter of apology
for Chief Green.
You are a political animal,
and for the sake
of your pension,
I suggest that you grovel.
It is now 8:15
in the morning.
Where's your partner?
I don't know.
I was hoping he'd be here.
Well, it is 8:15
and he is not here
and neither
are his letters of apology.
Bleichert,
get out of my sight.
Try and be a police officer.
OFFICER ON RADIO: Attention
all units in the vicinity
of Crenshaw and Stocker.
Code four.
Two dead. Suspect, dead.
Raymond "junior" Nash.
Warrant number 5-6-0-9.
Repeat. Code four.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
BUCKY: We forgot
about junior Nash.
Here he is, dead
in the middle of a stickup.
He was trash and a killer
and I'd been right
from the beginning.
We let him slip
and the innocent died.
(SIGHING)
Blanchard!
He's in the mers.
No. I beat up a wall.
For messing up Nash...
Not good enough.
I'm sorry, Bucky.
(GROANING)
I'm sorry.
Oh, fuck, Lee! Fuck!
BUCKY: Losing the first
Bleichert-Blanchard fight
got me local celebrity
Warrants
and close to nine grand
in cash.
Winning the rematch
got me a sprained wrist,
two dislocated knuckles
and the rest of the day off.
Smile at me.
Look soft and sweet.
I picked up
Lorna Mertz yesterday.
She had a copy
of a stag film,
her and Betty Short
playing les.
Pretty spooky stuff.
Did she mention me?
No.
And I checked
the case file.
No mention of that
number-leaving note
thing that you did.
Listen,
I'm withholding evidence
for you.
It's a fair trade
but it shakes me.
Are you sure
there isn't anything
you haven't told me
about you and Betty?
Betty and I made love once,
that one time last summer.
I just did it to see
what it would be like
to do it with someone
who looked like me.
Jesus Christ.
Bucky, that's it. I swear.
Bucky, please stay.
You stupid slut.
Stay. Sugar, stay!
Hey.
We're famous, Dwight.
Notorious.
Where's Lee?
Bobby DeWitt's
probably in LA. By now.
Lee always said I'd be safe.
You will be. You will be.
He had a sister.
What?
He had a little sister.
She was killed
when Lee was 15,
and they never
caught the guy.
Why...
Why didn't you tell me
this before?
He made me promise
never to tell you.
He thought it made him
too easy to figure.
Well, it sure explains
some things.
No, it doesn't.
Kay, where's Lee?
If you know,
you should tell me.
Kay,
Bobby DeWitt just got out.
Lee's all hopped up
on Benzedrine,
so what do you
think is going to happen?
Where is he?
Morrie Friedman called
a couple of hours ago.
The guy from New Year's?
Bobby's got a drug deal
somewhere
in a building Friedman owns,
the Olympic, I think.
When?
Now.
Jesus.
Dwight.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Bobby DeWitt?
Get your hands up.
Get up against that wall
over there.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Jesus.
I ain't out one week, and...
You're here for a drug deal
with Morrie Friedman.
I know that.
Look, I'm just looking
for a place to take a piss.
Lee Blanchard's here.
Did you know that?
Blanchard?
Man-oh-Manischewitz,
I ain't seen Blanchard
since my fucking trial.
Yeah,
but he's been on your mind.
And you've been on his mind.
I'm thinking that you let
the word out there knowing
he'd come down here.
Look, maybe
I flapped my trap at trial.
Maybe I was thinking revenge,
maybe talking trash
to my cellies,
but all I know is
what I read in the papers,
and when that fucker
killed them niggers...
Finish up.
I don't know
what his version is.
What's your version?
Sir, all this between
me and Blanchard
is that I fucked this
big-tittied Dakota cunt
named Kay Lake...
MAN: Hold it, pal.
(GUN FIRING)
Blanchard, behind you!
BUCKY: Blanchard!
(LEE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org