Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Previously on The Cleaner:
Everyone in position?
Depends on what position you
want.
-Akani.
-I slept with her,
but Melissa and me
were separated, and I'm sorry.
All right? I'm sorry....
every day since.
When Lula was being born
in the hospital,
I was down the hallway
slamming dope,
and I made a deal
that if he got me
through that day that
I would become
his avenging angel.
What I love and hate
the most about numbers
is that they're infinite.
Never-ending.
Everlasting.
The numbers up here
have been haunting me
for almost a year,
so I try to remind myself
there are only ten numbers
that we use.
The same ten
that we learned to count to,
using our fingers
and our toes.
20, 40, 60, 80.
Plus $1 ,600.
Plus gas?
-I included gas, Swenton.
-God, not this again.
Ooh, you know what? Back off,
Ivanka Trump, all right?
Um, no, I'm talking about gas
for the, uh...
for the night
that I was on surveillance.
You were on the same address
for 11 hours, Swenton,
and the mark never moved.
-Plus $1 ,600.
-So, no gas?
-Darnell?
-Yo.
One, two, three, four, 500,
six, seven, eight.
When you put them
into different configurations,
they grow, and they multiply.
They split and divide.
Everything
in the universe can be measured
by our fingers and our toes.
Ten numbers.
Just ten.
Akani, plus $1,600.
Please. It's not like
she's gonna cash it anyway.
No, she's gonna use it as a
torch and stick it up your ass.
Okay, that makes us square
on the Oxy mom case.
Rock star, too.
As long as he stays clean.
Cynic.
-Realist.
-Gosh, you know,
-boots, new phone.
-Phone.
-But you guys should
really check out these boots.
They're kind of a faux
endangered reptile
-kind of thing.
-Swen, get a new phone.
Hey.
We got all the food.
Which means you got what?
Oh, sodas, chips, avocado
and salsa for the guac,
corn on the cob,
-salad, pie-- cherry.
-And rhubarb.
Okay, so we need, uh,
beef kabobs, fish kabobs,
and two vegetarian
for Quinn.
Don't let me forget.
Hey! He's coming, huh?
Yeah, he's coming.
Well, that's good.
Who is Quinn?
When I was a kid,
I worked in my father's diner--
his father's before that.
One day, my mom got sick,
and I had to work the register.
You got to understand,
math-- not my strong suit.
My dad was too busy on the grill
to show me what to do.
I just jumped into it.
Three dollars for a tuna melt.
Dollar fifty
for fries and a soda,
$6.89 for the Gyros plate.
Suddenly,
the numbers started
making sense to me.
I don't know why,
but they did.
Something clicked,
and since then,
they're my only constant.
My ship in the tempest-tossed
seas of life.
Oh, it wasn't that funny.
You're late for your next
class. Go.
So, when your dad
was in prison...
This is the second time,
right?
Yeah. For possession.
Anyway, he needed someone.
A friend.
Another prisoner?
Inmate.
Same difference.
Will you let her finish?
So that was Quinn, the friend?
Mm-hmm, and he...
And what was he in for?
Robbery.
I'm gonna lie to you.
It's the same old story, right?
-Wrong place at the wrong time.
-It can happen.
And I was... I was in a bad way.
I mean, I'm real bad.
So it was Quinn
who got me sober.
No, scratch that.
Quinn saved my life.
Hmm. "He shall give his angels
charge over thee to keep thee
lest anytime thou dash
thou foot against the stone."
Poetic.
Luke. Chapter four, verse ten.
Sounds like somebody
spends a lot of time
in hotel rooms...
with Mr. Gideon.
Wait.
I met that guy with Mick, right?
Uh, Quinn the Eskimo?
Yeah. Mick knew him.
But the trip is,
his name ain't Quinn.
He ain't even an Eskimo.
I mean...
But, Darnell,
you're right, he is...
he is some kind of angel.
Hmm.
You know, back then,
Quinn doesn't save me,
I'm thinking...
I don't know.
I end up like, uh...
Well, like Mick.
I don't even know
how you wrap your mind
around all this theory,
Professor.
I've been working this theory
for ten months.
If I can't wrap my mind
around it now...
Go on, get out of here.
Oh, I don't mind. I'll help.
Harry, go.
See you in class
tomorrow, Professor.
Yeah, I'll pick it up.
Charcoal for the grill,
mesquite chips. Got it.
Yeah, I'll be home soon.
I'm just, uh, finishing up here.
Bye.
Buying a new truck?
Some day.
Sounds like
you're throwing a big party.
Mega--
disco ball, DJ, tons of blow.
Oh, nice. Special occasion?
Nah.
Oh, just immediate family?
Couple of friends.
Yeah, I could cancel my plans.
Party might be a little too
low-key for your taste, Akani.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Have fun.
You feel like conserving water?
Not so much.
What are you doing up so early?
I wanted to get my homework done
before school.
That's good. That's...
that's mature.
I wouldn't push that
maturity thing too much.
I peed in the shower.
Let me warm you up.
How have you been?
You and Teddy didn't come
to the house
for dinner Friday.
I know. I'm sorry.
We're good. Busy.
I'm taking
a few more classes at school.
Teddy's trying to get published
before the deadline.
-Hi, Mom.
-Oh.
Hi, Teddy.
Let me get you some breakfast.
Same weight
since high school, Mama.
Hey, Pop.
Come on. I want
to get to class early.
Bye, honey.
Tess, is he doing okay?
He's doing great.
He's just under
a lot of pressure.
We'll come by for dinner
this week.
Sofi, leave the beautiful
professor alone.
We got customers.
Bye.
Quinn.
Get out of my head.
The kids asked about him.
Good.
What did you say?
What they needed to know.
Which means what?
Which means, not as much
as you wish I did,
but more than
I would have on my own.
Well, that's the tricky
part, right, babe?
Telling our kids just enough
to, uh, keep their heads
clear, their eyes open,
but not so much
that you scare them off
from taking risks.
-Hmm.
-You know, the good ones.
We'll figure it out.
Mmm. Get out of my head.
Just so you know,
this is really gonna help
when I have nothing to say
in confession.
Do I have to stay here
for the party?
Yes.
Can I have a friend over?
-Of course you can, sweetheart.
-Good.
'Cause I was thinking maybe
I could invite Charlie Mintz.
You know what?
On second thought, no friends.
I told you.
Go get in the truck, all right?
We're gonna be late for school.
We're not, uh... we're not
at the boy talk moment, are we?
No.
Not yet.
Unless you got something
you might want
to talk to me about.
Can I talk to you later?
You sure can.
-All right, wait here.
-Dad, we're gonna be late!
Get in the truck!
I'll be right back.
ln 12 hours.
So, if I transfer my balance
to your card company,
how soon
can I get a cash advance?
It would normally take
two weeks,
-No. -but I can arrange to have
it done in ten business days.
That's-That's too long.
How about frequent flier miles?
No, I don't want airline miles,
Goddamn it!
-Hi, Teddy.
-Tess.
You missed the department
meeting again.
I covered for you.
The staff's sick
of hearing me talk.
-They'd rather dump me
and keep you. -And you?
I want to keep you, too.
You have to stop.
I will stop once
I get through this,
but it helps me write.
Tess, you understand
what this means for us
if I get published.
Tenure, a house,
kids.
Teddy... are you serious?
Come here.
Completely.
Mmm.
Hey.
You're looking good, Quinn.
Yeah. Mrs. Banks, you're a liar
and I love you for it.
Check out my husband
with Jasmine Marks.
-Flirt.
-Relentless.
I meant her.
How's he doing?
-He's good.
-Yeah.
Coaching Ben's football,
which basically just gives them
another reason to be pissed
at each other.
Lula's got him wrapped
around her finger.
Just like her mother?
Hardly.
He's clean.
Yeah.
And, you know, I think this...
deal he made--
if he's tempted to use,
the deal he made with God,
it stops him.
At least so far.
How's the marriage going?
Wow. Quinn, free therapy.
Yeah.
When he was shooting dope,
I was this heroic woman
just for sticking by him,
and now that he's some kind of
personal savior,
I'm just a lucky chick
who landed a guy
like William Banks.
I didn't mean that
the way it sounds.
You know what D.H. Lawrence
said about marriage?
Yes, I did a lot
of reading in the joint.
D.H. Lawrence said that
marriage was three things.
It was you, it was him,
and the third thing was
the thing that you created
together.
I don't know, maybe you just
got to work on that third thing.
You getting soft on me, Quinn?
I'm just counting on you two
to make it all work.
Cheers.
And I helped out his wife,
so he gave us an opportunity...
Excuse me?
-Yeah.
-Hi.
I'm looking for William.
D, you want to give me a minute?
I'm William.
What can I do for you?
A couple years ago,
you helped my cousin's wife,
Janelle Banick.
You may not remember.
Cross addicted
to Valium and alcohol.
60 day detox.
How's she doing?
Sober. Almost two years.
Ah, good. And you?
I'm not here to talk about me.
I have a colleague, a brilliant
mathematics professor actually.
He started using speed
about a year ago
when he started
working on his paper.
He, hopefully, will get
published this summer.
He used it to balance his class
schedule with his writing,
just speed.
And then he graduated
to cocaine.
Yeah.
Janelle told me about your fee.
Half now.
Please, I-I need your help.
Ben, if you want a ride,
we're leaving.
I'm coming.
Damn it.
All right, sit down, everybody.
We got a case up.
His name is Teddy Souplos.
He's a professor of mathematics
at Alta California University.
He's also a cocaine addict.
He's up for tenure this year.
If he doesn't publish,
he's done.
Publish or perish.
What? I watch TV.
Who made the touch?
Colleague.
All right, Akani, Darnell,
I want you hitting all the
dealer tracks on the West Side.
I don't actually
have to purchase
or take narcotics, do l?
Well, sometimes you might
have to make a buy.
Otherwise,
you get made as a cop.
And that is not so bueno, okay?
Let's go.
East Side are your weed dealers.
Mellow guys, good businessmen.
West Side: pharmaceuticals,
some meth dealers.
Not so nice.
Down by the water,
that's Shooters Row.
These fools even
suspect you're a cop,
they will drop you on the spot.
I don't want to speak
out of turn,
but you seem like
such a nice girl. l-I...
Don't patronize me with
the "nice girl" speech.
I'm here for the
same reason you are,
William is and I'm
pretty sure Swenton.
We're all here looking for
something better than we had.
Coke dealers take up
the entire North Side
of the park.
You go with cash,
you make a buy,
keep the conversation
to a minimum. Got it?
But William didn't say
I had to buy any drugs...
William's not here.
I have seniority.
So go.
And, Darnell,
I'm not a nice girl.
Everything's been arranged
for you
to go under at the university.
Here's your lD,
your class schedule.
Now, I want you to go into that
school's payroll office and...
I know, I know, I know.
-Stick to financials.
-Right.
I'm kind of excited
I'm going back to college.
I mean, l-I told you about
how I applied to college?
By taking my old man's "Girls
of the Pac 10" issue of Playboy,
and I let that ship steer
my academic future.
I applied to all ten schools.
And how many did you get into?
Uh, surprisingly, Arizona State.
Swenton, do not
make me regret this.
Come on.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Pre-med?
My mom is gonna be so proud.
I know I promised.
I just... I just need
a little bit more
so that I can write.
Teddy, no.
You-you... We want
a house one day.
Right, Tess?
Tess...
I need the money.
I'll pay you back.
Tess?
Hello?
Hello?!
Professor Souplos.
Hey. Hi, Harry.
Yeah, come on. Come on in.
You okay?
No, l-I'm okay, thanks.
Look, I realized today what l
want to write my thesis about.
When you were talking
about your parents,
something just clicked.
lt was completely inspiring.
And, like you said,
it would click, and it did.
That's excellent news.
Good for you. Good.
Can I ask you something, Harry?
Sure.
This is a rather
awkward request, so...
And feel free to say no.
But, uh, I just paid my rent,
and I'm being told that the bank
hasn't cleared my paycheck.
I-I know it's odd
-that I would even...
-How much do you need?
No, forget it.
You know, you don't have to...
I want to.
How much money do you need?
Uh, I guess
$500 would do.
Okay.
Actually, uh...
it would make my life easier
if we could get the cash, Harry.
Okay.
Teach just showed up.
Let's grab him.
Hey, there's about 150 yards
between him and us and about
400 rounds of ammunition.
Four hundred and eleven.
Darnell, don't.
This is what we do, right?
We protect the client.
-Shit!
-Unless you want to stand around
and buy more drugs.
Oh, William, pick up, pick up.
Man, we have a problem.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
William, we've got a problem.
Darnell's gone rogue
at the park.
Shit.
Don't say a word.
-Just keep moving.
-What are you doing, man?
What the hell are you doing?
What you doing, William?
Keep moving.
You had one thing
to take care of, Akani.
You want to get into
a pissing contest with me?
What the hell are you doing
having him make a buy?
-Do you want to hear my side
of the story? -Not unless
it ends in "Yes, William, we did
exactly what you told us to do."
It's a slight variation
on that, man.
And you. You think you're
some kind of cowboy now, huh?
You gonna ride in
and save the day?
All you needed to do
was make the mark.
You do not make a move on him.
And you don't carry
unless the rest
of the team is aware.
I make the calls,
I set the plays.
You don't authorize
that kind of move.
Okay, I was just trying to...
Yeah.
I'm a patient woman, babe,
wouldn't you say?
Some would say saintly.
So, do you think it would be out
of character for this saint
to want to put her foot
up our son's ass?
What did he do?
Our son seems to think that
smoking is a good idea.
Are they ours?
Nope.
Well, then, babe,
you-you can handle this.
William, you better get home,
or you may be down one child.
I'm on my way.
All right, get off my truck.
Go home, get out of here.
Swenton's going under
in the morning.
Hey, do you want us to stay
on surveillance?
What, after you've been made?
Get off my truck.
Nothing to say?
Go to bed.
What about my homework?
Do your homework,
then go to bed.
What about dinner?
You don't get dinner.
You know, you're making
some great decisions
with your life.
I guess that makes me
the apple then, huh, tree?
Are you ready for school?
I've been thinking
about Mom and Dad's party.
What about it?
lt was almost normal, right?
Mom and Dad were getting along.
There were sort of
normal people in our house.
The singing along
on the guitar was queer,
but it was normal,
for our family.
We have to hurry.
I'm meeting Charlie Mintz
to help him cram
for the marine science quiz.
I heard about the cigarettes.
Dad got really mad, right?
It's none of your business, Lu.
Hey, did Lula talk to you
this morning?
No, uh-uh.
About what?
I don't know,
she wouldn't tell me.
But I think it's about...
boys.
That horny little Charlie Mintz.
Huh?
I'll talk to her.
Hey, are we alone right now?
Yeah.
Alone is nice.
Alone together is...
really nice.
Could be.
Really?
Maybe.
Hey, wait.
Hey, let's go to the bedroom.
What?
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
What? What did I do?
-No.
-Is it about the bedroom?
About going to the bedroom?
No, baby.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry,
I thought I was ready.
Damn it.
You've only been home
for a while.
I'm sorry.
I'm almost done.
I cracked the equation.
You're not even close
to being done.
-What are you talking about?
-I read it.
That morning that you went out
to score, I read your paper.
What were you doing
on my computer?
lt doesn't make any sense,
Teddy.
It's just thoughts
that don't connect.
That's because you
couldn't possibly,
possibly understand
that paper.
It's words that don't connect
to anything.
It's the best thing
that I've ever written,
and the fact that you
can't understand it
means absolutely nothing.
Tess!
Okay...
Hey, Dr. Hanson, how are you?
Very well, thank you.
Fire.
Fire alarm, people!
There's a fire alarm!
I-I smell smoke.
I hope my car is okay.
Oh, wow, somebody...
Does somebody have a phone?
Anybody? I-I should...
I should...
We should probably
call somebody, right?
Go ahead.
All right, William, I'm in.
This college sucks, bro.
lt doesn't even
have a football team.
On point, Swenton.
What's that noise?
Um, nothing.
Souplos hasn't been paid
in months.
His last eight paychecks
were advanced.
All right, forget
about Teddy's financials.
Get Tess's.
-Why?
-Just do it.
Same thing.
They're advancing her checks,
too.
All right, look, get back
in the classroom.
Get eyes on Teddy.
Roger that.
And don't do a thing
unless you call me first,
you got it?
-All students and faculty
-I got it under control.
may return to their offices
and classrooms.
Go away, Lu.
It's me.
I'm busy.
I don't give a damn
if you're busy, Ben.
I want to know what the hell
you're doing smoking cigarettes.
You and Mom smoke.
Well, that's because
we're old enough to make
that stupid decision.
When you're older, you want
to do something that asinine,
be my guest.
Thanks, I'll give it
some thought.
You want to tell me
what the problem
is here, young man?
I don't know, Dad.
Why don't you tell me?
You better cut the crap.
What are you talking about?
Where did you get this?
ln the bathroom, on the floor.
-When?
-Yesterday.
ls it yours?
You know it's not mine.
-How come?
-What do you mean, how come?
What kind of question is that?
Because I'm clean,
that's how come.
And how am I supposed
to know that?
Because I told you that I am!
Where do you get off
asking me that?!
This is bullshit.
And I wanted you to hear this
from me, not Ben.
What?
ls it yours?
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
ls it yours?
Wow.
What am I supposed
to think, William?
You're supposed to think
it's not mine, babe.
You used to leave them
all over the house.
I used to pick them up
so the kids wouldn't find them.
And you always used
to tell me
that they weren't yours.
Well, I took responsibility
for that.
After you got clean,
what, the third time?
Don't give me that.
William, you're a great liar.
Okay, I know that.
So I'm gonna ask you
one last time.
ls it yours?
No.
It's not mine.
Then you find out whose it is,
who brought this into our home,
and you take care of it,
because whoever this belongs to
is not welcome in this house.
I'm terribly sorry I'm late.
Excuse me.
Terribly sorry I'm late,
everyone.
I was working on my paper,
and I got to thinking
about a couple of things.
The numbers that...
and there are only ten
of them....
I told you this.
About the fingers
and the toes, right?
Uh, but if you look...
at the-the equation,
the numbers that...
What's on my board?
Who was working on my board?
I saw an amazing opportunity
on the third parallel.
Did I ask for your help, Harry?
N-No, but you were...
Well, I just thought...
You thought what?
Thought I needed your help?
That-That you-you
were just gonna solve this
and save the day?
Shit, write my paper for me?
ls that what you thought?
I don't need your help, Harry.
I don't need any of it.
Wait, stop, I only figured
out a small piece of it.
Stop!
I didn't ask for your help.
I didn't ask for anything!
I'm sorry, I'm...
Please give me bars.
lt was just awkward as hell,
Quinn.
lt... you know,
it completely freaked me out.
There's my son,
my wife looking at me,
you know, looking at me
like they used to look at me,
practically calling me a liar
to my face.
No, you know what?
Melissa did call me a liar.
Whose rig do you think it was?
Oh, man, you don't
think it was mine.
Quinn, I don't know
what to think.
You don't think it was mine.
You know, I don't
know what to think.
I think you better sit down
right now, brother.
before I stand up.
I'm sorry.
I swear on the heads
of your children.
Look, you don't have to do that.
I swear on the heads
of Lula and Ben
that was not my rig.
Man, I wouldn't do
something like that
to you in your own home.
Hell, man,
the old Quinn wouldn't even
do something that low.
Well, maybe.
Whose do you think it was?
I don't know, but
I got to find out.
You're damn right you do.
I'm sorry, man.
Unbelievable.
The guy goes wacko, okay?
I can't get bars.
I'm thinking,
"When is this building built--
like, the 1940s or something?"
It's like a bomb shelter.
Couldn't get a signal
for like a quarter of a mile.
-Get a new phone. -Still
waiting on that phone call.
I couldn't get bars.
Get a new phone.
You know what?
lf it were up to me,
I would have just dropped him
right there in the room.
I mean, you had the green light.
You know what?
I... couldn't get a signal.
I would have done it
if it were up to me.
Bullshit.
I tend to believe her.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for William.
Hi, um...
William is right out front.
You were paying for his drugs
and you hired me.
I didn't know what else to do.
I should have told you.
I didn't want to keep
giving him money.
I didn't.
I also didn't...
want to lose him.
He's such an amazing
person, William.
Oh, I really wish that
you could see him the way
that I do.
So, what now?
Now?
He's lost your money.
He's not getting published.
He's losing his job.
He's losing his mind.
He's losing his family.
With everything he's lost,
I still can't promise you
he's bottomed out.
I made you some tea.
Oh, honey,
I'm not a tea kind of guy.
It's chamomile;
it will relax you.
Oh, I don't need to be relaxed.
A boy tried to kiss me.
Give me the tea.
I'm gonna kick
that Charlie Mintz's ass.
Actually, I tried to kiss him.
But Charlie
didn't want to kiss me.
Well, Lula, listen to me now.
Sometime in the very,
very distant future--
and I mean very distant--
there's going to be another
boy, not Charlie Mintz...
Dad.
...and this boy,
he's going to think you're the
prettiest girl he's ever seen,
he's going to think
you hung the moon,
and there will come a time
eventually when he'll want
nothing more than to kiss you,
and when that time comes,
baby...
Yeah?
I'm gonna want
to kick his ass, too.
All right?
-Okay?
-Okay.
Yeah.
Well, first off,
l'd just like to say
that it was a nice surprise
when I heard from you.
I mean, I thought
our encounter was...
You'll get your money
if my guy is there.
Well, that would be terrific,
William.
Now, the financial agreement
we had was, uh...
-Three hundred.
-Cool.
Look, your boy
is down at MacArthur.
Dude is sketchy as hell.
His ass should be teaching
home ec.
First class--
how to take a bath.
Look, he ain't got shit
to buy shit
and he's looking to score.
He ain't going to be leaving
without scoring
and he ain't scoring
anytime soon.
I'm on my way.
With my money?
Yep.
Hey, Quinn.
Hello, Mrs. Banks.
You, uh, selling a little
door-to-door D.H. Lawrence?
No, I just came
to get my guitar.
Oh, right. Uh, hey, Lula,
can you grab
Quinn's guitar?
One second.
Your esposo told me
about the rig somebody left.
That's bad.
Yeah, you have no idea.
Oh, I do.
I saw the look on Will's face.
Hmm.
You have any idea
who it might have been?
Nah, it's...
maybe Crazy Kenny or Joy.
Here you go.
Thank you, darling.
It never ends.
-Bye, Quinn.
-I'll give you a call.
Okay.
Excuse me, Quinn?
Yes.
I don't know if, well...
What is it, Lula?
I just... I wanted to thank
you for saving my dad's life.
Hey, Lula, the phone's for you.
Coming.
-Bye.
Hey, man, can you hook me up?
Nah, man, I don't mess
with them illegalities, bruh.
See that cat right there?
He's been slinging all morning.
Hey, man, can you hook me up?
Maybe.
What you need?
Blow.
I got... I got this.
It's worth a lot.
It's worth...
-Oh, I know what it's worth.
-Yeah.
Ow...
What are you doing?
How are you feeling?
Numb, mostly.
I can't believe all
the horrible shit I did,
-the things I said.
-Well,
nothing that hasn't been done
bigger and better before you.
It's a start.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Man, I just...
Man, I just couldn't...
I just couldn't keep clean.
Leaving the rig
in your bathroom...
I just... was really high, man.
l... heard somebody
and I just freaked.
I'm sorry, Will.
I get it.
I swore on your children.
I get that, too.
I need your help.
I know.
And I'm going to help you,
Quinn.
I'll help you get straight,
I'll help you keep straight,
but you can't...
ever come to my house again.
Not ever.
Why?
Don't ask me that.
Just know that I'm gonna do
my best to help you and...
that you're not welcome
in my house
ever again.
Man, I saved your life.
I know you did,
and now I need to live it.
We're even.
Thanks for waiting for me.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org