Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kup and Hot Rod just bought it.
I can't deal with that now.
Face it. Magnus.
The Decepticons are gonna dog us
until they see us dead.
Then that's exactly what they're gonna see
Prepare for emergency separation!
That's too dangerous.
What choice do we have?
The Autobots have been terminated.
Excellent!
And the Matrix with them.
Aaaaa! Unicron, why?
Take me to Unicron.
Take me now!
Did we have to
let them detonate 3 quarters of the ship?
Seeing how
they would have detonated 4 quarters
I think it was a good choice.
But now how we are going to get there
in this wreck?
Perceptor, can you locate a place
to set down for repairs?
Gamma waves in this sector of space
create marginal navigation probabilities...
however,
ahem, yes, I believe I can.
The planet of Junk is in this vicinity.
Then lets go for it.
Kup!
Grimlock!
Slag!
Anybody?
Hot Rod, Help me!
Kup,
Kup!
Help...
Kup,
talk to me.
Fix me.
Sure, Kup,
right away.
Brace for impact!
Say something,
anybody?
Remind me to give the auto-pilot a raise.
Daniel?
I... I'm okay.
Let's try to salvage this thing.
Can I help, too?
It's rough out there, kid.
I think Daniel can make himself useful
with this.
It was Spike's exo-suit.
Dad's exo-suit?
He told me all about it.
Here, try it on.
Now try to walk.
Come on, you can do it.
Just think about what you want to do
before you do it.
It's kind of tricky,
woah, uh.
Keep on practicing,
you'll get the hang of it.
Come on, showtime's over.
We've got work to do.
This must be the junk capital
of the universe.
Stop, thief!
No welcome-wagon, "hello, stranger!"
with that good coffee flavor for you.
Yeah, or your money back!
Offer expires while you wait.
Operators are standing by.
That does it.
Well, what do you think?
Of all the circuit glitched diode
blowing dim wittery,
you left a piece out.
No way, you're just a little stiff.
Anyway, all things considered
you did an amazing job, lad.
Amazing.
Really?
Yeah,
you even got rid of a nasty
burr on my rotator.
Now let's find the Dinobots
and get off this twisted planet.
Don't act hostile.
I'll use the universal greeting.
Universal greeting?
Watch
I'll have them eating out of my hand.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong?
See
the universal greeting works everytime.
Now, without making any sudden moves,
offer them an energon goody.
This is getting expensive.
Don't worry, they'll reciprocate.
I thought they
were supposed to reciprocate.
No more.
Empty.
Reminds me of the Niter slave mines
on Golgonath 7.
Everyplace reminds you of someplace else.
Experience, lad,
you should learn to appreciate it.
Lot of good it's done us so far.
Hey, what's going on over there?
Has the imperial magistrate
reached a verdict?
I have.
Guilty or innocent?
Innocent.
Feed him to the Sharkticons.
Aaaaaaaa!!!
Hahahahahaha...
We've got to get a new travel agent.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong.
What is this place?
The world of the savage Sharkticons
and their cruel masters, the Quintessons.
I am Kranix.
My planet was destroyed by Unicron.
Unicron?
Who's Unicron?
A planet that devours everything
in it's path.
So that's the monster's name.
No, please!
I'm the last survivor of Lithone!
No! No!
Let him go!
Soon you two shall receive your sentence
Has the imperial magistrate
reached a verdict?
I have.
Guilty or innocent?
Spare me this mockery of justice.
I repeat,
guilty or innocent?
Innocent.
Aaaaaaa!!!
Not the end I'd wish for, lad.
Me Swoop no see nothing.
Me Grimlock positive Hot Rod and Kup close.
Me Slag say you full of Beryllium baloney.
Me Grimlock say you full of Cesium salami.
Beryllium balony!
Friends find, look behind.
Who say that?
You go wrong way, you fool I say.
Me Grimlock fool?
Picture you got, not fool you not.
Me Grimlock no like you!
Ow! Why boy hit my nose?
Wheelie say, find friends today.
Me Grimlock say, we on our way.
Unicron,
why did you torture me?
You have failed.
No, Unicron.
Ultra Magnus is dead,
and the Matrix destroyed.
The Matrix has not been destroyed,
and Ultra Magnus lives,
on the planet of Junk.
Stalk him,
tear him apart,
and destroy the Matrix.
Be sure the fittings are securely welded.
AbsolutlyPositivelyDefinitly, IWouldn't
HaveltAnyOtherWay, AnyOtherWayAtAll.
Woah, this exo-suit's fantastic.
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it.
Forward, avanti, apfel and like,
go for gusto...
Hang on.
Decepticons!
We've got to draw them off
and double back to the shuttle.
There goes the shuttle.
What do we do?
Transform, Transform, YouCanDolt,
IKnowYouCanDolT, YouCanDolt.
Transform.
Human germ.
There they are!
Attack!
Make a break for cover.
I'll try
and unleash the power of the Matrix.
Till all are one!
Till all are one.
Open! Damn it! Open!
Prime, you said the Matrix
would light our darkest hour.
Magnus,
I want the Matrix.
Never!
Sweeps, terminate him!
Die! Die!
Unicron, my master,
with this, I shall make you my slave.
Before his imperial magistrate
delivers a verdict,
would you like to beg for your lives?
It sometimes helps,
but not often.
I can't transform.
Keep trying.
Silence or you will be
held in contempt of this court.
I have nothing but contempt for this court.
Guilty or innocent?
Innocent.
They've got more Sharkticons
than we have photon charges.
Then let's hold a demolition derby.
Haha, didn't even bend a fender. Haha.
Yeah, but look! There's a lot more of those
can digging, grill cracking things.
We can't hold out forever, Kup,
but we can give them one humungous
repair bill.
Execute them!
Excuse me.
Me Grimlock want to munch metal.
Haha, I never thought
I'd be so happy to see those bozo's.
Me Grimlock no bozo, me king.
Sharkticons, execute them!
Me Grimlock say execute them!
I think the problems on this planet
will be solved very shortly.
Yeah, but what about our probles?
We need a ship.
You get ship, if I get trip.
Who are you?
Him Wheelie,
him freind.
He'll be mine too if he can find a ship.
Skip stare over there.
That's a ship?
Who cares, as long as it flies.
Ultra Magnus...
WithoutTheMatrixTherelsNoHope,
NoHope, NoHopeAtAll.
First Prime, now Ultra Magnus.
What do we do?
Look!
Don't look behind door number 2, Monty.
It's time to play
end of the line my valentine.
Geroni-roni-doo-ron-ron-i-mo!
It's not hard to knock 'em down.
It's getting them to stay down
that's the trick.
They're indestructible.
And they're everywhere.
You check-in, but you don't check-out.
Steady as she goes, Bob.
Snoopy visitors get mud in the eye
by and by.
Film end.
It's Hot Rod.
And Kup and the Dinobots!
Guns aren't exactly friendly.
Neither are they incase you haven't noticed.
What was that universal greeting again?
Never mind, I remember.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong?
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong...
Me Grimlock not kisser, me Grimlock king.
Have a nice day, and please close cover
before striking, friends!
Breep drit
aw rootie! So say the Junkions.
Where'd you learn to talk like that?
TV.
We talk TV. You talk some TV?
I talk some TV,
and now the news, don't touch that dial.
Bah weep graaaagnah wheep ni ni bong...
By George kimosabes
your smashed up friend soon like brand new
with ninety day warranty.
Happy motoring,
Cock-a-doodle-do!
Look, he's alive.
Unbelievable!
Your all alive.
The Matrix?
It's gone.
And with it all hope.
No!
Galvatron has it.
Where's Galvatron? Where is he?
And the answer is
Unicron.
Then we've got to destroy Unicron.
Yes, friends, and now destroy Unicron,
kill the grand poobah,
eliminate even the toughest stains.
No fuss, no muss
Hurry, hurry, hurry, sale must end,
rush right on down and test drive
rightest model with no obligation.
New improved Junkion
planet is sleek sexy import
with turbo handling.
Yeah! Destroy Unicron,
kill the grand poobah,
eliminate even the toughest stains...
Unicron,
Unicron, answer me!
See this,
the Matrix.
I now possess that which you most fear!
You will do my bidding
or taste my wrath.
You underestimate me, Galvatron.
For a time,
I considered sparing
you wretched little planet Cybertron.
Now,
you shall witness it's dismemberment.
No!!!
Decepticons, we're under attack!
Scramble!
I don't believe it!
Doesn't this remind you of anything, Kup?
Nope,
never seen anything like it before.
What happened to Moonbase 2?
Where's my dad?
That's what we're gonna find out.
Patented enamel resists fire
rain and corrosion
for up to 5 years
satisfaction guaranteed.
Or your money back!
Where's Hot Rod?
I don't know,
but I hope they didn't get him.
Quick, this way.
The Matrix!
It will do you no good, Autobot.
It cannot be opened.
Not by a Decepticon!
Like it or not, we are allies now,
against a common foe.
Destroy him, Galvatron, now!
Or you yourself will be obliterated.
Of course, my master.
Puny Autobot,
you lack even Primes courage.
Me Grimlock kick butt.!
Me Grimlock need new strategy.
Help!
Daniel!
Arcee! Kup!
Dad!
Daniel!
Dad, what can I do?
Knock down the acid cover!
How?
Blast it, son!
But I don't have a gun.
Use your exo-suit.
Hurry!
Dad!
Daniel!
You did it!
Yeah, I did it.
Come out, Autobot,
we all must die sometime.
Not today, Galvatron.
I will crush you with my bare hands.
Die, Autobot!
First Prime,
then Ultra Magnus,
and now you.
It's a pity you Autobots die so easily,
or I might have a sense of satisfaction now.
Arise, Rodimus Prime.
Optimus...
No!
This is the end of the road, Galvatron.
Now, light our darkest hour.
Spike, Daniel!
Springer, what's going on?
No time to answer that now,
let's get outta here.
Look!
Autobots, transform and roll out.
I knew you had potential, lad.
Destiny...
You cannot
destroy...
my destiny...
Let this mark the end of the
Cybertronian wars
as we march forward to a new age
of peace and happiness.
Till all are one!
Till all are one...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org