My old man wrote me a letter from prison once.
It said, "If you don't wanna end up like me,
stay away from crime, women and drugs."
Problem is,
it don't leave you with much else to do, does it?
# DURAN DURAN: Planet Earth
# Only came outside
# To watch the nightfall with the rain
# I heard you making patterns rhyme
# Like some New Romantic
# Looking for the TV sound
# You'll see I'm right some other time
# Look now, look all around
# There's no sign of life...
- Put the fucking gun down!
Put the fucking gun down, you Spanish cunt!
Put it down! Fucking put it down!
Don't fucking move, you fat pot-nosed cunt!
Where is it, you fucking little cunt?
# You're looking at Planet Earth
# This is Planet Earth
- Fucking put it down or I'll kill you!
- For fuck's sake, just tell us...
- Where's the fucking gear?
Tell me where the fucking gear is!
Tell me where it is!
Else I swear I'll fucking kill the lot of you!
Where? Where?
Ten years in paradise living the dream.
It had to come to an end one day.
But there was a time when me and the playboy
had the world in our hands.
Anyway, fuck it.
Better to be someone for a day
than no-one for a lifetime.
What is it?
Learjet.
Only way to travel.
Be someone.
I have only one thing to say.
You turn if you want to.
The lady's not for turning.
Someone's had it.
Have it right, woman.
I never lifted your money!
- Leave her alone, Joe.
- It's all right.
I'll sort it.
- Yeah, run along, boy. Do as your mother says.
- You touch her and I'll kill you.
Now get out, you bum.
Be someone.
- What?
- I'm gonna be someone.
And I'm gonna ruin you.
You'll never be anything.
You ain't got the character, boy.
Now, go on, fuck off.
You pay me or else you've fucking had it!
I'm fucking sick of it, do you hear me?
I'm fucking sick of it!
What am I gonna do, Jim?
Fancy a bit of sun?
I'm fucking polo.
I got something needs delivering.
I'll look after you.
Get the bag straight to the man.
If you get lost down there,
just ask for the playboy.
I understand, Jim.
But tell me what's in the bag, please.
Biscuits.
Biscuits...
# FRANKIE GOES TO HOLLYWOOD:
Welcome To The Pleasuredome
# The animals are winding me up
# The jungle call
# Hoo ha, hoo ha
# In Xanadu did Kublai Khan
# A pleasuredome erect
# Moving on, keep moving on, yeah
# Moving at one million miles an hour
# Using my power
# I sell it by the hour
# I have it so I market it
# You really can't afford it, yeah
# You really can't afford it
# Shooting stars never stop
# Even when they reach the top
# There goes a supernova
# What a pushover, yeah
# What a pushover
# We're a long way from home
# Welcome to the Pleasuredome
# On our way home
# Going home where lovers roam
# Long way from home
# Welcome to the Pleasuredome
# MARY JANE GIRLS: All Night Long
# Oh, something's got me so excited, baby
# A feeling I've been holdin' back so long
# You got me shook up, shook down,
shook out on your lovin'
Listen, you'd better fuck off now.
Go on.
Is that my bag?
- Oi, kid. Is that bag for me?
- Yeah.
- So, what's your name, kid?
- Frankie.
Kid Frankie, eh?
Here!
Take it.
So, what's your story?
- I'm just doing what Jimmy asked.
- He said you were from good stock.
Did you look in the bag?
So, what's your plans?
I dunno.
I'll see you out, then.
You had to wonder how this
character ended up on the beaches of Spain.
You drive.
It was never about the money for Charlie.
It was about the power and what went with it.
And could you fucking blame him?
He just loved the lifestyle.
Stay down! Don't look at me!
Don't fucking look at me!
I shit you not, he walked on water.
Everything he touched turned to gold.
His fucking bed made itself in the mornings.
That's how cool he was.
What you fucking do that for, you lunatic?
- You've just fucked us!
- And fucked 'em, he had.
Everyone knew it was the Peckham Four.
There was a national witch-hunt for them.
But the police were too busy nicking
fare-dodgers and junkie bag-snatchers,
while Charlie and the gunman
slipped across the drink towards Spain.
Like I said, he walked on fucking water.
You can drive, can't you?
# LOOSE ENDS: Hangin' On A String
This is where it's at, son.
Look around you.
Shot to pieces back in London.
I tell you what, play your cards right, and I might
give you a job in the club. How's that sound?
- Yeah.
- Good boy.
- Charles! Charles!
- All right, son, how are you?
- All right, Charles?
- Local brasshouse, got it?
- I've never had a brass.
- Never had a brass?
You leave it to me. I'll allocate you a plate later.
- Charlie.
- Ronnie.
Got those couple of cases of Bolly
in the boot of the motor you wanted.
I'll get a barmaid to pick 'em up.
Are you with me tonight?
You ain't wrong, mate. She's given me a pass.
Ronnie, Frankie. Frankie, Ronnie.
As it happens, my Shirl's there shopping.
If you see her, say hello.
I will do. I'll speak to you later.
Come on, we gotta go.
# What did I do wrong?
- All right, Shirl? All right, Nor?
- All right, Charl?
Spending the old man's money?
Fuck me, he's a bit of all right.
Who's the boy?
- It's the Kid Frankie.
- Dish.
Listen, Laura's next door buying a little twinset.
She's got the right hump with you.
Put the car in gear.
- Put the car in gear?
- Put it in gear, put it in gear!
You wanker, Charlie!
I waited for you for three hours last night.
Where was you?
Fucking South London gangster? Look at you.
Cardboard cut-out cunt.
You fucking look like a Paki.
What's the matter with you?
Drive on.
# You, you, you, you
# You got me hangin' on a string now
# Am I your plaything?
# You never told me you were waiting...
Lay so much as a fucking finger on her
and you're dead.
- I weren't looking at her, I swear.
- It's OK, I'm only playing.
That's Carly, my partner's girl.
He's in Gibraltar on a bit of business, but a word
of warning - he's protective and she's...
You know, just leave it at that, eh?
Anyway,
what are we gonna do with you, kid?
I tell you what, there's a party at my bar tonight.
- Do you wanna drive me?
- All right, yeah.
I'll give you a few pesetas. Go and get yourself
some evening wear. Then pick me up.
Hey, Charlie.
Who are you?
Carly, meet the Kid Frankie.
He's driving us about tonight.
# RICK JAMES: Ghetto Life
# When I was a young boy
# Growing up in the ghetto
Are you fucking sure?
You look like
you're about to walk onto Centre Court.
I think you look edible.
# BLONDIE: Heart Of Glass
How you doing?
Lovely to see you again.
All right, mate, how's it going?
- Come over here. Give us a kiss.
- Charlie!
Get them drinks.
Stick it on my tab.
Hello, gorgeous.
I'll speak to you later, sweetheart.
Do you want a drink? You go and have a dance
and I'll bring it over to you.
- I'll have a Babycham.
- All right.
What do you reckon, eh, kid?
Aye aye! Look at him, look.
Get up there!
Look, over here, kid. Here they are.
Charlie! All right there?
Here we go. Aye aye!
How are you doing, son? Ha, ha! There you go.
Are you all right, Ron?
Ronnie, I'll have the same.
Champagne and a beer.
# Mucho mistrust love's gone behind...
Danny, meet the Kid Frankie.
Frankie, meet Danny.
Frankie, Ronnie. Ronnie, Frankie.
You met him earlier. They're with us.
- How are you going, son?
- I'm good, thanks, Ron.
- I'm Ron.
- Listen, Danny's Ronnie's pal.
Ronnie is Sammy's pal
who's my partner who's down in Gibraltar
on a bit of business.
Got it?
- Where are you out of, kid?
- The blue.
Good boy!
My Shirley loves you.
The story goes, Danny and Ronnie
were on the run for a robbery that went wrong.
But their wives, Shirley and Nora,
were more aggressive than the Flying Squad
and hunted them down on the coast.
Taxi!
Here we go, look at that!
Champagne for everyone.
Frankie, you got this, son?
Who's that?
That's the mayor.
All right? Do you want a drink?
He's the main man.
Send him over some champagne, will you?
Good boy.
Ha, ha!
# Once I had love and it was a gas
# Soon turned out to be a pain in the ass
Frankie, are you still with us, kid?
Yeah.
Listen, why don't you stick around for a bit?
We could do with a driver.
Really?
Yeah, why not?
I'll stick you on the payroll
and put you in charge of the Merc.
Not unless you've got to go back to England
for something?
I don't know what to say, Charlie.
Well, don't, then.
I've gotta teach you how to drive, though.
# SIMPLE MINDS: Don't You Forget About Me
# Hey, hey
# Oooh, ooh
Now you try.
# Won't you come see about me?
# I'll be alone dancing...
Hola.
Two cervezas, please.
I'd like to put you over this bar
and fuck you in the arse.
¿Qué?
#...inside and out
# Slow change may pull us apart
# When the light gets into your heart, baby
# Don't you
# Forget about me
# Don't, don't, don't, don't...
Two beers, please. I suppose sucking my cock's
out of the question?
I suppose it is, seeing as my old man's
over there and he's a big cunt.
# I say la, la, la, la...
- ¿Dónde va? ¿Dónde va?
- What?
- ¿Qué pasa contigo?
- Don't keep touching me.
Fuck off inside, you're out of your depth!
Keep your hands to yourself! What's the matter
with you? You served lunch on a dirty plate!
Excuse me. Fuck off!
Who the fuck is that?
That's my partner, Sammy.
Fuck off! Go on, then, do you want some?
- Fuck off!
- ¿Sammy, cómo estás?
Ha, ha!
Quick! The sharks are gonna get you!
Drop the steps. Come on, lively!
Come on, boy. In you come.
There he is! Ha, ha!
Come on.
Come on. Up you get, come on.
Get up here.
- Straight up. What happened?
- What a cunt, the geezer!
No surprises for guessing
which one he was in the robbery.
The geezer was so hard,
even his nightmares were scared of him.
What you do that for, you lunatic?
You've fucked us!
We've gotta go on our fucking toes now.
Well, good. I hate this fucking weather, anyway.
Sammy had been in Gibraltar
helping a flamenco singer called Carlos,
who was being bullied
by some Dutch drug smugglers
that were using his house by the sea
as a lookout
to bring marijuana in from Morocco.
# MARTHA AND THE MUFFINS: Echo Beach
Everything's gonna be all right.
If Charlie was the playboy,
Sammy was the businessman.
And he knew if he had Carlos in his pocket,
he could smuggle drugs from Africa himself.
- Carry on, Charlie.
- ¡Gillipollas!
Hey, I said sorry. Now leave it.
And drugs, unlike the waiter, were the future.
# On a silent summer evening
the sky's alive with lights
And that was Sammy, the partner.
He was a bit like Robin Hood, apart from the fact
he robbed anyone and gave to himself,
and probably killed their families just for fun.
Nice fellow, eh?
Charming, don't you think?
And from the moment he met me,
he fucking hated me.
He was only trying to serve me lunch
on a dirty plate. You know what I'm like.
- You will eat in low-end places, won't you?
- Low-end?
They charge an absolute fucking fortune in
there. I should have glassed every one of 'em.
Sammy, this is the Kid Frankie.
He drives us now.
Did you miss me?
Terribly.
How was Gibraltar?
Ream, Charl.
I've got this singer Carlos in our pocket.
He's even coming down the club tonight.
This little Dutch firm, they're finished.
Carlos is ours.
Do me a favor, go and sort yourself out
and tell me about it when we get home.
You're bleeding over the fucking deck.
# BUGGLES: Video Killed The Radio Star
#...killed the radio star
# In my mind
# And in my car
# We can't rewind cos...
- Darling, it's horizontal strokes.
Let me finish.
Oh, oh-oh, oh
I like that bit.
- What was it?
- Horizontal strokes.
Sorry.
Listen, Charl.
What?
I really appreciate what you've done for me.
But...
... maybe I should go now.
I don't wanna get in the way here.
It's all right, son. You're with me.
I told you, don't worry about Sammy.
He's wild, but he's got a good heart.
Anyway, fuck all that bollocks.
There's a party down at the club tonight.
I need you to drive us.
That Dutch firm might show up.
Wanna come for a swim, Frankie?
#...broke your heart
# Put the blame on VCR
# You are
# A radio star
# Video killed the radio star
I'm Carlos and I'm pleased to meet you.
And you, Carlos.
Sammy tells me you've got a little problem
we might be able to help you with.
I'm hoping so, please.
You're with us now, son.
You ain't gotta worry
about them fucking Dutch mugs any more.
We'll take care of that for you.
I've gotta tell you,
you look better on the LP covers
than you do in the flesh.
What happened? You look fucked.
Ah, los banderos ingleses.
- What's he say?
- He said you are criminals from England.
- Tell him to fuck off.
- No, no, no, whoa.
No.
Offer him some champagne.
From us.
Go on.
That's the mayor.
- Looks like a fucking iron.
- He probably is.
Ingleses,
muchas gracias.
You're welcome.
# A FLOCK OF SEAGULLS: I Ran
Oh!
Sammy, the Dutch are in the club.
Danny, the Dutch are here. Let's go!
Ronnie, they're here!
Come on.
Move it!
Go and sit in the corner.
We've got aggro, Charles. The Dutch.
Charles, cop for it.
# I walked along the avenue
# I never thought I'd meet a girl like you
# Meet a girl like you
- No. Not in here.
# With auburn hair and tawny eyes
# The kind of eyes that hypnotize me through
# Hypnotise me through
# And I ran
# I ran so far away
# I just ran
# I ran all night and day
I wasn't that stupid.
I knew the difference between right and wrong
and I knew I should have gone,
right there and then.
But as much as I was out of my depth,
something kept pulling me back.
Give us a kiss.
Give us a kiss!
Come here, boy.
Put that out.
Right, here are the rules.
You take her shopping,
you let her get what she wants.
You take her to lunch,
you let her eat what she wants.
But you take her to a bar drinking
and that's when we fall out.
I get back from Gibraltar and I find she's drunk,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
We understand each other?
And one last thing,
you even think about trying to get hold of her...
Sammy, I'd never do that. She's your lady.
All right. We'll be back just before sunset.
OK. Good luck with the Dutch.
Shut your mouth about the Dutch.
It's nothing to do with you.
While Sammy and Charlie went
to make a deal with the Dutch,
I had to look after the snake.
The way she fucked with people's heads,
I should have stayed in bed.
# BELOUIS SOME: Imagination
Would you like to see the menu?
A bottle of Bollinger, please.
- No.
- Please.
- One glass.
- No.
- I'll tell Sammy you raped me.
One glass.
A bottle, please.
# Only you can understand the way I feel tonight
# She blamed excesses
on the American Dream
# So seldom witnessed
# Never seen
# Ha, ha, ha, ha
# Imagination
# Could make a man of you
# Could make me love you too
# Imagination
# Is all I want from you
- Fuck!
- Me?
Shut up a minute. They're back.
- How are you supposed to drive me in that?
- Are you sober?
Can I smell your breath?
It's all right. Remember, you haven't had a drink.
Maybe.
Dirty fucking Dutch!
Liberty-taking...
Hi, darling.
Hey, Charlie.
- You seen what they've done to the Merc?
- What's happened to you?
They've fucking shot the car to pieces,
that's what they've done.
Get Danny and Ronnie and
tell them we need them at the club tonight.
Oi!
I said, get Danny and Ronnie and get yourself
back here. We need to check this lot's working.
You're bleeding everywhere.
You'd better get up the hospital.
- Five is a prime number, innit, Charl?
- Don't fucking drive me mad, Sam.
It's half down to you that I've got this.
I asked you,
what about the Dutch firm?
Are they heavy? Do we do business with them?
No, not you.
Not Sammy Brooks.
He wants to run around fucking killing people.
What do you reckon, boys? Nice, eh?
Not the espadrilles.
You need heels, babe.
I'm obviously not gonna wear it
with fucking espadrilles. I was just showing you.
- Sweet?
- Amazing.
- Ain't nothing getting through these vests.
- Good.
Try it on me.
Yeah? How far?
From about where you was.
- Are you ready?
- Go on, then.
Fuck!
Any good?
Fuck. Still here, ain't I?
My turn, Charl. Use the shotgun.
- Are you sure?
- Go on.
Ready?
Ready.
Sammy?
Sammy? Are you all right, son?
Might start wearing one of these
all the time, Charl.
You should do. It'll help you sleep better.
It's like a kick up the bollocks, Charl.
It's a blinder.
Here you are.
You try it.
What?
Put the vest on.
Sammy, what are you doing?
What?
Fuck.
- This is fucking madness. I don't want to...
- Oh, shut up!
Here, are you all right?
Kid?
Are you all right, son? Come on.
Are you all right?
Fucking liberty.
- What?
- You know what.
What do you mean? He's all right.
Go on, stick him in the boot if he's moaning.
Don't worry, son. You'll live.
What's the matter? You're off, ain't you?
It's just that... I'm just...
It's all right, don't worry.
You ain't gotta explain nothing to me.
It's just, it ain't a bit of me, Charl.
I ain't one of yous.
Here, look, come here.
Here, take it.
Any time you want a holiday,
you come and see me, all right?
Don't, don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it. You just make sure
you come and see me again.
You'll be all right, you know that, don't you?
Am I?
Course you fucking are. You've got character.
Anyway, look, I've gotta go and sort out
these Dutch cunts.
I'll see you later.
Take care.
Ta-ta.
The way I saw it,
it was go back to London and wank my life away
playing Donkey Kong in the kebab house
or sign up to a life of crime, women and drugs.
What else was I gonna fucking do?
# SHANNON: Let The Music Play
# Let the music
# Just to groove
# This groove again
# No, no, once again now
# Let the music
# He'll come back
It's eight miles straight across
from Morocco to Gibraltar.
Every night, we had one chance when
the Navy patrol boats were far enough apart
for us to sneak our dinghies full of drugs
through the middle.
And it weren't easy, our line of work.
Cos you had to get up around five, have some
paella, if you're lucky, a bit of shrimp,
then wait for night.
We prayed for clouds
so they could give us that extra bit of cover.
Even then, Sammy was the only one
that made the call.
Sometimes we misjudged the timings
of the patrol boats.
And as I wiped Moroccan kids' brains off me,
I questioned my morals.
But with the amount of money at stake
and Sammy breathing down my neck,
there was no time for regret.
It ain't good news. We've lost a few of 'em.
Oh, well, you live and learn.
Unless you're a dead kid.
It was Danny and Ronnie's job to get the puff
from the dealers,
load up the boats with the barrels and make
sure the mules headed in the right direction.
Unless it was Ramadan.
Fucking Holy Month costs us fortunes,
because parents wouldn't let their kids go,
even when we doubled their carry money.
But we got round it. We went to the orphanages.
Sammy was the eye in the sky
and everything went on his order.
He was the only one
that could give the green light.
Me and Charlie were on beach patrol.
It was our job to make sure
the kids didn't run off with our drugs.
They're thieving cunts, Moroccans,
it's in their blood.
So we'd grab 'em out the dinghies, sling 'em
in the back of our van before they could run off,
then we'd drive into the Linea, switch lorries
and send the puff off to Madrid to be sealed.
The bath is empty. I repeat,...
...the bath is empty.
- Go! Go!
# Shooting stars never stop
- Go!
# Even when they reach the top
# Shooting stars never stop
# There goes a supernova
# What a pushover
# Yeah
- Come on, then, you little fucking pikeys!
- Come on!
Come on, venga! Venga!
# We're a long way from home
With the Dutch out the way, we changed
the way drugs were smuggled into England.
We slashed the prices
and drove them through the Continent.
Our operation grew so big,
I was bringing my mates down to help.
I lived to regret it cos, like Moroccans,
South Londoners are thieving cunts
and couldn't keep their hands to themselves.
Fuck Frankie!
And the ginger cunt.
He looks like Ronald Mc-fucking-Donald.
You shoot your mate in the foot, you can go.
If not, Ronnie'll shoot you in the foot.
Sam, please, I can't shoot him,
he's my fucking pal.
- Ronnie!
- All right, all right.
Leave it out, Dan.
I've known you since I was five.
Fucking hell. I'm sorry, mate, I've gotta do it
or I'm gonna get fucking shot.
Look what you made me do.
Sorry, mate.
Argh! Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
Ronnie!
Leave it out, Sam. They're kids.
Argh!
Fucking hell!
And you,
you'd get one right through the fucking nut
if you wasn't Charlie's boy.
The funny thing was,
as my life got bigger,
my world got smaller.
The more money we made,
the less time we spent enjoying it.
Sammy cut away anyone he didn't need.
Every day above ground
was a result around him.
No-one was safe. I'm telling you, fucking no-one.
Sam, there's a geezer out front
wants to see you.
Who is it?
One of the mayor's lot.
Hello, English. How are you?
What do you fucking want?
The mayor is having a dinner party
at his residence this evening.
He has requested your company.
What for?
That's between you and him.
A party, eh?
We expect you at six.
It's glamorous casual.
Tell your man we'll be there.
- OK.
I tell my man you'll be there.
Whatever. Come on.
Listen, we can't exactly blank him.
We'll make a night of it.
- What's fucking glamorous casuals, anyway?
- I'd better dust my tux off, eh?
What for?
For the party.
No need to bother, Dan.
Oh, yeah, Sam? Why's that?
What do you think, Ron?
What's that mean? You dropping us?
No-one's dropping anyone.
But some things are for us only.
- All right?
- I thought we were all partners.
Well, we fucking well ain't partners, Ron.
You and your pal are on the payroll.
So don't start getting fucking lemon.
There was never talk of partnerships.
You both fucking knew the deal
and we've looked after you.
Sammy, are you fucking winding us up?
No, I'm not winding you up, Ron.
Ronnie, come on.
Let's go.
- What do you reckon?
- Fuck 'em. They're gonna have to swallow.
Listen, Frank, this ain't like the real world.
Every cunt on this coast is your pal
when you're looking after 'em.
The next day, they wanna fuck you,
and the day after that,
they wanna be your pal again.
It's a fucking dog business.
What about you?
Me?
I'm different.
Fucking hell, kid. This is where you wanna be.
Three years, this'll be mine.
Nice gun.
Tell the mayor
he's got a fantastic place here.
Ask him if we can rent one of the wings.
Le gusta tu casa.
Dice que, "Es posible arrendar un ala aquí?"
Lo primero que me interesa saber
es qué es lo que están trayendo
en los botes aquellos?
What's he say?
He said, "Thank you."
And?
He would like to know
what are you bringing on the boats?
What boats?
Dice, "Qué botes?"
Dile que, en este mundo, todo
se puede arreglar si uno conoce la gente clave.
He say anything is possible
if you know the right people.
Amigos?
Amigos.
OK.
Una cosa más. Y es muy importante.
Con la coca, no.
Marijuana, ningún problema.
Siguen trayendola, bueno.
Pero, si con la coca, hay problema.
There is one thing you must know.
The cocaine.
You must never bring it onto his coast.
The marijuana is OK.
But if you sell the cocaine, it is a problem.
And if there is a problem,
you lose.
Buenos amigos, eh?
Amigos.
Ese chico
me lo sientan al lado para la cena?
He's saying he would like
to sit next to you for dinner.
Tell him it's OK.
# DAVID BOWIE: Modern Love
# I know when to go out
# I know when to stay in
# Get things done
# I catch the paperboy
# But things don't really change
# I'm standing in the wind...
What do you reckon?
- Oi-oi!
- Wahay!
# Never gonna fall for modern love
# Walks beside me
# Modern love
# Walks on by
- I think we should knock down that wall, darling.
- Whatever you want.
Get rid of all that Spanishified shit.
I want red, black and chrome everywhere.
See that terracotta? It's gotta go.
I want marble throughout.
- My gun cabinet?
- Can't you put them under the bed?
#...God and man
# God and man
# No confessions
# No religion
# God and man
# Don't believe in...
That should take care of it.
Now fuck off out of my house.
He means it.
Now, be careful, there's a day's money in there.
Go on.
And keep the change, you Toby.
Oooh! Ha, ha!
- I think that was out, Charl.
- Sammy, it was in.
- No, that's... Carl?
- Ace.
- No, it was out, Charl.
- It was in.
It was fucking out! Don't fucking cheat!
- Cunt.
Sammy, it was in!
I ain't playing, Charl.
Oi!
- I ain't playing no more, Charlie. And you.
You sad fuck.
Come on, mate.
# Never gonna fall for
# Modern love
# Walks beside me
# Walks on by
# Modern love
# Gets me to the church on time
# Church on time
# Terrifies me
# Puts my trust in God...
With the mayor on our side,
we fucking smashed it.
As long as we wet his beak
and stayed away from cocaine, he loved us.
While the English police sat around scratching
their canisters wondering how we did it,
we opened the club for Sunday lunch,
sat back and enjoyed our roast.
¡Hola! Magazine.
Leave off, Sam, please.
We only wanna have
a bit of roast dinner.
We don't know
what we're supposed to have done.
Sammy, come on, it's Sunday.
- Fuck 'em, Charl, they're not welcome.
- Come on, Sammy, sit down.
Come on.
It's all right, lads.
- Sit down, enjoy your dinner.
- Don't worry about him. Come on, sit down.
Come on.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, look at it.
Cunt.
Ain't got a bit of class.
Thinks it's the bollocks
cos its old man's warm.
I think she's lovely.
- You're just jealous.
- Fuck off!
- Shut up. What do you know? It's just a brass.
- That's rich.
Charlie, Frankie, come here.
Come here.
I'd give a grand to fuck you, boy.
If you thought that was bad,
it was nothing compared to what the chef said.
- We've run out of lamb.
- You're joking?
# TALK TALK: It's My Life
# I've asked myself
# How much do you...
#...commit yourself?
# Don't you forget
# Caught in the crowd
# It never ends
Come here. Charl.
- What?
- See the state of these feet.
Come here.
Go on, girls!
Wahay!
Come on, Ronnie!
Here, you wanna sort your old woman out!
# Two potato, three potato, four
# Five potato, six potato
Go on, love, give it the old...
Wahay!
Hi, Charlie.
How is he?
Please don't blow him out.
You all right, mate?
Yeah. You?
Like my pool?
Yeah, it's lovely.
What are we gonna do, Charl?
- Can we just wipe our mouth and move on?
- No.
I can't just wipe my mouth.
Listen, Sam,
you got Carly, you got your place up here.
We're moving in different directions now.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I wanna do my own thing for a while,
see how it goes.
Just cos I nicked your watch for a fucking laugh?
It's not a fucking laugh, Sam.
You planted it on Frankie and he's my mate.
Well, you've only known that cunt five minutes.
I've known you all my fucking life, Charl.
Don't make this difficult, Sam.
I'll still be about.
I just wanna do my own thing for a bit.
Don't give me them eyes.
The good thing about drugs is
they make you feel good.
The bad thing about drugs is
they make you greedy.
# THE KNACK: My Sharona
What is it?
The future.
Cocaine.
Pure.
What about the mayor?
Fuck the mayor.
What do you reckon, kid? Good buzz?
Fantastic. My cock's shrunk
and I can't feel my neck.
What's the plan?
Well, I've got the Colombians sweet,
I've got the pilots sweet,
I've got the drop zone sweet.
Now all we need to do
is get the fucking mayor sweet.
Come on, kid, think. This is worth fortunes.
How about we stick someone into the mayor?
- A sacrifice.
- Who's gonna do that?
Think about it. He likes boys. My mate Sonny,
a right skaghead in London, right,
absolute fucking heroin addict.
You know what they're like when they're
clucking. They'll do anything for a fix.
- Exactly.
- Can he be got?
What a fucking amazing plan, eh?
Cocaine junkie rent boys and a corrupt mayor.
And this is how it was gonna work.
Flying the white from Colombia
straight to London was too hot by now.
So the South Americans had more produce
than they could shift. That's where we came in.
They'd fly it as far as Morocco
and, from there, we'd switch planes
and run it across the Gibraltar Straits like before.
# M-M-My Sharona
But it weren't like marijuana.
We couldn't afford to lose one package.
It was worth too much.
But if our sacrifice worked
and we kept the mayor sweet...
... we'd wind up with more money
than we could dream of.
Ah, I'm so pleased
you invited me down here, Frankie.
- I don't know how I'll be able to repay you.
- I'm sure you'll find a way.
So, what was it you said you wanted me to do?
Oh, just meet some fella.
- What's he buying?
- A bit of this, son, a bit of that.
Usual stuff.
Sweet. You know, I'm so glad I'm clean again,
otherwise I'd be in a squat in Peckham
with a needle hanging out my arm.
Clean? I thought you said
he was bang in trouble, you cunt.
Fuck it. We'll get him drunk.
Give us my Wilson.
- What's that?
- A putter.
Ow! Fuck!
Sorry, I'm a bit rusty.
I see it didn't take you long
to buck up with your mates again.
Well, no-one else wanted me.
Seeing as me and Ronnie are old pals
and went to school together,
it seemed stupid to fall out
over something so silly.
- Why don't you fucking grow up, Sam?
- I wish I could, Charl.
- How are you two doing, anyway?
- Yeah, not bad.
- Just brushing up with my irons.
- It looks that way.
Here, can't you find
your own fucking club to play in?
- I'm a member.
- Hark at it. It talks.
- That's what they say about you.
- Yeah?
It's a bit strong, innit,
coming from a known grass?
Fucking grass?
Who did you get that from?
- Danny.
- How come you've never done any bird, then?
Cos I'm sensible, prick.
Talking of pricks, how are you doing, Frankie?
- All right, boys?
- All right, Carl?
- How are you, darling?
- All right, Frankie.
- How are you?
- Shut up, you slag.
Fuck off, Sammy. Don't try and make
a fool of me in front of your mates.
Birdie.
We had more coke
than we could handle.
The more we sent back home,
the more they wanted it.
And by 1987, London was covered
in a white blanket.
Every fucking one was at it.
From city boys to rent boys,
yuppie girls to call girls.
There were even stories of the Royals getting
stuck in, banging it up their fucking toffee noses.
Maybe that's why she called her son Charlie.
And how do you think she survived
on four hours' sleep a night?
In our own little way,
we were shaping the future of our country.
After cocaine, it would never be the same.
It brought us together, pulled us apart,
made us sell our souls as well as our mates.
It was a glorious time.
#...for the touch of the younger kind
# My, my, my
# Aye, aye
# Whoa!
And as long as we kept this old bastard happy
and Sonny did his job,
it was never gonna end.
He say you have the face of a film star.
Well, tell him, I said thanks.
And I've actually been thinking
about getting into acting when I get home.
Dice que gustaría ser un actor.
Fantástico!
Dile que si quiere ser un actor,
yo tengo algo que mostrarle.
He say...
if you want to be an actor,
he has something to show you.
Yeah?
Come on, toilet. Come on.
I fucking love them Colombians!
I thought it'd be a fucking bag, wouldn't you?
- What for?
- Fucking old knob.
Fuck him. Come on.
It's still welcome. Fuck that.
Hey!
Chico.
Amigos.
Yeah, mate. Amigos.
Amigos, huh?
Argh!
Hijo de puta! Cabrón!
- Hijo de puta!
- Fucking hell, that was quick.
Jesus, Sonny, what did you do to him?
He whipped his cock out,
so I done him in the arse.
Good boy. Did he like it?
I don't know. Do you want me to stick it in yours
and you can find out?
No. No, you're all right, mate.
I'd do anyone that wants to know.
# ROXY MUSIC: Avalon
# Now the party's over
# I'm so tired
# Then I see you coming...
I'm gonna fuck you so good, you'll be buying me
diamonds from Cartier by the morning.
But as much as I wanted to,
I couldn't.
It was the one thing I swore I'd never do.
# Avalon
Everybody knows who you are back in London.
They couldn't believe it when I said
I was coming to do work for you.
Good for you, son.
No, I'm all right.
Everyone's talking about your bar.
It's like Charlie's Bar this, Charlie's Bar that.
They love it back in Peckham.
One day, I'm gonna have a bar like yours.
I'm gonna do it up like Peppermint Park,
get all my mates down...
Shut up, Sonny, for fuck's sakes!
You're doing my swede in.
The playground is full. Fly by, fly by.
Charlie.
Qué hace con este chulo de mierda
en este huerto?
He says, "What are you doing
hanging around in the orange groves
with this vicious little cunt?"
What does it look like? I'm having a stroll.
Dice que un paseo.
- Cocaína.
- He say...
- I know what he said.
- Ya te lo dije antes.
Si quiere jugar bandero en buena parte,
aquí no. En mi territorio, no.
Porque es un problema, y problema serio, eh?
He warn you that
if you want to play Wild West on his coast...
...it is a problem.
So, ask him what he wants.
Come on, hurry up, for fuck's sakes.
I'm getting sunburn.
- He says he wants nothing.
- Good. That's that, then.
Hey, ingleses.
There is problem.
Yeah, whatever.
Jules. Come on, boy.
Please stay with me tonight. I can't bear
to go back to him after being with you.
I wish I could.
I've gotta go meet these fucking Colombians.
What for? Can't it wait?
Baby, if I could get out of it, I would.
Do you really think I wanna be standing
on a hillside near Estepona all night?
What time are you meeting them?
Can't you come after that?
It's not till sunset.
I'll try and come and see you after.
- Good boy.
- Listen to me.
This is our secret, all right?
If Charlie finds out, he'll fucking kill me.
Our secret.
You're unbelievable.
Where the fucking hell have you been?
You were meant to be
at the drop zone an hour ago.
What have you been doing?
Sipping that shit?
- Oh, and you ain't?
- Get out my fucking chair!
What's that smell?
- Smells like perfume.
Shut up, Son!
No-one asked you.
- It is fucking perfume. Who's been here?
- It's mosquito spray. They're everywhere.
- That fucking mayor's on us!
- Why? Where did you see him?
Listen, we've gotta keep the Colombians sweet,
otherwise they'll fuck us off!
We don't wanna fall out with them.
All right. I'll speak to 'em.
No, I'll fucking speak to 'em.
It's better coming from me.
Really?
Maybe you should take it easy with that, Charl.
Don't fucking tell me what I can and can't do.
You're only where you are
cos I fucking put you there.
Now get your coat.
We've gotta go and sort this out.
Move!
Fancy a game of Pacman, Frank?
# OMD: Maid Of Orleans
How the fuck did Sammy know we was here?
- Hector.
- Charlie.
How are you?
Good to see you. OK?
Good to see you. You all right?
How are you doing, mate?
How's it going?
I was just telling our friends here
how you're always late.
Sorry about what happened earlier.
Unwanted company. Won't happen again.
We change our drop.
It's too risky there.
They building hotels everywhere.
Yeah, I kept telling him, "Move down the coast,
it's too hot for us round here."
Sí. Your partner is wise.
You should listen to him.
Anyway, it's done now.
We're all here.
Let's just wipe our mouths of what happened
and move forward, eh?
So, why not a big drop next?
We can move double the amount.
Can you handle that?
Can we handle it?
What do you think we are? Spanish?
- I like your partner, Charlie. He has mucho ball.
- Yeah.
We've known each other since we were kids.
He's one of your own.
Well, we'll speak on telephone.
Same call box, same time.
For sure.
- Bye, Charlie.
- Take care.
Safe journey.
What the fucking hell are you playing at, Sam?
How did you know we was here?
What are you doing slipping in on my deal?
Listen, Charl, that's not important now.
Keep your fucking deal.
We've all got the same problem
to deal with right now.
Which is?
- The mayor.
- So?
What are we gonna do? Kill the geezer?
Yeah.
Here, one of you two talk some sense
into this fucking div.
What else are we gonna do?
- What do you mean?
Well, what else are we gonna do?
Shut up shop and fuck off back to Peckham?
Bollocks.
This geezer can close us down in an hour.
You.
Now, I don't wanna be your mate,
but am I talking bollocks here?
Can he be got at?
Course he can be got at. Anyone can be got at.
We do this one thing together
and then we go our own way.
No agg.
You got any tools?
Bring 'em.
Ta-ta, Charles.
How the fuck did they know we was here?
I don't fucking know.
Like I told you earlier,
- drugs make you greedy.
- Bollocks.
And we were about to blow the lot,
down to cocaine.
We'd fucked with the old country.
They'd had enough.
They shut us down, took away everything we
had before we could even chop out another line.
But we were so out of our heads,
we couldn't even see it coming.
We were about to learn the hard way.
Here you are, have some of that.
Wait here a minute.
Oh, what do you fucking want, you snake?
- Shut up, bitch. Where's Ronnie?
- Akip!
Fucking wake him, then.
Leave off, he'll fucking kill me.
I'll kill you, if you don't. Go and wake him.
Fuck.
What do you want?
We ain't got nowhere to sleep.
What did you fucking wake me up for?
Why didn't you just let 'em in?
Fuck off.
Hurry up.
All right, mush, keep it down. I'll buzz you in.
Are you still awake?
I'm hardly gonna be asleep, am I?
Listen.
We'll get the mayor out of the way
in the morning.
We'll be back in business by lunchtime.
We've gotta open the club.
Sonny reckons he's throwing a party
tomorrow night.
He couldn't throw a tennis ball.
Hey, Charl, I've been thinking about
getting one of them Learjets.
The only way to travel.
How much?
No, you buy into 'em.
Like share it with a pop star.
Maybe Madonna.
Holiday?
No.
For work and that.
You know what I might do next?
Go on.
Slip down to South America.
I reckon we'd crack it down there.
Plot up,
send the odd parcel home.
We'd be caked in six weeks.
Fly backwards and forwards in the Lear.
That's it.
Now you're talking.
We're really living, ain't we?
Every fucking minute.
Sweet.
- Where did you kip?
Ronnie's. You?
Round my mate's time-share.
Are you ready for this?
Course I fucking am. Couldn't get no tools.
Have a peep in the boot.
Are you fit?
Come on.
- Let's do this lively.
- I've gotta take the kids to the beach.
Right, who's gonna go and have a look about?
- Any volunteers?
- We'll do spuds, eh, Charl?
One potato, two potato, three potato, four.
Five potato, six potato, seven potato, more.
Ron.
I tell you what, this is bollocks.
Good fuck, was she?
Better than I thought.
But seeing as she hadn't come in
a couple of years, what else did I expect?
You're a fucking...
What, Sam? What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna shoot me on the spot?
Blow your chances here?
You're a mug.
You always have been.
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna put one right through your nut.
If you get out, you ginger cunt.
Wait.
Come on.
Remember when I told you
me and the playboy had the world in our hands?
Well, it passed.
Don't you fucking move!
Put that fucking gun down now! Don't you move!
Don't fucking move!
You fucking cunt! Take that!
# Look now, look all around
# There's no sign of life
# Voices, another sound
- Where is it?
- Tell us where it is, for fuck's sake!
Tell me where the fucking gear is!
Tell me!
Else I swear I'll fucking kill the lot of you!
- Where is it?
- La cocina.
- Where?
Get in. You fucking move, you little fucking prick,
and I'll kill you!
I'm fucking telling you,
don't you dare fucking move, you little cunt!
- Stay there!
- I've got it! Sweet!
See you all in the port, five minutes. And lively.
Come on, we're on. Come on.
# ADAM AND THE ANTS:
Kings Of The Wild Frontier
- You look like you need some sleep, my friend.
- Whatever. Got the money?
Hang on.
Come on, lively.
Es mierda.
- What?
- He says washing powder.
What are you talking about, washing powder?
Fuck you, you cunt!
I'll fucking do you right round the canister!
Go on, fuck off!
# I feel beneath the white
Just when I felt
things couldn't get worse, they did.
We couldn't even flog a fucking ounce of Persil.
We'd no more Rolexes and Porsches left to sell.
There was only one thing for it.
I don't know how much of this I've got left in me.
Shut up, you little cunt. You're all right.
All we need to do is get a grand together
and we're back in business.
I've got these Algerians sweet up in Cádiz.
We'll go to work with them.
Oh, I'm fucking sick of running around!
Fucking gyp for a few poxy parking tickets.
Look, Frankie.
It's Nora and Shirley.
So?
Don't you remember?
Remember what?
Remember when Shirley said
she'd give you a grand to fuck you?
No way, Charl.
Charl!
Hello, girls.
How are you doing?
- Bloody hell.
- What happened?
I've been decorating my new place.
Listen, Shirl, I'm really sorry
about what happened to Ronnie.
I bet you are.
Look, it's Frankie down there.
- You remember him, don't you?
- Jesus, he looks terrible.
Looks like a fucking pikey.
He's OK,
he's been helping me decorate.
Still got the look, though, ain't he?
I'll be back in a minute, all right? Don't move.
- What's he on?
- He's off his fucking trolley.
Listen, we could be on here.
Get in the bar and have a wash.
Fuck off, Charl, no way.
Listen, boy, there's a fucking grand at stake.
Now, get in there now!
Charl, I'm not... I'm not fucking
brassing myself off to them wretches.
- You fucking are!
- I ain't.
If you don't, I'll shoot you.
Now, get in there now! And wash your cock.
And get a semi.
So you're all right, girls?
- What are you doing around here?
- Been in Gib getting fags.
Yeah. Good earner, the salmon.
Here, listen.
Do you remember
when you used to like my little Frankie?
- Yeah, yeah, he was a nice kid.
- No, but I mean...
- Remember when you used to really like him?
- He was gorgeous. Looks fucked now, though.
Fucked?
I wouldn't say that. He's still got the rogue smile.
He needs a good bath, if you ask me.
Listen.
Do you wanna fuck him,
the pair of you, for a grand?
- Eh?
- You said you'd give a grand to fuck him.
Fucking hell.
That was years ago, man.
Listen.
Just put your fucking bag and keys
on the back seat and fuck off!
Hurry up!
- Fuck off!
- What's going on?
- What's it look like? Get the keys. Start the car.
- I'm sorry, girls.
You two really had it once, do you know that?
Look at the fucking state of you now!
Just get in the fucking car!
You fucking... You should be ashamed of
yourselves. You used to be so fucking cool.
Shame on you, boys!
Fucking wankers!
- Fuck off back to your caravan, you pikeys!
- You fucking poofs!
- Shit cunts!
- Come on, come on.
What do you want?
Give him a Stuyvesant.
- What?
- Rothman.
Rough man? Rough man? Fucking Rothman.
Give him a Rothman, the cunt.
Yeah, he'll be wearing a blue tracksuit.
Ta-da.
Fucking mosquitoes are everywhere!
Stop fucking driving me mad about mosquitoes.
- You're going to Cádiz.
- Why aren't you coming?
It only needs one of us.
What's up? Are you fucking scared?
I don't even know where Cádiz is.
It sounds like a load of bollocks to me,
sitting around,
waiting for fucking Algerian sailors
with green hats,
bags of gear in run-down ports.
Leave me out.
Qué gillipollas.
Cerveza.
Sss-ss!
A funny thing.
It's a lot quieter on the way down
than the journey up.
No-one wants you around
when you've got nothing left.
I wanted out so badly
but I couldn't just walk away with nothing.
Freeze!
Jesus!
Charl.
What's happened to you?
You all right, Sonny?
You look like you've gone right to the front.
I took your old bar on, Charl.
Done it up like I said.
It's really cracking on.
Where's Frankie?
He's on his way back from Cádiz.
You seen any of the others?
- I don't see anyone. Not after what happened.
- What about my Sammy?
You hear things,
but no, I ain't seen him in years.
I just keep my nut down.
If it weren't so hot,
I'd say come down there for a drink.
Yeah?
Maybe I will.
- They still want you here. I'd give it a wide.
- Tell you what.
We'll have a reunion party.
- What for?
- What do you mean, what for?
I can pull a crowd like
you've never seen before, son.
I'm not saying that.
I don't know, Charl. It's just...
I don't know, Charlie.
Yeah, yeah. That's what we'll do.
We'll get the old firm back for a night.
Be fucking blinding.
It's changed down there, Charl.
I don't mean no offence,
but you can't just steam in.
No offence?
I ain't just fucking steaming in, boy.
That club's still mine.
Well, legally it's mine, actually.
Hark at him, all the long words now.
Come on, son, it'll be blinding.
One little night.
For old times' sake.
Listen, you go and sort out the balloons,
and I'm gonna put the word out that I'm back.
Who to?
Fucking everyone!
Just like the old days, eh?
Yeah, like the old days.
I nearly got my throat cut in Cádiz, Charl.
Don't that tell you anything?
Listen...
Get loads of balloons, pink ones.
I like them fucking massive ones
with "party" written on them.
Don't buy the kiddy ones,
they're a waste of money.
Oh, and er... find out where Sammy lives.
I want to surprise him.
The good thing about losing everything
was there was nothing else to lose.
I had one last plan,
one last person who could help me.
Whether she liked it or not...
we had unfinished business.
So it's not just a rumor.
What?
You do look like shit.
Thanks.
How would you know?
I always ask after you.
If that's true, why did you fuck me over?
You didn't need me to fuck your life, Frankie.
You did that yourself.
Frankie...
I can't work you out.
I've got to go.
Sammy'll be wondering where I am.
Is that it?
Read it.
Right, let's have a look at you.
Fucking hell, look at the state of you.
Come here.
That's it.
That's better.
Right.
You look terrific.
What about me?
Ream, Charl.
You look ream.
Yeah.
Have a look at this.
Look at that.
Got it?
We're still the bollocks.
Come on, let's get out there.
# SLY FOX: Let's Go All The Way
# Let's go all the way
# We can make a better way
Listen, have you got the gun sorted out?
Just make sure it's empty, all right? All right.
Maybe I should have driven across the border
there and then.
Gone through the slips while I still could.
But there was one thing left I had to take care of.
And if the plan was right, I was going to enjoy it
more than the first time I got high.
Did someone order a cunt?
Cos one's just showed up.
Listen, I've got a bit of work.
Do you want in?
Why shouldn't I just kill you?
Cos I've got a drop lined up.
- What sort of drop?
- A large one.
White.
Why come to me?
You're the only one
that knows what they're doing.
Go and wait by the gate.
Carly, get me a pistol.
Something I can hide.
It's got a full clip. What do you want it for?
Never mind.
Give us a kiss.
Frankie, listen.
I know we ain't got along too well
over the years, had our ups and downs,
but I really appreciate the fact that
we can do a bit of business together now.
To be honest,
you was the first person I thought of.
You're the only one I can trust.
I really appreciate that.
You're a good kid.
I hope this is the start of something new for us.
How much did you say there was?
It'll be worth the walk.
We ain't got to get in there, have we?
That's where it's coming.
It's other people's shit and piss.
They won't mind.
Here you are, get ready for them.
They're coming.
Look.
There must be more.
I don't believe it, Sam, this is it.
Is this what it's come to?
I've sniffed more than this in one day.
We had it all once, Sam, and it's come to this.
We really fucked it!
Not me, boy. You fucked it.
Bitch!
Get out of the water. Drop your weapons.
Give yourselves up.
Hands in the air.
The maddest thing about crime is
it's like a drug. You never know when to stop.
As much as I wanted the fairy-tale ending
with her...
... I wanted it all for myself as well.
You might want to check that,
what with my track record.
I just did.
What for? You can't kill me.
You're a fucking loser like the rest of them.
Trust me, if you don't pull the trigger,
I'll be seeing you again.
You wish, bitch.
# BLONDIE: Call Me
# Call on me, oh, call up, baby...
Remember that letter
my old man wrote from prison,
about staying away from crime, women
and drugs?
What a load of bollocks that turned out to be.
I tried the lot and won,
and drove off into the sunset.
# I know where you're coming from
# Call me on the line
# Call me any anytime
# Call me, I'll arrive
# You can call me any day or night. Call me!
# Cover me with kisses, baby
# Cover me with love
# Roll me in designer sheets
# I'll never get enough
# Emotions come, I don't know why
# Cover of love's alibi
# Call me on the line
# Call me, call me any anytime
# Call me, I'll arrive
# When you're ready we can share the wine
# Call me
# Ooh, he speaks the languages of love
# Ooh, amore, chiamami
# Chiamami
# Ooh, appelle-moi, mon chéri
# Appelle-moi
# Anytime, anyplace, anywhere, anyway!
# Anytime, anyplace, anywhere, any day!
# Call me, my love
# Call me, call me any anytime
# Call me for a ride
# Call me, call me for some overtime
# Call me, my love
# Call me, call me in a sweet design
# Call me
# Call me for your lover's lover's alibi
# Call me, I don't mind
# Call me, call me any anytime
# Call me
# Oh, call me
# Call me...