Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Target four. Wanna take the other truck?
- Roger.
Move by the truck.
Move in right there.
Roger. He's wounded. Hit him.
Start hitting the truck.
Get the truck and him.
Go forward of it and hit him.
Roger.
Go ahead and store that.
Another guy moving right through.
Good. Fire. Hit him.
Get down on the floor.
I said, down. Down.
You. Down. Now.
Let me see your hands.
Get the hands over your head.
Over your head!
Get down.
On your knees.
There. Stay there.
Get your hands up.
Get down.
Shit, there's a kid in there.
That's not our problem.
None of this is our problem.
Get your hands in the air.
Hey.
How's it going, little man?
You all right?
I was 27 years old the first time I died.
I remember there was white everywhere.
There was war, and I felt alive.
But, really, I was dead.
- So how old?
- Twenty-seven.
Here he is. Starks, Jack.
Born in Vermont.
Hasn't got a family listed.
Naval hospital will take care of it.
Oh, my God.
- This soldier's alive. This man just blinked.
- Been tagged already.
- Worry about the others.
- No, no, look at this.
Oh, shit. Code blue, code blue.
We need a doctor.
Get a doctor over here now.
Sergeant Starks was very lucky.
A little more to the right,
it wouldn't have come out.
He has retrograde amnesia,
acute psychological suppression.
We couldn't find any family...
...in the States, sergeant.
- I'm sure you have friends.
- I want the paperwork this afternoon.
- Get him on the next flight out of here.
- Yes, sir.
He's recommended you for
the Bronze Star, sergeant.
- There is help for you, sergeant.
- Of course there is.
Of course there is.
You guys all right?
- Our car won't start.
- That's your mom?
- Yeah.
- What's your mom's name?
Jean.
Hey, Jean.
Can you hear me?
Can you wake up?
I need you to try and stay awake.
- Oh, God.
- Your mom taking anything?
- What's your name?
- Jackie.
Nice to meet you, Jackie.
Tell you what. Why don't you do this.
Wrap it around yourself...
...and you try and keep your mom awake,
and I'll go work on your car.
- All right?
- Okay.
Oh, God.
No. Oh, no...
What do you think of all this snow?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
What are these?
Those are dog tags. See, they got the name
and the date of birth on them.
- What for?
- In case I get lost...
...or can't remember who I am.
- Can I have them?
- Yeah, you can have them.
- Thanks.
You think you can reach the ignition?
Go ahead and give it a shot.
Just keep turning, all right?
Keep going.
It works.
Hey, get your fucking hands off...
Get your fucking hands off my daughter.
- Mom, he fixed our car.
- Jackie, get in that car. Now.
- Mom. He fixed the car.
- Get in the goddamn car!
- How's it going?
- Pretty good, man.
- Where you headed?
- On up in Canada.
- I can take you to the border.
- That'd be great.
- All right, bud, jump on in.
- It's freezing.
- Hey, man.
- Hey. Thanks.
Jump on in here. Hey, no problem.
My God, it's cold.
- Must've been freezing out there, boy.
- Yeah.
It's colder than a witch's titty with
a brass bra on doing pushups in the snow.
- So you drive?
- Yeah, sure.
All right, man, great.
We'll switch up in a bit.
You ever been to jail?
- No, I've never been to jail.
- I'll tell you what, buddy...
...it's a whole lot
goddamn worse than war.
It's probably worse
than anywhere you been.
I doubt that.
Are you kidding me?
What's he pulling us over for?
Recreation.
Jackie and Jean are the only things
you know for certain about that day?
Yes.
Are you aware that we have no last name,
no place of residence...
...and no record of any physical
presence for these friends of yours?
I'm afraid I might have to actually
hear that answer, Mr. Starks.
Yes.
Officer Harrison
had been shot three times.
He was long dead
by the time we got there.
Jack Starks could be
blocking the incident.
It would explain his well-conceived plan
about the little girl and her mother.
- Objection.
- I have heard of Gulf War syndrome.
War is just a CNN special. Half the shit
that went on in Operation Desert Storm...
...can't be tidied into
a top-of-the-hour headline.
Couldn't be said neatly,
so couldn't be said at all.
- There was someone else.
- War's ugly.
- And they don't put ugly on TV.
- My client thinks he already died once.
- I don't really remember all of it...
- He doesn't know what's going on.
...but there was someone else.
I think that's what happened.
If Starks did kill that officer...
...can't hold a man responsible
for a damaged mind.
We, the jury, find the defendant
not guilty by reason of insanity.
Jack Starks, I hereby sentence you
to be committed...
...to an institution
for the criminally insane...
...where I hope the doctors
and proper treatment can help you.
Come on, bud.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Get him up.
Please believe...
What are you doing? I don't belong here.
- I don't belong here.
- No, I don't think you do either.
But neither of us
can do anything about that now.
Please. Please.
Let me out of here.
Let me out of here. Please.
- How much did you give him?
- Fifty cc's.
- And he's been in for the full three hours?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, get him out.
Jack, can you hear me?
Jack, blink for me if you can.
- He didn't lose consciousness.
- Do you wanna put him back in?
No, take him out of it.
Take him upstairs
and check his vitals every hour.
Now that's, I think, the context
in which to view what's going on.
Perhaps you may have seen a lead story
in The New York Times.
Good morning, Dr. Lorenson.
You're the cop killer, right?
- That obvious, huh?
- TV, you know?
Helps soothe an active mind.
I'm Rudy Mackenzie. Welcome.
Listen, I...
- I don't really feel like talking.
- You know, that's a shame.
I don't believe
in disposable language either.
You know, small talk, little talk,
chitchat. Useless.
The game.
The game's something else, though.
This here is our court.
I'm ready to throw the ball. Come on.
All right.
What are you in here for?
- I tried to kill my wife.
- Don't you go to jail for that?
Yeah, well, I tried, like, 30 times.
I never planned on doing it, you know?
It was always
in the heat of the moment.
And she kept threatening
to have me put away until finally...
...she did.
- Thirty times might make you seem crazy.
- Yeah, or just... Or just plain stupid.
Because you'd think by the 20th time,
I would've found an alternative method...
...or maybe a more effective one.
- Morning, gentlemen. How you doing today?
For me that is a really
difficult question, Dr. Lorenson...
...because the world around me is shrinking,
and the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse...
...are coming to see me today,
and they're not bringing flowers...
...which just makes it really difficult
to get organized.
And you, Mr. Starks?
- I'm fine.
- So you're okay?
You tell me, doc.
You think there's
something wrong with me?
You're a little underweight.
Maybe I'm working it off in my dreams.
Done with the small talk?
Hey, it's okay.
Mr. Starks, glad to see
you're cooperating this time.
We're here to help, Jack.
We're only doing what's best for you.
Hold him while I get the tranquilizer.
- Get him down. Fuck the tranquilizer.
- No.
No, that's not necessary. Get him up.
Nurse, get the jacket.
The only thing
your mind's missing's a conscience.
Wait. Dr. Becker, how long
do you want us to leave him in for?
Just strap him in for now.
Help. Help, please.
Motherfucker.
Let me out of here.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
- Listen, I hate to bother you.
- Then don't.
But what about Starks?
What about Starks?
Should we be just...?
Should we be trying to help him
any way we can?
- Yes.
- Should we be leaving him in there like that?
The medication I've given him
is intended to adjust...
...maybe even reset, his violent proclivities.
Peel away some layers of hate.
The apparatus is merely
a safe place for that to happen.
The grounds and the halls, where I can't
monitor side effects I can't predict, aren't.
But how can you be monitoring
the effects while he's in there?
I consider the time he's spent
in there part of the treatment.
You can't break something
that's already broken.
I don't belong here.
I can't breathe in here.
I can't...
I'm gonna blow your head off.
In case you hadn't figured,
it's Christmas Eve.
You're never gonna get a cab here.
Thanks.
You got somewhere
you need to go?
I'm not sure.
Well, let me ask you that again.
This time, look around
and consider your options.
Have you got somewhere
you need to go?
Yeah, I do.
Well, great. Get in.
So where can I take you?
I don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
- I don't know.
Okay.
Well, there must be
another shelter I can call.
Yeah, well, thanks a lot.
Merry Christmas to you too.
Great.
That was our last option.
What am I gonna do with you?
Nothing.
I'll...
- Listen, thanks for bringing me this far.
- Where are you going?
You'll freeze out there.
You don't even have a coat.
- I'll manage.
- No, you won't.
You'll die of cold,
and then I'll have to feel guilty.
And I've already got more guilt
than I know what to do with.
You want a drink?
No, I'm okay.
Shit.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
You know what?
It's Christmas Eve and...
And I have a couch,
so you can stay on it.
I'm gonna go take a bath.
Fix yourself something to eat
if you're hungry or anything.
There's nothing to steal, but don't be
a jerk and take something anyway.
No. I wouldn't.
- My name is Jack.
- No.
Let's not do the name thing,
because it's...
I don't wanna meet you.
I may wanna help you tonight,
but I don't wanna know you, really.
Okay.
What's this?
Best I could do
with what was in the fridge.
Thanks.
No problem.
- You want a drink?
- Yeah, sure.
It was pretty good, considering.
Your fridge has quite an array of things.
Not a lot of food, but...
- Freezer has a rock in it.
- What rock?
There was a stone in it. It said "petal. "
That's snooping.
It was my mom's senseless idea
of a nickname.
It's...
So you're a waitress. I mean...
I don't know what I mean.
Okay.
I hate Christmas.
Hey.
Hey, wake up. Jackie.
- No.
- Who are these people?
- What?
- Who are the people in this picture?
That's my mom and me.
- What do you mean, your mom and...?
- No, wait a minute.
- Where's your mother now?
- My mom is dead.
- What do you mean, she's dead?
- I mean, she's dead. Dead. Gone.
She passed out with a cigarette and
burned to death a long time ago, all right?
No, no, no...
Listen, I'm sorry. Listen.
I don't know how...
- What's the date today?
- What?
I know this sounds crazy.
What year is this?
2007.
What? What?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Jack Starks.
Get the fuck out of my house.
- What'd you do, snoop all over the place?
- No.
God, you had no right.
You had no right to go through anything.
Look at me.
I know this doesn't make any sense,
because it doesn't make sense to me either.
Oh, my God. If you don't get out now,
I'm gonna call the cops.
No, please. Please, wait.
I won't hurt you. Just talk to me, please.
L... Your mom was passed out
on the side of the road when I met you.
She was wasted.
Jean, her name was Jean.
- Just stop it!
- Look, I gave this kid those dog tags.
No, no. No, you didn't.
Jack Starks did,
and Jack Starks is dead.
What?
What do you mean, he's?
He's dead.
His body was found New Year's Day, 1993,
Alpine Grove.
He's dead.
- It can't be.
- Well, it is.
Listen, listen. I don't care who
or where you think you are...
...you're not Jack Starks.
So whoever you are, I did a nice thing...
I did a really nice thing, and you've really...
God, you've really made me regret it,
so please, please, would you?
Would you just leave? Okay?
Don't you remember me?
- Oh, my God.
- Look at me.
I'll leave, okay, I'll leave, but look at me.
I'm not lying to you.
I met you. I met you and your mother,
and there was no one around for miles.
I couldn't have known that from a pair
of dog tags you had lying around.
You put those down, and you get out.
Don't you remember me?
- Don't you know? I'm...
- You get out!
I'm...
Okay?
Please.
Please get out.
I'm gonna blow your head off!
Jackie.
Oh, God.
I can't believe you left him in all night.
You didn't say anything when I asked...
I expected some common sense
on your part. Open the drawer.
Is he dead?
No. Get him upstairs immediately.
He's dehydrated.
I want him on an IV
by the time I get up there.
I tried to tell you
when I came to your office...
I expected you to take him out.
You're a physician. I shouldn't have
to spell everything out for you.
Jack?
Tom.
Tom, can I speak with you
for a moment, please?
- What have you done with Jack Starks?
- What do you mean?
- He's unconscious.
- He's recovering from Loxadol and Ativan.
Loxadol? He didn't need neuroleptics.
You know that from what, a couple
of two-minute stares across the room?
He didn't need antipsychotics,
if that's all you gave him.
After he attacked me,
I figured he'd need a little placating.
You sure he wasn't provoked?
Are you sure you wanna make
an accusation like that?
I'm not making any accusations.
He's bruised up.
Happens sometimes
when you gotta restrain them.
Listen to me.
He is not gonna end up like Ted Casey.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
but he's not a lab animal.
You can't reprogram them,
no matter what cocktail of drugs...
You really don't let up, do you?
Just because you failed Ted Casey...
...doesn't mean the rest of us did.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
it's Christmas, remember?
Hi, how are you? Sorry I'm late.
- Hi, Babak.
- That's a nice wave.
- Hey, Jamile.
- Hey.
Okay, that's great. That was the truck.
Now point to the ball.
Very good.
Wanna hold it? Feels nice. Strong.
I need you to stay with me
for just a little while more, okay?
We'll get there.
Could I have some water?
I have some water?
Here you go.
What the hell kind of drugs
are you people giving me?
Just something to keep you calm.
Did you just say something?
I said, the drugs are to keep you calm.
Did you sleep well?
- I wasn't asleep, was I?
- You were asleep for nearly a whole day.
It's December 26th, Jack.
How are you feeling?
- December 26th?
- That's right.
- 1992?
- Yes.
And that's the sun, and you're on Earth.
And I know you know better, Jack.
Who the hell are you?
My mom is dead. 2007.
Jack Starks is dead.
Get out of here, get out!
- You left me in there.
- In where?
You left me in that thing. In the drawer.
And then...
...you put me in a straitjacket.
We were forced to use restraints,
if that's what you're referring to.
- It wasn't a fucking restraint.
- That's exactly what our equipment is.
Relax.
Don't act like I don't know what's real.
You're suffering from delusions
as part of your condition.
No, I know what's real, I know.
You strapped me into something
and stuffed me in a fucking drawer.
It wasn't a dream.
I don't know what you're trying to pull,
but I wasn't...
I have to say...
...this is the most resilient I've seen
a patient undergoing this treatment.
I had a patient a few years ago.
His name was Ted Casey.
Ted sodomized a 7-year-old girl.
His lawyers asked me to have a look at him
because after his deeds were done...
...he climbed into the trees
of the forest where he killed her...
...and howled like a dog.
Ted never went to prison because everyone,
including me, believed he was sick.
So he came here. Then one day a little girl
came with her mother to visit her relative...
...and I caught Ted stealing looks at her.
The kind you really have to steal,
if you know what I mean.
I asked Ted then...
...if he could remember what the little girl
who he'd slain was wearing.
"Oh, yes," he said. "I remember it.
I remember it well. "
Those were actually his last words.
What happened to your face?
I was careless. It won't happen again.
I'll say a prayer for you, Jack.
Maybe God will pick up
where the medicine leaves off.
You sure you know where to find him?
Jack.
What are you doing, Jack?
What are you gonna do to me?
I thought I'd just ask you
to come inside with me.
- What if I didn't want to come?
- Well, I'd probably ask you why.
Because I'm not crazy.
You suffer from a delusional disorder.
It doesn't mean you're crazy.
It just means you're confused.
You're here instead of jail because
your condition...
...played a role in your crime.
- I didn't kill that cop, but I don't remember.
Your mind's ability to distinguish
between your fantasies...
...and the real events that happened...
The real events that have happened to me
have been fucked up, not my mind.
Jack.
I'd like to ask you a question, if I may.
Since when do people around here
start asking for things?
- Okay. Smoke?
- That's what you wanna ask?
No.
I wanted...
I wanted to ask you how your treatments
with Dr. Becker are progressing.
Fine. Fine.
I hope you'd tell me
if that wasn't the case.
Why? Why, what would you do?
What would you do?
I would try to make it stop.
- I'm not sure I want him to stop.
- So it's helping?
They're making me feel like
a different person.
You coming?
We're gonna freeze out here, you and I.
Could get hurt if they catch you
trying to leave again.
What do you know about the shit
they do to us in the basement?
What shit?
- You know what I'm talking about.
- No, I don't.
Yeah, you do. That jacket.
- What jacket?
- The fucking drawer.
Now, stop playing games,
you know what I'm talking about.
I know that they take you down there.
I know that they put you in it.
The rest of it, it's...
It's a trip, you know,
it's like a serious vacation.
I found out I'm gonna die.
Well, mortality is actually
a great thing to be familiar with.
I'm gonna die in four days.
That's what I found out.
They find my body in four days.
What are you two yapping about?
We're talking about our ability
to go forward in time...
...to go into the future.
I mean, that's what
we're talking about, right?
Yeah, that's right.
If you need to find something out
when you're in there, just calm down.
The less you freak,
the less you'll trip out.
Yeah, but all this shit from before
just comes tumbling...
Yeah, but that shit is in the past.
Focus on what you need to get now.
- I gotta get back in there.
- That could be a problem.
- Why?
- Lorenson's got her claws into it now.
When she started getting suspicious of me
was when they stopped putting me in there.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org