Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
The story, it's happening to us now.
We're living it.
It's alive, it's real, it's breathing.
And we can give it a happy ending.
Jake...
Angelika, we'll find your sisters.
All right? We'll bring them back.
Bring back her sisters?
Bring them back?
Bring them back with what?
Magic beans?
- Why do you say that?
- Magic beans don't work!
They don't bring people back to life.
They did not then and they will not now.
You go wait by the horses.
Jacob, wait by the horses.
- Sorry.
- He was doing what he thinks is right, Will.
He was trying to help.
- We can not fight the entire forest.
- You're just scared.
Just scared?
I'm terrified.
You should be too.
Don't you understand? The idea of going
back in there - nothing makes sense there.
It's like being inside Jake's head.
God, I hate him.
He makes me...
He drives me mad.
He makes you feel weak, doesn't he?
Yeah. He always has done.
The thing is, I can't...
Protect him.
My father thought
he could protect his family too, Will.
(clears throat)
Pah!
Jake. Jacob, come back.
Jake!
Come back, Jake!
You're a fool!
Now do you see?
I made that armor.
It's not magic, it's just shiny.
Oh, no!
This lovely Fräulein
will not be coming with you, caro storyboy.
She will be staying here with me.
It's all right, Will.
Just go. Go.
(Jake) What's this?
It's a mess, that's what it is.
It was hardly a snap, was it?
- More tension in the snap board.
- (Bunst moans)
- We need the trunks here now.
- What do you suppose I'm doing?
And this is the last time I'll ask you,
is the chuck basket secure?
- Yes, it's secure.
- It's secure.
Cor!
So, if we find these 11 girls,
we don't get guillotined.
Can you believe, these bumpkins actually
think they were devoured by the forest?
- (Bunst chuckles)
- (creaking)
And what exactly do we think?
(snapping and strange noises)
- (Jake) All right. Positions, lads.
- Jake?
- (Jake) Check for takeoff.
- Jake!
- (Jake) Right, you ready? Steady it.
(Jake) And three, two, one. Takeoff.
- Woo-hoo!
- No!
Gargh! Oh!
Jake? Jake?
Jake?
Jacob?
(Jake) Dammit. Every time.
We need more height. And can we check
the alignment? The alignment is crucial.
Stop this now, Jacob.
You're going to kill yourself.
Oh, good. That's just great,
because then it will just be you, Will,
and you can have anything
and everything that you want.
What is it exactly you do want, Will, huh?
What? Is it Angelika?
You want her?
Fine. Take her, she's yours.
Is it the money? Take that. That's all you
seem to do these days, is take and take.
Jacob Grimm, you petulant child!
Argh! Oh!
- Ow!
- (creaking)
What was that? Something moved.
I saw something move. Did you?
D-d-d-don't ask.
Please don't ask me to look.
All my life I've studied these folk tales, Will,
and now I find one that's for real.
It's not beans.
It's real.
I mean, don't you understand?
I have to do this.
Ow! Agh!
All right, Jake.
What do you want me to do?
What? Honestly?
You're my brother.
I want you to believe in me.
I need you to help me.
All right, lads. Let's launch me off
into the flaming belly of hell.
Wait. I think you're overcomplicating it.
- What?
- A catapult's not gonna work.
Yeah, you're right.
- What other gear do we have?
- Uh...
- Huh!
- Well, there's the...
What about the flying-witch rig, with
a grapple and a hook to catch the window?
- Yeah.
- Good idea.
We haven't got a hook and grapple.
They'll have hooks at the village.
We'll ride like the wind.
- Will, we've got the hooks, right?
- We'll be no time at all.
No, I've got it.
Huh!
Oh, great!
This is suicide.
Probably.
(man) Bring some water, Sasha.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
(strange voice) Sasha.
Sasha.
(caws)
The great Cavaldi.
Children in danger
and here he is, hiding out.
Scusa.
Ah, poor birdie.
(screeches)
(screams)
- (child screaming)
- Huh?
(screams)
What is ha...?
- Cavaldi.
- Huh?
Sasha!
Sasha, run to my voice.
Sasha, this way.
Got you.
Cavaldi.
Get inside.
It will be fine.
I...
I do believe I've soiled myself.
Oh, good.
I thought it was me.
Hm. I taste good.
Sasha!
Can't catch me,
I'm the gingerbread man. Ha ha!
- Sasha!
And one...
We're doing fine, Will.
(Jake) That's good. Steady.
Will! Come on,
keep it together down there.
We're almost there.
Put some muscle into it.
Life without Jake.
Will, concentrate.
Only a matter of seconds now.
That's good, Will.
Keep going.
(sighs)
Hah! Oh!
Oh.
Where was I? Oh, yes.
Settling down.
Honest labor.
Crypts. There's, uh...
One, two, three, four.
Five, six.
Seven, eight. Nine, ten.
Eleven, twelve.
Uh... Will!
Will, it's strange,
there's twelve crypts.
And they're evenly spaced in a circle.
Yeah, it's like a clock face.
Easy. Easy.
All right, Will.
I'm going in, Will.
He's going in.
That was lucky.
It's...
What's this? It's a crown.
It's a...
Oh!
It's a book of spells.
(snap)
(rustling)
(noises and rustling)
Jake?
It's a book of spells. Huh.
That's the blood moon.
Twelve crypts.
Eleven girls.
I'm new at this, darling.
If I'm doing it wrong or if there's a certain
way you like it, Grandmother Toad...
I'll just try to be gentle.
Now show me
the way back to Angelika's house.
(toad croaks)
Make up your mind.
(gasps)
Sasha?
(growling)
(howls)
For you, my queen.
Oh!
(man) Sleep.
Sleep.
(softly) Jake.
Oh.
Huh!
(chokes)
Ha! Will!
Jacob.
What? Huh!
(croakily) Jacob.
Look at me, Jacob.
Am I still the fairest of them all?
Tell me I am the fairest of them all.
Jacob.
And I will make
your dreams come true.
I've got you, Sasha.
What do you desire, Jacob?
Fame?
Power?
Angelika?
You love her,
not him.
He doesn't love her.
Not like you, Jacob.
Jake!
- Argh!
- Oh!
Jacob Grimm, you bedwetting piss bucket!
Ha ha!
Look at me, Jacob.
- No, no. Don't look at her.
- (cries)
(croakily) Jacob. Jacob.
Look at me, Jacob. Jacob!
(cries)
Rapunzel!
(screams)
Good timing. Nice disguise.
She's still there, Will.
She's still alive. She's up in the tower.
- For 500 years?
- Yeah, but they haven't been kind.
- Grab the ax.
- Huh? Right.
They tricked her, Will.
They tricked her.
Because she has the spell for eternal life,
but not for youth, not youth.
So she'll rot for eternity, waiting for
someone to come and rescue her.
- Come on.
- Was that Sasha?
- It's this way, Will.
- No, no, it's not.
- It's that way. Grandmother Toad told me.
- What?
Trust the toad!
Come on!
Stand aside, Will.
It's the ax, Will.
It's enchanted as well.
Stop them!
Jacob!
To the horses. Run!
(Queen) Stop them!
Sasha!
Sasha! Sasha.
She's not breathing.
- How can she not be breathing?
- It's impossible. I saw her walk.
There's no breath.
No pulse.
- Sasha.
- Cursed forever!
They shall all perish
beneath the blood moon.
The drawings. The spells.
(crone) The blood moon comes tonight.
(laughs)
It has to do with the eclipse.
Listen to me.
We know why your forest is enchanted.
It's under the power of
the Thuringian queen.
She's stolen your girls for their youth,
for their beauty.
She needs twelve.
Sasha was meant to be the twelfth.
The queen needs one more
to make her spell work.
You're right. Clear out these children.
Get them to Malsburg or Frankfurt.
- (Jake) Leave before the eclipse.
- (horns)
(man) Listen!
(horns)
(herald) People of Marbaden,
citizens of France,
all honor and glory be
to General Vavarin Delatombe.
He rides to the aid of his people.
Où est Cavaldi?
Generale! Generale!
Generale!
Ecco Cavaldi!
What are you wearing?
Ah, this.
Precautionary measure.
Generale.
All is well. Everything is in the hands
of your most devoted...
Argh!
If all is well,
why were two compatriots of these men
arrested on the road to Malsburg?
And why would they not stop telling tales
of extraordinary occurrences
in the Thuringian Forest,
spreading superstition and rumors
amongst my troops?
These Grimms are thieves and liars.
Every demon they have killed
they have created.
- No, no, that's not true.
- That's a lie.
But I have confessions.
(gasping)
- Arrest them.
- Baissez-le! Baissez-le!
Vite. Vite!
You see?
You German people,
what you think of as heroes.
New citizens of France,
vanquish your darkest fears.
Burn the forest.
(crowd object and grumble)
And with it...
the Brothers Grimm.
(General) Adieu, Grimm.
And farewell to your tales.
They will not be remembered.
Burn them.
I, uh, sorry.
Bye.
Elsie! Elsie!
- Jacob.
- Will.
Fire.
(screaming)
Bingo.
(Angelika) Will.
Angelika!
The feet. The feet.
Where did you find this?
Where did you find it?
(explosion)
- Run, Jake.
- Wait. My book. My book!
Forget the book, Jacob! Run!
This is the life, eh, Cavaldi?
To be victorious in the field,
with one's troops around you,
enjoying a simple meal,
a soldier's meal,
- by firelight.
- (explosion)
Romantic, huh?
- (Will) Wait!
- (growling)
Father?
Where have you been?
(groans)
Cold. So cold.
(Queen) Come to me, my frozen prince.
Be mine...
(gasps)
...now and forever...
...in love.
- (both) No!
- Angelika.
- It's my father.
- Stop looking. He was trying to kill you.
Jake!
Angelika!
Angelika. (growls)
Will, Angelika's the twelfth.
The twelfth.
(inales harshly)
What the devil?
What kind of magic, huh?
What tricks?
Where are you going?
Come back here!
You, stand your ground.
That is an order!
I command you. You traitors!
Come back here!
Argh!
Generale. Generale.
Grimmy. Miracolo!
How is this possible?
Run, Will.
(hums lullaby)
Sleep well, princess.
(ravens cawing)
It's started, Will.
It's started.
- (Queen) Yes.
- The blood of the twelfth, my queen.
Wake up, please.
Will, push!
I am.
Will, try the magic ax.
Try the ax!
Ha!
Give me that.
Back, back!
- I held the ax the same way you do.
- Concentrate on getting up in the tower.
I don't have time...
(gunshot)
- We found the missing girls.
- They're in the crypts.
I mean, they're in the crypts.
Grimms, story time is over.
- Execute them.
- No, no. That's who you want. Up there.
I said execute them.
(cocks pistol)
Generale.
I wish to resign my...
Resignation accepted.
Italian never agrees with me.
(belches)
Mild indigestion.
It will soon pass.
(growling)
Is this one of your tricks, Grimms, huh?
- Run, Will.
- Jake?
Be a soldier!
(valet) How dare you insult my general?
Die, barbarian.
(thud)
(General) Heagh!
Oh, wait. No. Oh!
Huh!
- Bingo.
- You killed my friends.
I only wish you had more.
Still, there is always your brother, hm?
Where is Jacob, by the way?
Beg.
Argh!
No!
I want you to beg.
Oh, God, no, no.
Brave general, don't kill me.
Argh!
All I wanted was a little order.
A slice of quiche would be nice.
(sighs)
Soon we shall be one, my love.
Ah!
- Yes.
- My queen.
(Jake) Stop!
- Huh!
- No.
Finish the spell, my love.
Agh!
Argh!
(Jake screaming)
(mumbles)
(groans)
Where am I?
I'm exhausted.
Stop her, Will.
No. Not the knife, Will.
Not the knife!
She's got control of them.
When the moon again becomes full,
so will I.
And your kingdom will once again be mine.
- You can stop her, Jake.
- I can't, Will.
This is your world, Jake.
It's just you.
- Finish the story.
- (Queen) Yes!
I don't know how.
Am I beautiful?
I can't hold on.
Ah!
Who's the fairest of them all now?
- You can stop it, you know the story.
- No, I'm weak.
- It's you. It's you.
- I can't.
Oh!
Will. Will!
Will, Will.
Argh!
I'm sorry.
Come here. All right, now.
All right, Will.
Um... OK.
All right.
(Will gasps)
Such brotherly love.
- Such sacrifice.
- Will. Will.
Don't look her in the eyes.
- He's dying, Jacob.
- Leave him alone!
Because of you.
Can you save him?
Do you have your magic beans?
Because I do.
(Queen claps and gasps)
What a beautiful bedtime story this will be.
Did you not know, Jacob?
Truth is much more terrible than fiction.
Will.
Do you want to live?
No.
No, my queen.
Oh, no. No, my queen.
I am here.
(whimpers)
Complete the spell, my sweet new prince.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
Say it.
You are the fairest of them all.
(Jake) No! Don't kiss her!
(Queen screams)
So cold.
Look what you have done!
Angelika?
You killed my daughters!
- My queen.
- Stop him!
- You must die!
No, Will. No!
Argh!
Who is the fairest of them all?
No!
Grimmy.
Signor Grimmy.
Please. No, please.
Tell me what to do.
Serve my queen.
No. Grimmy?
Demon queen, hear me.
Swallow my curse from
the dark heart of my ancestors.
(laughs)
Maledetta.
Maledetta!
(Cavaldi) Hello!
Can anybody hear me?
Hello!
Hello.
Jacob!
Jacob, it is I, Cavaldi.
Jacob.
Where's Will?
Will.
Oh, God, Will.
No. God, no.
Wait.
I know this story,
from my childhood.
There is still time, Jacob.
Look.
See? Hurry, Jacob.
The spell can be broken with a kiss...
- Yes, a kiss. A kiss, yes.
...of true love.
Make sure, in your heart, true love.
Or the kiss will be the kiss of death.
(gasps)
Yes.
- (child #1) Eva!
- (child #2 ) Heidi!
(Cavaldi) Bingo!
- Lily!
- Elsie!
Angelika!
- Will.
- Hurry, bambini. Hurry.
Will. Come on, it's over now.
You can get up.
Will, the spell's broken.
Will?
We did it.
Will.
(Cavaldi) Perhaps another kiss.
Not you.
Hm?
Maybe you should give it a try, Angelika.
(children laugh)
I just had to know what that was like
before the story ended.
Will!
(villagers cheer)
(children scream excitedly)
Good people of Marbaden,
you have nothing further to fear,
because I and the Grimmies,
we have destroyed the dark heart of evil.
You are free!
Grazie! Musica!
(German folk dance)
I would like to keep this.
It saved my life.
- Of course.
- Grazie.
And this, you should be
more careful about this.
- It's very good, but I think it'II...
- (Jake) Is that mine?
- Sorry I never believed in you.
- Well, I never believed in you either.
So you are brothers.
You're welcome here any time,
any time at all, Grimms. This is your home.
- I thought you ended up with the girl.
- You see that?
What? The sun?
- The day's not over yet.
- Yeah, right!
- Would you call this a turning point?
- I'd say we're on the verge.
- Really?
- The verge, Will.
That's fantastic.
Cos I've been thinking
of an alternative career path.
- One that uses all of our new expertise.
- Will.
- I haven't sorted it yet...
- Will, this is the real world.
We're men without a country,
we're enemies of the state,
and worst of all we haven't a single bean.
- It's a good name, though, isn't it?
- It's a damn good name.
Let's dance. Come on.
(wolf howl)
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org