Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Can you take me to Carl?
Need some help?
I've got a present for you.
If you need me...
or if you feel like I'm around
but you can't find me...
just...
Shine it like this.
Go ahead, take it.
You like it?
- Carl?
- What's the matter?
What?
What's wrong?
What happened over here?
Just broke all by itself.
- Did you break that plate?
- I broke the plate.
Well, hey, let's...
Let's break 'em all,
how about that?
You little fucking liar!
I should've drowned you
like the runt of the litter.
You don't lie in my house.
This is my house!
- He's just a boy.
- Shut up!
You're not his mother!
She's not your mother.
She left us, Carl.
Remember that.
See that?
Wait. Jesus Christ!
What the fuck is this?
Get back-Get over here!
Playing with dolls?
You little faggot!
God!
What are you,
some kind of a woman?
- Get up!
- But, dad-
Damn it.
You want something to cry about?
I'll give you something
to cry about, woman!
Mama's boy!
I didn't raise no faggot!
Stop your crying.
You want to iron like a woman?
- Let me show you how to iron.
- No!
Help me.
See?
She was my first.
I made such a mess.
Now what I have to do...
Why are you here?
Don't lie.
- I came to help you.
- You're lying.
Bitch.
Whore.
Cunt!
You sound like your father.
He was nothing.
He is nothing.
Who told you to say that?
Do you remember the first time
he talked to you?
Were you in water?
Maybe you went swimming.
It was my baptism.
My father, he...
he pushed me under.
I think I had
some kind of seizure.
I think I was drowning...
and everybody just looked at me.
Nobody helped me. Nobody.
Except him.
My father...
he took me home that night...
and he broke three of my ribs...
and fractured my jaw.
I was six years old.
What your father did to you
is evil.
What he did to you was wrong.
He treated you like a thing.
He was more...
powerful than me.
No. No one should be
treated like that.
Is that right?
In what world do you live in?
Carl, where is Julia Hickson?
No names.
Where is she?
I know you, Carl.
You want to tell me.
Oh, you know me?
Oh, you know who I am?
Where is she?
Where's Julia?
That can't be right.
Danger pulse.
- No change.
- Christ.
What about emergency cessation?
Gradually terminate the feed,
disable the receptors-
It could lead
to massive shock...
and, Henry, could you please
shut that thing off?
What's going on?
That hypothetical situation
I told you about?
- It's happening.
- Can't you stop it?
It's not that simple.
Well, you stopped it before-
Yes, tha twas different.
That was Edward.
With Stargher, his mind
is unfamiliar territory...
and she's lost.
She thinks this is real.
Well, is there anything
that we can do?
Whatever we do runs the risk
of making things worse for her.
Worse. That's great.
So she's lost somewhere?
- No. No.
- No, what?
I need you here.
Fucking stop! Stop!
Let me thefuck out!
Let me out!
Get me out, you sickfuck!
Fuck you!
Let me out.
Do something.
Do something to end this.
I got bugs crawling
all over my body.
It gets worse.
You're completely unprepared
for this.
Ah, Dr. Kent,
we've been over all this.
Yes, but I've been
through the process.
She went through the process,
too, and it didn't matter.
You don't know him.
Be lucky.
Come on, guys.
Ready?
Peter, the first few minutes...
will be very disorienting.
Rememberto stay calm
and focused.
Instincts play a very important
part here, so trust them.
All right.
Peter, you've read her file.
Hit her with something personal.
And remember, Peter...
it's not real.
Have you seen him? My boy?
My little one?
His father took him from me.
I spit it out my hole.
Big deal. don't mean anything.
My child's an abomination.
He has no soul.
Is that you?
You all right?
Hold me.
This isn't real.
Did daddy do a bad thing?
Don't be scared.
This isn't real.
Naughty worm.
I'll kill you!
Fuck you, motherfucker!
Catherine,
wake the fuck up, now!
Mairzy doats and dozy doats
And liddle lamzy divey
A kiddley divey, too
Wouldn't you?
When you were in college...
Your baby brother
had a car accident!
He was in a coma for six months
before he died!
And I'm sorry for saying that!
Butyou gotta wake up!
God!
It's not real.
This is not real!
Not real!
It's OK.
What the fuck happened?
Where are we?
Oh, my God.
Is this where he keeps them?
No, it's OK.
Don't be scared.
I will never hurt you.
I'm your friend.
And Peter-he's afriend, too.
Do you know where this place is?
Like on a map?
I am so proud of you.
Even if Peter
doesn't find Julia...
I promise I will come back
and help you.
- What are you doing?
- Let's go.
It's over.
I know how to find Julia.
I just can't leave him here!
God damn it, Catherine,
let's go!
- Carl!
- I know how to find her.
- Let's go!
- I'll come back for you, Carl!
I promise that I'll come back!
Catherine, we gotta go now!
- That means he's back.
- How's Catherine?
Take it easy, Peter.
Is she OK?
Just breathe.
- Is she OK?
- Yeah, I think she is.
Can you get me
out of this fucking suit?
Yeah, Cole here.
- Cole, it's Novak.
- Yeah, what's up?
I want you to go
down to the basement...
at Stargher's workplace and
call me when you get down there.
They haven't finished
building the grid yet.
Fuck the grid!
Call me when you get down there.
- You OK, Pete?
- I'm fine.
You want to tell me
what happened in there?
You in pain?
- What happened, Peter?
- I saw her.
- Who did you see?
- I know where to find her.
- Who?
- Julia. I saw her.
OK. Why don't you come and
let Dr. Kent have a look at you?
- Cole?
- Yeah, this is Cole.
Now, what am I doing down here?
That machine that he uses-
there's a hoist.
I want you to look
for a plaque...
or a metal plate
with some sort of logo on it.
Yeah, I got it.
It's Carver
industrial equipment...
in Bakersfield, California.
I want you to find out
every goddamn thing...
that you can
about that machine-
who used it, who sold it,
who bought it.
Just find out
everything you can.
I'll call you from the chopper
in about twenty minutes.
All right, let me have a look.
Good.
The FBI has left the building.
What? I haven't had a chance
to clear Novak!
What did you expect me to do?
There's no way
I could stop them.
Go.
- I'm OK.
- Are you sure?
Let me have a look.
- All right.
- OK.
Peter, just talk.
What if your mind
is playing tricks on you?
They shot you
full of drugs, Peter.
Who knows
if what you saw is real?
Catherine, open this door.
- I promise...
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna help you.
Stop.
Do not jeopardize your career.
Stop! It's dangerous.
What are you doing?
- Miriam.
- What's she doing?
- You know what she's doing.
- For Christ's sake.
Jesus!
- She changed the codes.
- You can't get in without them?
- She reversed the feeds.
- What does that mean?
The process is intended
for her to go into his mind.
But instead,
she's bringing him into hers.
Stop! No more!
I promised I'd come back
and help you.
See? I always keep my promises.
Can I stay here...
with you?
Oh...no, honey, I'm sorry.
It doesn't work that way.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
Yes, there is.
When I was a little boy...
I found this bird.
He was injured and...
had a broken leg or something.
Well, my father
found out that I had it.
And I knew that he would
do something horrible to it.
It was just a matter of time.
So I took it to the sink,
and I-I held it under.
It was better for the bird.
I saved him.
I can't do that, Carl.
I won't.
It doesn't matter.
It found me.
It always finds me.
Agent Novak? Go ahead.
- Cole?
- Novak, listen to this.
The hoist was sold
to a guy named Bainbridge...
who tried to build
a machine works out near Delano.
Bainbridge
ends up in bankruptcy court...
and the state winds up
with the land.
And guess who they hire
to seal the place up.
Aw, you're fuckin' kiddin' me.
No. I'm not the kidding type.
Carl Rudolph Stargher.
- Where's the land?
- Exit 10, off highway 99.
- We're on our way now.
- Got it. I know where that is.
Help! Help me!
This is the area.
My world...
my rules.
Help!
Do it.
It's not real.
Me got boy.
Boy me got.
You cannot kill me.
It's OK.
Save me.
You can stay here with me.
Here!
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK.
You've gotto back away.
Scoot back. Back away!
Back up from here. Back-
it's OK.
Are you OK?
You OK?
You're OK.
Agent Ramsey?
Yeah, Ramsey.
She's here.
OK, let her through.
Somebody outside for you.
What is she doing here?
Said he wanted to see his home.
It's pretty strange.
She's keeping his dog, Peter.
I'd say pretty fucking strange
is par for the course.
I almost didn't recognize you.
How long do you getto be
a civilian?
A couple weeks...
till after the inquiry
and see what happens.
Ramsey told me
you were thinking of...
What do you call that thing?
- Reversal?
- Reversal.
With that kid
you were working with?
- Yeah. Edward.
- Edward.
Are you sure
you want to do that?
Absolutely.
You're not worried about
what might happen?
I would never do anything
to hurt Edward.
It wasn't him
I was worried about.
What about you? How are you?
I'm not sure. I...
I remember pieces of everything.
According to the FBl...
you guys put me on some
drug-fueled mind-benderfirst...
then triggered a memory
I already had...
and officially
we found Julia Hickson...
through good old-fashioned
detective work.
I guess this is
hello and good-bye, then.
I guess so.
Thanks for everything,
Catherine.
- Be safe.
- All right.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org