Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
You love, Dickens?
No I don't.
You want to kiss the cut on his head
and hold hands.
But, he's a sissy.
He's a shark hunter.
He has a submarine too.
Except it's a fake.
He's gonna be rich and buy a real one.
He has more pennies than you.
Hey, wait for me.
That monster shark might be about.
Don't worry.
Dickens the sea captain will save us.
He's sailing under the seas now.
He's diving deep to the place
where dreams are made.
"He walks a lonely shore all littered
with dreams and hopes..."
Dickens, my brave sea captain.
Avast ye, you scurvy...
I'll have you keelhauled.
I'll have you strung to the yard arm
and sent to Davey Jones's locker!
- Have mercy on my soul!
- Mutiny.
Looks like the pirate took
the captain prisoner.
- Mercy.
- Those who die will be the lucky ones!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Wait a minute,
he looks more like a farmer.
He's not really a captain...
- or a prisoner or anything.
- Go on in, Dickens.
- Stay in your room till I call you out.
- Okay, Dell, okay.
Afternoon, Miss Munro.
Hello, Patrick.
Is it afternoon?
My, how the day flies, you know.
"My, how the day flies you know."
I do appreciate all you do for me,
Patrick.
You are such a kind young man.
- Well, I always try...
- I know.
I know. Now, Patrick...
these deliveries...
they is all paid for, ain't they?
Sure.
Thank you.
Are you...
are you go...
will you...
I will.
I will... but not here.
Not in the yard...
not by the tomatoes.
It's a zoo room.
It stinks of disinfectant.
Miss Munro.
What are they doing?
She's touching his boy-thing.
It's gone all angry and red!
She's kissing it!
She's sucking his blood!
- He's trying to call for help.
- She's a vampire.
You're next.
Oh, shit. Why'd you stop, Miss Mun...
We're safe. We escaped.
I thought she was gonna be my friend.
Say... isn't that the rabbit hole you found?
It looks bigger than before.
Maybe I could crawl in.
I want to look in. Show me.
Okay. All right.
Mustique!
I'm falling very slowly, dear.
The sides of the holes are filled
with cupboards and book-shelves.
Can you hear me?
No, don't listen to her!
She's gone, Jeliza-Rose.
It's too dangerous to rescue Mustique.
You have to face up to it.
Take that! She's not dead yet.
You just wanna take her place.
You're all traitors.
You don't have hearts.
You're just heads!
- And you too!
- No, no.
Jeliza-Rose, please.
I want to help save Mustique.
I truly do. Because of my eyes,
I can sense things in the dark.
You're better than those other two.
I'm sorry Mustique was so mean to you.
I'm almost a ghost.
That's why Dell didn't see me.
I really think I am...
don't you?
I really can't say, Jeliza-Rose.
I don't know about those things.
Come in, Mustique.
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
This is radio Jeliza-Rose.
Am I loud and clear?
Come in, please.
Over.
Dickens?
Thought you was a squirrel.
He's spoiled.
He's cutting muffins, is all.
I guess that's what it is... I guess.
Whatever it is.
Your daddy sleeps a lot.
- My mama does too.
- Is she a ghost?
No, not any more. Not really.
She's just a dozer.
She isn't as pretty as your daddy.
Her hair isn't nice like his is.
It's only fake.
See.
That's funny.
You fooled me because I didn't know.
It's not supposed to be funny.
It was Mustique's idea.
Dickens... will you help me
save my friend?
She may be dying.
She's farther than the ocean, I think.
I probably can't do it.
But you're the captain!
Yeah, I am.
Because I've got my own submarine.
Can we feed the shark?
I'd like to do that.
If you want you can help me too.
We can lure it.
Meaner than death.
Okay, I'll help you.
Then you'll rescue my friend?
Yeah.
What'll happen?
The end of the world.
The monster shark will die?
The monster shark never dies.
Bad dog.
You watered all the fish and seaweeds.
Bad dog!
- You're the bad dog.
- No, you're the bad dog.
- You're a bad dog!
- You're a bad dog for looking.
We better go.
If the monster shark catches us here,
we're doomed.
Monster shark!
Monster shark. Gonna kill you.
It's gonna eat you.
The bus! We can hide there.
No, that's a bad place.
It's wrong there.
No. Come on!
Can't go there.
You use the bus for shark bait
and it tips over and burns up.
And then you get in trouble.
And Officer Waller said "You can't
drive a bus on the tracks, Dickens...
you should know that.
That'll get you sent away, Dickens."
So I can't go there with you.
I can't go there with you.
Captain, you're acting wei...
- silly - Can't go.
Sometimes you just worry about it
too much.
Just pretend it never happened, okay?
I better go home now and eat, I think.
Maybe we can find some food together.
We shouldn't play no more today.
You have to save my friend.
You said you'd do that.
I don't know, because I make mistakes
if I try some things.
But you have to.
You promised.
What is your friend?
A head.
- A doll's head.
- Does she bite?
No.
Her mouth is like this.
She doesn't have teeth.
All right. Okay.
Wait! I got her. It has to be her.
- It has to be.
- Yeah, it has to be!
No, it's weird.
It's not a head at all,
it's not like what you said.
And that's all that's down there, okay?
There's nothing but dirt and more dirt.
She's dead.
I can feel something coming.
It's the monster shark!
He's coming for the bait!
- Look out!
- Wait! Where are you going?
Dickens! Dickens!
Dickens!
Damn you. Trouble-maker!
Vandal!
Hold on, Jeliza-Rose. We're coming.
Come on, hurry up.
Is she dead?
I can't be sure.
Look, she's breathing.
She's weak. And must be pretty hungry,
pretty thirsty too.
What's that?
Smells like disinfectant.
- Look, I try to be good, okay.
- Dickens...
And I'll get the boy.
Where are you going, Jeliza-Rose?
Don't go downstairs. Dell's there.
Don't go, Jeliza-Rose.
I wish Mustique were here.
Don't cry. Mustique's gone forever.
Don't go downstairs. I'm afraid.
- You're always crying.
- Baby.
- I'm not a baby.
- You act like one.
Cry baby.
Cry, cry baby, cry baby.
Maybe you two want to come with me?
Well, you're coming anyhow.
Please don't go, Jeliza-Rose.
What is that terrible smell?
I told you...
disinfectant.
What can she be doing down there?
I don't know.
We'll find out.
To meet again like this...
I won't let you go though. Not again.
No more running away.
I love you so much.
There's so much damage done already.
But I'll save what's left. Oh, I will.
Put this there.
- Who welcomed you down here, child?
- Not me, Dell, I didn't!
Not me.
Wigs and blush, they won't cut it, child.
You can stay and watch if you must,
but you be quiet or else.
Now I want to chill him.
What a mess.
This isn't fun. This is a sad man.
This a sad, sad man.
Now...
Sinister apples.
Sinister, sinister apples.
I'm tired, I'm tired, tired, tired.
See the skin has to be peeled.
And then the fat trimmed...
and the bones, they get sprinkled
with powdered Borax...
then the shaping of the wire begins...
and the mending,
the sewing, the varnishing...
Rose.
Arise, Rose...
and behold Noah.
- Is he all better now?
- Course he's better, course he is.
Are you gonna give him something?
A gift for his new life.
- Like what?
- Oh, I don't know.
You have to choose. It has to be
something dear to you, though.
- No, not me!
- No, not me.
- No, don't. Oh, please. Please!
- Don't, Jeliza-Rose... I'm scared.
Not me! Jeliza-Rose, I'm your friend.
Jeliza-Rose!
- Goodbye. - No.
Have a nice trip.
Jeliza-Rose, get me out.
- We're so afraid!
- Somebody save me. Help!
Can anyone hear me? Help!
You brought Noah back to me.
So we'll share him now.
But you're his.
You understand, child?
Go to the porch, draw in,
it's the fumes.
It's unhealthy for your lungs.
Go on, get!
It's a new day.
We'll get your house in order.
An untidy home means an untidy person.
Monster! You nasty thing!
Nasty thing.
Come on, things to do.
Come on. Up. Up!
Dickens.
- Gotta clean, clean, clean.
- Clean, clean, clean.
Wash me in the blood of Jesus
And clean the tarnished soul
He will heal me
Make me whole
Wipe it!
Rise and shine
We'll rise and shine with Jesus
In my new home in the sky
With loaves and fish He'll feed us
His pierced hands will lead us
And we'll rise and shine with Jesus
in the sky
Now when we get to heaven
That sin'll be all compared
And angel's wings we're given
as we climb them golden stairs
I'm gonna strip off
and put on a pure white robe
Scrub clean my sinful soul
So wash me in the blood
Wash me in the blood of Jesus
Now...
seal your eyes and mouth,
extend your arms and hold your breath.
Do your panties.
Beer braised rabbit with carrots
and onions and potatoes.
A jar of lemonade and butter tarts
for dessert.
Fruits of Eden all for the children of Noah.
Jeliza-Rose...
this is where you belong...
Jeliza... this is where you belong.
You're part...
you're part of the family now,
you hear me?
We cannot have any strangers here.
They'd take daddy away from us.
Do you hear me?
Dear Lord...
I hold up a hand to Death.
I keep that troublesome stranger away.
- That is my calling. - Hallelujah.
When you love something,
it doesn't have to die or go in the ground.
Nothing has to change, for I am
the keeper of the silent souls. Amen.
Amen.
Now, eat. Stuff yourselves.
Yeah.
He's good.
I waited for you for so long.
And now...
after all these years, to have you here...
I love gravy.
- You won't be leaving me again.
- Lemonade.
You'll be staying put for a long while.
He looks like a burrito.
Sleep of the just.
Did you ever know the old lady?
Rose, you ever know your grandma?
She died when I wasn't even born yet.
You missed a saint.
I owe her my life.
She tended my sorry body
after that bee darn near killed me.
Nasty, nasty bees.
Nasty...
buzzy bees.
Course I...
I can see more than most,
even with my eyes closed.
Yes.
I can see birds and...
rabbits and...
curious little girls hiding behind bushes.
I can see everything you can imagine.
Course...
curious little girls hiding behind bushes...
sometimes see more than they should.
Best minding one's own business,
you hear me?
Otherwise, Rose,
bad things might happen.
Bad, bad things might happen
under the sun.
You smell awful.
You reek of the devil, Rose!
You're dead.
You finished making that trap, Dickens?
Dickens!
Nasty.
Diseased.
Come on, hurry up now, Dickens.
Nasty.
Sateen Lips?
Baby Blonde?
- Are you there?
- Yeah, hallelujah.
Behold brothers and sisters,
she's been washed in the blood of Jesus.
A full recovery is expected.
I've never been so happy.
I'm alive!
Jeliza-Rose, you know I love you,
don't you?
Honey, I'm sorry.
I'll do something nice for you soon.
- I promise, baby.
- Hallelujah. She's born again.
- Jesus is giving her a new brain.
- Have some chocolate.
Wash me in the blood
Rise and shine, dear.
Mustique's alive!
She's okay and happy.
Just a dream. Trust me.
- I know everything.
- Stop it.
Stop pretending you're her.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
It's not just a dream!
That's what you get! You're a bad dog!
Hi, Jeliza-Rose.
I better go because I didn't knock
and that's rude. So I'll go, okay?
I didn't knock, so I'll go, okay?
Don't go! Don't go.
I've got good news.
Mustique's all right!
She's in the hospital
but she's got a body...
and she's gonna get a real brain too!
I'd like a new brain sometimes.
Because I think a new one is shiny!
Yeah. She was happy.
I guess she isn't a doll any more.
She must be pretty.
She's beautiful.
She's fabulous, dear.
And we're gonna make you fabulous
too, darling.
That one.
Scarlet Surrender is best.
Now, sit still...
- or you'll make me do it wrong.
- I won't move a muscle.
As I don't have muscles anyway,
so I won't move them.
Puff your lips.
Get ready.
There.
I think you're nice.
It's silly.
You got red on me.
Silly kisser.
The old lady who lived here
was a silly kisser too.
She kissed me.
That was when I was little.
She was my grandma.
She never kissed me...
because I didn't get born yet.
Sometimes she did this in my mouth...
and that was fun.
It was a snake, I think...
or a goldfish dancing.
Some days I'd be here all day
kissing with her.
She's a nice lady. Except she's dead.
Dickens...
she was your girlfriend.
You were her boyfriend.
No...
I was her cutie... I was her little cutie.
But she...
she did fall down the steps and die.
I ran down when she did that.
Because I was just little,
I didn't know what to do.
I was scared.
- She's nice lady. - Dickens...
you're a little cutie.
You're a little cutie too.
Silly kissers!
Silly...
A bomb!
They're exploding the ground!
It's bigger than firecrackers
and bullets.
- I love firecrackers.
- Me too. I really do.
It's the boom hole!
It's the edge of the world.
It's the Hundred Year Ocean.
I got a secret.
If I say, you can't tell, okay?
Because if Dell knows she'll wallop me
good and I'll be in trouble forever.
What is it?
It's a giant atom bomb.
And the end of the whole world.
Yeah, like a big tidal wave
that goes whoosh!
And everything gets cleaned away
like chemicals...
and the Baby Jesus returns
forever and ever.
Amen.
I wanna see.
I don't know. Maybe tomorrow
when Dell drives to town.
If you show me...
you can keep the arm.
Is it a boy or a girl?
Because a girl is nice, I think.
- It's a boy.
- How can you tell?
- No, that doesn't mean it's a boy.
- Yes, it does.
It's a thingy.
You got a thingy. I know.
No, that's wrong. I don't have that.
I don't have that.
Dickens.
Dickens...
I'd like to see your secret.
I don't know.
You're my boyfriend.
My cutie.
You're my dear sweet Captain...
and I'm Mrs Captain.
I don't understand that.
I better go home, I think.
Dickens has a girlfriend.
He's your boyfriend.
He's my husband.
And I... I... I...
I'm his wife.
He's dreamboat. He's a sunny cloud.
Kiss me.
- You're a girl.
- Kiss me and I'll be a boy.
- Girls don't kiss girls that way.
- Please.
Oh baby.
You're disgusting.
That was fun. That was great.
- You're my best friend.
- And you're mine too.
And I love Dickens!
He's the sweet prince.
He's the great king.
He's apply juice and jerky!
We're a happy family.
And Dell will marry daddy
and look after us all.
And we'll explore the Hundred
Years Ocean. It's a dream come true.
It's Christmas!
And what do we have here?
I think a baby is in me from kissing.
I think it's Mustique.
I think she's come back.
Tell Dickens.
Tell him about the baby.
Then he'll let you see his special secret.
Maybe he's alone.
But maybe Dell's still there.
Let's go.
Let's go see Dickens special secret
in his room.
My sweet honey rose
Strange dark flower rose
Jeliza-Rose
Hello? It's us.
It's Jeliza-Rose.
It's a real nice day for a tea party.
Me and Glitter Gal are here...
in case you're not too busy.
Jeliza-Rose. See what happens when
you're small and hungry all the time?
You're nasty. You deserve it.
Maybe I am nasty,
but at least I'm alive.
Get out while you can,
or she'll close a trap on you too!
Shut up. Shut up!
It's not fair! I didn't know
you were there. You scared me good!
No, no, it was an accident.
You just got spooked, that's all.
- It was all them ugly dead things and all.
- No, that's not right.
No, that's not right.
Because Dell makes them alive again
and that's what she does!
And she's Jesus how she makes
them alive again!
You scared me good,
I didn't know you was there!
I think I fainted.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that again or I'll die, okay?
Okay.
All right. I'm sorry.
I think I'm sorry too. Think so.
Dickens...
Glitter Gal wants to tell you something.
That baby sounds like a strange thing.
We can build a castle...
and Dell will marry my daddy.
But...
you have to show me
your special secret first.
No, I can't build a castle.
I don't know how.
I don't know how. No.
Dickens... if you show me your secret...
I'll love you forever.
I'll show you, okay? Just once only.
But if I don't unpack this bag before
Dell gets back, I won't eat tonight.
So you wait, okay? You wait.
Don't touch nothing.
This is Dell's place.
All right.
I'll wait for my cutie.
You're my kisser.
What do you wanna see his special
secret for? You're better off not knowing.
Look what happens. I was curious.
You know what Dell's gonna do to me?
We have to help him.
You do it. I don't wanna get in trouble.
That's it, that's it. I'm free, I'm free!
We can't wake mama,
so we can't talk like this...
unless we talk like this first.
Because we're ghosts.
- We're quiet ghosts.
- Nice.
Your house is the witch's cave.
We're disappearing
and we won't get caught.
Yeah, that's a good idea, I think.
Because Dell will wallop me
for having company.
It's Halloween.
My room! My room, my room.
You better get on the bed so you don't
crush nothing important, okay?
Okay.
- Is there candy in it?
- No.
It's my special secret.
It's the eight wonder.
The great wave.
The end of the world!
Dynamite.
- How do you explode them?
- Like a firecracker, I think.
Like a war bomb! Boom! Kaboom!
And everything gets cleaned away.
The end of the world. Blown to bits.
So I'll keep them.
Yeah, I'll keep them until I'm an old man...
and then I'll kill that shark...
and I'll be a hero...
I'm pretty sure.
And I'll help you.
That way we can be on TV.
Because you love me.
I'm your wife forever.
That's baby's asleep, I think.
It's snoring.
She's growing.
She's coming tonight...
or tomorrow.
I bet she's pretty.
I bet she's pretty,
I bet she's pretty like you.
Where's that place?
The whole bottom of the ocean.
There are whole cities there,
with people and dogs.
There are castles there...
and farms and husbands and wives...
and babies, and ghosts...
and silly kissers too.
And kissers that do this...
- It's mama, I think.
- Is she awake?
I don't know.
Because that never happens,
but maybe it happens.
If mama quit dozing
I'll go see if she wants soup.
Dickens, I'm scared.
Me too.
If we go together, we're safe.
Yeah, all right.
Mama?
It's damn bad.
Dell says someday mama will wake.
And she says someday there'll be a
pill or a story or something...
and that'll make her eyes
come alive again.
Because if she gets buried
she'll be gone for good.
That's my gift.
And that's daddy's map!
No, no, they're Dell's.
It's all hers.
Her place is with mama.
It's daddy.
And that's Dell.
She was beautiful once.
Not a pirate or a ghost.
She had two good eyes
and she loved your daddy.
They were kissers.
Young kissers.
Dell and my daddy were young kissers.
No.
They do it like we do it.
No, no...
I'm Dell...
and you're my daddy...
and we're married...
and our baby's coming.
Filth! Evil!
Rotten! Rotten!
No, Dell!
Doing that in here!
Dickens, bringing that nasty...
- nastiness into our home!
- No, Dell, no.
This is my room, mama's...
I'm sorry, Dell, I'm sorry.
Like father like daughter!
Spy! Watching in the bushes,
you vile nasty child!
- I didn't do anything! - Liar!
Dell...
Spy... with your little spies!
No!
You'll starve now, you hear me?
No more food for you! No more you!
Dell, no, Dell!
Now. Who have we here?
It's Mustique!
A troublesome creature.
- She's mine! I hate you!
- I don't think so. No, no, no.
Now look at what you done.
Look at what you done now!
All right.
All right, my boy.
- Dell's here. Dell's got...
- Leave him alone!
- Leave him! Witch!
- Get off me!
Leave him!
Mama.
I've got your hat, you witch!
Now you'll get stung by bees and die.
You'll die.
And get out in the earth and die!
Mama.
You're gonna die now!
I didn't do anything! I didn't!
I didn't do anything!
She's got them all, daddy. I'm next.
When she finds the squirrel gone
she'll destroy me for sure.
Probably she'll hang my head
in her living room!
You're dreaming yourself
far away, daddy.
Further than the Hundred Years Ocean.
Beyond Jutland...
deep, deep, deep...
in the place where dreams are made.
We'll be a happy family.
We'll build a castle of crooked branches...
and flattened pennies.
Eat meat...
and butter tarts... and drink lemonade...
from gold-plated paper cups.
I'll dream myself there too.
If I shut my eyes and try hard enough...
maybe I'll wake inside your dream.
The end of the world.
Dickens!
You killed it!
You killed the monster shark, Dickens!
I love you.
Little girl.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay, little girl?
I'm hungry is all.
Well, here... I have something.
Are you traveling alone
or with someone?
Don't know.
I guess Dickens will come and get me.
I'm pretty sure he will.
So your parents weren't on the train?
You're all alone like me then.
It happened so fast.
So fast.
We're two of the lucky ones...
thank God.
Very, very lucky.
Dickens? Dickens?
Dickens?
- You stay far. - Dickens?
Mess elsewhere.
Dickens?
Where are you, boy? Dickens?
My captain.
It's okay. It's okay.
We're safe now.
We'll take care of each other,
how's that?
And I'll make sure you get
where you're going.
They're beautiful. Aren't they?
They're my friends, you know.
They have names.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org