The passenger list, sir.
Oh, very good.
Who are the Edmunds boys,
Private Brooke?
Three brothers, sir,
all posted to South Africa
on the same day...
my birthday in fact, sir.
Is that so, Brooke?
I don't believe it.
Is that...?
What on earth
is he doing down here?
Get down to
the waterfront, Brooke.
Get customs to pull
this chap to one side...
Van Diemen,
South African Boer.
- Escort him here, please.
- Yes, sir.
Tell him...
tell him
Major Carlysle would
very much like to see him.
Yes, sir.
This one's short.
Get me another.
Yes, sir.
Brooke,
where are you off to
in such a hurry?
I've been asked to escort
one of them Boers.
The major wants
to see him.
Let me have a look
at that.
We should have hung
them all, shouldn't we,
instead of giving them
a king's pardon?
What's his name?
Bloody hell.
With me, Brooke.
Come on, girls.
Next, please.
Oi.
Uh, Mr. Van Dimon.
Diemen...
Van Diemen.
So, Mr. Van Dimon,
what brings you
all the way to our remote little
corner of the world?
Well, I'm curious.
Curious?
You'd have to be very curious
to travel thousands of miles.
Bloody right, I'm curious.
I'm very curious
to find out
why you boys crossed
two oceans
to help the British
burn down my farm.
Well...
Arjan Van Diemen.
And I thought
the war was finished.
Not for you,
you murdering bastard.
You're under arrest.
Give it over.
Go on.
Give him
his rifle back.
Now, you bloody fool!
Put your weapon away.
Do you know
who this is?
That'll be all.
Thank you, Saunders.
Jesus.
Don't make me
write you up.
Get back to the docks,
Brooke.
Give some real soldiers
a hero's welcome.
Yes, sir.
Apologies for the undignified welcome,
Mr. Van Diemen.
Saunders there was
with me in South Africa.
He seems to have forgotten
the war's over.
I'm sure you understand.
Mm.
So you do exist.
I led a detachment
of cavalry
for nearly two years
trying to catch up with you.
We chased you clean
across the Transvaal
whilst you caused havoc.
And you, Major...
you couldn't even catch
a simple farmer.
What's your plan here,
Van Diemen?
You're a long way
from home.
You too.
On the contrary,
this is home for me now.
Home?
Huh.
Home these days seems to be
most of the globe to you British.
So are you planning
on buying some land here,
perhaps take up
farming again?
No, I guess we didn't
leave you with much, did we?
Well, for what it's worth,
Mr. Van Diemen,
I hope you do find
your new home here.
Come here.
What is this?
It's a piece of home.
- Home?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you mean, home?
It belonged
to my grandfather.
Sometimes he would cry
over this.
Looks like sand to me...
red sand.
You're very pretty.
There's a lot prettier
in this town.
Some of them officers'
wives, they...
No no no no, I've seen
lots of women...
wahine on Tahiti.
You could be
a princess there.
Take your hands off me.
I'm quite capable
of walking by myself.
Come on, Sergeant.
You've had a bit too much.
Goes with the rank,
Corporal Drake,
- with the rank.
- Yes, Your Highness.
"Goes with the rank."
Oh, watch yourself
there, Teddy.
Don't you "Teddy" me.
Oh, hey. Oi.
There's a lantern on
in the stables.
I'll have his guts
for garters.
Well well well,
what have we here?
If it isn't young Lucy
and a bloody savage.
What are you two
doing in here,
besides the obvious?
I don't think
I know you.
Do you know him?
Never seen him.
Wonder where he gets
his money from.
Weren't interested
in our horses, were you?
He's talking to you.
You think he
understands English?
Anyway,
you're trespassing
on army property.
I think a thrashing
might be in order,
gentlemen, eh?
Now come and take
your punishment
like a good
little savage.
- Hold him up.
- Get up.
Eh?
I'll teach you to mess
with our women.
Get up.
- What did you say?
- Leave him alone, you bastards.
You should have taken
your thrashing, boy.
Savage!
Christ, you bloody...
Jesus Christ.
Jesus.
You bloody killed him.
We need a doctor.
Get a bloody doctor!
Sir...
You walked
into the stables
and he simply
attacked you?
Yes, sir.
Unprovoked?
Well, we did ask him
what he was doing in there.
We thought he was
after the horses.
- That was all?
- Yes, sir.
Levin.
That was about
the way of it.
And this was
the way of it?
Yes, sir.
That were the way of it.
He was off that whaler
that came in yesterday.
Sergeant Leybourne.
I don't think our man
will be getting far, sir.
Let's make sure
he doesn't.
He's been seen
heading off up the coast.
I'll need
half a dozen men.
That should be enough.
And horses.
He's on foot, so we'll soon
catch up with him.
What about dogs?
No, no dogs.
This isn't a blood sport.
I won't have it
turned into one.
Now that local scout...
Mr. Bryce, sir.
Yes, Bryce.
I want him here,
fully provisioned
within the hour.
We'll leave at first light.
See to it.
Van Diemen.
I don't suppose
you saw anything?
You know, we could use
another good tracker.
The reward is
100 sovereigns...
100 sovereigns alive,
25 if dead.
That's a lot of money.
You see that man?
He butchered
British officers.
I don't want that scum
anywhere near me.
That needn't trouble you,
Sergeant Major.
You shan't be
accompanying us.
You and Corporal Levin are in
no fit state to be chasing anybody.
The pair of you
will return to barracks.
I trust I make
myself clear.
Yes, sir.
- Well?
- Yes, sir.
Look, when I arrived
yesterday at the harbor,
I didn't see
any whaler.
They left without him
on the afternoon tide.
The skipper was
angry as hell,
charging around, shouting at
everybody if they'd seen him.
I tell you, I was near
to locking him up.
Why so angry?
Well, he'd lost his
harpoonist, didn't he?
A good harpoon man's
worth gold these days.
These all his belongings?
Yeah, these and his
kit bag over there.
- That too?
- Yeah.
All right, dismount.
Sergeant Leybourne,
these horses need a rest,
- just a few minutes.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Bryce, what is it?
Maori.
See? The weight's
all on the toes.
No heel print.
The weight's right.
By the spacing...
his height.
It's him.
If he keeps heading
up this coast,
he'll reach
Dunney's Point,
find a boat... whew,
away at sea
'fore you know it.
Very well.
- Private Barker!
- Sir.
Get up on those rocks, man, see if we
can't get around the headland
- before the tide comes in.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Van Diemen,
is there a problem?
It's not him.
No disrespect
to Mr. Bryce here,
but our man was used
to wearing shoes.
This man,
whoever he was...
he never wore shoes.
With respect, Major,
I don't think our man
is just another sailor.
I think
he's coming home.
Sir, if we go
right away,
we should be able to get around
before the tide cuts us off.
Thank you, Barker.
All right, mount up!
Van Diemen!
Blast the man.
Barker, get his horse.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Bryce.
Your man left
empty-handed, didn't he?
That's right.
Your Mr. Van Diemen
was right.
Raupo bread.
Maori pollen bread.
Where would he get that?
Look at the size
of this fire.
Whoever this fellow was,
he was in no hurry.
Mr. Bryce, are you
seriously telling me
that we've been following
the wrong man all day?
Same build, same height,
wrong Maori.
I knew we should have
gotten bloody dogs.
We'll double back,
pick up the trail
where our Mr. Van Diemen
disappeared on us.
And you're quite certain
you can do that?
I'll have two trails to follow
instead of just one.
Well, we'd better get on
with it then, haven't we?
Mm, been fishing, eh?
Head, feet.
So you knew I was
watching you, eh?
Good.
Mm.
So you've made yourself
some shoes?
Mm, clever boy.
Horses won't be much use
to us from here on, Major.
Al right.
Thank you, Mr. Bryce.
- Private Barker.
- Yes, sir?
You'll take these horses back
to base in the morning.
Yes, sir.
- Crowther.
- Yes, Major?
- We'll keep yours as a packhorse.
- Sir.
Do not move
unless I tell you to.
I said do not move.
Stand still.
Stop.
Shut up.
Argh! Bloody hell.
That's better, eh?
How much are they
paying you for me?
How much?
100 sovereigns alive,
25 dead.
25?
Mm.
A lot of people
would be happy with 25.
Lucky I got you.
If I have to kill you,
I will.
Mind you, anybody
who'd be happy with 25
would probably be
too stupid to find me.
Yeah, they would.
That's 75 sovereigns'
difference alive or dead.
I'll tell you what:
What will you give me
if I promise
- not to choke myself to death?
- Just walk.
What are you reading?
Hey, I asked you
a question.
That "the wicked
will perish.
The enemies
of the Lord
shall be as the fat
of lambs."
Mm.
"But the righteous
showeth mercy, and giveth."
The 37th psalm.
I spent a lot of time
in a missionary school.
That's where
I learned to read.
You're an educated man.
Does that make
a difference?
Perhaps.
Why?
Because education
distinguishes
the civilized man
from the savage.
Ah, there are no savages
here then.
The missionaries taught
us all to read...
all of us.
My father could quote your
bible from cover to cover.
"You cannot know
your enemy," he said,
"until you know
his God."
And did he find
their God?
Oh yes, he met Him
at the end of a rope.
So what's my life
worth now?
125 sovereigns?
I am not a killer.
You'll have
an honest trial.
I'll get
an honest hanging.
What is that?
Let me see.
You can trust me.
Wife? Daughters?
Pretty.
Yeah.
How old are they...
your daughters?
Eight, and the twins
are six.
And where do they live?
Back in town?
They don't live.
They're buried
in South Africa somewhere.
They say when
children die, they...
they stay children
forever.
You can't start a story
and not finish.
It's not good.
It's not good
for your soul.
Stop here.
Two hours.
All right,
let's keep moving.
It's just mouku.
You can eat it.
You didn't know that,
did you?
Mind you, you weren't
brought up here.
You see this?
Meke-meke.
Just a little nibble on that
and you'll be
spewing your guts out
for days.
I shouldn't have
told you that, should I?
"And His blessing covered
the dry land as a river
and watered it
as a flood."
I could build us
a raft.
"As He hath turned
the waters into saltiness,
so shall the heathen
inherit His wrath."
Stop.
Sit. Sit.
Don't move.
I'm not moving.
Turn around slowly.
Drop the pistol.
Drop the pistol!
No.
What?
Drop it.
No.
I'll shoot you.
You know,
when I travel
I always keep
an empty chamber
in case of accidents.
Before you cock it,
I'll have a bullet
between your eyes.
You're lying.
Truth is
I'm not really sure.
I've been careless
these past two days.
Of course,
we won't know until
you pull that trigger.
I don't believe you.
Fine.
And I will
pull the trigger.
Fine.
Well, if you're right, I'm dead.
If I'm right, you're dead.
But until you pull that trigger,
we won't know.
Drop the gun.
No.
- Drop the gun.
- You drop your gun.
- I'm not dropping my gun.
Fine.
Let's just walk to shore.
And keep your hands
where I can see them.
No. No.
I will pull the trigger.
I'll take my chances.
My legs are getting cold.
You should have
stayed over there where it's dry.
You are the most annoying man
I have ever met.
I should kill you
for just being annoying.
I thought
you weren't a killer.
I'm not, or I would have
shot you right away.
In which case
you'd be dead.
Well, we don't know
that yet, do we?
I'd like a smoke.
No.
Damn you.
Come on, come on.
They meet here
separately.
Hold there.
There's two now.
- Both of them? Two men, both of them?
- There's two.
- All right, which way?
- This way.
Sa-bine.
Sabine.
Is that your wife?
What language is this?
I told you
I'm from South Africa.
You're one of them Boers.
Sounds like a bushpig.
"Boer"...
it means "farmer."
You're the strangest
farmer I've ever met.
You fought the British,
didn't you?
My grandfather led our people
against the British.
He was a great leader,
a warrior.
But he lost.
He lost like you.
And this brought great
shame on our people.
And we were labeled
Tangata Hara...
men of sin, rebels.
I never lost.
Well, why are you here
then, in my land?
Where is your farm,
farmer man?
You fought the British
and you lost too, didn't you?
You lost.
And that's not
all you lost, is it?
Where'd you learn
to track a man?
Hey.
Dabe.
What do you mean, Dabe?
Dabe... my father's
houseboy,
old Hottentot.
Hottentot.
What's a Hottentot?
A South African bushman.
A bushman?
I've never seen one.
You never will.
All gone, good as.
Like me.
As dumb as they are,
they will catch you
and probably shoot you.
If I were in your shoes,
which I am,
I'd just worry about
them finding me.
You can't run forever.
One of us will find you.
You best pray
it isn't me.
But I'm not the one
who's running.
I think you're the one
who's running away.
And I think...
I think you left
your soul behind.
Now untie these
before I break
your bloody neck.
You know, when you sail
for a long time,
you've got to get on
with all the blokes.
If someone
doesn't get on,
we just throw them overboard
at the next port.
With you,
I don't think
we would have waited
till the next port.
Your wife...
how did she die?
Did she get sick?
Did she get sick of you?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
Thanks.
Walk.
- What is this?
- Biltong.
I'd rather die
of starvation.
Right here.
Something here.
Blood.
Fighting or...
Which way?
Come.
Wouldn't it be easier
if we just wait
for the river to calm down?
No, I'm not taking chances
with the rain,
not in this
bloody country.
It's not going to rain.
I'm a sailor.
I can tell you the weather
from the color
of the water.
I lied, okay?
I lied.
Come.
You're taking me back
to be hanged
for something
I didn't even do.
Huh?
What would you do, huh?
What?
Oh, Mr. Silence now, huh?
Mr. Silence?
You say another word...
I'll hang you myself
from that bloody tree
over there. You follow?
Oh, you lie as well.
Huh?
Jezus Christus
Allemachtig!
You lie just by
saying nothing.
In fact,
everything you don't say
is one big lie.
What in God's name
are you talking about?
Well, that's the second
question you've ever asked me.
You going to answer it?
Well, you just said you'll hang me
if I said another word.
Argh!
Come, you, come.
Walk.
Your wife...
she died in that war,
didn't she?
It's none
of your concern.
- She did, didn't she?
- It's none of your concern.
I was just asking.
Why do you...?
No.
I just...
She never died
in no bloody war.
But I thought
you said...
I don't know how
she died, all right?
All right.
When the sporting British
couldn't beat us,
Lord Kitchener
sent his troops down
to burn our farms.
He drove our women
and children off
like cattle.
He penned them
in these
barbed-wire camps.
I don't know
how they died...
sickness, starvation.
There's no one left
to tell.
Listen, we both
hate the British.
I don't hate the British.
- Yes, you do.
- I don't hate the British.
I hated my God
for a time.
I stood naked
in front of Him.
I reviled Him.
I was so angry.
I thought
I knew Him.
Then I remembered
that God did not create
the savage in me.
"Though He slay me,
yet will I trust
in Him."
"But I will maintain
my own ways before Him."
Mm.
I still think
you hate the British.
You think you can get me
to set you free?
- Well, I don't know.
- You think
that if you could make
you and me the same,
that would make me
set you free?
I fought for something.
You're just
a bloody criminal.
I'm not a criminal.
You're walking
on my land.
My tupunas named
the mountains and the rivers.
It's my lineage.
And I saved your life,
bushpig.
It's about respect.
Let me tell you
about respect.
During the war
me and my men...
we would cut off
the trigger fingers
of the bravest British
officers we captured...
only the bravest
officers, mind,
the ones most worthy
of respect.
You understand that?
That's what I did
to people I respected.
Doesn't leave much hope
for me then, does it?
Hope kills fools like you
every day.
Sergeant, let's send
Corporal Crowther
back to base
for fresh provisions.
This is taking a damn sight longer
than I'd hoped.
Yes, sir.
You'd better show Crowther
where you think we'll be this evening,
'cause I don't
bloody know.
It'll just be
a rough guess, Major.
Yes, I'm sure it will,
Mr. Bryce.
Do you think
he's got him, sir...
that Van Diemen?
Without a doubt.
Are the stories they
tell about him true...
you know,
butchering our men?
Well, let me put it
this way, Private...
if it weren't
for the reward,
we'd probably be spared the trouble
of executing him.
I reckon that'd
serve him right, sir.
Drake was a good man.
Drake was a trousered
ape, Private,
a disgrace to his uniform
and his rank.
Begging your
pardon, sir,
but he didn't deserve
to die the way he did.
No, you're quite right.
Indeed he didn't.
You haven't seen action yet,
have you, Private?
No, sir, not as such.
Not yet.
I hope to, sir.
A word of caution:
Just be sure
that when your children
ask you what you did...
what you did
in defense of the realm,
that you're able to give
them a worthy answer.
I beg your pardon, sir?
If he's still alive,
he'll be given a fair trial.
If he's guilty,
he'll be hanged.
An example
will be made.
Te Ara Ruamano.
The path of Ruamano.
He's like our
spiritual guardian.
And he's known to save those
of his people in danger.
What?
This... you pakeha call it
Telson's Gorge.
Let me look.
Look, you can draw your gun
and shoot me.
Don't doubt it.
I will shoot you.
That bullet will cost you
75 sovereigns.
Nice.
North, south,
east.
Oops.
Damn you.
Come.
Come come come.
No no, I don't care much
for that idea.
- I will let you go.
- Let go.
I'll let you go.
Go ahead, let go.
I swear I'll shoot you.
Well, you can try.
But to get your gun,
you're gonna have to let go
of this rope with one hand.
I'll break your bloody neck
if you jump.
Or you could
fall in with me.
And with that pack,
the rifle
and your fat puku,
you could sink and drown.
I'll shoot you
as you fall.
You might miss.
And I might drown.
Ruamano might save me.
But we won't know,
will we,
until you let go?
You wish to fight me?
Come. Come.
Get up.
I'm innocent.
What's the matter
with you, eh?
I'm just trying
to uphold the law.
You're a liar.
It's got nothing to do
with the law.
It's for money.
You've sold your soul.
You know they're
going to hang me
for something
I didn't even do.
There were witnesses.
Yes, soldiers.
And a woman.
She's a pakeha woman
and I'm a Maori.
It was soldiers
who did it.
And it was soldiers
who hung my father.
They made me watch.
Then they forced
my head around
and made me watch them
hang my grandfather.
If you kill me,
you will condemn yourself.
They will find you,
no matter how long,
how many years...
What's a few years
worth, eh? Eh?
What's it worth
to a condemned man?
Eh? Argh!
Do it. Do it.
Do it!
You can't kill me.
You can't do it.
Are you all right?
I'm quite well,
Mr. Bryce.
Thank you.
You bloody little Maori.
- That's enough.
- No.
That's enough, Mr. Bryce,
unless you plan to carry
him back to town.
Sergeant, tie him up.
Renwick, get the rope
and tie him up.
Well, Mr. Van Diemen,
you've obviously endured
- a tough couple of days.
- Yeah, Major.
You needn't fret, sir.
100 sovereigns are yours.
Admirable, most admirable.
Come on, get up.
Get up, you bloody savage.
Renwick, give us a hand.
Get up, your murdering
bastard, you.
Major, with your permission,
if you tie his hands in front of him,
it'd help him walk
easier and quicker.
All right. Sergeant, do as
Mr. Van Diemen suggested.
Sir.
Renwick.
I didn't expect to see you
until our return, Sergeant Major,
Well, sir,
Corporal Crowther said
your orders were for me to bring
supplies with due haste, sir.
I'm sure the corporal
said no such thing.
Well, now you're here,
you'd better get about it, I supposed.
Just remember,
Sergeant Major,
this is not a vendetta.
Yes, thank you, Saunders.
All right, Sergeant Major.
Tough bastards,
aren't they?
My family fought
against them
in the land wars
30 years ago.
Good fighters,
clever as the weasels.
You face them doing
one of those godless
war-jigs of theirs,
their haka,
screaming like a pack
of wild dogs,
mate, you know
you're in trouble then.
Fierce.
And the women are worse.
Excuse me.
I should know.
I married one.
Some meat.
Thank you.
Where's he going?
Feeding our meat
to a murderer.
What, is he
comforting him?
Feeding the savage.
- Thanks.
- Mm?
For this.
You must have been
quite a soldier.
I was never a soldier.
More like...
we were a small rabble.
We stopped the British,
but only
for a short while.
You were fighting
for your land,
fighting for your
freedom.
That'll make a soldier
out of a man.
Fighting for my freedom?
Well, you were,
weren't you?
I'll tell you
about the freedom
I was fighting for.
Late one morning
the day after New Year's,
I was riding home
to my farm.
I saw Dabe
for the last time.
He was hanging
from my neighbor's tree.
What, the British
hung your Dabe?
No.
Not the British.
My neighbor...
he hung him
for stealing a duck.
82 years old.
No old bushman was going
to steal from a white man.
My friend...
he hung him from a tree,
left him there
for six months
as an example.
Did you avenge him?
No.
I went to war
and fought for that
bastard's right
to do it again.
That's the freedom
I fought for.
Without freedom
we're nothing.
When they hung
my grandfather,
he called to me...
"It's you now, Kereama.
You must rid us all
of this hara."
The shame?
But I ran away.
That's different.
You were only a boy.
That's why
they never hung me.
I wasn't big enough.
Soldiers just threw
the bodies into a hole.
I couldn't even
bury them properly.
So I ran away.
But I always knew
in my heart
that I had to come back
and set them free.
So that's why
you've come home...
to restore your family honor
and your own?
I almost made it.
It's just
beyond that ridge.
But you denied me that.
You denied me that...
you and your Dabe.
Saunders, I think
the prisoner will be fine
without your attention.
Come on, mate.
Come on, get up.
You'll be all right.
Come on.
These ropes
were cut, see?
Mm-hmm.
He has a way with rope.
- He has a way with rope?
- Mm-hmm.
What, you knew?
You let him go.
It was tough enough
catching him.
In God's name, man,
do you really think I'd let him go?
Well, I'll tell you
one thing for sure:
Somebody let him go,
and in a hurry.
He cut through his
wristband as well.
We'll get him.
How is he, Sergeant?
The savage beat him
pretty bad, sir, but he'll be okay.
Mr. Bryce.
How long?
Two, three hours perhaps.
But he's in bad condition.
He'll leave an easy trail.
He won't get far.
Van Diemen?
Mr. Bryce knows
his business.
If you'll excuse me,
gentlemen,
but I have a score
to settle.
Right, we'll leave
camp here.
Major Carlysle, sir.
This had better be
important, Saunders.
I just wanted
to ask, sir,
now that the prisoner
is armed, what your...
Armed?
How armed?
Did Sergeant Leybourne
not bring it to your attention, sir?
The prisoner made off
with Renwick's rifle.
Unfortunately, it would appear
that the niceties of justice
are fast becoming
a luxury we can
no longer afford.
You have my permission
to shoot him on sight.
However, this is not
to be a game.
There's no place here
for sport.
I'll see court-martialed
any man
who doesn't kill him cleanly
with the first shot.
Do you understand?
Mr. Bryce.
He could have gone
one of two ways.
Take the wrong one...
- Mr. Bryce, please don't tell me...
- I'll find him.
Well, do so,
and quickly.
This is a sacred place...
the home of Ruamano.
I would come here
with my grandfather
when I was a little boy.
I'd have to wait outside
while he entered
into the cave
to talk to our
spiritual guardians.
Now it is my time...
time to redeem the mana
of my fathers.
There's only one way
out of here.
You know this camp.
Bryce has lost the track,
but only for a while.
That won't last.
We have to get you
out of here.
Believe me, they will
shoot you down.
I'm still curious
to know
why you cut
the trigger fingers
off the British
soldiers.
God tells us it is a sin
to kill other men
unless you are
protecting your home
and your loved ones.
It stopped good men
from sinning again.
Get up.
Come.
Bryce was better than...
than you thought.
There's plenty of cover.
If we split up,
we can get around them.
But they'll just keep on
following us.
They haven't got us yet.
Look, I can't run. I can't climb.
There's no way around them.
- You have to.
- I can't run.
We may not have to.
It's your life.
No, it's your life too.
And I'm not a killer.
We can fight.
Ja?
I need you to do
one thing...
one great thing.
No.
You must.
I won't do it.
You must help me on my
journey to Hawaiki.
What?
It's the final resting place
for our people.
Don't let them hang me.
I don't want to die
like my fathers,
hung from some post
without mana,
without dignity.
I'll take it from you.
Saunders, Bryce,
round to the right.
Sergeant, with me.
Damn.
Van Diemen.
Another trophy
for His Majesty's justice.
He had courage.
He needs respect.
Not your soundest economic
decision, Van Diemen.
I have a little saved.
Bugger that.
I'd rather have his head.
The price will be
on your own.
Yeah.
We have to take
the body back.
At least have your men
bury him, Carlysle.
We cannot leave him here.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Van Diemen.
Enough time has been
spent on this.
- There you go.
- Thank you, Murray.
You think Bridget
will like it here?
Without a doubt, sir.
I've ordered the linen
you requested, sir.
It'll be here in plenty of time
for your wife's arrival.
He's alive.
Sergeant!
Sergeant Leybourne.
I want a man in every
port, every harbor
on the lookout for a Maori with his
right index finger missing.
Now, damn it. I want him arrested
and brought here alive.
Van Diemen.
Major.
I heard you were
leaving us.
This country has
no interest for me.
Australia?
There's a place they've named
Van Diemen's Land there.
Mm, I like
the sound of it.
Leaving without
your reward?
Thank you.
There we go.
25 sovereigns.
It could have been
four times that.
Mm.
He's alive, isn't he?
It must have been
like old times for you.
He didn't even scream
when you cut his finger off.
I suppose you have
your reasons.
I suppose I'll never quite
understand what they are.
It's quite the sum.
But why so generous?
You were there,
weren't you?
Did you give the order?
Did you give the order
to burn down my farm?
No, I did not.
Oh.
Tell me one thing:
Was anybody
in the house
when you watched it
burn to ash?
No.
I can assure you of that.
Sir. Sir, we're ready.
The captain's gonna be
wanting to weigh anchor.
Yeah.
Major.
Van Diemen.
You know, I've sent
messengers to every port,
every whaling station.
Seen one of these before?
At most you've bought him
a few weeks,
perhaps a few days.
I sincerely hope
it was worth it.
Do you know
what a few days of life
means to a condemned man?
Right about there.