Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
On his 35th birthday,
l decided to tell Julius Benedict...
the truth about himself.
Julius already knew
that he was the product...
of a scientific experiment...
conducted by the American government.
A top-secret experiment designed
to produce a physically,
mentally and spiritually
advanced human being.
He knew that,
unlike other little boys,
he had not one, but six fathers--
All very distinguished men...
especially chosen for
their genetic excellence.
And of course,
he knew about Mary Ann Benedict,
the remarkable young woman...
who was selected to be his mother.
Sadly, he had long lived
with the tragic knowledge...
that his mother died
while giving birth to him.
Now, what Julius did not know,
not until this very moment,
was that about a minute
after he was born...
his mother gave birth
to another baby boy.
l have a brother?
Ya.
He was sent to an orphanage
in Los Angeles...
at the same time
l brought you here to the island.
Julius had spent his entire life
here on the island,
helping me with my research.
l always thought he was happy,
and had no desire to leave.
How wrong l was.
l must find him.
Julius, Julius!
Wait, wait.
l couldn't believe he was going.
He wasn't equipped to deal
with the outside world.
All of his knowledge was from books.
Julius could speak 12 languages.
He excelled in history, science,
mathematics, literature.
He was pure in body and in spirit.
Ahhh!
But for the first time,
Julius would not listen to me.
He's probably just like me.
The nearest island with
an airport was 27 miles away.
But Julius did not care.
He had become obsessed
with the idea...
that his brother, Vincent,
was in some kind of trouble...
and desperately needed his help.
Honey, l'm home!
- Oh, no!
- Oh, no.
- Get going!
- l'm going.
Oh, hello, hello!
Oh, my goodness!
Good-bye.
- We're gonna be late for work.
- l need my horoscope.
- Yeah, horoscope.
- ''Your judgment is at its peak today.
Use it wisely,
and romance will follow.''
- Ooh, good one.
- l hope so.
Ladies!
- Vince!
- l thought you broke up with him.
l did, l did!
- You don't mind if l talk
to your sister, do you?
- She doesn't mind.
Don't give him any money.
Uh, no, no, l promised Marnie
l wouldn't give you any money.
Don't look at me like--
Don't do that thing
with your eyes.
l'm not even supposed
to be here with you.
You are here,
and so am l.
Maybe millions
of people go by,
but they all
disappear from view.
l only have eyes
for you, Linda.
l only have
eyes for you.
Mmm.
- lt's the baby Klane!
- What?
- Hi.
- Can l help you?
- Uh, yeah.
Where's the little shit?
You'll have to be
more specific...
concerning the clientele.
Benedict.
Oh, he wouldn't come in here.
- lsn't that right, Marnie?
- Who, Vincent?
That weasel? That creep?
l wouldn't serve him if he crawled in
on his hands and knees.
Take out the papers
and the trash
Or you don't get
no spending cash
lf you don't scrub
that kitchen floor
You ain't gonna
rock and roll no more
Yakety-yak
don't talk back
l knew you were trouble
the second l laid eyes on you.
Excuse me. l just have never
heard this kind of music before.
Yakety-yak
don't talk back
Take out the papers
Take... out...
the... papers
Take out the papers
Take... out...
the... papers
And the trash
Trash
La-la-la
Mada-dada
Hey-tow
Thank you.
Raf-a-hoo
Fa-haf-ha
Sew-do-a
Fair-da
Wa-fa
Hava-do-ha
So-do
Begga-do-fow
Well-a
Beta-do-tha
Juggle-baba
Betta-do-thee
Rugg-a-do-a
Higga-do-ha
Tucko-day
Ragga-do-ga hoo-ha-yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, Vince!
Listen, Al,
you gotta help me out.
l'm into the Klane
brothers for $20,000.
- You borrowed money from a loan shark?
- What do you got?
Got anything for me?
See what you got.
We're doing this
too often, Vince.
l'll give you something.
l got a nice BMW
up on 4, stall 20.
Vince, l'll take all
of these you can get.
All right, Tony.
- For you.
- Thanks, Tony.
Yeah.
Whoa, Tony!
There's only $4000 here.
For a car like this is $6000.
We're in a recession.
Everything's tough.
You wanna try someone else,
no hard feelings.
No, l just could've
used some more.
- You okay, Vince? You seem worried.
- Yeah.
Your bowels troubling you?
What an amazing country.
Hey.
Gotta light, pal?
Oh, excuse me.
l don't smoke, pal.
Yeah. Ha-ha.
Yeah, good stuff, huh?
- Pickin' up something
for the girlfriend?
- l don't have a girlfriend.
Do women really
wear those things?
lf you're lucky, they do.
l can't believe it.
- You're from out of town?
- Yes.
As a matter of fact, l come from
an island in the South Pacific.
Whoa!
What the hell did
you do to him, man!
l did nothing.
The pavement was his enemy.
Let me check him out.
A light concussion.
Uh-oh.
- l carry him to a hospital.
- No!
l think you should
just take off, man.
Find your horse
you came in on.
l'm so sorry about this.
- l feel terrible.
- Me, too. Thanks a lot.
- Sorry.
- Yeah, l'm sorry.
The next time you should
really consider wearing helmets.
Yeah, have a nice day.
You don't have to buy them.
Just don't say they're cheap!
These are quality socks.
What a day it's been.
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, oh! Jesus Christ!
$53! Are you
out of your mind?
Your vehicle is in a handicapped zone,
if you didn't notice.
So, do l look
normal to you?
You don't have a handicapped
sticker in your windshield.
Oh, come on.
You don't need a sticker.
Handicapped, my ass!
l'll need your
driver's license, sir.
Look, l'm sorry
l lost my temper.
Driver's license,
please.
- Look, l had a very bad day.
- Driver's license... please.
You've got over 200 outstanding
parking tickets, Mr. Benedict.
You just had your birthday.
Your driver's license expired.
Happy birthday.
Watch your head.
Thanks.
Come along, now.
So this is where
my brother grew up.
l'm so happy he had so many
children to play with.
And that's where
he must have slept!
Yes, it was.
How did you know?
lt's the one l'd have chosen,
close to the fire extinguisher.
ln case of a fire,
l could have given the alarm
and saved all the other orphans.
We've had only one fire
in here at St. Charlotte's.
Vince Benedict started it,
we like to think by accident.
Tell me a little bit
about Vincent.
Was he a great athlete?
lnterested in chess and poetry?
l'm certain God had a purpose
when he created Vince Benedict,
but it had nothing
to do with chess or poetry.
Oh, l'm sorry.
Odd, the contents
of his files are missing.
That is Vince?
He looks so happy.
He should.
That's Sister Maria,
- his biology teacher.
- l always liked biology.
So did Vincent.
He disgraced Sister Maria,
who had to leave the order.
Then he stole all the money from
the library fund, and ran away.
l must find my brother.
Do you know
where he might be?
Jail, a man of his character
can only be in jail.
You're full of goodness, Julius.
l pray you never find him.
Benedict, visitor.
- l'm looking for Vincent Benedict.
- You got him.
l have rowed halfway
across the world--
Wrong, l just rowed a day--
l've been looking forward to
this moment my whole life.
l've been on my island,
l'm telling you.
This is incredible that--
l have looked for--
You've gotta talk
into the phone, Bozo.
Vincent.
Yes, Vincent...
l know you don't
know who l am.
- But believe me, l came--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
l've got another six hours
to pay the money back.
Tell the Klane brothers that harassing
a man already in the slammer...
is beneath even them,
all right?
l don't know any Klane brothers.
l'm your brother, Julius.
Huh? Come again?
My name is Julius,
and l'm your twin brother.
Oh, obviously.
The moment l sat down, l thought
l was looking into a mirror.
We are not
identical twins.
- Oh, no?
- No.
l wouldn't be
too sure, pal.
l don't lie.
l am your brother.
You must let me help
you get out of here.
You want to
help me get out?
Yes, right now.
Well, money talks,
and bullshit walks.
How can bullshit walk?
That's slang, huh?
Yeah.
l'm in fast company here.
Take a look over there.
See that man?
Pay him money, all right?
They let me out.
l'll be anything you want,
your aunt, uncle, sister...
your cousin,
brother-in-law, anything.
- All right?
- Okay, l pay right now.
- You pay now.
- Okay, Vince.
Okay. Go pay.
All right, pay him.
What is this,
''Candid Camera''?
Ahhh, oof!
Twinny, l hope you didn't
blow your wad on the tickets,
because l'm gonna need
a lot more money to get my car.
- l have more money.
- You do?
l'm glad to help you.
Vincent, l'm your brother.
- l love you.
- Whoa!
Look, ease up
on the love talk,
because l'm gonna be tossing
my cookies in a minute.
Tossing your cookies?
Oh, that's more slang!
Where the hell is it?
- This is your car, isn't it?
- Yeah, that's it.
You pay a huge fine,
then they hide it on you.
- How'd you know this was my car?
- We're twins!
l'm so excited. Now we can
go to museums together,
talk philosophy together,
read books together.
- Play chess together.
- Get lost together.
Vincent!
He's so full of energy.
Blue Sedan DeVille.
This is beautiful.
Where you guys going,
out to Hawaii?
- Catch some of them big waves?
- Yeah, something like that.
We have plenty
of room on level 4.
l'll call you
next Saturday.
Whoa, where you going
with my desk?
Takin' back this
furniture, man.
- You're six months behind.
- You're behind!
Six months behind.
That's the problem.
There's no trust
in the world anymore.
l tried to stop them,
Mr. Benedict.
That's all right, it was
time to redecorate anyway.
Vincent Benedict lncorporated.
- Sports agent...
- Airborne!
- Mr. Benedict?
- Yeah?
- lt's Al.
- lt's Al? Ooh, Al, Al, Al.
Look, Miss Busby, uh--
Al, hang on a second.
The corporation's in
a transitional period right now.
Take a couple of days off.
When we regroup, l'll call you.
Whatever you think is best.
- All right.
- l'll take this.
Yeah, go ahead.
Take that.
Before l forget,
happy birthday.
Oh, how sweet.
That's very,
very nice of you.
- Aqua Velva?
- Mm-hmm.
You shouldn't have.
Stacey.
l'll give you
a call, okay?
All right, all right.
Al, save me!
Brand-new Caddy on level 4.
l'll be there!
Don't move! Bye.
Whoa!
Time's up, Vincent.
Did you hit me?
Because l didn't feel a thing.
l felt that.
You gotta understand
something, Benedict.
l like my work.
These are the most unfriendly acts
you're committing.
l don't know
what the problem is,
but l'm sure it
can be resolved...
- without resorting to violence.
- Yeah.
Okay?
Okay.
- You moved too soon.
- He did?
Ahhh!
A little chest pain?
The first rule
in a crisis situation:
You negotiate first
and you attack last.
You negotiate first,
then you attack.
- You never negotiated.
- Na-hah!
You don't know what
kind of an enemy l am.
- Who are you?
- l'm Vincent's brother.
- We're twins.
- That's right.
- You're firewood!
- Axe, Axe, Axe!
You have no respect
for logic.
- But he's got an axe!
- Ahhhh!
And l have no respect for those
who have no respect for logic.
You're a very stupid person.
You tell your brother,
he messes with me, he messes
with my whole family!
l love it when you
hit people, Julius.
Boom!
That was great!
Actually,
l hate violence.
But you're so good at it!
l've got an idea. We should
go into business together.
You could be a boxer.
l could be your manager.
- l don't think l could fight for money.
- No problem!
You do all the fighting,
l'll keep all the money.
l'm really worried
about you, Vincent.
How much money
do you owe?
Don't lie to me.
We're twins.
- l can feel your pain.
- Why do you keep saying that?
We're not twins.
We're not brothers.
We're nothin'!
Twenty thousand.
Due this morning.
Come on.
Don't worry about
anything, Vincent.
As long as l'm with you,
l won't let anyone harm you, okay?
Well, you're
a good guy, Julius.
Now, hang on
to your seat!
You know what?
l completely forgot.
l promised this
friend, Sammy,
that l'd pick his car up
from the airport.
Put it in the slot.
Would you do me
a big favor?
Would you drive this car back
from the airport for me?
Oh, l would love to.
Good, that would
really be a big help.
Do you have a manual, please?
- A manual?
- Yeah.
- lt's in the glove compartment.
- Oh, yeah.
There it is.
- What are you doin' with the finger?
- Learning to drive.
Whoa!
lt's not up here.
Maybe it's under
the back tire.
Look... l mean, usually he
leaves the keys behind the tire.
- Geez!
- What's the matter?
That dopey Sam,
he forgot to leave the keys.
No. Oh, well.
A lot of handicapped children
are gonna be very disappointed.
Handicapped children?
This car was supposed to be auctioned
off at their charity drive tomorrow.
Oh, well. Let's go get
something to eat.
Maybe we should try
to open it ourselves.
Do you really think
we should do that?
lt's for children.
You got a point.
l saw a guy from
the Auto Club do this once.
What do you know,
beginners luck!
These cars have
terrific alarms!
l'll get it in a minute.
Just a second, Jules.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
lf you lift the rear end at an angle
greater than 45 degrees...
the mercury switch activates
the automatic cut-off system,
so that the alarm's
computer thinks...
that the car is being
towed and shuts off.
Can l have the keys
to your car?
You know,
the keys to your car?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No yodeling.
Lovely day.
Come on, Julius.
Step on it!
Yeeeoow!
Oh, my God!
- l am amazed at how well it's going.
- You're doing good.
Don't use both feet
at the same time.
- Just use the gas.
- Okay, one foot.
- One pedal at a time.
- Okay! l will do it!
Pick up the phone,
the phone.
The little thing down on
the right that's making noise.
This is Vincent's car.
Can l help you, please?
- Julius!
- Vincent, where are you?
Look in your rear-view mirror.
You see that little dot?
That's me.
Hello, yeah. Hello!
What are you
doing back there?
There's going to be a lot of
lights coming up, a supermarket.
- Supermarket.
- Take your foot off the gas.
Apply it to the brake.
lt's the thing next to the gas.
The brake pedal.
- Very gently.
- You got it.
Bye, Vincent.
All right.
Okay, it's a supermarket.
Ohhh!
That's what l call fun.
Did you see me
with the two wheels?
l can teach
you that, Vincent.
Julius, let me tell you
something about America.
Nobody likes
a smart ass, all right?
So, what do you think?
Angel's food
or devil's food?
Devil's.
- You know what
l really love about Vince?
- What?
He's a force of nature.
- You're outta control.
- No, l'm not.
That poetry he pretends to write,
they're old song lyrics.
l know. Geez,
you think l don't know that!
- l don't think you know that.
- Well, l do.
lt's this style thing.
That's how he expresses himself.
And he means it, even if
he doesn't know he means it.
- Vince has a truly romantic soul.
- l can't hear this anymore.
Well, don't, 'cause if you
had a boyfriend like l have,
you'd make him a cake
and he'd love it...
and you'd get laid.
- Ah!
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
She's not bad.
l had no idea
that these magazines...
had things like
this inside, inside them.
You didn't? Where've you been?
A desert island?
l come from a tropical island
in the South Pacific.
lt's around 300 nautical miles,
south, southwest of Fiji.
l just got here yesterday
and l already found my brother.
Your brother?
That's right.
My twin brother, Vincent.
- Twins?
- Vince!
- Linda.
- Hi.
Oh, you look gorgeous
in this light.
- You do.
- Really?
Hi. Who's this guy?
This is Vincent's brother.
- l didn't know you had a brother.
- Me, either.
You know each other?
Allow me to introduce
these lovely ladies.
- This is Linda.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Her charming sister, Marnie.
Sisters?
Twins?
Are you sure
this guy's all right?
He's okay.
He's helping me out.
He's from outta town,
kinda latched on to me.
Okay, well, great seeing ya.
Catch ya later.
Great seeing ya.
Oops!
l've only been
driving an hour.
- Linda's your girlfriend, isn't she?
- Yeah, kinda.
- ls Marnie your girlfriend, too?
- Marnie?
Marnie hates my guts.
She kinda likes you, though.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- She hardly knows me.
- That's the best way.
You see,
women love men...
who are mysterious
and devious.
Keeps them on their toes.
-lt excites them. You know what l mean?
-No.
- You do like women?
- Very much so.
They're strange
and sensitive.
They have compassion.
l have the highest
respect for women.
You're a virgin!
That's private.
A 230-pound virgin.
lt's all right.
lt's something--
lt's just one
of those things.
Oh, Julius.
My little baby poodle.
Such a baby cat.
Look, did l neglect you?
Not anymore. Come on.
That's a good little pussy cat.
This is sweet Julius.
Okay, here you go.
You named
your cat Julius?
The secret to take-out eggplant
parmesan is extra cheese.
- There we go.
- That much cheese?
Oh, yeah.
The more cheese, the merrier.
There you go.
l know you're probably used to
growing your own vegetables...
and spearing fish on the lagoon,
but here on the mainland,
we just nuke it.
That's it. Here we go.
Feast your eyes.
Dinner is served.
- Yummy.
- Yeah.
- Ahhh!
Through the lips, over the gums,
look out--
Look out stomach, here it comes.
Ta-dum!
- Julius!
- Oh, l like nuked food.
- Mm-mmm!
- Mmm!
Now let me get
this straight.
One of our fathers was
a famous football player?
- Yes!
- And another one was...
- a physicist at M.l.T.?
- Yes, he won the Nobel Prize.
Naturally! All of our dads
were these big shots.
And Mom...
was like... superwoman.
But she didn't survive
the delivery.
And l was sent
to an orphanage,
while you were raised
on a tropical paradise...
by a scientist who
you do research for,
but who doesn't pay you,
because you don't need money.
Did l leave anything out?
l think it's important we try
to find our fathers.
Oh, you mean the geniuses
who contributed...
to the sperm milk shake.
Why are you being so immature
about all this?
Do you know how many times
l've heard stories like this?
lt's every
orphan's fantasy.
My real mom and dad
were rich...
and beautiful.
But there was a mix-up
in the hospital...
and l got switched
with another baby.
But one day, there's gonna
be a knock at the door...
and there they'll be...
with open arms,
crying, ''My darling.
''My treasure.
We didn't know.
How can we make
it up to you?''
Let me tell you something
for your own good, Julius.
lt's a crock.
l liberated this from
my file at the orphanage.
Here it is.
Read it and weep.
''Dear Sister Anderson, your request
for orphan's benefits...
- ''for Vincent Benedict has been denied.
- Denied, yeah.
''According to our files,
his mother did not die...
- ''during birth.
- She's not dead.
''We have a current
address for her at...
''172 Canyon Glen Drive,
Los Angeles.
''Vincent's case seems to be
one of simple abandonment,
and as such,
he's ineligible for aid.''
That's right, Julius.
She abandoned me.
This letter was written
30 years ago.
We were five years old.
Our mother didn't die
when we were born!
You knew all this time
where she was...
and you never
contacted her?
l don't know about your mother,
''Miss Perfect, 1952,''
but my mother was a slut
and if she's still alive,
l hope she's
in a lot of pain.
She dumped me once.
There is no way l'm gonna give
her a chance to do it again.
lf they have lied to us about Mama
for all these years,
maybe they lied to her, too.
We got to find her.
- We have to check this address.
- You do what you want.
l got a cash-flow problem.
- Hello.
- Hey, Vince, we haven't
forgotten about you.
You better have our money
tomorrow morning, or else.
Or else what, you blimp?
Oh, we're rollin'.
Tests on the new low-temperature
gaskets look great.
- Mr. Garfield, there's a man--
- Not now.
- Who are you?
- l'm Webster.
- lt's okay!
- Christ! You were never
supposed to come here.
We were never
supposed to meet.
- You're supposed to be--
- Driving that car down to Texas.
l got my driving gloves.
l got my driving glasses.
l got my driving hat.
But l got no car.
The car was there.
The merchandise was in the trunk.
Your instructions
were on the cassette.
He wants more money.
That's what this is about.
- He wants more money.
- Whoa, whoa. Let me explain.
Sit down.
l got a reputation
to uphold.
People put their trust in me.
They know l always
deliver the goods...
and l always come
back with the money.
This is making me look
very bad professionally.
- This is bullshit. The car was there.
- That's right.
The parking attendant
thought we were going to Hawaii.
- The parking attendant?
- He liked the car.
We put on those loud shirts
so we'd look like tourists.
You know,
l just realized that...
in over 20 years of service,
not one of my clients...
has ever seen my face.
l don't think that's
a problem. Hey!
No, please, please!
- Hi.
- Oh, excuse me, could you
tell me who lives here?
- Grandpa,
this man wants
to talk to you.
Thank you.
Hello?
Yes, can l help you?
l'm terribly sorry
to disturb your party.
l know this may
sound strange,
but l'm looking for someone
that lived here a long time ago.
Mary Ann Benedict.
She was my mother.
You're Mary Ann's son?
That looks just
like you, Grandpa.
Honey, why don't
you go inside...
and help Grandma
with lunch, okay?
Dad?
Uh... no!
- But maybe technically speaking.
- Dad!
Dad!
- Wait a minute!
- Dad! lt is you!
This is a big surprise.
Dad, this is incredible.
l don't know what to--
We could use a drink.
Where'd you come from?
One of my fathers! You don't know
what this means to me.
Uh, Mr. Webster, l hope you are
happy with the vehicle...
we chose for
your little journey.
When you get near Houston,
phone 713-555-0342...
and ask for uh, uh,
Beetroot McKinley.
He will arrange to trade you a briefcase
for the merchandise in the trunk.
Thank you.
Mary Ann Benedict.
l haven't said that name
out loud for over 30 years.
Your mother was...
an amazing woman.
Oh, the times l've wondered what would
have happened if l'd have married her.
Why didn't you?
Oh, l asked her to.
She turned me down.
She said she was afraid...
to have any more children.
See, they told her
you had died at birth.
Who told her we died?
Mitchell Traven,
the guy with the clipboard.
He supervised the experiment
for the government.
He still runs a genetics lab
at Los Alamos, New Mexico.
l'll have to pay
him a visit.
Watch out for him.
He's kind of a dickhead,
if you know what l mean.
Dickhead?
No, l don't.
But... l'm learning.
l'm concerned about the time frame.
That's my private line, honey.
l'll take care of that.
You boys, excuse me.
Beetroot McKinley talkin'.
Who is this?
Uh, Webster.
l'm callin' from California.
l happen to have something--
Some merchandise
that you might want.
Well, bring it to me, son.
Let me enrich you.
Well, uh, Mr. Beetroot,
it's the amount
of enrichment...
that l wanted
to talk about.
Don't try and renegotiate
with old Beetroot, son.
Now look, Beetroot,
if we can't renegotiate,
we wither and die.
Look, there's no way,
Mr. Beetroot,
that l am going to deliver
any damn Cadillac...
unless l know for sure
that l have...
twenty for my cut.
Twenty! You little
shit-for-brains peckerwood!
You're out of your
goddamn, greedy mind!
- l guess that seems
a little high for you.
- Yeah!
l'm a reasonable man.
How about fifteen?
- The deal is five!
- Five?
l could do better
than five here.
lf you can do better
than five million dollars,
well, then, son,
you take it.
Beetroot,
l'll see you in Houston.
After all, fair is fair.
l'll just have to find it in
my heart to live with your offer.
Well, good.
Five million!
Five million dollars!
Five mil-l-lion dollars!
Five, five million dollars!
Five million dollars!
Five m-m-million!
Cash, lots of cash.
Whoa!
Listen, the most amazing thing
has happened, Vincent.
- You scared the living shit outta me.
- l met one of our fathers.
He told me about
a man in New Mexico...
- who probably knows where Mom is.
- Oh, great! Yes!
- Listen, she didn't abandon you.
- No?
You know what l mean?
She didn't abandon you.
- She didn't even know you were born.
- Oh!
- They told her that l died.
- No kidding?
Look, Julius,
l'm in a hurry.
- You know Sammy, who gave me this car?
- Yeah.
You remember Sammy? He wants me
to take this car to Houston.
- So l'm gonna be gone a couple of days.
- Houston?
Hous--
- Hou-- No!
- You know something?
New Mexico's on
the way to Houston.
A lot of places are
on the way to Houston.
Use the house,
make some phone calls.
Throw wild parties.
Take advantage of your brother.
We have to see this man, Traven,
in New Mexico.
- No, we don't have to see
this man in New Mexico.
- Yes, we do!
And l'm coming with you.
We'll go see the man.
- l take a shower. l get my bags.
- Get your bags.
Be right out. Oh, boy!
l'll be here, bro.
Okay.
This place is a zoo!
Wait, wait.
- Happy birthday, Vince.
- Oh.
- God.
- lt's not my birthday.
Better late than never.
- Oh.
Look what Marnie
made for Julius.
- You baked?
- Yeah. ls Julius around?
- He's taking a shower.
- l'll go give these to him.
So-o-o!
- Where'd you get this car?
- Sammy. You know Sammy.
- Where you going?
- lnside. Have some coffee?
You're going somewhere and you
weren't even gonna say good-bye.
Take out your papers and your trash
Or you don't get
no spending cash
lf you don't scrub
the kitchen floor
You ain't gonna
rock and roll no more
Yakety-yak yakety-yak
Don't talk back
Marnie!
Excuse me, but l was
just taking a shower.
Good singing.
l baked you some cookies.
- Cookies?
- l guess it was a dumb idea.
No, not at all. l'm really
looking forward to tossing them.
- l should put on some clothes.
- l'm sorry, l'll turn around.
Linda and l just came by
'cause she baked him a cake...
- for his birthday.
- l had birthday, too.
Oh, that's right.
You're twins.
Huh?
Whoa.
What is it?
l don't know what it is,
but it's worth a fortune.
- A fortune? That's great!
- Yeah!
Excuse me!
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org