Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Oh, no.
- Hang on, Charlie!
Donna, Charlie.
Are you guys okay?
Please tell me you're okay.
Donna? Your knee's
in an even worse place this time.
Oh, thanks.
You guys, look.
Where are we?
This would be
the unclaimed-baggage warehouse.
I saw this place on TV.
Oh, my gosh. There's at least 50 years'
worth of unclaimed luggage in this place.
Please, someone, tell me it's beautiful.
Hey, Spencer. Looks like your sister's...
...not the only one who's gonna
get a good Christmas this year.
- Somebody wanna unzip me?
- Sure. Sorry.
Cool.
Oh, boy.
No! Please don't kill me.
That was a friendly honk, meant
only to respectfully attract attention.
Oh, hey. Sorry to scare you.
I was just about to carve a beaver.
Carve a beaver. Got it. Got it.
Hey, do you guys sell biodiesel here?
We got regular diesel and unleaded gas.
That's about it.
Unless you want a statue of Lincoln
carved out of a telephone pole.
What harm could one tank of diesel do?
What have I done?
Oh, thank God.
That doesn't look good.
So, what's the cool things you found?
Say hello to my surfboard.
I found a walkie-talkie family pack.
It has cameras and video screens
inside of them.
Oh, I just took a video of the inside of
my ear using a penlight and a macro lens.
Now, who wants to see my ear canal?
Come on.
No, thank you.
I'll watch it, then.
Spencer? Anything you wanna tell us?
Oh, this. It's for my sister.
She loves princesses.
Then why don't you give her
the rich girl over there?
Kidding.
What'd you find?
You know, I have no idea,
but how cool does it look?
Hey, that's an 8-track tape player.
According to the Massachusetts
8- Track Collector Magazine...
...I have the largest collection
of cassettes in the state.
But I don't mean to brag.
This is one of my favorites.
Could this night get any better?
What is he doing?
What are you doing?
- Hoffman.
- Shut up.
Hoffman.
Not now.
Hoffman, I think you should
take a look at this.
This better be good.
What in the sam hill?
Oh, Charles.
Hey.
Yeah, Charles.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look, I saved him, I'll dance with him.
Okay.
Hey, you let me touch you.
I'm touching you, kid. Don't get
any ideas. I can still take you down.
All right, Kmart, let's see what you got.
Okay.
You realize if you tell anyone
about that photo you saw...
...I'll have to kill you.
- Right. Lips sealed.
Not telling anyone, I swear.
Good.
- It was a nice picture, though. I liked it.
- Nice try.
No, I mean, I think girls
look really good in glasses.
Not that you don't
look good without them, of course.
I mean, that's not what I meant at all,
you know?
- I was a dork.
- Hey, join the club.
You're not a dork. You just...
You just need someone doing
better PR for you than your sister.
Are you gonna pass out or something?
Oh, man. I mean, we gotta go.
You know what, guys? We gotta go.
My sister's expecting Santa's sleigh soon.
We don't know
how we're getting to the hotel.
Why do you need a hotel when you've got
a nice concrete room to go back to?
- Run!
- They're on the move, boys.
Don't lose them in here.
Van Bourke, guard the door.
But it's Christmas Eve, sir.
Can you just...
...leave them alone?
Split up, split up!
We might wanna
get off the main road here.
- Grace, come on.
- Dirty. Okay.
Okay, nobody panic.
Nobody panic. Nobody panic!
Donna, I have a confession.
I was never a good runner.
I can't even do the running man.
You smart guys are all the same:
Good on test day, bad on fight day.
Follow me, men.
Watch out for your footing, guys.
I don't want anyone falling behind.
There's the door.
You guys, look, it's the hotel.
Oh, boy.
Move it, moron.
They're escaping out the back.
- It's the Hoover International Lodge.
- We need to get down there.
How? You got four snowmobiles?
Watch the Winter Olympics?
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
What are you doing?
We're going to the hotel
to find Spencer's sister.
Way to go. Anything else
you wanna tell him?
Van Dork, I'm afraid you know
too much now.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Okay, now go!
Wait, I promise I won't talk.
Please let me out!
Hey! Hey!
Last one down the hill is a fired apple.
We seem to be moving a tad rapidly.
Tree! Watch out!
- Pine needles!
- Nice steering, Tex.
I usually like to try to avoid clichés,
but we've got some company.
More trees!
Take evasive action, boys!
Steer around the trees.
How do we steer?
You know, if I wasn't so utterly
terrified, I might be having fun.
Drift!
My butt!
Cowabunga!
Sweet Jehoshaphat!
Look out, he's gonna hit us!
Lean left!
I'm coming, Mr. Porter!
This is all wonderful fun...
...but you do realize the enormous
amount of trouble...
...you're gonna be in
when I catch you, right?
Not if I can help it. Paddle!
Oh, you wanna speed up, huh?
Okay!
Wait for me!
Not to be a stick in the mud...
...but we're moving
at a very dangerous rate of speed.
- I'd like to second that interjection!
- Keep paddling until I say when!
Please tell me you're gonna stop
at the hotel!
Yeah, we are, but you're not!
Hit the brakes!
Unbelievable.
I don't get paid enough for this!
Holy cow!
Well, this should be interesting.
Darn.
Van Dork, aren't you coming with us?
No, you guys do what you gotta do.
I'm just gonna sit here and you know...
...throw up for a little bit.
- Go.
- Spencer.
- Yeah?
- Be careful, okay?
You guys are acting like
you had too much sugar.
Don't worry, Van Bourke. We're okay.
Wait up, you guys.
Guard cat.
You were a worthy opponent.
Ain't it a little past your bedtime, sonny?
I want a Christmas tree.
What about that little one?
What do I look like,
freaking Charlie Brown?
This big one's expensive.
You got any money?
- Sunday potluck, don't forget!
- All right, partner, see you there!
You wanna come in for some eggnog?
Oh, man.
How am I gonna get to my kids now?
Your kids?
No, sir. No kid should be alone
on Christmas Eve. Not in an airport.
I really appreciate it.
However I can repay you, just name it.
Oh, no.
The mayor dropped it off for an
oil change, but he's out of town.
You use it to pick up your kids
and head back here.
I'll get you a rental car
in the morning.
I can't drive that thing.
It gets terrible mileage.
I'd loan you my Caddy, but squirrels
ate through the brake lines.
I'm afraid this is your only choice.
Depends how much you wanna
see your kids.
Forgive me, brother squirrel.
Oh, man.
I hope the boys in the Sierra Club
don't see me in this.
Thanks.
Okay, so my sister is in room 424.
We've got like 14 minutes and... Thirteen.
Okay. Now I'm mad.
Elevator.
- What are you doing? Get in.
- We'll take care of him. Get your sister.
Here, take these walkies.
You'll need them.
Don't you kids know that you're supposed
to be good on Christmas Eve?
Physician, heal thyself!
It's Shakespeare.
Man, you're no end of help
in a fight, are you?
Oh, well. Maybe next Christmas
will be better than this one.
Sir, I advise you not to do that.
Punk, watch this.
Thanks for the tip.
Oh, perfect. Now everything hurts.
My contacts are going crazy.
Once a dork...
...always a dork.
You are so not a dork.
Kid!
- Hey, kid!
- Santa's sleigh arrives in nine minutes.
- We gotta find her.
- It's time to pluck your eyebrows.
- Is my sister Katherine in there?
- Who wants to know?
Her brother wants to know.
Well, I'm not allowed
to talk to strangers.
Let me handle this.
Move!
Oh, no.
Room service! Room service!
Hey! No! Stop that!
Stop. Stop that.
You're gonna get me in trouble!
There were some kids running wild
in the hall...
...and I was just trying to stop them.
It wasn't me.
It sounded like you.
They're very talented children.
I'm just gonna go find the children.
Right now!
- Charlie, where are you guys?
- Engaged with the enemy at the moment.
- Taking evasive action.
- We think Spencer's sister is downstairs.
- We need you guys to keep the coast clear.
- Roger that.
Donna, time for Han Solo
and the Death Star.
Trust me. It's a nerd thing.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Not a Star Wars move.
Oh, no, no, no.
- No!
- Room service! Room Service.
- Room service! Get your free food here!
Now, I know this looks bad, but...
And now so do you.
Oh, no.
Merry Christmas, Katherine.
Don't you just wanna take a picture?
Oh, you're all in so much trouble.
Just don't wake up my sister, okay?
Any more requests?
Milk and cookies?
A jail cell with a view?
Mr. Porter, now, I know you probably
don't want to hear this...
...but I think that maybe you should just
let these kids stay at the hotel.
- It's Christmas.
- Is that your sage advice, Van Bourke?
I will take your opinion
into consideration one day...
...when I actually care what you think.
Oliver...
...as soon as I get these kids
back on their planes, I quit.
March.
Sir, are you taking us to the U.M. Room?
I would never do that to you
on Christmas morning.
- Really?
- No.
You'll all be much happier
here in your own private rooms.
- Private rooms?
- You don't expect me to let you...
...stay together and plan your
next assault on me and my airport?
It's "my airport and I."
Hey, get this, Strunk and White,
"me and my airport" is correct.
- Dang.
- Oh, and by the way...
...all those stranded passengers
you saw sleeping in the gate area?
There are too many of them
and not enough planes leaving.
So I thought
since they followed all the rules...
...and since you have such nice,
comfortable rooms to stay in...
...that you wouldn't mind
if I bumped you from your flights...
...and let them go instead.
- Sir.
- Don't worry.
You'll be able to leave this afternoon
or by this evening.
- Tomorrow for sure.
- You can't do that.
As a matter of fact,
it's one of the few things I can do.
Lock them up.
I'll be in my office watching
your every move on camera:
There'll be guards posted
outside your doors.
If you find your way out of here...
...I'll be the first to congratulate you
and admit defeat...
...because you will have accomplished
the impossible.
Good luck.
Hey, guys.
Thanks for all the help with my sister.
You know, I'm sorry that
all your Christmases have to be ruined...
...because of me.
We probably won't see each other again
after our flights leave, so I just...
...wanted to say
that I had a really good time...
...and that I think we make
a pretty awesome family.
Maybe the thing is it's just none of
our families are meant to stay together...
...you know?
Maybe that's it.
Except for you, Grace.
Actually, that's not totally true.
I thought your parents weren't divorced.
Well, not from each other,
but they sort of divorced me.
What do you mean?
They just don't seem
to like it when I'm around.
That's why they travel all the time.
They're in Paris right now.
- So is that where you're going?
- No. I'm already home.
I live 20 minutes from here.
I flew in today from boarding school.
I figured it'd be more fun hanging out at the
airport than sitting at home with my nanny.
She wanted Christmas off anyway.
Now I'm really depressed.
You guys have vents in your ceiling?
- Yeah.
- Then I'm getting us out of here.
- Spencer.
That guy's watching us on the cameras.
He'll see everything we do.
Not if he doesn't see what we're doing.
Just go to sleep, you little monsters.
- Okay, phase one finished?
- Check.
Okay. On to phase two.
What was the worst Christmas gift
you ever got?
That's easy. My brother Frank gave me
the same Christmas present for 14 years.
Hated it.
- What was it?
- A punch in the head.
Ready? Go.
What the?
Stupid cheap cameras.
Doesn't get any better than this.
Oh, we're supposed
to take away chairs.
- I win!
- Can I say something to you?
What?
Who needs Hawaii?
Donna? Are you okay?
It's really small in here.
I know. It's great, isn't it?
Charlie, just because you compensate for
your abandonment issues by squeezing...
...yourself into small, womb-like spaces
doesn't mean everybody else does.
What?
My mom's a psychologist.
Donna, I won't let anything
happen to you.
I promise.
Thanks.
Oh, Charlie, you didn't.
Sorry, I get nervous.
I had a hot dog when I got off the plane.
Oh, Charlie.
Yeah, can we hold all of those until
we're out of the confined space, please?
Will do.
- Where are you going?
- The food court's this way.
Trust me.
A few hundred yards and I'll be...
Charlie!
Charlie, please tell me you're okay.
Hey, Donna.
I told you I'd get you out of there.
This is where Mr. Porter
put all the Christmas decorations.
Hey, hey!
Wake up!
Wake up! Check the rooms, you idiots!
Does this mean we can go on break?
All clear.
I don't think any planes...
...are gonna be flying today.
- Nope.
Looks like we'll be spending
another day together.
Sounds good to me.
Is that?
Oh, my gosh.
Man, wasn't easy getting this
through security.
It's Christmas.
You know what, guys?
I've got an idea.
Let's do this.
And then I said, "That is my food. "
Donna, how did you get here?
Van Bourke...
...we need your help.
I need a list of all the kids
traveling with families...
...and the passengers
traveling by themselves.
Okay, this one's mine
and that one's yours. Okay?
Can you also please get the unaccompanied
minors back here at 7 a. M?
Oh, one more thing.
I guess I owe you a congratulations.
As promised.
Who trained you kids, the Navy SEALs?
Look, sir, just... Divorce kids are
more resourceful than others, that's all.
Any chance you can tell me
what you're up to now?
Something nice. You know, nothing bad.
I promise.
Any chance of you trusting me
and not locking us up again?
I was just doing my job.
You do know that, right?
Just like I've just been doing my job
every Christmas for the past 15 years.
Bet your family hates it
that you work on Christmas.
Not much of a problem,
since my wife left five Christmases ago.
That why you don't put up
the decorations?
Well, let's just say
they don't remind me of happy times.
We were just, you know,
trying to have a Christmas.
- We thought you'd care.
- Why would I care?
This is an airport.
You're passengers.
- So?
- So passengers leave.
There's one thing I don't get.
I bump you off your planes...
...and I keep you
from your families at Christmas.
Why do you guys seem
almost happy?
Because you didn't keep us from our
family. At least, not our new family.
Right.
I got it.
Mr. Porter.
We got you something.
Sorry we wrecked your vacation.
Almost there.
Highway mileage, not city mileage.
Highway mileage, not city... Oh, come on!
Why?! I've already filled you up
five times!
How can you drink so much?!
You yellow monster!
Good morning.
Merry Christmas! Everybody up!
Happy holidays, everyone.
Merry Christmas, Katherine.
Spencer.
- Spencer, Spencer.
- Oh, whoa, hi.
Spencer, look what Santa brought me.
He even brought back Sir Poops-A-Lot.
Santa's a nice guy, huh?
Santa came back.
It's Santa.
- Who is that?
- I thought you knew.
I hope you've all been
good little boys and girls.
Okay. Okay. Stay with me.
- Yes.
- Santa.
Get me a chair, you idiot.
- Here you go, Santa, sir.
- Yes. Thank you.
I'm looking for Owen Marks.
I'm Owen Marks.
- Well, merry Christmas, Owen Marks.
- Thanks, Santa.
Oh, you're welcome, Owen.
Merry Christmas.
You're not, like, gonna be scared
of him now, are you?
Not after the night I just had.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait for me! Wait
for me. I wanna help. I wanna help.
- Merry Christmas.
- All right. Merry Christmas.
Man, I'm glad you guys
already have a Santa Claus.
There was a dead mouse in my costume.
- Dad?
- Daddy! Daddy!
Merry Christmas, pumpkin!
You drove from Pennsylvania for us?
Of course I did, Spence. I'm your dad.
Through a blizzard? In your car?
Yeah. Actually, I...
I drove a Humvee.
A Hummer! You drove a Hummer
from Pennsylvania...
...in a blizzard just to see us.
Yeah, yeah. But, hey, let's just
talk about happy things, shall we?
I take back everything
I ever said about you.
Wait, what...?
What kind of things did you say about me?
Alan Davies!
I'm...
Actually, it's...
Sorry, I'm 36.
You're at an airport alone
on Christmas morning, aren't you?
Yes, Santa, I am.
Well, Alan, come on over
and get your present from Santa.
Awesome. I'd love a present.
- A basketball.
- Oh, I love basketball!
Check this out. I used to be an all-star.
Hey, can you throw that back?
I have a lot of presents to give away,
but before I do...
...I just wanna thank my friends
over there for setting all this up.
If they actually worked for Santa...
...they'd be fired so fast
their heads would spin.
But they did a wonderful job
here this morning.
And since they did,
I want them to know...
...that they'll be flying out of here
first thing this morning!
Merry Christmas!
- You're friends with Santa?
- Yeah.
I guess I am.
Hi.
Do you like dolls?
I don't know.
Not as much as I used to, I guess.
I am 12, you know.
Did you know that I found
that Christmas tree?
You did? How?
Let me tell you a little story
about a man called Beef.
Okay.
It all started on a cold, stormy night.
Me and Aquaman started trudging
through the snow.
Yeah. Yeah, Mom. We're fine.
You know, it turned out that it wasn't
such a bad night after all, you know?
In fact it was...
It was actually pretty great.
So...
Yeah, I'll call again
when I get to Dad's house.
Mom?
I...
I love you.
Her name is Lady Sleeps-A-Lot.
Oh, Val, what's wrong?
Oh, my gosh. Are the kids okay?
- Honey?
- It's Spencer.
Well, is he all right?
He said that he loved me.
Oh, criminy, Val.
You need to start dating more.
Do you know how ridiculous you look?
Really.
So it's all right if I call you sometime?
Why do you think I gave you
my phone number, goofball?
It was nice meeting you, Donna.
You're a very special young lady.
Man, you're so hot!
Yeah, I know.
Other side. The middle.
Down low. Too slow.
I should have noticed because "too slow"
rhymes with "down low. "
Why didn't I see that coming?
Well, hope you have a nice Christmas.
How could I not?
Got the whole place to myself.
More fruitcake and eggnog for me.
Yeah, you know, I was sort of thinking.
Maybe if you don't wanna go home
quite yet...
...you know, maybe you could...
...I don't know, spend Christmas with...
...my dad and my sister and me.
Took you long enough, noodle-head.
Come on.
Oh, hey.
You guys have any money for gas?
I kind of maxed out my cards
on the way here.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org