Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
That's him.
That's him inside the store.
- Are you sure?.
- Yeah.
[ Clicking ]
- You see which car is his?.
- [ Clicking ]
- [And.erson ] I can't tell.
- [ Camera Clicks ]
Oh, no. No, no.
Come- Come on.
[ Anderson ]
Shit.
Fuck! He's gone.
Which one?
- I don't know.
- Come on! Come on! Which one?.
I don't know! They're all
leaving at the same time!
[ Curtis ] Well, choose one.
The Denali or the pickup?
Right there.
The pickup.
Go, go, go!
- [ Groaning ]
- Come on!
- How do we know you're not
just gonna leave us here?.
- I guess you don't.
Cut the shit!
That's really funny.
- Oops.
- Asshole.
[ Shouts ]
Oh, I hopeyou're dead,
you clumsy fuck!
[ Groaning ]
Hey. Hey. Hey, man,
areyou all right?
[ McCain ]
Lucky to be alive.
Of all the
stupid things.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, can you hear us?.
- Are you all right?.
- Erin?.
I think it's safe to say
you were too heavy,, huh?
- [ Mutters ]
- F'uck off.
- My shoulder.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Shit. Whoa, whoa.J ust wait.
Ah, man,
your back is bad.
You do understand
that was our onlyweapon.
Back off!.
It was an accident, all right?.
- What's the matterwith you?.
- You trust this guy?. Huh?.
Oh. I see
what's going on here.
I-What, you two are gonna
start workin' together now?.
What the hell difference
does it make?.
Is that gonna get us
out ofhere any faster, huh?.
- I don't think so.
- [ Coles ] What areyou doing?.
Don't!
Don't untie him!
- You stay outta this.
- We had an agreement!
Yeah. I'm hedging
my bets.
Thanks.
You idiot.
It's you and me now.
[Coles ]
What's the matterwithyou? Fuck.
[Bound. Man ] You betterstayin the garbage,
'cause I ain't through with you.
- All right. This is gonna sting a bit.
- [ Grunts ]
- Son of a bitch!
- So who's Erin?.
Your wife?.
Or my daughter.
I can't rememberwhich.
At leastyou got somebody
outside ofthis place.
You'll remember her soon enough. Soon as
we get out ofhere, it'll all come back toyou.
How can you be so sure we're gonna like
what we have when we get out ofthis place?.
I mean, what could have brought us all here
that's worth remembering anyway?.
Nothin'. That's exactly it.
Nothin' we can remember here...
is gonna have anything to do with
who we really are.
The choices we make from here on
out ofthis shit hole-
that's what's gonna
define us.
- You really believe that?.
- Yeah, man. I do.
Shit.
I didn't want to say anything around those
two otherjokers, but... I know who we are.
- You remember something?.
- Yeah.
Aboutyou and me?.
Yeah. This smell.
This smell for the longest time...
out there
and then in here.
See?.
[ Inhales ]
- I remember. I have orange trees.
- You have orange trees.
- Yeah, on my ranch. It's been
in my family for generations.
- Shit.
- I'm Coles.
- You're Coles then.
I'm William Coles.
I really am.
- He was right.
- I think he was guessing.
I don't have kids.
At least I don't think I do.
Wait a minute.
Why areyou telling me this?.
- Don'tyou see?. You're McCain.
- Me, McCain?. No!
- Yes.
- You actually remember this?.
I-
Our original terms that we proposed
toyou are more than fair.
You want this bid,
you get back to me within an hour.
No. No, butyou
have to be McCain.
- You have to be McCain.
- What makes you so sure?.
F'orwhatever reason, you're the only one
I feel like I can trust...
and ifl can remember that,
they're not far behind, so we gotta get out now.
- What ifyou're wrong?.
- I'm not, okay?. You're McCain.
- It's the only thing that makes sense.
- F'uck. I'm not McCain.
- What?.
- I remember too.
What?.
How could you do that?.
Humiliate me like a dog!
Like a stinking fucking dog!
- You tried to humiliate me!
You see this?. You see?.
- Get the hell off!.
- Theywere turning blue!
- Get off me!
- What's the matterwith you?.
- How could you fucking do that?.
You would have done
the same thing.
You were the one
with the gun!
Hey.
There's someone outside.
- [Spanish Rad.io Announcer]
- [ Coles ] Where is he?
[ McCain ] Right over there.
See him?. Behind the gate.
Is it them?.
[ Coles ] No, I d.on't think so.
It's gotta be too soon.
- Hey!
- [McCain ] Hey!
[McCain ]
Hey! Hey,you! Hey! Over here!
Hey! Hey!
- [ Coles ] Over here!
- [ McCain ] Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Back off.
Let me try.
- Can you see anythi ng?.
- [ Rad.io Announcer Continues ]
[ Coles ]
Um, uh, move it around. Move it around.
- [ Coles ] Whoa, whoa. What's that?
- Holy shit. It's a kid.
- [Pound.ing]
- [McCain ] Kid.! Hey!
- [Men ] Hey!
- He doesn't understand.
[ Coles ] He d.oesn't know whatyou're saying.
He d.oesn't speak English.
[ Speaking Spanish ]
- What the hell?.
- [ Spanish ]
- [Announcer Continues ]
- Ramon. Vamos.
[ Men Shouting]
Hey! Hey!
[ McCain ]
Go getyourparents!
Wait, wait, wait, look!
He's going back! He's going back!
- [ McCain ] You sure?
- [ Coles ] Yeah. He's good.. He's going to them.
[ Coles ]
Yeah, he's getting in. Look at him!
- [ Pound.ing On Wind.ow]
- [ Coles ] They're coming! Whoo-hoo!
You did it!
[ Laughs ]
Whoo! Over here!
Look over here!
No. No!
No! Help!
Hey! No. Shit!
- No!
- F'uck it.
Shit.
[ Metal Squeaking ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Handcuffed Man ]
Hey, can I get some help up here?.
[Bound. Man, Ind.istinct]
Here.
Thanks.
You know
I'm not gonna be able to get those off.
Thanks anyway.
You think
I'm afraid of dying?.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I didn't tell you
to give up.
What's the E.T.A.
on our backup?.
At least
20 minutes away.
I'm over this.
Let's crash.
Police! Nobody move.
- [ Curtis ] Where is he?
- What's this?.
- I got nothing overhere. You?
- [ Curtis ] Clear!
- Got people back here?.
- [ Anderson ] No?.
- You see him?.
- No.
Where is he?
I said. where is he?
[ Speaking Spanish ]
- [ Men Laughing ]
- [ Curtis ] Who owns the pickup?
You think ifyou keep talking
they'll eventually understand?.
[ Speaking Spanish ]
- Theyellow pickup!
- Theyellow one is mine.
- [ Keys Jingle ]
- What about it?.
How stupid do those guys
thinkwe are?.
Might have been
born at night but not last night.
Hey, step on the gas.
Let's pick up Leon and Ray
and finish this up.
F'irst the locker,
now this.
- Hey.
- F'uckin' tracker.
[ Coles ]
We gotta get that gun.
- We already tried.
- Not together, we haven't.
Well, let's get the rope.
I'll d.o it.
You guys had your chance to fuck this up.
Let me. Maybe I can get it.
They're gonna be here
any minute, all right?.
So does it matterwhat we do?.
We can draw straws, whatever.
I'm sick ofwaiting for these bastards.
I swear, I want 'em to come back.
And what areyou gonna do?.
Whine until they surrender?.
- Why don'tyou two shut up?.
- [Bound. Man ] Fuckyou.
- You're the moron that left the gun up there.
- [ Handcuffed Man ] Hey.
I remember.
I was seven
and.you were nine.
We- We wanted. to go out
on the lake one d.ay with some friend.s.
You remember?.
You know me?.
My dad told us
not to go...
because of the storm.
We said. fuck him.
What d.id. he know?
We went out in the old. man's
MacGregor 26...
and. we got in some
argument about...
who was the only pitcher
to win M.V.P.
[ Whispering ]
Sandy Kaufax.
And. we argued.so much
about it...
that we didn't realize
we couldn't see land anymore.
I was reallyfuckin'
scared..
And. I could.see that
you were- were too...
even- even though you kept
talking like it would be okay.
And. then this big wave came
and.- and. turned. us over.
I- I remember goin' down...
and being disoriented.
Thinking ifl could.n't find. which way was up,
I was gonna d.ie for sure.
And then this hand-
This hand reached down...
and grabbed me...
and.pulled. me up.
You must have seen
how terrified. I was.
You looked me
in the eye...
and you told me
not to give up.
No one was gonna d.ie.
We all- all had. to
stick together...
and. keep each other
hold.ing onto the boat.
That's what we did...
for four hours.
We held on...
just like you said..
[ Laughs ]
Hey, that's really touching and all.
Completely useless though.
Enough with the boats, kid.
Who are you?.
Just listen
to what he's saying.
He's right.
We gotta work together.
No, listen to what
I'm saying.
Ifhe knows who he is,
then maybe he can tell us who we are.
It doesn't matter
who we are!
'Cause they're gonna
be back here any minute.
- All right, we got one shot at this!
- Hey, tell us whoyou are.
Who areyou, kid?.
Tell us. Tell us, kid. Kid!
Sorry.
I don't know who the hell
you are.
I don't care.
Maybeyou are a kidnapper.
I don't know.
Butyou know what
I think?.
Maybe somewhere along the line
you just forgot whoyou were...
before you become one.
But regardless,
we can't do this withoutyou.
[ Clicks ]
The plates aren't visible
in any ofthese shots.
[ Shouts ]
- Wait a minute.
- What?
Right here. In the reflection of
the gas station window.
- That's their front plates.
- You upload that to Molina. Get a cleaner shot.
[ Coles ]
Let me know. Let me know when it's coming.
- It's coming. It's coming.
- [ Laughs ]
Wait. Let's just tip it.
We tip it-Just pull down. Yeah.
- There it is.
- Oh! Whoo!
[ Chattering ]
- Where'd she go?.
- She said she needed some air.
- Coffee?.
- No, thankyou.
Yeah. I can't drink
any more either.
May I?.
Bill's father
was completely self-made.
But before he had anything,
he built this place up at Eagle Ridge.
Beautifulplace.
Right there in the foothills.
Burnt down
a few years ago.
Bill decided to...
rebuild it by hand
just like his father.
He's one of the wealthiest men in the state,
barely has time to breathe, but...
he had to do it, you know?.
Show himselfhe could.
Must be nice
for the two ofyou to have.
I mean,
a place to get awayto.
You should see
the sunsets there.
Only next time,
we let it go from up there.
- Be sure you keep this door
open when the shit goes down.
- I'm on it.
- You know how to use that thing, right?.
- Yeah.
Great vantage point
from up there.
You get out to that truck quick and get it
started so we can get the hell outta here.
[ Clicking ]
What's that?.
It's Erin.
She's my daughter.
Beautiful.
So thereyou go.
Nowyou got something
to fight for.
&& [ Whistling Classical ]
&& [Joining In ]
&&[Whistling Continues ]
&& [ Ends ]
Shit! Here they are!
[ Glass Shatters ]
Merry Christmas.
Dig a hole big enough
for three people.
[Snapping Fingers ]
Soon as they come in,
let it go.
- You got it?.
- Yeah, I got it.
Captain, we got a partial on the plate
that Anderson sent.
Put it on the wire.
They can't be more than 40 miles
from that gas station.
Hey, Ray. Call Ritter and make sure
he's putting the plane down on time.
- Ray?.
- I know. I know. Back to the scanner.
Hey!
- [ Clangs ]
- Get the lights.
- Woz!
- Brockman.
- [ Whispers ] Go!
- [Man ] Hey!
- Now!
- Come on. I got some burgers foryou guys.
Shit. Where the fuck
are you, assholes?
Quit jerking each other off
and let's go!
Watch out!
Leon! Leon, it's me!
[ Groans ]
- [ Groans ]
- What the fuck?.
You okay?.
Nobody move!
Everybody down!
Coles, you move,
you're dead.
- Hit me.
- Get him down! Woz, get him down!
Goddamn mess.
What the fuck happened here?.
You look like shit, Woz.
We got no prints on the 20
we got from the custodian...
and.nothingyet on theA.PB.
we have on the vehicle.
I been working with this plate from Molina.
I run it through the D.M. V., but it comes up d.ry.
I ran a state-wid.e search
on all open investigations, and. I got a hit.
It seems the narcotics task force d.own
in San Diego 's got an open investigation.
These kid.nappers- they're meth d.ealers.
They've got a rap sheet a mile long...
and. they're suspected. Iinks
to murd.ers on both sid.es ofthe bord.er.
This Stefan Burian
is the ri ngleader.
- Get everything San Diego has on these guys.
- I've already got a call in.
So that's it?.
That's all you've got to say?.
- It happened so fast.
- You know,you been workin'forme...
for a couple months now,
handling deals, collections...
all kinda tough shit.
Babysitting two suits
in there...
- is what's too much foryou to handle.
- No, I- I-
I fucked up.
You better pull your shit
together, man.
This is far from over.
[Tires Screeching]
What did you do that for?.
[ Bound Man ]
What-
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Where you gonna run to, Coles?.
Come here!
[ Coughing ]
Oh, shit.
Better take him
and the rest of ours out back.
Takes talent
to fuck it up so bad.Iy.
Go and clean the shit up.
Then we're heading out ofhere.
We kill them before
we're free and clear...
the mess gets
even bigger, right?.
You don't have to
kill them.
I'm not.
Good.
[ Cocks ]
You are.
- [Erin ] Here, Dad..
- It's from both of us.
- That's Erin.
- [Man ] Has she everhad.
a reaction to insulin before?
- [ Woz] I d.on't know.
- [Man ] Is her mother there?
Anybod.y that can say-
- I 'm divorced. I have no idea.
- She's not breathing. We gotta get her inside.
-[Defibrillator Thumps ]
- [Heart Monitor Flatlines ]
[ Woz Sobbing]
[ Crying ]
God, baby.
That fuckin'
lighter, Woz.
They've been gone
for five years.
You either
get over it...
or pick up smokin'
again.
Go and finish them off.
Take the fuckin'
rent-a-cop with you too.
Your cut will be here
when you're done.
- Hi.
- Have a seat.
There's been
a development.
Do any ofthose men
look familiar toyou?. Their names?.
You everrecall
seeing anyofthem...
- with Mr. Coles?
- No. Who are they?.
These are the men
who have your husband.
Excuse me, Captain. Lieutenant James
of Narcotics Task F'orce San Diego's on line one.
Now who the hell is this?.
[ Static ]
Did you get the keys
to that truck?.
We can't go for the truck.
- I don't have the keys.
- Doesn't matter. We still got a shot.
Ifwe get up over the ridge,
should be able to find the interstate.
You may be right.
How many rounds you got left in the gun?.
Just keep moving
this way.
[ McCain ] You guys can powwow all night.
I'm gonna get outta here.
- What the fuck areyou doing?.
- Whoa!
Aw, shit. What's the matterwith you?.
Put it down.
- Oh, fuck me.
- Theywant me to finish this.
Then I get outta here.
- What?.
- You see what's happening here?.
You fucking-You fuck.
Soyou are one ofthese pieces of shit, huh?.
- I tried to tell you!
- F'or once in your life, shut up, all right?.
- Ifl don't kill you, they're gonna kill me.
- Listen, you're not doing this.
- It's not that simple.
- What doyou mean, it's not that
simple?. Of course it's that-
Was it that simplewhen you ripped
that phonejack out?.
Guywas bleeding to death in the other room.
You're saying you were only doing it for him?.
What's the matterwith you, man?.
We didn't do this!
You're onlyworried
aboutyourself...
and the murder rap
over this dead guard...
so don't start talkin' about simple, 'cause this
whole thing couldn't be further from it.
We should be runnin' now!
Get out ofthis shit hole!
- You don't get it, doyou?. This is it.
- No, no, no.
- This is who I am.
- Bullshit. Put it down.
- You turn around right now.
- No, man. You want to kill me, do it to my face.
- Do it.
- No, you do it. Show me whoyou are, huh?.
Do it!
Is this howyou want Erin
to rememberyou?.
I'll giveyou anything
you want. Anythingyou want.
J ust fucking don't do it.
Don't fucking do it!
- Mywife and my daughter are gone.
Both fucking gone.
- Don't fucking do this.
- I just want this to end.
- No!
[ Gunshots ]
This is DetectiveJames Curtis.
[Woman ] Detective Curtis,
I've got Captain Parker on the line foryou.
Curtis, a local worker and his son
reported suspicious activity...
at a chemical warehouse off Blythe Road,
1 5 miles west of that gas station.
Are you sure
they check out, Captain?.
Listen. There's an undercover
officer on the scene.
[ On Scanner] We d.on't know ifhis cover's
been blown, ifhe's alive or ifhe's d.ead..
Affiirmative. We'll be there in five minutes.
Tactical's 20 minutes out.
- [ Captai n ] 1 0-4.
- You ready for this?.
Yeah.
- [ Ray] Hey.
- What?.
We got a problem.
Stay with the car.
Keep it running.
Hey, you.
Am I lookin'
at a cop?.
Cop?.
[ Voices Chattering]
[ Chattering, Laughing]
- You worked.so hard. to make d.etective.
- Here, Dad.. See?
Hey. So you like
this place?.
Yeah. Keeps the money clean.
Hey, you read.y?
I'd. tellyou not to d.o
something to make me look bad....
but then I know you'd just
do something to piss me off.
- Well, if I didn't need
the money so bad, I just might.
- Hey, money's good.
- [ Chuckling ]
- It's good to haveyou back, you know?.
It's like old times.
Where'd.yourfriend.s go?
You double-crossing
son of a bitch!
[ Shouts ]
[ McCain ]
Turn him around! Move!
Look.
There it is.
- Come on!
- [ Curtis ] You wait for backup.
- [Woz Coughing]
- [ Laughing ] Whereyou going?.
Ain't overyet.
Oh, what the f-
You saved my life.
[ Gas Trickling ]
You okay?.
Yeah.
- How's the arm?.
- It's all right.
This guy's been undercover
for the last eight months.
His fucking command.staffiin San Diego
hasn't talked. to him in three weeks.
I don't know
if I could do that.
It's gotta be instinct.
What, police work?.
No. Surviving.
[ Laughing ]
You guys should
consideryourselves very lucky.
A few more minutes
of exposure to those chemicals...
and you would have gone
into full arrest, neverwoken up.
My memory-
will it ever come back?.
The human body can endure
significant trauma, Detective.
F'or better or forworse,
it'll all come back sooner or later.
[Woz]
Okay.
[ Officer]
Captain.
[Blood. Pressure Meter
Pumping]
[Mrs. Coles ]
You d.on't have to d.o this ifyou d.on't want to.
I just don't know of any other way that we can
be together. What's stopping us, Detective?.
Celebration in ad.vance.
'Cause I have a plan.
A plan that could see us all retired
within the next two weeks.
- Hey, you tell him yet?.
- Tell me what?.
This is a mark worth millions.
No security on corporate insurance.
That'll cover getting him back fast,
no matter what the price.
[Mrs. Coles ] With the prenup we have,
there'sjust no other way.
I want them all dead
and the trail leading to McCain.
- If something goes wrong-
- It won't.
But if it does?.
Then we'll just do
what we have to do.
- [Med.ic] Hey. You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
Captain.
I thinkyou're
lookin' for this.
[ Coles ]
There's someone I wantyou to meet.
Can I trouble you
for a cigarette?.
I don't smoke.
Wouldn't be lying
to me, now, would you?.
And if I were?.
&& [Acoustic Guitar]
&& [Man Vocalizing]
&& [Man Singing]
&& [ Continues ]
&& [End.s ]
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org