Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
This is Tow-6 to base.
Hello? This is Tow-6 to base. Pick up.
Get your hand off the doughnut.
- Hello, Tow-6, this is base.
- Thank you.
- How long to get back?
-15 minutes.
See you soon.
That's a ten-four.
Hoffman told you? What the hell
are you doing listening to that idiot?
You probably just cost this company
the whole account!
Jesus, Mary...
Hang in there. Help is on the way.
Hang tight.
You're going to be okay.
Don't move.
Can you hear me?
Easy, easy! Watch his left arm.
It could be broken.
Careful.
Check this out.
It was velcroed under the dash.
Thanks.
He had a gun.
Let's go back, then.
I ought to slap her.
Big ass.
She was a bitch. A real bitch.
Tell me about it.
Fine, chump!
Okay, kids, wake up.
I'm going inside.
Kids, you ready?
Yeah, we're ready.
We're going to knock on the door.
Knock on the door, Biggs.
Police!
Police! Freeze!
Don't even think about it!
Get away from the gun!
What are you doing in here?
Hands behind your back.
Let her go, you moron!
You're going to have to kill me!
Hands in the air!
Against the wall! Do it!
Get over there!
Not my baby!
Come here. Get over here.
- Freeze!
- My baby's crying.
Stay where you are. Freeze!
Just let me check on my baby.
- Step away.
- Have a heart, man.
Get away!
Excellent work, young man.
What a fight!
Okay, Michael.
Regular or extra-crispy?
Damn, Michael!
I could've done that.
I'll need a tetanus shot.
Help me out of this chicken suit.
That's $ 120 more.
With the taxes Americans pay,
health care should be free.
You got my vote, honey.
But you're still $ 18 short.
Marie!
Mark.
Mark. What happened?
Don't worry.
It's not as bad as it looks.
See? Legs still work.
But your neck, your arm.
I got a plate there from an old injury,
so they put that on as a precaution.
I don't know what happened.
I'm driving the truck to base.
The next thing I know,
I was upside down in the cab.
Then you were very lucky.
You have no idea.
Officer Porter,
thanks for your help.
I'm sorry, you're under arrest.
- Is this a joke?
- This is no joke.
Come on. We'll straighten it out
down at the station.
Hey, Cosmo.
This one's on me.
About time, you cheap bastard.
- Only one.
- Then I'll make it a double.
As long as I live, if I never see Gerard
in yellow tights again...
...I'll die a happy man.
Hey fellows, look.
Look, you're on TV.
Look at us! We're on TV!
We're on TV. Make it louder!
When he grabbed you by the throat,
I thought I'd take a dump.
I did. I had to go change my underwear.
Look at my head! 27 stitches!
All because of this scumbag!
27 stitches, my ass!
The Conroys have made allegations
of excessive use of force...
...particularly against senior
Deputy Marshal Samuel Gerard.
I don't look like that.
That guy's ugly.
Nice suit. She'll have a martini,
and we'll take a check.
- Who died?
- Shut up.
Reporting from the federal courthouse,
Stacia Vela.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the U.S. Marshals!
put your hands together...
...for the U.S. Marshal Service.
Speech! Speech!
Noah Newman, Cosmo Renfro,
Savannah Cooper, Bobby Biggs!
You guys are, without doubt,
the sorriest excuse...
...for a warrant squad
I ever worked with.
But nobody got hurt.
It's probably important.
And you stayed close on the lead dog.
- Which means you get to keep working.
- Get paid too?
A round for this group here,
and a double milk for this kid.
Mr. Warren. We seem to have
a small discrepancy.
Let me help you.
That's not me.
You caught that. You're aware it's
illegal to carry a handgun in Chicago?
Come on.
You ever try towing a car on the
Dan Ryan at 3 a. m. without a handgun?
What about East 42nd,
1 st Avenue in New York City?
- What about it?
- Ever been there?
Never.
Then you wouldn't know about the double
homicide took place there last December?
Obviously not.
That's interesting.
Because the prints we took off you...
...flagged this.
Federal arrest warrant for Mark Roberts.
Prints from the crime scene
match yours.
This is bullshit.
Let me talk to a lawyer.
Don't touch me.
They got a lawyer...
...for your extradition hearing!
You're going back to New York.
I've never been to New York! I don't
know nothing about a double homicide.
Get him out of here.
You'll have plenty of time
to explain that in New York.
You got the wrong man.
Get him out of here.
Thanks.
- Warren. Mark Warren. What's going on?
- I don't know.
Why is it taking so long?
It's still being processed.
Hold it there.
It's okay.
What's happening?
Just a mistaken identity.
Where you going?
Just be cool, baby.
Everything's going to be fine.
I'll be right back.
Hello, Deputy.
I'm surprised you made it.
Catherine.
This is Stacia Vela.
This is U.S. Marshal Catherine Walsh.
She's the boss.
Delighted. I've seen you so much on TV.
You're very lovely in person.
Thank you.
You're welcome. I'm going to take Sam
away from you for just a minute.
Sure. I'll go and wait at the bar.
Never one to be afraid of the obvious.
I admire that in a man.
Did I do something?
You hit your prisoner while he was
in handcuffs. He could sue us.
He bit one of my kids,
got smacked on the head. So what?
- So what?“
- Yeah, so what?
27 stitches is „So what?
He needed a smack on the head,
he got it. What's the big deal?
D.C. wants to take full advantage
of this Conroy bust.
You are going to personally escort
these clowns to the federal pen.
You will give
a little speech to the press.
You are going...
...to do a nice little P.R.
song and dance and then...
...you are going to go fishing...
...or something.
You're going to take a vacation.
You're going to be happy.
The plane leaves at midnight.
You be on it.
Keep moving.
Right over there. Let's go.
Welcome to the unfriendly skies, Sam.
72.
Check.
84.
36.
Check.
Set your bag over here.
Look at the bright side.
We're on time.
Close up.
Lock it up.
All locked.
Clearance, F-PATS 343, Memphis.
Okay. It's on to Memphis and then
La Guardia, and we call it a night.
Turn out the light. It's late.
Be a couple of minutes.
Got to use the can.
You can hold it.
We got 20 minutes.
I've been holding it.
I have to go right now.
I'm serious.
I'm about to explode right here.
Can he go?
Yeah.
7- C.
All right, let's go.
Split on ice. „
7 letters.
Banana.
No, bananas.
Bananas. Plural.
Bananas.
What was that?
Cabin pressure! Oxygen mask on.
Sinking 2,000.
Engine failure on 2 and 3.
Indy Center, this is F-PATS flight 343.
We are declaring an emergency.
Mayday, Mayday!
Going through 240.
13,000.
I've got it.
11,000.
We're at 10,000.
What was that?
We lost engines 2 and 3.
A and B hydraulic failures as well.
Look at your charts. See if there's
any airport we can make.
Nothing close.
There's a road 20 miles ahead.
That's it then.
Indy Center, this is F-PATS 343.
And still losing altitude.
We have lost 2 engines...
...and we need to make
an immediate emergency landing.
Make the announcement.
Brace for an emergency landing.
Place your head between your knees
and brace for impact.
Keep your heads down. Brace for impact.
3,000.
2,000 above ground. Sinking 1,500.
I got the road.
Okay, gear down.
1,000.
500 above the ground.
100 above ground. Brace for impact.
Jesus Christ!
Holy shit!
Oh, God.
We're running out of road!
Get down.
This man is unconscious.
This man right here.
Get the weapons.
All right, dudes, you're swimming.
Clear!
Mine didn't open!
Give me those keys!
Slow down! One at a time!
Keep it moving!
I ain't going in that water!
Going somewhere?
Hold that light on these shackles.
I'll get this guy out of here.
Play any tricks, our guys'll shoot you.
- Stand up!
- I can't swim!
Get out!
We're going under!
Leave them!
Leave the rest of them!
Come on! We got to move out!
Get your head up there, jackoff.
A deep breath!
Calm down! You want to live?
They found the 2 that fell
from the plane.
That Chinese fellow dropped in some
poor old boy's roof and into the bath.
- Looks like a bowl of gumbo with ribs-
- I get the picture, Sheriff.
We still got one prisoner
unaccounted for.
Mark Roberts. He was seated in 10-D.
I guess the river got him.
No, the river didn't get this guy.
He's loose.
If you can't find him dead someplace,
he's running, folks.
We got a fugitive.
Seems we might have ourselves a bona
fide federal fugitive out on the lam.
Name of Roberts, Mark J.
Somebody give me a map.
- Who's got a map around here?
- I got one.
Thanks, Earl.
I want you setting up roadblocks,
general radius...
...of 10, 12 miles.
20.
He's got a real big head start.
Okay, 20 then.
That sounds good.
- In all directions, just like a big-
- Perimeter.
Circle deal.
Which should start somewhere near...
What do you think?
Said perimeter to extend downstream...
...from Brookport...
...to Mound City.
Every bridge across the Ohio River
from Golconda...
...to Metropolis to Cairo...
...needs to be closed down.
Extending south from Alexander...
...and Pulaski county lines,
have every house, hotel...
...hospital, back road and backwater...
...searched for Mr. Mark J. Roberts.
Get his picture on local television
and keep it there.
Please consider him dangerous,
and please...
...act accordingly.
Found a shoe. Looks like prison issue.
Okay. Continue to search.
We found the place he came ashore.
Jesus!
Looks like the skies
weren't too friendly last night.
- Sam used up 8 of his 9 lives on this.
- He's over there.
- Where?
- It looks like he's in one piece.
Sammy, how you doing?
Think they got
a fat-free menu in this joint?
- What are you talking about?
- Anyone else hungry?
- I don't believe you two.
- Smells good.
How can you talk about food
at a time like this?
I wonder if they have
that vinegar barbeque.
- On the French fries.
- On the meat, the fries...
- It's big in England.
- It's big everywhere.
- You all right?
- No, who's got my clothes?
I do.
Nice?
I knew it!
- Told you he wouldn't like it.
- I got the same thing last Christmas.
Anybody got $9 so I can buy a T-shirt?
You owe me $85 for this.
I got one.
State police found a shoe
over here near Hillerman.
What do you got?
Oh, boss, nothing, "nada".
It's like this guy doesn't even exist.
- Is this food free?
- Eat up. It's on the County.
He called himself Mark Warren.
I.D.s were forged.
Mark Roberts ain't nothing but
a photo and prints on a warrant.
- This is the guy?
- Cute.
Noah, you bring my gun?
Cute, huh?
Where will I find
Deputy Sam Gerard?
Here!
Bertram Lamb. I'm director
of the Diplomatic Security Service...
...State Department.
Special Agent Frank Barrows.
- What's up?
- Mark Roberts.
What do you know about him?
Double murder, robbery, escape.
These men were not ordinary civilians.
They were my agents,
murdered by Mark Roberts...
...in cold blood at the U.N.
last January.
- That's not on his warrant.
- All information...
...on this was sanitized
for reasons of national security.
- Why'd Mark Roberts kill your guys?
- We don't know.
All we have are his fingerprints at the
scene. We've chased him for 6 months.
So we're working for you now, huh?
That's not my intention.
Your reputation precedes you, Deputy.
We want you to continue
running the pursuit...
...but we want Roberts fast.
Okay, we're fast.
We'll need to be kept
in the loop on this.
We'll try to keep you up to speed.
So one of my men will
join your team to do just that.
Special Agent John Royce.
No offense, but we actually work a lot
faster if we don't have any help.
No offense taken.
You don't have a choice.
I've cleared this with Marshal Walsh.
Royce is one of our best men.
You'll find him useful.
Good luck, Deputy.
How you doing?
- If it's any consolation, I wouldn't-
- It's no consolation.
- Take off your sunglasses.
- Why?
So I can see your face.
How'd you pull this duty?
Your fugitive murdered 2 of my friends.
I volunteered.
Ever make a fugitive arrest before?
- No. Planning to shortly.
- You have a weapon?
A big one. You?
You sure you want
to get cute with me?
- Got a backup weapon?
- Never had the need.
Get one. Keep that in your suit
unless I tell you to take it out.
Get a Glock.
Lose that nickel-plated sissy pistol.
Let's move. I'm not having fun. You
know I get cranky when I don't have fun.
We know, we know.
Get the state police director
on the phone.
Cooper, get the background
on the Chinese guy in the plane.
Cosmo, get the local sheriff lined out
and ready to go. He's feeling weak.
Working on it.
You come with me.
I think he likes you.
Martha?
Just drive.
- How soon can I get on that airplane?
- Soon as we get it on the barge.
I got something on that shooter
in the plane.
Name's Vincent Ling. He was on his way
back to the pen. Just lost an appeal.
Serving a life sentence for murder
for a Chinese mob hit.
Sheriff in Metropolis just found this in
a dumpster behind a laundromat.
All right. Our boy
got a new set of clothes.
- Where's Metropolis?
- I don't know. Ask Superman.
Shut up, Biggs.
Get on the radio, move that perimeter
20 miles south of the river.
He might've made it into
Kentucky already.
Statistically, he's more likely headed
for a city.
St. Louis. North.
He's no statistic.
Not yet.
Holy shit! Sammy, you're a lucky man.
How many dead?
Eight.
You got your little black box?
Save that light.
What's that?
That is not a ballpoint pen.
Zip guns aren't standard issue on
federal corrections prisoner transports.
No, that's in those spy movies.
I saw one on TV one time.
- That James Bond movie.
- Shagadelic, baby.
Shaft.
Send it to a lab.
Stinger.
XL-17, Korean.. 22 caliber.
He found it with his little flashlight.
What the hell are you doing?
That was my phone.
It was my personal phone.
You're under arrest for obstructing
a federal investigation.
- It's not convictable.
- It's arrestable.
Are you crazy? Is this guy crazy?
No, but he's a carrier.
My superiors won't like this.
I am your superior.
Sit down and shut up.
When you keep information from us,
it pisses him off.
Deputy, get me out of these cuffs
right now.
Get out of them yourself.
What are you doing?
What's he doing?
What's next, cow tipping?
That's pretty good.
- Very slick.
- Very slick? He broke my glasses.
I've never seen that.
I have.
Don't have a heart attack, Earl.
You've lied to the cops before.
What's the trouble, officer?
Fugitive's on the loose
from the plane crash last night.
Is that a fact? Shit!
You seen this man?
No, I've never seen
anybody like that.
What about you, ma'am?
You seen this man?
No, me neither.
Thanks for your help, folks.
Drive! Drive! Drive!
Push!
Chester, you okay?!
You done good, Earl.
An 18-wheeler rammed a roadblock
15 minutes ago.
They found it outside of Paducah.
It was heading south.
All right, load up!
Like I said, south.
We're going to need boats.
This guy went into the swamp.
Shit, I hate swamps.
Lester, it's U.S. Marshal Renfro.
We're going to need boats.
Swamp boats. Right.
Like they use in the swamp.
Bad news. He got a. 38 off the trucker.
- How many rounds?
-6 in the gun, 12 more in a box.
Makes no difference.
He'll be dead from snakebite by dark.
He won't get far in that boat he stole.
It ain't got no motor.
Boats. I hate boats, bugs and boats.
Sam, he got a boat from here.
Could I have your attention?
We'll divide up and search this swamp.
One officer with each of you.
Who knows most about this terrain?
Who's the ugliest, most inbred,
country son of a bitch here?
You come with me.
How long will you be?
Everybody com-check with me now on 3.
- Sam.
- Com-check 3.
You get a visual, put up a flare...
...call for backup, stay in the boat!
How long will you be out?
I got PTA tonight.
We'll be out till we catch him.
PTA's on hold.
Be careful.
I got a visual.
Put up your flare.
He's moving.
I'm going in.
Stay in the boat. Wait for us.
Through there.
Pull up to that bank.
Get around to the other side.
Be careful. This man's mad
and he's got a gun.
It's him.
Go! Faster!
I'll take the gun.
Come on, move! Move, move!
What happens now?
We dance. Walk.
Drop the gun, pal.
It's been a long day.
Let's end it on a positive note.
For me or for you?
Everyone lives,
everyone wins.
How long will I live if you take me in?
You forget about the plane?
Look around, you're caught.
It's over.
Let's go home.
You go home.
Gerard's been hit.
He's over there.
- How is he?
- He'll be fine.
How is it to nearly get killed?
If he was trying to kill me, he'd have
shot me in the head, not the vest.
Ever occur to you maybe he just missed?
We're not dealing with a guy
who misses.
Maybe it's time to let someone else
catch this one.
- You don't think I'm incapable-
- You're capable, sure.
Okay, then let me do my job.
Don't make me wrong, Sam.
You screw up and I swear-
I know.
I love you, Sam.
But don't think I won't fire your ass.
Biggs, you and Cooper are staying here.
We're going back to Chicago.
We'll find out who put that gun
on the plane and who Mark Roberts is.
Take us to the airport. Who's got
my gun and credentials?
Look, I made a mistake, okay?
I usually work alone.
We're lucky I got shot, kid.
Lucky?
If he'd shot one of my deputies,
you wouldn't see your mama again...
...I'd be in jail for shooting you.
We're lucky.
I thought we don't
take our work personally.
We don't.
I do.
Just a sec.
Starbucks.
Some guy has a question
about his grinder.
Excuse me.
Can you talk?
Wait a minute.
Were you hurt? I saw the crash on TV.
- Baby, I'm fine.
- They keep saying you're a criminal.
You murdered 2 people.
No, no, it's a lie.
Marie, listen to me.
Where are you?
I can't tell you that now.
I know there's some things
I didn't tell you about myself.
Believe me. I didn't do
what they say I did.
You do believe me?
I want to believe you, Mark.
I'm just confused and scared.
Now, Marie, listen to me.
Before we met,
I worked for the government.
I was on a routine assignment
when it was ambushed.
I killed 2 men in self-defense.
Marie, I did not murder anyone.
Believe me.
I wouldn't lie to you.
What are you going to do?
I'll find the person who set me up
and clear my name.
It's something I thought
I could hide from, but I guess I can't.
Will I see you again?
Oh, come on now. Don't be crazy.
Of course you will.
I hate involving you in this, but,
baby, I got nobody else I can trust.
I can trust you?
Of course you can.
I love you.
I need your help.
Henry?
Got the casebooks on Roberts?
There was a woman at the hospital
when he was arrested. Paid his bill.
- In cash.
- Find her.
U.N. garage has cameras.
Get the date and time of the murders,
find the tapes.
We'll never get clearance for that.
Get the clearance, get the tapes.
Don't tell me what we can't do.
I'll get it done.
- What?
- Roberts' apartment was clean.
Been there 6 months,
neighbors barely remember him.
Where'd he work?
- I'm going there next.
- How about now?
What about the zip gun?
We covered workers at the Bureau of
Prisons who could've planted it...
...except for one guy, Kevin Peters.
- Out on sick leave.
- Find him. Check them all out again.
I want to go through their families,
their associates...
...changes in personal habits...
...bank records, medical,
the works.
- Stand on them till one squeaks.
- I'm on it.
To see you walk in...
...was like a mainline of ego boost.
I must've done something right...
...to see you come all the way here
in one piece.
It was all you, Sarge.
Little birds talking
about big dollars to bring you in.
Dead or alive?
Emphasis on dead.
On the plane, they tried.
Almost succeeded too.
You tempted?
If you're the traitor they say you are.
That's bullshit.
- I got set up from the word „go. „
- By who?
That's what I got to figure out.
It's somebody on the inside.
Got instructions by the usual channels.
Supposed to make a drop-off.
Then all hell breaks loose.
I thought I could disappear.
Boy, was I wrong.
Your next move?
Find the Chinese bagman from the
U.N. garage and hope he leads me...
...to whoever set me up.
Get righteous again.
How will you do that?
I got ideas. Got the stuff?
It's clean.
The key?
Take it all.
I don't want you back here again.
You don't believe me?
I've gone as far as I'm prepared to go.
I'll catch the rest on CNN.
Good luck to you, man.
You're a lucky guy.
The old lady just kicked...
...day before yesterday.
I'll move out what you don't want.
It's perfect.
- What do you got?
- We're in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania.
We got this guy says our fugitive...
...jumped him near Eddyville, Kentucky.
Tied him up and stuffed him
in his own camper.
How long?
Let me find out.
- How long was he in there?
-6 hours.
6 hours.
What do you want? We're exhausted.
We haven't slept for 2 days.
Stay on the trail.
Sleep next month.
Biggs and Cooper found a guy
tied up in his truck...
...who I.D.'d our man.
Harrisburg. Seems he is heading north.
Maybe now you'll start listening to me.
Explain why a ruthless assassin keeps
going out of his way to let people live.
We're right on it.
What's up?
Found his lady.
Where the hell is-?
Marie Bineaux?
- Yes?
- U.S. Marshals.
What's this about?
Just a few questions.
May we come in?
Just a second.
Thank you.
What do you want?
You recognize this man?
Never seen him before.
- Excuse me.
- Really?
No.
You sure about that?
Yes. Sorry.
This is a receipt from Chicago Memorial
for a Mark Warren.
Paid in full. Is that your signature?
We can verify your signature.
Are you here legally?
Familiar with
harboring and abetting laws?
That's five to ten years.
Then they kick you out.
Why are you threatening me?
Even if I knew this man...
...that's no crime.
I've done nothing wrong.
Mark Roberts has.
DSS Special Agent...
...Sam Harmon.
Your friend killed him
with his bare hands.
Sam was a friend of mine.
So was Neil Kasinski.
- Neil had 3 kids.
- Stop doing this to me!
I don't know anything.
I haven't heard from him and I won't.
I haven't seen him.
So you do know him.
- You lied to us.
- A federal offense.
Put those things away. That's enough.
I'm sorry if we upset you.
If you have the need,
you can call me...
...at this number.
Did you do that painting?
Beautiful.
You have talent.
I love the little airplane.
Who took this photograph?
- A friend of mine.
- He's good.
Who said it's a he?
Nobody. I just figured.
I mean, you look so...
...happy.
If that's all...
...I need to get to work.
Let's go, guys.
You're wrong about him.
How's that?
This is not a man who could've done
the things you said.
This is a killer who committed murder
and probably will again.
He'll do anything
and use anybody to escape.
I'm glad you won't see him anymore.
That was good work.
Yes, it was.
Newman, set up a surveillance
on Ms. Bineaux.
- Get a tap order for here and at work.
- He won't make that mistake.
He'll contact her.
I'll bet my Bears tickets.
Kevin Peters...
...the guy who was out sick,
must be the one who planted the gun.
2 days before the plane crash,
his sister gets 20K in her account.
Where is he?
At the gym. Must have been one of those
24-minute viruses.
Royce, go with Newman.
Get me those U.N. surveillance tapes.
I haven't worked out in months.
I got to get my fat ass back to a gym.
Yeah, you're getting old.
And weak.
Gym of the Living Dead, huh?
Hi, how you doing?
U.S. Marshals.
See this guy around?
I think he's the last one here.
Check the showers.
Thanks. I'll go check out over there.
Kevin Peters?
I got a dead guy here! Come on!
Damn! The dude we just lost is the guy
who set up the zip gun hit on the plane.
I don't get this. What's the connection
between the Chinese and our fugitive?
Get me the U.S. Marshal's office.
We got a homicide.
Where's the coffee?
Someone's calling
on her boss' cell phone.
Carla, get us a lock on that call.
Mark, it was horrible.
The police found me.
I knew they would.
But are you all right?
Just follow the plan.
This will all be over soon.
It will be all right.
We'll be together.
Video print on that.
You have the key to the locker?
Good. The documents are in a briefcase.
Can you bring them to me tomorrow?
Yes, of course.
That's my girl.
I love you.
I know.
I love you too.
I got to go.
What have we got?
Tapes from the U.N. hit.
5 cameras.
I've digitized and synchronized them.
Henry intercepted a long-distance call
from Roberts to his girlfriend.
We're getting the location
on the cell site.
Excellent.
Roll them.
Here we go.
Who's that?
Kasinski.
Kasinski?
My fellow agent. He was killed.
And a mystery guest.
I assume it's Mr. Roberts.
Stop.
On the big screen.
Move in close.
Bingo.
That's the Chinaman from the gym.
Mr. Slice-and-Dice.
Print it.
Mr. Slice-and-Dice and our mystery man
have a bag exchange here.
What do you think is in the bag?
I'll bet it's not his dirty laundry.
Your friends are intercepting this.
- What do you know?
- Nothing.
Carla, screen 6.
Who's that?
To the big screen.
Blow it up.
Back it up.
Go forward.
That's Agent Harmon.
Lamb said they were killed
in cold blood. Looks like self-defense.
What's going on?
It doesn't look like
the story Lamb told us.
Big screen.
The briefcase.
Cosmo, how did they say
they connected our man to this crime?
A fingerprint match.
Move in.
Fingerprint match.
Did they find his gloves in a garbage
can and turn them inside out?
Print it up.
We got to go to New York.
What the hell are these?
And what's in New York?
A rat.
Now listen, Sam,
I'll do the talking, okay?
Don't get up.
You make a better target
sitting down.
Is this visit to deliver our fugitive?
Not with the horseshit
you've been handing us.
Excuse me?
John Doe's fingerprints
you had planted at the scene.
Want the illustrated version?
Would you excuse us,
gentlemen, please?
Where'd you get the photos?
Off U.N. surveillance tapes.
That is highly-classified material.
- Know anything about this?
- I'll look into it.
Tell you what I'd look into
is how you got those fingerprints.
You had them on file
because the guy works for you.
Is that right or wrong?
We want information,
or I'll go to Washington.
The man you know as Mark Roberts...
...is in fact Mark Sheridan...
...ex-U.S. Marine special forces,
ex-CIA black ops, recruited by us...
...and until last year,
one of our kites in New York.
Someone who does our dirty work
without official connection.
If something goes wrong,
the string's cut, he's on his own.
Somewhere along the line,
Sheridan went bad.
We got this from the same tapes.
Who is he?
Xian Chen, People's Republic of China,
cultural attache“ to the U.N.
In fact, a member of Chinese intel.
For the past two years
we've known there was a mole...
...in the State Department,
selling secrets to China.
We suspected Chen
delivered the money.
Chen led us to Sheridan.
Agents Kasinski and Harmon
were supposed to...
...intercept an exchange between
Chen and Sheridan at the U.N. garage.
It went south.
Sheridan was better than we were.
Better than us all.
Why did you keep this from us?
Very simple. Need to know.
We believed you'd quickly apprehend him
and we'd sort the issue out internally.
Seems our confidence in
Deputy Gerard was misplaced.
He allowed Sheridan to escape...
...and managed to get shot
in the process.
I admit it was wrong
to withhold information from you...
...but the fact remains,
Sheridan killed those agents.
He's still at large.
He's armed, he's dangerous.
Until we have him, we won't know
the extent of the leak.
Now you have your precious information.
What do you intend to do?
Catch him.
Got you, son of a bitch.
I want surveillance
on the Chinese consulate.
I checked the New York office.
They're setting it up now.
Not bad for government work.
No. Black canvas bag.
I'm wearing the clothes off my back.
I have no clothing.
-3 hours late.
- We came into La Guardia.
Hi, Sam. Nice to see you too.
- Whose food?
- Go ahead.
See what you can do, please.
Cosmo, you look so sad.
Miss me?
No, I miss my new Armani jacket,
my shirts, ties...
...everything.
You know, I hate this place already.
Sam, we're at O'Hare.
Marie just retrieved a briefcase
from a long-term locker.
- Bought a ticket to-
- New York.
- What about the cell-phone trace?
- Just got it. It's in Manhattan.
Third Avenue and 42nd Street.
Get on the plane with her.
Our guys'll meet you.
Third Avenue and 42nd.
We're going to work.
Get your stuff. We're neighbors with
Mark Sheridan. Let's go, look alive!
Our fugitive is in a 4-block area...
...between 42nd and 46th Street,
1 st and 3rd Avenue.
Do a full-target search.
- What can I do for you?
- Seen this guy?
- No, sorry.
- He might have changed his appearance.
Wait a minute, let me see that.
I've seen a guy who looks like that.
Rented an apartment here a few days ago.
This guy?
Didn't I just say that?
Give me a line.
What's going on?
I got him.
Police! Nobody move!
- He's gone.
- Nobody home.
The dressing room's back there.
He likes toys.
- Good picture quality.
- Turn it off.
Isn't that the Chinese consulate?
Okay, baby.
We don't have much time.
They're outside. Did you bring it?
Where is she?
Saks. She's trying on a dress.
She's not trying on a dress.
He's with her. Get in there now!
Excuse me.
Just looking for a shoplifter.
We checked. No sign of Sheridan.
Girl's on her own.
Stay with her. Whatever you do,
do not lose her.
We're all looking for the same guy.
I got Chen.
He's leaving the consulate.
There!
Watch this apartment.
If we got Chen,
Sheridan won't be far behind him.
Let's hit the road.
Cooper, Biggs'll pick you up.
Newman, we found Chen.
He just left the Chinese consulate.
I see him. In pursuit.
He's getting in a cab.
Where are you guys?
Heading west on 51 st Street.
We'll lose him.
Where are you?
Tired of waiting on you!
That cab on the left.
He's stopping.
I got him.
Sheridan could be anywhere.
Stay alive.
Cosmo, Royce, take the left.
Newman, with me.
- Stay on Chen.
- Right behind him.
Guy in the green watch cap...
...with a briefcase, looking at Chen.
What the hell is a watch cap?
Is it Sheridan?
No, but grab him.
We got him.
Hold it, back off!
Watch cap just changed bags
with Chen. You follow Chen.
I'll follow that bag.
That bag's got to be the bait.
Taxi!
Out of the car!
We're headed north on 3rd
in a silver Cadillac.
We'll find you.
Got him up there on the left?
You with me?
I'm on the 59th Street Bridge.
We're with you.
Just coming onto the bridge now.
You still got Chen?
We're following him.
He's pulling into the Chinese consulate.
You mind not lighting that?
Yes.
What the hell's he doing
at the graveyard?
Biggs, park here and cover this gate.
Got that, Sam.
Looks like he's heading for that chapel.
- Well, he's not going in there to pray.
- No, sir.
A cab's leaving the cemetery.
Have NYPD pick it up.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I bet Sheridan does, though.
Sam. We're at the consulate.
No sign of Chen since he went inside.
What should we do?
Put the NYPD on him. I want you and
Royce here now at Queens Hill Cemetery.
Where's Queens Hill Cemetery?
Ask a cop.
- You know?
- I'll get us there. Put it out.
Throw it out. Thank you.
What do we do now?
We wait.
You know...
...our day could be worse, right?
Is that...?
Right there.
It's Barrows. What's he doing here?
You won't believe who just arrived
in a funeral procession.
Agent Barrows. He's in a silver Lumina
about 7 or 8 cars back.
Got him?
Think he's here for a funeral?
Cover the side of the chapel.
Got you, Sam.
Cosmo, where you at?
I'm in traffic in New York City,
where do you think? We're on our way!
Go inside, be sure
there's no way out the back.
The Lord is my rock...
...and my fortress...
...and my deliverer...
...my God, my strength...
...in whom I will trust.
My buckler and the horn
of my salvation...
...and my high tower. „
All right, people, pay attention.
We got Sheridan.
Front of the chapel.
Let him go inside.
Will you move?!
See the lights?
Son of a bitch,
why'd you do it?!
What are you talking about?
You don't know?
You're selling secrets to China.
An American response
to an invasion of Taiwan.
Strategic defense of South Korea.
Make sense now?
Why should it? I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Don't lie to me!
- Don't kill me, don't kill me!
- I'll do what you want.
- Don't worry, I won't kill you.
You'll make me righteous.
Why'd you set me up?
Why'd you set me up?!
Lamb was closing in.
We needed a fall guy.
With you caught red-handed...
...we were free and clear.
We? Who's we?
I can't-
Who?
If I tell you, he'll kill me.
He won't have a chance.
Pick it up.
Come on. Let's go. Pick it up.
On your feet.
Let's go!
Pick them up!
I got it!
Hold it!
Shooter on the roof!
I think it's Chen.
Drop it or I'll drop you!
Do it!
Put your hands on your head!
It's safe. We've got the shooter.
Head for the front gate!
Copy that.
Where are you?
We're coming into Queens now.
Sheridan's headed toward the front gate
in a black Lincoln. Try to stop him.
We'll be there!
What really happened there?
Hell with this.
Just forget it.
Here we go.
Come on. Come on!
We cut him off at the gate.
He broadsided us.
He's heading north along the east wall.
Give me your hand!
Come on! Come on!
- Let me go.
- I won't leave without you.
I can't make it.
We won't make it.
Please go.
Sheridan's over the wall.
Cover the street.
I'm on my way!
- Cuff this girl.
- Down!
I see him. I'm on him.
We're in back of the Lorali Building.
He's inside.
Get the cops.
Seal it off.
- Where'd he go?
- This way!
Wait for the cops!
Back up.
Wait! Wait!
Sam, is everything okay?
Do you copy?
You're all right. You won't be hurt.
Are you in here alone?
Yes.
They're here. Coming up.
Seal and evacuate the building.
U.S. Deputy Marshal.
You alone?
Yes.
Relax.
Get back.
Oh, Jesus, kid.
This is Gerard, room 814. I need an
ambulance. Newman has been shot.
What happened?
Sheridan got a shot off. Newman came in
and he just walked right into it.
Walked right into it.
Don't move. Don't talk.
Don't move, don't talk.
You copy?
I need an ambulance.
Get your EMS people up here now.
Hold this rag on this kid.
Turn it around!
Get down from there and face me!
You'll have to shoot me.
Turn around!
I can't. I can't be caught.
This is unit 115. We're en route
with a 32-year-old male.
Multiple gunshot wounds to the chest.
ETA: 5 minutes.
Hey, partner, can you hear me?
His name is Noah.
Noah, can you hear me?
He's in fib.
You got it?
- Does he have a chance?
- No, we lost him.
This is Linda Carlton outside
the U.S. Mission to the U.N.
Many details are still unclear,
but we can now confirm...
...that Special Agent Frank Barrows...
...was killed at Queens Hill Cemetery
during a stakeout...
...to capture fugitive Mark Sheridan,
suspect in 2 murders...
...at the U.N. 6 months ago.
Though unconfirmed, sources report
Barrows may be implicated...
...with Sheridan for selling top-secret
documents to the Chinese government.
Deputy U. S. Marshal Noah Newman
was also killed...
...as Sheridan eluded police
in a spectacular escape...
...leaping onto the roof of a
moving subway, then stealing a car.
He'll say „Diplomatic immunity. „
All we can do is deport him.
Antonio Kimber, one of our kites,
said he was instructed...
...to make the exchange.
Phone records check out.
He was paged from Barrows'
office this morning.
He didn't cheat, he didn't lie.
He didn't use me.
I let him go.
I'm so sorry.
We found an abandoned car...
...in a park in Jersey near the
Holland Tunnel. This was on the seat.
We got half a latent.
Sheridan's right index.
Good work, Henry.
Something I can help you find?
Tetralezine...
...for motion sickness.
- Where the hell are you?
- Put Kim on.
Line two. Hold on.
Any ships leaving...
- ... where we found the car?
- Only freighters and containers.
- Any with passenger berths?
- I'll check.
Sozel Shipping has a freighter.
The Utviken, loading grain in Bayonne.
It's leaving tonight.
3 passengers, no names.
Immigration didn't require it.
Heading up through Canada.
Get me a helicopter.
You got it.
Where's he going?
- I'll call Bayonne PD for backup.
- I don't need them.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
What's the matter with you?
You can't do this.
I know how you feel,
I loved that kid too.
But this is wrong.
I'm telling you as a friend.
I'm not your friend.
Fine. Forget it.
You want to kill Sheridan,
go ahead.
But remember this: You forget
everything you taught me about this job.
The rules, the regulations, the code.
You do this, and it's all about you.
It's not about Newman. It's about you.
The great Sam Gerard.
Yes, I am.
You always have to win.
Yes, I do.
Want to kill him?
Let's go!
Do you hear me?
Look right down there.
Off to the right.
- That's it?
- The freighter with all the lights.
We'll take her down.
Yeah, that's him.
Supposed to be a couple.
Only one showed up.
Where?
Cabin 4, C-Deck.
Freeze!
Know what?
You look like hell.
I'm tired.
I'm beat up.
- Get some rest, I'll wake you.
- I'll be all right.
That must be the gun that shot Newman.
I see you went with the Glock.
Just like yours.
Can I see it?
Kind of, sort of...
...want to emulate you,
you being my mentor and all.
These things are so cool.
They shoot underwater.
Pour sand in them, they'll shoot.
Shoot every time.
Good choice.
- Get some rest.
- I'll just get some coffee.
You want some?
Black. Four sugars.
This is a first.
You must be truly exhausted.
Stairway down.
Nursing station.
Remember? Second floor.
Officer?
I need you to log this in
with evidence tech ASAP.
What about him?
I'm DSS. I can keep an eye on him.
Thanks.
Remember me?
You are really...
...on my very last...
...nerve.
You've been a mind-boggling
pain in my ass.
Why couldn't you just die
at the cemetery?
Or on the plane?
Cut yourself out of the rest
if you want.
Sit up.
You know the job.
You had the same training.
We eliminate threats.
You are the threat.
Guess what?
I'm down to my last option here.
It was you.
You set me up.
You were the traitor.
Yeah. I'm the man, Mark.
You're the delivery boy.
I needed a fall guy to make the bag drop
in case things went south.
Like the two DDS agents
you gunned down at the U.N.
Their blood is on your hands.
If it's any consolation,
I chose you because you're the best.
That was my mistake.
But I'm going to fix it now.
You'll put that knife down
like a good boy and-
Good night.
What are you doing?
- He tried to escape.
- Better shoot him, then.
Want to use your old gun?
It's Sheridan's.
No, it's yours.
You filed off the serial number.
The gun he took from you...
...the gun he shot me with.
The one you've carried since.
I bet the bullets we pulled from my
vest match those that killed Newman.
Why did you shoot that boy?
Didn't have a choice, really, Sam.
He interrupted while I tried
to put 2 into Sheridan.
Kind of like you.
What'll your story be?
You caught me turning him loose?
I'll think of something.
I got yours, you got mine.
You'll just have to
cuff me and take me in.
Welcome home, Mark.
You want to start running again?
I'm going back to bed.
Marshal Walsh, is it true that Mark
Sheridan was exonerated by this hearing?
After considering the facts...
...the U.S. Attorney's Office
has decided...
...to drop all charges against
Mr. Sheridan. He is...
...free to go.
How does it feel?
Righteous. Very righteous.
Do you have anything to add?
For what it's worth,
I'm sorry I shot you.
That's okay.
Everything's back to normal.
God, I hope not.
Excuse me.
They could use a night on the town.
Take them out and have fun.
Go on. That's an order. Go on.
Can you handle that?
Yeah.
You owe me an apology.
Yeah, I know.
Cosmo, I know.
But...
But what?
I don't even like you.
Let's go drink a toast to
Deputy Noah Newman.
If we're going to drink to Newman,
we better use milk.
- You still owe me for the jogging suit.
- Of course.
Make out a requisition in quadruplicate.
You'll need a white copy,
yellow copy...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org