Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I think I saw something!
Steady lads!
Past the French border and
we'll be safe over there!
Falcon!
- Private, coming in hot!
- Then lift it 30!
Stay with me, private! Private!
Wing commander Gutsy,
this just came from a sea border.
- None of them made it back alive.
- None of them?
- But those were some of our top fliers.
- I'm sorry, sir. I'm just a messenger pigeon.
If we don't find some more birds fast,
our goose is going to be cooked.
VALIANT
BIRDS ON THE MARCH
Across the nation and the globe
pigeons are taking wing
in a fight for freedom.
Delivering top secret messages
from behind enemy lines,
these fine pigeons are
applied of the allied forces.
It's the Royal Homing Pigeon
Service that leads the way.
Whether cutting through enemy
lines or just coming wise.
These power pigeons are
the marvel of bird.
But don't come for dubs.
War bomb birds play a vital role
in raising seed for the troops.
Wait a minute.
Nursing girls at two o'clock.
Now that's what I call a task force.
Laundry bird bath. Why not?
These hotty heroes need to look their best.
Of course not just any pigeon
can make the cut out.
But there's always room for a few recruits.
And there they go. Off to
another exciting mission.
Homing pigeons, we salute you!
This is a shot boys, watch this.
Two in the corner, eight...
- Valiant, do you mind?
- Sorry. Felix!
Felix, I could do it!
I could do that, Felix!
- Do what, lad?
- I could be one of those brave recruits.
Taking wing in a fight for freedom,
I know I could! I know it!
Valiant! Did I ever tell you?
When I was your age,
I was all ready on the cost of France.
Aquatic brigade.
Gull division.
If it weren't for that wooden drum
taken that shram deck,
- I'd be there right now.
- Maybe you're right.
I'm just what they're looking for,
a pigeon with that something extra.
You know it's not a wing spand,
it's a size of a spirit!
Look at them!
Look at that move!
Royal Homing Pigeon Service! Magnificent!
Commander Gutsy!
The most decorated pigeon ever!
- Much obliged. Thank you, thank you.
- Who will have a drink with me now!
- What would it be, boys?
- Hot juice, shaken, not stirred.
He has always drinks on the house!
- Hot juice. Shaken. Not stirred.
- Merci beaucoup.
He's from France!
- So, what's the news from the front?
- Can't say of course. Classified.
But danger is our business. And I'm
sorry to say, business is all too good.
Let me through! Got to get
to wing commander now!
- Excuse me, wing commander!
- Yes?
- Sir, where do I sign up?
- Aren't you a bit underwaist?
Talking about small wings, man.
There's always a place
for a few valiant birds.
Sign up is tomorrow in London.
I'd love to stay and chat, but
duty calls and we must answer.
Dukes up, boys!
Let's make wing.
Hip hip hurray!
General!
You've come back, general Von Talon.
Congratulations, sir.
Under the Geneva convention as an officer
I have the right to be treated as a pigeon of war.
Have no fear, you will be.
Take him to the cage!
Get your talons off me!
Pigeons, ascetic little creatures.
You don't eat your prisoners at war, do you?
Eat you!
I'm a vegetarian.
Have you ever worn cape?
- Who is your contact in resistance?
- You know they'll send a crack team to rescue me?
Rescue you?
You're a pigeon!
- How important do you think you are?
- VIP. Very Important Pigeon!
Very Impudent Pigeon!
Who is your contact in Resistance?
Speak!
This canary will never say it.
- Listen to your mother, you can't go!
- Mom, there's a war going on and I want to do my bit!
- Why! Why! Why!
- Oh, mom! Good bye.
Please listen to what I tell you!
- Mom!
- You little baby!
Mother, it's not helping!
- Mother, honestly, I'm going to be fine!
- You were such a cute little egg!
Mom, I'm not an egg anymore!
It's time I left the nest.
No one thinks I can do this.
Maybe my only chance to show them
and myself that they're wrong!
Well, at least have some
breakfast before you go.
Mom, no thanks.
- Valiant!
- Right then.
I love you.
Good bye!
My little baby.
- Go there Valiant!
- I'm off now Felix! Wish me luck!
- Good luck!
- Good bye!
That boy is gonna do great.
LONDON 57
Valiant pigeon! Fearless flier!
Flier in the ally forces.
Fight the enemy.
Not fight the ladies.
Spits danger smack in the eye!
Look at that!
It's London!
Oh, this is easy.
I mean you go as I tell you.
All you're gonna do, keep
your eyes on the pebble.
Give a chance to boogie this day.
Find her and the
crumbs is yours!
Has it gone that way,
that way or has it not?
Find her and the crumbs is yours!
Which way is under?
- That one!
- That one?
Oh, no! Bad luck again!
Get one more go! I think
you're gonna win this time.
Serious thing, which
one has the pebble?
Wow! I know you're excited...
Why don't you set again...
- You've been cheating! Give me my crumbs back!
- Listen. I know what you're thinking...
Come and get me, falcons!
Strike me down if I tell you lie.
Look at him. That was lucky.
Prayed for answer, that's
never worked before but...
Hello, mate! Lost control, but then you
could not offict by the time you drop in.
- Bugsy is the name.
- I'm terribly sorry, I'm Valiant.
- So what brings you to my manner?
- I've come to be an aviator.
With the Royal Homing Pigeon Service.
Fighting for king and country!
I've never been much of the
howling glory bird myself.
I'm rather partial to a little
something called freedom.
Yeah, I fleet about as at least.
Now I tell you what to do, all way to do it.
- Are those flies?
- Oh, they're friends of mine.
So, RHPS recruit,
right this way mate.
I'm feeling rather patriotic
myself all of a sudden.
- There he is!
- Come on, after him.
Let's keep going, come on.
He's here somewhere.
I can smell him.
Follow in here.
- Hello. Two on the list please.
- Valiant pigeon.
- Reporting for duty, sir.
- Never heard of you.
Valiant pigeon.
The Valiant pigeon.
- You don't have Valiant on your list?
- No!
- Clerical error.
- Should I have?
Yes, I think you should have.
Look at him, he's a perfect specimen.
He's as fast as lightning,
strong as knocks.
Fits all for high standard.
The bird's a legend
in his Hempshire area.
Too small! He should be yea high
and he's not even hey high.
- Charming, that's charming.
- But you!
- Have you by any chance heard of a war fare?
- I've got me a rare feather condition.
Makes me itch.
Clear of the territory. Get lost!
- But, wing commander Gutsy...
- Yes. Wing commander Gatsy. That's right.
Valiant is the best mate.
They went to school together.
You don't wanna get on
the wrong side with him,
if he hears about this you're
gonna lose those stripes, mate.
- You know wing commander Gutsy, you say?
- Well... Oh, yeah.
- Well, that makes a difference. Sign here.
- Thank you. Thank you, sir.
There he is!
You clowns!
When I get hold of you,
I'm gonna knock your beak!
- Hey! That's it! Enough.
- Get your wings of me!
- Where do I sign up?
- Just sign here.
- All right, in you go.
- Thank you, sir.
Who is this Gutsy anyway?
If I see your ugly face around
here, I'm gonna have you!
- We made it!
- Sight on town.
We're in the Royal Homing Pigeon Service!
The elite of the elite! Fighting
the heroic battle to save...
Save? I'll tell you for this.
Each word like a charm.
So with that I'll be here to sky way.
Cheers mate, good luck. God bless.
If you get back in one piece, be sure to...
Hello? Hello?
Gents, hello! Hello!
- No! There's been a terrible mistake!
- Trust me, this is all gonna work out brilliantly.
Hey! Come on! Come back!
It's so bright.
- Sorry about that.
- You'll be good, you little fellow.
Hey, little fellow! It's not the
size of your wing spand, no!
- It's the size of your spirit!
- If you say so, mate.
- Can't argue with that.
- I'm Tailfeather, this is Toughwood, my brother.
Not the sharp to speak on, block.
- What?
- But...
If you're ever in the scrum, there's
no better bird to be your team.
Absolutely.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Valiant.
- Valiant? It's good to meet you.
Let's go! It's two foot to Tailfeather.
Quite elite unit, on quote they
seem to let in anything with wings.
Including those flies.
Certainly your bottom.
- Wait! Who do you think you are?
- I'm Lofty, tedious word to pigeon.
I come from a long and
honourable line of warrior pigeons.
Lads!
I trust you had a blaze of journey.
Well, I think I'll speak for all of us when I say
the right must have been bumping on the way.
Maybe check the suspension on that motivate.
We are thirsty, if we could have some
cold drinks, that would be nice.
Oh, that certainly can be arranged.
Line up! Spread feathers and
tell me you're flamingo!
So that's it in all.
For the next six weeks
your tails belong to me.
You'll learn to march like bird,
fly like bird and fight like bird.
I will make birds of you,
turkeys even if it kills you!
- Except you. You won't last a week.
- Permission to die trying, sir!
It's like this, ladies. You will shape up
and you will shape up fast
or I will personally draw
you out of the claw!
Funny, you should. I would love to get drown
down, I was gonna bring out a few hutton.
- Hey, leave him alone! He help me to...
- Hut down, beaks queek.
I'm more interested in letting
you all drop and give me 50
courtesy of your short little friend here.
Training at last.
I say wouldn't it be more sporting if the
chap who actually committed the...
Gentlemen, welcome to the
Royal Homing Pigeon Service.
For the last time what was your mission?
And where are these
messages coming from?
Very well. Have it your way.
- Allow us to black out his feathers!
- And his knees.
And his feelings.
No, worse. Much worse.
We have ways of making you squawk.
What kind of birds are you?
This is hugely!
One two, one two and hop!
Now forward report
to the nursing docs.
- Hello nurse.
- Look at that!
- I've been waiting for you.
- Do you have a little something
for a brave pigeon about to
go into battle? Hey, darling?
It just so happens I do
have something for you.
- Did you hear that?
- Is this what you had in mind?
Wow. It's awfully big. You're
kind of short for a nurse.
Look who's talking, I'd say you're kind
of short for a carrier pigeon.
- I'm Valiant by the way.
- All right then Valiant. I'm Victoria.
I know you lads have had a tiring day,
and what you need is a nice relaxing shower.
Then you are to a fancy dinner.
We'll get your little feather cut.
Set you up with some uniforms.
- Oh, sorry fellows.
- You got me!
That's it!
Come here!
We're all turning for a good night sleep.
So this is where the smelly rotten
bits of disgusting refue set up.
And our sleeping quarters would be well.
Never sleep in the attic.
- Well, this isn't so bad.
- Oh, just like home.
I've had enough!
Speak!
Lieutenant Mercury, Royal
Homing Pigeon Service, 4121444697.
Bring me the truth serum.
Come on, come on.
- One shot of this and we will know everything.
- I'll never talk! Never! Never!
Wakey wakey!
You bad reigns are squad F.
You know what that means?
Squad Fantastic!
Philosophical!
No, it means you are
the fliers of the future.
The far future!
But mind you're somehow
estimate you the carrier pigeons of today.
Good maneuver. It might work
if you kept your eyes open.
- Back to your nursy down there.
- Thanks, Bugsy.
You must really like it here, because this
is the third time you get to see me.
- I wish you be more careful.
- Oh, don't you worry.
Where I come from, danger is our business.
Oh yeah, we spit danger in the eye.
If the condition, I can take it.
- And where do you come from?
- West Nestington.
That's near Nestington, it's
some close to the west actually.
Oh, Valiant!
Well I have to return to my duties, so...
- Good bye.
- Oh, Valiant wait!
As homing pigeons it's our
duty to transport messages.
In a worst of conditions
wind, hail, slip, snow,
bombs exploding, bullets flying
and as if that weren't enough,
mother nature has the audacity
to create a little something called
The Falcon.
Twenty pounds of pigeon eating muscle,
measuring five of your wing spands.
They like to fly seek their pray,
speed excessive 200 miles per hour.
But not to buy it. Not yet.
The first strike is merely for impact.
They'll let you drop of it.
They make sure you're defenseless, and
scoop you up in their razor sharp talons.
And in the dark of the night you'll have not a
split second to recognize friend from foe.
Friend or foe?
- Foe!
- No!
You idiots, it's a pigeon!
Friend or foe?
- Foe! No!
- Friend!
- No, it's a foe.
- Yes, yes!
Friend or foe?
- Friend!
99. 100. 101. 102.
To survive his mission a pigeon must have
the strength to carry his message capsule.
You must have the speed
to fly like the wind.
You must have the ability
to vault maneuver the enemy.
And you must have the
endurance to battle relevance
flying long distances over raging suds.
- Me again.
- Valiant.
Oh, my favourite!
How did you know?
The parrot is to be right about we doing!
This is why I think I'm afraid of height!
You are afraid of height!
- That's it!
- Come on!
- Good afternoon.
- Hello Guts. What news?
Not good I'm afraid. We just
lost squadron E over Belgium.
That means these new
recruits are at any chance.
- They have to leave tomorrow.
- You can't be serious.
They haven't even finished the training.
Sorry, but those are the orders. Have
them ready at 8.00 tomorrow. Cheers.
Commandor Gutsy is here, so I
suppose you'll be out soon.
I know! I know! I can't wait! This is
the moment I've been waiting for!
Well, I'd like to be part of
what you come home to.
I don't care if you're a hero. Just
concentrate on your getting back.
You need to understand something, lads.
Our losses have been heavy. We got to stop it.
You're all we've got! And so
today we fight for our country.
Tommorow our feathers may be
flopped from our rifless bodies.
And our bones bend to rubbed
weasels. But never mind that.
On this day in this place
let it forever be known
that you, pigeons did your
part in the heroic battle for...
- Seeds!
- Freedom!
Right! You will be commander
Gutsy support wing.
I expect you to do whatever it takes
to ensure the success of this mission.
Chaps, the message we have been sent
to carry is of the utmost importance.
The upcome of the war could well depend on it.
We pigeons have never been entrusted
with more critical or dangerous mission.
May you fly straight! And may
your instinct guide you home.
- What did Gutsy mean by highly dangerous?
- I don't know. But I can tell you this.
I am a bird of principle. And
my number one principle is
don't get involved with anything
called highly dangerous!
And I will never violate my beliefs. Do
not ask me to violate my beliefs.
You're talking to the wrong pigeon.
Sir, point of clarification please.
Recalling the highly dangerous mission.
I truly regret that I have but one
life to give for my country.
- I'd love to die. But I can't. Not on Sunday.
- Are you finished?
Not quite, listen, maybe I'm not
that conscientious, but I do object.
Get back to the barracks! Now!
Do I still have to go on
a dangerous mission?
- Now!
- Yep.
- Take that as yes, I do.
- Now!
- Hey, where are you going?
- Keep it down, mate.
- Got some serious flying ahead.
- Flying, what do you mean flying?
- Flying to where?
- Back to old Trafalgar square, son.
- You're not leaving, you'll break up the team.
- Team? I'm not a team player.
These question aren't why I'm
leaving, but why you're staying?
Why am I staying? Because
it's my duty, it's our duty!
Hold on! Sorry!
Did I miss something?
Did we start this? No.
Did we make those?
All those? I've seen them before, mate.
And this is not a great sight.
The truth is, I'm scared.
Don't tell them that.
Cause I'll deny it.
- Well, I'm scared too.
- Then come with me.
- Just have the square we asked. Come on!
- We didn't make Trafalgar square either.
Where do we go if they start
dropping bombs there?
- No, I'm staying. I'm doing my bit.
- Yeah, luck to you, mate.
Anyway, keep your wings in front of you.
- What's up then?
- What's going on?
It's time for me to fly home, all right?
So I guess this is farewell.
- Wait, where are you going?
- You can't just leave, Bugsy.
Look, I've got urgent
business to take care of.
I better catch the wind
while it's blowing.
Look me up when you get back, kid!
You know where I'll be!
Gentlemen, take your places!
Our mission is to be dropped behind
enemy lines in occupied France.
To make contact with
the French resistance.
To get a top secret message and bring it
back here by sun dawn tomorrow.
Good luck. The fate of the freedom
loving world depends on us.
- Wait!
- Hey, Bugsy!
You can't go without me!
I can't let you go with glory!
Good luck, lads.
- Hey, Bugsy! Thanks for coming back!
- I'll tell you the truth,
it's the first work worth I've ever done.
We're gonna be fine. Right, Lofty?
Indubitably! Birds of a feather are all that.
- Going off to you mate, we stick together.
- Hey Tailfeather, can you believe that
we're the ones they pick to save the
most important mission in World War II?
- Yeah!
- Me too!
Truthfully, I'm not a good singer anyway.
- Enough already! You've been chattering for days!
- Hey, who gave me the serum?
You want me to talk, okay I'm talking.
I'm glad you did this. Homing
Pigeon recruit is only good,
but it's a stiff effort beat
rubbish all the time.
I got feelings and I wanna express them.
I always used to think my favourite
color was blue, cause it's for boys...
Shut up!
I didn't deserve that treatment I mean
most of you treat me like this!
Even that charming Resistance chat
with that fabulos view over harbour
the last time I was in the attic in San Pierre...
San Pierre.
The truth serum is genious.
Cover his cage!
- I'm curious what is your favourite color?
- Pink!
Not a hot pink, just a kind of pink pink.
You know what I mean, just pink.
- Excuse me.
- I like pink too.
Come on! Cheer up, Valiant!
It's difficult for me.
- Gentlemen, get ready to drop!
- Are you ready to drop?
I think I'm not that ready!
It's okay to be scared, fellows!
I'd be worried if you weren't.
It won't get past,
but you'll get used to it!
Go! Go! Go!
It's stuck!
- Sir, let me help you!
- No! Go now! That's an order!
Yes, sir.
Come on Gutsy,
get out of there!
Oh, come on.
- Hello? Hello? Will you help chaps?
- Hold on there, we'll get you out.
Yeah, little bit of a tenuous landing.
Are you saying it got to be worse?
Look out!
- Sorry Lofty.
- Not to worry, old chap.
What's that? Bit of a muddle.
- But at least we're all in one peace.
- Not quite all.
- Where's Gutsy?
- He was still in the plane.
- What do you mean he was still in the plane?
- His cage got stuck. I don't think he got out.
That's it! We're dead!
We're finished! Nice knowing you.
You're quite mistaking, boy.
I'm sure he made it out.
Gutsy always makes it out, he's going to
come and find us any minute now.
And give us the plans for the mission.
- Then who has back up plan?
- You want the back up plan?
- We die. That's the back up plan.
- But I'm not ready to die!
- Am I ready? No one's asked me!
- So many books to read! Regret!
We're dead. Thank you very much.
Everyone be quiet. Quiet!
We need a plan.
And the plan is, is to find a safe
location to plan the next move.
- You heard the bird.
- So our plan is to make a plan?
Come on.
France is spooky.
Quiet! Did you hear that?
There's someone in there!
Somebody better go and have a look.
All right, I'll go.
All righty turkies, let's go.
Valiant, just pull yourself together.
There's nothing in here.
Unless you're counting guns, bombs,
all the falcons, pigeon eating falcons.
Pigeon eating falcons!
Tailfeather, you grabbed the grail.
Hello, my pigeon friends.
You are the RHPS, no?
- French resistance, Mers division.
- I'm glad to see you. I'll tell you.
- How did you find us?
- Well, there was the plane and the explosion.
And this gleaming and pleeding.
More scleemings and beggins and cryings,
whinings, winging, yelling, poohing.
- Enough about that.
- Absolutely.
Definitely, yep.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Charles De Girl.
- De Girl? Why did they call you De Girl?
- Because I am a girl. The one and only girl.
- I like France.
- Do you speak French?
- Well, may we...
- Does o la la mean anything to you?
Or wa wa woom! Bon jour?
All right! We don't have time for this!
You have a message, we have a mission.
- Let's get on with it!
- Not so fast, monsieur!
This is Rollo. He's an expert in sa...
Sabotage!
Pardon.
Now monsieur, before you
continue on your mission,
it's our national cost on to...
- Break the bridge?
- Cut the cheese.
- Thank you for your hospitality,
but we just don't have time to eat.
And anyway we're birds.
- We don't eat cheese.
- We don't?
- Look, about that message.
- We will take you to it. But the road is dangerous.
And guarded by the enemy falcon.
But this cannot be a problem for
such highly trained pigeons.
- That is why you are squad A?
- The things is you see...
- Squad B.
- Not squad B.
Squad C?
You are squad D?
Just between us, squad D was never
really what it was cracked up to be.
I will not lie to you, you will
definitely be among the falcons.
- Wow, that was a fine fromage.
- Can you burp on Q?
I can burp on all the letters. Not just Q.
Watch this. A. B. C.
Be silent! The falcons!
- I say!
- Excuse me.
Come on.
Falcons!
All clear!
Stop that!
Oh, squad F.
- We are here.
- This is invigorating.
The attic! There it is!
Fly, English pigeons! Fly!
- Oh, dear. Sorry.
- Dirty bird!
Lofty pigeon at your service.
Hold on, mademoiselle!
He's heavy, this one!
Faster!
Sabotage!
To the right!
I'm gonna get you!
Hold on, De Girl!
This is it!
I must do the secret knock.
- Who is it?
- De Girl.
- You must do the secret password.
- Jacques, there is no time!
- Have you any?
- Wine?
No, no, that is yesterday's password.
- Trees?
- No.
- Seeds?
- No, no.
Falcons!
Jacques, move it!
- Let me give you le message.
- You can give me le massage.
Pretty sure it's a full body massage.
Message! The message that is to go to
London. Our freedom depends on it.
And who carries them?
- Wait. I'll take it.
- Bugsy?
- And you said you weren't the team player.
- I see it my own way.
- Good luck, Bugsy.
- Fly straight.
And let our instincts guide us home.
Good bye. And good luck, pigeons!
Okay, farewell.
Absolutely charmed.
Just one tiny thing. How are we gonna
get out of there! We're trapped!
I've got an idea!
Where are they?
Let's go!
- Hey, it worked like a charm!
- They'll be teaching that one in the Academy!
- I just thought the others are okay.
- Count on it!
Let's go.
I say let go!
You can't do better than
that, you English pigeon!
Bugsy!
It was not easy, herr
general. But I have...
catched their leader!
- The leader?
No, perhaps, assisstant leader.
- But along, herr general.
- Get on with it!
May I present you,
the message! Ta-ta.
The high commander will be pleased!
There will be medals, photographs,
commemorative spanks!
I will personally deliver it to him.
They must be desperate indeed to give the
message to this putrid smelling reject.
Oh no, Dennis! You're squished!
He was my favourite.
I am putrid stinky rub. Eat me,
you'll be sick for a week.
- Take him away!
- No!
I've got feather condition!
Wait. On second thoughts
he may prove useful.
Yes! Oh, yes!
Oh, thank you.
You're very wise.
What would you like?
Cards? We can play cards.
Find the pebble?
I've got a lovely voice.
That would be noisy...
I was thinking more along
delights of a celebration dinner.
Celebration dinner!
Brilliant idea!
I cook well, I cook well!
I can make great crumbs in oven.
Oh, you haven't tried my
bread crumb bird seed thing.
No, pigeon on the glass.
It was a lovely liebfrau reduction.
What did you do to him?
- You're all right, mate?
- Wait a minute now!
That little bell should be over there!
Who was I kidding?
I don't belong here.
I've let everyone down. Folks even
wouldn't be here if it weren't for me.
Folks! There's Valiant! Follow me!
Hey! Lofty! Toughwood!
- Chaps!
- Gutsy! You're alive!
What happened?
Tell us what happened!
Plane exploded. Shoot gave out.
Free fall at 300 feet. Set on fire.
Flew through barbed wire, picked up
some shrap from a straight granade.
Thought I was on the wrong
move. And here we are.
Right! We can dispense
with the chit chat.
I guess the falcons require the message.
- Yes, sir.
- Where's Bugsy?
He sacrificed himself to save me.
The falcons got Bugsy and the message.
- Which way did they go?
- That way.
Oh, no!
Britania rolls way!
Come on, pull yourself
together. Snap out of it!
Come Bugsy, let's find us
the way out of here.
When there's a will, there's a way.
Right. You chaps sit tight.
I'll fly in avoiding the barriers,
clever traps and deadly ambushes.
Then some resistance.
And secure the message.
Absolutely. Gutsy by
name. Gutsy by nature.
I will bathe.
- Bring me my best cape.
- Yes, herr general.
- Join the army you said.
- You did, it was your idea.
I'm not listening!
I'm afraid it's not that
simple as I thought.
This is a highly fortified bunker stuffed
with the guills, with enemy falcons.
There's one opening, scarcely
big enough for a homing bird.
It's down the barrow of that gun.
Gentlemen, I'm afraid it's hopeless.
I'll do it!
Bugsy.
I'm too young to die!
I can't believe it!
- Hey!
- Hey?
- Valiant?
- Bugsy.
Hey! The message!
It's in there.
Oh, no! Red is strong and decisive!
- Red it is!
- Yes, general!
- No wait, the blue has the actual chimb.
- We'll do as you like, general.
They're coming!
Valiant, get down!
- So many capes to someone!
- I'm sick of capes! I hate capes!
Here goes.
- Okay, you're out of here, Bugsy.
- It's of no use, he took the key with him.
- Complete the mission!
- Bugsy! I can't!
Forget about me! You've got the
message, now get out of here!
- No, Bugsy!
- Go.
Don't! Don't do it!
Underlingk?
- Underlingk!
- Yeah, herr general!
- My beak wash!
- Yeah, herr general.
- Cuffingk?
- Yeah, herr general!
- My talon clippers.
Valiant! They're coming!
- Get him!
- Stop him!
What's going on!
- Bugsy!
- Valiant!
Come on, last chance. Get up!
What is that!
Not to watch around,
gotta go! Come on!
Well done, my lad!
- You're from squadron E, right?
- It's a long story, I'll tell you later!
You idiots!
Valiant! Bugsy!
- We did it!
- You made it!
- And the message?
- Yes, sir! Safe and sound.
- Good man!
- Thank you, sir.
Right lads, we have a message
to deliver. Let's make wing!
Those falcons are gonna think
twice before they try to mess with us!
Enemy fliers!
Toughwood! Tailfeather!
- Take them away! Dispose!
- Yes, sir!
Come on lads, attack formation!
Valiant, complete the mission.
You are way to go.
Give me tail, pal.
Let's go chaps!
You're tired, little bird? Won't
you like to rest in my belly?
So you are the elite?
The best of the best?
I hope I'm gonna make it.
I think I'm gonna make it.
I'm going to make it!
You can't escape me, pigeon!
Valiant back so soon!
What a nice excitable boy!
Falcon! Set the alarm!
Set the alarm!
It's just you and me, pigeon!
This is where it ends.
You are nothing but
a lonely woof pigeon.
You are no match for a falcon.
It's just as I imagined!
Pieces and shreds!
Valiant!
You ugly stupid falcon!
Come out, little birdy. I may
even spare your puny little life!
Just stay calm.
You can do this!
You squeak!
My name is not squeak!
My name is Valiant!
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a message to deliver.
That's my boy!
Valiant? You've made it?
Valiant pigeon.
Sir, I have a message to deliver.
WAR ROOM
Gentlemen, a change of a plan.
We now land in Normandy.
FOR VALOUR
Well done, son.
This could mean promotion.
- I'm proud of you. You are credit to the Service.
- Thank you. Thank you, sir. It's been a...
Sorry! Sorry!
- Valiant!
- Well done!
You medal beauty.
Well done, mate.
Seed!
WINGED WAR HEROES
Hold there, Valiant!
I saw her earlier!
I was doing all right to you, kip.
- Hello, handsome!
- I say!
Shall we shake, Tailfeather?
- Oh Valiant, would you like to dance?
- Sorry, I'm not available.
Well you don't know how available I am.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org