Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
"Take It To The Limit"?
Artist and year?
1975. The Eagles, of course.
Very funny.
That's not a song. It's ridiculous.
You made it up.
That is definitely a song.
It's a good song, and a winning song.
You give up?
On belay.
"MacArthur Park." Richard Harris.
1968.
1968? I didn't even think they had
recorded music back then.
Excuse me. I have a signed album
by Mr. Harris.
It was cutting-edge stuff back then.
Peter, check your sister's belay.
Want to tell him we're not 15?
Why bother? We'll always be 15.
Dad, she needs a second cam.
That won't hold in a fall.
Screw you.
Listen, Annie.
No matter how experienced...
...a smart climber always wears a belt
and suspenders.
Two cams are safe, three's better.
I'm not kidding. We're not moving
until you put another cam in the wall.
I have three cams.
He's yanking your chain.
Watch out!
Amateurs at twelve o'clock!
Check your safety!
Too much weight!
It's not gonna hold!
Hold it together, you two!
Now get a grip.
We're getting out of this.
Annie, how close to the wall are we?
Keep still, goddamn it!
Stop moving around! Stop!
Dad!
Both of you...
...keep very still.
Try and stay calm.
Annie.
Is the other cam moving?
No.
Try and reach the wall.
See if you can anchor us back in.
Try it.
It's moving!
Peter, get your knife.
What?
Just do as I say.
Get it!
You don't have much time here.
You have to do something for me.
Cut me loose.
One cam can't hold us all.
You have to cut me loose...
...or else I'll pull everybody down.
Everybody will die!
Shut up, Annie!
It's one dead or three, Peter.
Don't make him do this.
You're gonna kill your sister.
Annie will die if you don't.
- I won't do it!
- Cut the rope!
- I can't!
- Stop it!
That cam is gonna come out
and Annie and you will die!
- You'll kill your sister!
- Stop it!
Cut the damn rope!
It doesn't matter about me. Cut it.
We're out of time!
Don't do it!
No one will blame you for it!
Just cut it!
Annie and you are gonna die!
Just cut it, Peter!
We're cleared for the Siachen glacier.
A doctor's on standby.
I was heading there anyway.
Mail and supplies.
I can drop you on my way back
to K2 base camp.
Sounds good.
I tried to visit you a few days ago.
But the weather closed in.
Annie's at base camp.
Arrived last week.
Would you like a tea?
No, I'm fine.
You must try the tea. It's very good.
Indian, of course.
We may be at war with them,
but their tea's the best.
- Forgive me. Mr. Garrett, isn't it?
- Yes.
National Geographic is always welcome.
The only Westerners who come to
Pakistan without conquering something.
The colonel's angry. Only 25% of his
medical supplies are onboard.
And three days late.
Look at this place.
In six years, I've lost 800 men.
Not one to the enemy.
But the chopper was full of stuff.
Not for my men.
For Americans who can pay $3 million for
climbing permits.
Elliot Vaughn, the entrepreneur.
He's got 40 people with him to try K2.
I've been seconded to his team.
Seconded or sold?
That's a question only a general
in Islamabad can answer.
Three o'clock.
Time to wake up the Indians.
So Annie's coming in
with Vaughn's team?
She's leading a WNN documentary crew.
They're going up the mountain
with him.
Have you seen her?
Not yet. One of the guides told me.
What about Vaughn?
What's he all about?
Pretty much what you'd expect.
Sensitive, kind, modest.
Your typical billionaire.
Four years ago his team took
on the south face.
Was 800 feet from the top
when weather closed in.
Twenty-four hours in the death zone.
Next morning, he walked down.
He's a bloody good climber.
- Got your update, Annie.
- What's up?
That cyclone's tracking fast
from southeast.
Let me know if anything changes.
What are you..?
I just happened to be in the area.
I heard WNN hired you. And you're
hosting it. Congrats.
They needed someone who could climb K2
and look presentable.
Not much of a rush.
That's not true. They wanted the best.
I read about you on the Eiger.
Fastest female ascent.
Dad would be proud.
When you leaving?
Early tomorrow morning. We want to
be summiting by 2:00 Wednesday.
What does the mountain say about that?
I thought you laid siege to it.
I didn't know it could be scheduled.
It's a plan, Peter, that's all.
Vaughn's aggressive. He knows what he
wants and goes for it.
I admire him.
How long have you known him?
Wherever you're going with this,
you're wrong.
Nobody ever affects my climbing.
Was that two of them, Cyril?
Or has this stuff just gotten
better than we thought?
- Frank.
- Good to see you.
- Tommy McLaren. Colorado Kid.
- You ready to go?
You lead, I'll follow.
There's my leading lady. Hi, Annie.
- How was your trip?
- My stomach's still up there.
Luckily I passed on the eggs Benedict.
Excuse me for a minute.
Ed Viesturs.
It's an honor to meet you.
- Elliot Vaughn.
- Nice to meet you.
This guy has been up Everest five times.
He's climbed 12 of the world's
14 highest peaks.
All without oxygen.
Rock on. By comparison, all of us
are merely amateurs.
- It's a real honor, Ed.
- Welcome to base camp.
Thank you.
Outdoors magazine wants
to interview you.
"Bankruptcy at High Altitude."
How much can we...
Yes?
I could go and come back, or...
Looking for Skip?
Yeah.
Try the command tent.
Thanks.
Skip?
I'm Peter Garrett.
- Good to meet you.
I got your message.
Bad luck about your porter.
I've got four you can meet tomorrow.
Supplies you need are no problem.
The Swedish hooker's taking longer
than I thought.
There's no shortage of entertainment.
You saw Mr. Vaughn fly in?
He's hard to miss. What's this
about his climbing to a deadline?
- Friend of yours?
- My sister's climbing with him.
Annie Garrett.
Vaughn's got this publicity stunt
for his new airline, Majestic Air.
He stands on the top of K2 waving
as the inaugural flight goes overhead.
Are you serious?
I'm deadly serious.
Your sister's safe. No one knows
these hills better than Tommy McLaren.
He told Vaughn they'd get up there.
I know I did.
I'd have told him anything
for $1 million.
Is that what he's spending?
That's just for Tom. Bought his
company out for the entire season.
Not that I'm pissed off.
Look what I get to drag to the top.
56-year-old movie producer
with dysfunctional bowel syndrome.
He's got the runs, mate. Permanently.
The Bench brothers bet
he won't make it past 18,000.
- What do you think?
- What do I think?
It depends. I'm so broke I might have
to shove him in a crevasse myself.
This is Monique, our base camp manager
and medic. Monique, Peter.
We've met. You should look at these.
Don't mind her. She's French-Canadian.
Some days she's Canadian
and can be quite pleasant.
Today, she's obviously French.
How about some Spanish mackerel
for the bow?
My name's Cyril. I'm not much,
but I'm all I think about.
Watch out for him, he's like a dog.
If he sees something...
...he tries to shag it. If he can't
shag it, he tries to eat it.
If he can't eat it, he pisses on it.
It's easy to tell us apart,
because I'm the shy one.
No, no, no, señorita.
Here you go.
Have a drink on Mr. Vaughn.
What time's the laser show?
Is this thing on?
Howdy!
Everyone hear me all right?
No!
You're the lucky ones.
Welcome to the highest party
in the world!
Okay, maybe I did overdo it
just a bit.
Four years ago, I came here
with a dream to climb K2.
The toughest mountain in the world.
As most of you know,
that attempt ended in tragedy.
On Wednesday,
with the help of Tom McLaren...
...I intend to fulfill that dream.
And while I'm at it, take care
of some business, Texas style.
At 0900 hours, Greenwich Mean Time...
...the inaugural flight of Majestic
Air will fly over the summit...
...and we'll be there to wave them on!
To the other teams climbing,
I'd like to say be safe...
...and good luck.
Kick up your heels
and enjoy the barbecue!
What about the weather, Mr. Vaughn?
We hope for the best.
You know something we don't?
The weather closes in
and people die up there.
Or don't you have to worry about that?
Anybody who doesn't worry
about that is a fool.
Brian Maki did a high-atmosphere
analysis of the last 4 decades.
Most years there's a 9-to-12-day lull
before the fall storms.
On August 2nd, we calculate
an 82% chance of fine weather.
Give me odds like that
in the oil business, I'd be rich.
Who's the leader, Mr. Vaughn?
Who makes decisions that mean
other people live or die?
Who plays God, so to speak?
There can be only one leader.
It's always the best climber.
I've made it clear to everyone
that Tom McLaren is that man.
Even the Pakistanis agree.
They're giving you a 21-gun salute.
Okay, let's party!
Thanks for that, Elliot.
You climb as good as you talk,
we'll get you there.
You know that old guy
who was asking questions?
Montgomery Wick.
Remember Dad used to talk about him?
They were in the service together...
Of course, I remember.
I miss him, Annie.
I miss him just as much as...
I can't talk about it.
You never have.
There's nothing to say.
He's gone, Peter.
Look, you can blame me all you want...
...but that last cam would've failed.
It held the two of us.
You want to do this?
Okay, fine, let's do it.
You didn't give it a chance.
- He knew it wouldn't hold either.
- Of course he didn't.
We were his life.
He would've died rather than take
a chance anything might happen to us.
I think we owed him the same.
But I did what I thought was right.
If you're so right, why haven't
you climbed? Or been to his grave?
I'm not going up there for a TV show.
I'm going up there for him.
I want to be the person
he always wanted me to be.
When I'm up there, I feel close
to him.
I touch his soul.
Take care up there.
This is it.
Wish you were going with me.
Not this time. Take care up there.
It'll be a great day for Texas.
And Scotland.
What is it?
Spindrift coming off the top.
That's local. If something was coming
in, it'd show on the other peaks.
Your sister's fine, man.
You look after yourself.
You too. Thanks for everything.
Understood, Tom.
You guys take good care up there.
Thanks, base. Out.
Well, you heard it.
Computer model shows it's building.
That's a concern.
We're about an hour from
the bottleneck, right?
Let's kick it and get up there.
Gets any worse,
we'll shelter under the ice cliffs.
If it comes in fast,
we're totally exposed out here.
It's not fast.
He said it's slow-moving.
There's a 70% chance
it'll turn east and miss us.
I'm not gonna risk a storm.
Not at 26,000.
We're not suggesting anything stupid.
The weather could turn.
The odds are with us.
We're five hours from the summit.
We turn back now, that's it.
We've lost our window.
I know. Elliot, I'm aware of that.
It's my responsibility.
I won't let a marketing campaign
compromise our safety.
You think this is
about a marketing campaign?
Come on, Tom.
This is about getting to the top.
I don't give a shit
about the publicity.
This is a life statement for me.
We're only 500 feet from
the bottleneck. Let's keep going.
Okay.
Let's go.
980 hectopascals and falling.
Lenticular cloud to the southeast.
Winds at 80 knots, rising.
Tom says he's going on.
What's base camp pressure?
Pressure's dropped two points
in four hours.
You made your case. We listened.
We decided.
It's too high a risk. Why am I here
if you don't listen to me?
I'll assess the risk. As to why
you're here, I wonder myself.
I'm Annie's brother.
McLaren's pulling them back, right?
We're on target. They're going on.
The wind's hit to the south.
What's your satellite show?
We've assessed the data.
We're going up.
It shows bad air coming in from India.
What the hell are you doing?
- How high are they?
- 26,000.
- What are you doing?!
- Warning my sister!
Leave it! That's enough!
Tom McLaren, come in.
Tom McLaren, this is base camp.
Do you copy?
Tom McLaren, do you read?
Come in, base.
You've got a major storm coming in.
You've gotta start down.
Who is this?
Peter Garrett.
You copy about the storm?
Where's Frank Williams?
Put Frank Williams on.
Skip here. We're looking
at the weather screens.
If this doesn't turn, you'll be in
big trouble. Turn back immediately.
Do you copy?
Yeah, I copy that.
Thanks, Skip. Out.
How we doing?
I'm pulling the plug.
We're going down.
- Just hold on.
- I'm sorry, Elliot.
You pay me to make these decisions.
I'm paying you to get me to the top.
Jesus! Elliot, you told me
I was in charge up here.
You are! Why are you vacillating?
Because some second-rate guide
got on the radio?
Nobody knows this mountain better
than Skip.
Skip Taylor's a hustler. He was
jockeying me to be in your boots.
Don't crap out on me now.
Come on, what did you think?
She'd just lift up her skirt
and pull her panties down for us?
Is this how you got up Everest twice?
I'm going down.
Fine. Fine.
Go down. Go on. Sit it out.
The storm will turn and you'll spend
the rest of your life living it down.
That should do wonders
for your business.
I'm sorry, can I? Please.
We're going back!
We don't have a choice!
We are dead on the ridge! Let's go!
Fuck you!
Annie!
Annie, can you hear me?
I'm all right! I'm safe!
Elliot!
I'm fine! We're okay!
Avalanche!
Annie, are you there?
Can you hear me?
Come in, base, this is summit team.
Do you read me?
Anybody, do you read me? This is
the Vaughn summit team. Come in.
Summit team, this is base camp.
Do you copy?
If you're gonna do that,
do it outside.
Base, this is summit team.
Are you trying to contact us?
Here. Let me.
Oh, my God. That's Morse code.
My dad taught us when we were kids.
Said it could save your life.
Smart man, your father.
He sure was.
There's three of them.
Vaughn.
Tom.
Annie.
I'm sorry, Kareem.
You say there are three.
Maybe there are others.
Maybe.
Tell them we can't keep talking.
We gotta save power.
He's right.
What's he saying, Annie?
They're coming to get us.
It's not just snow.
It's gonna be ice and rock.
We need special tools.
I don't know how much we have here.
Then how do you get it
up there, Mr. Garrett?
Then we dig with our bare hands
if we have to.
Whatever it takes. We have more than
enough guys here to get this done.
What the hell do you want to do?
Just leave them there?
Peter.
You can't ask people to work there.
That high, just staying alive is...
So we just walk away
and forget about them?
They had one fuel can each. They can
melt ice and rehydrate for a day.
At 26,000, without it,
their lungs fill with fluid.
That's pulmonary edema,
they die within another 12.
That gives us a window of 36 hours.
Montgomery Wick.
Wick speed-summited in 24.
We're not Montgomery Wick.
Even if we were, how long does that
leave to get through the rock and ice?
We don't know their exact location.
How long will that take?
I won't let Annie die.
So what are we gonna do?
Nitroglycerin, Mr. Garrett.
I wouldn't touch it
with an English barge pole.
We use it to blast rock
for gun emplacements.
It's low-freezing
and more powerful than symtex.
My responsibility ends at that door.
I want to make one thing clear.
This is your decision.
It's got nothing
to do with the Pakistani army.
Which is a legal way of saying
I think it's madness.
A magnificent madness, though.
Good luck.
Stop!
Skip, don't move your feet.
Everybody keep very still.
Okay, Skip.
Let me get this straight.
You want to go up that hill...
...with nitro on your back
and hope that it doesn't jolt?
That's right.
A hundred thousand sperm
and you were the fastest?
Skip here's agreed to go,
so I need four more.
It'll be a speed ascent,
in pairs, one canister per team.
People have to share?
Won't everyone want their own bomb?
Ed.
You're the best climber here.
I'm not one to walk away,
but I think it's suicide.
If we just leave them,
what do you call that?
It's reality. You're willing
to risk six lives to save three?
How do you feel about that?
The same way you do.
Your best friend died on Everest.
What if it was him up there right now?
I will go.
Ali is my cousin. It is my duty.
How about it, Mal? You and Cyril
have been up there before.
No...
Why would we want to leave this place?
Luxurious accommodation.
Fine cuisine.
Sultry weather.
Frostbite's off my dick.
I reckon we should wait
until they chuck in a ski lift.
Good idea. Imagine coming to the
Himalayas and actually climbing.
Especially when you have
to complete your autobiography.
And rustle up those all-important
endorsements. You wankers!
What's bloody wrong with you?!
We're in.
Thank you.
I need one more.
I'll write a check now
for anyone who goes.
Whether Elliot makes it or not,
I'll be waiting when you get back.
Half a million bucks.
Does that include the tip?
My brother's got explosives.
They're gonna blast their way down.
Blast their way down.
How are they gonna find us?
We might as well be on Mars.
It's not a question of how,
it's how long.
It's time that's gonna kill us.
We have to lay down a schedule.
A regimen we all adhere to.
Edema sets in
if we don't keep drinking.
Now, I figure, three water bottles...
...that's half a cup each,
every 2 hours.
After that, fuel cells to melt ice,
and finally...
...we use the dex syringes.
Chances are we're all gonna get
pretty sick...
...but if we keep to the schedule,
keep to it...
...maybe we can hold out.
Annie, we need to give them the grid
reference for our last known position.
She says they were about 300 feet
above the Anvil, heading down east.
The shoulder ice field.
I checked their manifest.
This is what they have.
We leave at dawn.
They got 22 hours if they're lucky.
How high can we chopper in?
Rasul says 21,000.
Any higher, the air's too thin.
He drops us.
How fast can we get there?
Negrotto Col's the only place we can
land. From there, 27 hours.
Five hours short.
We need Montgomery Wick. He's the
only man who's done it faster.
Will he do it?
Four years ago, a big storm blows
an American team off the hill.
There's nine up there, including
his wife. She was a guide.
He knows he can't help her, but he
goes anyway. The only one who did.
He lost all his toes to frostbite
but dragged 3 guys off the mountain.
They owe their lives to him.
What do you reckon?
Where is he?
On the mountain.
Up the shoulder, where he always goes.
They never found his wife's body,
so he keeps looking.
The guy's a lunatic.
That's just what we need.
Yeah. Strap on the nitro.
That's a great idea.
Smoking next to the nitro.
Although, bro and I always hoped
that you'd blow us.
Why are you going?
The money, of course.
Skip hasn't paid anyone in months.
You know of a better way out?
Can you climb?
Peter wants to know if I can climb.
Worst I've seen.
Couldn't climb a ladder.
You're that good, huh?
Yeah. But it was a very tall ladder.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm trying to kiss my ass goodbye.
It's dawn.
If the weather's cleared,
they'll be on their way.
I know.
Thank you.
And your brother?
Has he climbed since Utah?
No.
People say he lost his nerve.
Have you heard that?
Yeah, I've heard that.
Annie!
It's a pack! Quick!
I'm not interested.
You went before.
Men owe you their lives.
Four years ago.
Now I just climb for myself.
My father was a climber. Royce
Garrett. He climbed Everest with you.
I don't care. I don't live my life
so you can look up to me.
My sister's dying up there.
Before you lecture me,
get your facts straight.
It'll be less embarrassing.
Up there, you're not dying,
Mr. Garrett. You're dead.
What the hell happened to you?
Vaughn's people are offering $500,000
to anyone that goes.
Maybe that'll make a difference.
Why would they do that?
He's one of them.
What's their supply situation?
Enough for 22 hours.
Twenty-two.
Who's coordinating at base?
- Vaughn's people.
- That's a mistake.
I'll need someone there I can trust.
Taylor, you know the mountain best.
Skip's one of the best climbers.
We'll need him.
Let's agree on one thing:
This is not a climbing democracy.
On a rescue, we don't vote,
question or argue.
You listen and do exactly as I say.
Chopper will take you back.
Here's how we'll split it up.
Malcolm, you'll climb with Kareem.
- Cyril, you'll...
- What? No, I bloody won't.
You've been up the mountain too long
and forgotten the rules.
Never eat at a place called "Ma's"...
...don't play cards
with a fellow named Doc...
...and never climb with a stranger.
I'm going with my brother.
Frankly, I'd rather climb
with the Sheila.
My rules: I put a strong climber
with a weaker one.
You'll climb with Kareem.
Mr. Garrett,
you'll be climbing with me.
Cyril. Guess what?
Come on, darling.
Give us a smile, eh!
It's the second best thing
you can do with your lips.
We'll take the west ridge.
Cyril, the Mushroom.
Malcolm, Hockey Stick Gully.
Speed up all of them is the same.
We're as high as I can take you!
Move it! I can't hold it for long!
Next!
I'm having trouble
maintaining altitude.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org