Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- Sorry about the rough ride, Mr. Taylor.
This weather just came out of nowhere.
- How much farther?
- I should have you on the ground
in about fifteen minutes.
- Did you hear that, honey?
We're almost home.
- Whatcha reading there, Trooper?
- Sweetie, the nice lady
asked you a question.
Ah, last night he would hardly stop
talking about it.
Kept insisting that one of those
dinosaur things
was hiding in the closet.
- Oh, dinosaurs, huh?
- Oh yeah, kid's got a heck
of an imagination.
Don't even try talking him out of it.
- I know what you mean.
Oh! My daughter's his age.
She sets her mind on something?
Look out.
- We should get
the two of them together.
- Yeah.
- Sweetie, what is it?
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know.
Baby, talk to me.
- Oh shit.
- Where are you?
- Ah, we stopped for gas.
- Call my cell
the moment you get to the concert
so I know you made it.
- Yes, Dad.
- And no booze.
Just because I've lost my mind
and I'm letting you out of my sight
for a whole weekend...
- Don't you trust me?
- I'm your father,
I don't have that luxury.
- Well you better get used to it,
'cause this time next week,
I'll be 3,000 miles away.
- And I couldn't be prouder.
Thanks.
Listen, I know you think
you're all grown up
and you don't need my advice,
but you're still just a kid, Sara.
We don't always get second chances
when we screw up.
And another thing,
don't let what's-his-name
behind the wheel, the wrestler.
- I'm not gonna let anyone else
drive, Dad.
Love you.
- Goodbye.
- No regrets, right?
- Yo. Hitchcock.
The action's right here.
- And here we have the fabled
Man-squatch.
One false move
could alert him to our presence.
- Raargh!!!
No...no!
Whoa.
Bin Laden, what's up man?
- Sal!... relax.
- Making new friends?
- Yeah, I'm making new friends...
- Ay, ay, ay, wanna be our friend?
Ah, I guess not.
I'm serious, is anybody else
kinda nervous about this guy,
or is it just me?
- It's just you.
Hey, how's it going?
- Not bad, looking forward
to a little R&R.
- Yeah, well I don't think
you'll be needing these to crowd surf.
- Yeah, well the... um...
canyon's got some nice runs, so...
- You're going to do some
rock climbing?
- Crossed my mind....
Where's uh, where's Sara?
- She's probably taking
another lesson, right?
- You're hilarious.
- Let me shoot some of this.
- Who's the film major?
- Oh, shut up.
- No.
- Come on.
- There she is.
- Ah, I know, I'm late.
A screw-up with our booking,
I had to do a little sweet-talking.
- We still get the plane?
- Have I ever let my best friend down?
- No.
Coldplay, here we come.
- Whooooo!!!!
- This is gonna be a killer, Sara.
Here's to Sara, huh?
The best...
shit, the only pilot I know.
- Are you nuts? Put that away before
you get me in trouble, seriously.
- Nice work, cuz.
- Ooof! Careful.
Somebody's been hitting the gym.
- Ah, Sara?
- There you are, hey.
- Oh here, I'll get these for you.
- Sal, take note.
- Ha, ha, ha...
- Hey, man.
- Cory.
- My cousin.
I told you about him.
- Sure, hi.
- Hey, Bruce.
- You know Mel, Sal.
- Smile.
- Okay, are we all set?
- Yeah, come on.
- Yeah, just waitin' on you,
sweet cheeks.
- He's such as gentleman, isn't he?
- He's charming.
- Bags?
- Yes, bags, bags, hey, bags!
- Really, man?
- I need some help, come on.
- You okay?
- Yeah, no, I'm fine, I'm fine.
- Ahhh!
- What do you have in this thing?
- Let's go.
- The weather going to be a problem?
- For flying?
- Yeah.
- It's a low cloud,
it'll burn off any minute...
Hey, just relax, okay?
Let me do my thing.
- Okay.
- Hey, so Sara, the General's cool
with this all, right?
- Cool with what?
- With you doing
the whole sky captain thing.
I mean, it didn't really work out
too well for your mom, so...
- Could you be any more insensitive?
- Relax...
Look, no offense, Sara.
I'm just, ya know...
- None taken.
I'm not my mother,
and he's a Colonel.
Let's just go have some fun, okay?
- Yeah, heh.
- Remind me why I'm dating you again?
- That's it?
- What were you expecting?
A private jet?
- For the money we're paying I half
expected John Travolta to walk out.
- Fuel isn't cheap,
we're already getting a discount
through the flight school, so stop.
- Yeah, come on. Live a little.
- How much d'you think one of these
little puddle jumpers costs anyways?
- If the music thing works out,
I'll send you a brochure.
-"If" the music thing works out?
- Sorry, "when" it works out.
- "When" the music thing works out.
- Yeah.
- All right, pilot.
- Okay, baggage goes in the rear.
Everything you don't want
to carry on your laps.
- All right, I'm going in the rear.
- You always got a lot of baggage.
- Comin' in.
- I should go talk to him.
I'll be right back.
- Oh yeah, get Rain Man.
- Hey, be nice.
- I'm super nice.
- Get your booty in there.
- God, Sal.
Oh wow.
- Um... we're going to get...
really friendly.
Where'd Sara find the stiff?
- He found her.
- What do you mean he found her?
- He just kinda showed up one day.
She was looking for a study partner.
Smart guy.
- Wait a second, she's playing
hide the sausage with her tutor?
- I guess a big brain can be a turn on.
Not that I speak from experience.
- Big brain?
He's a trust fund prick.
- Come on.
- Beer?
- No.
- Trust fund, what do you mean?
His parents rich or something?
- Or something.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You sure?
You don't look so good.
- Yeah, yeah I am, sure.
- Okay... well....
let's go.
- Why do you let Sal do that?
Talk about your mom that way?
- He likes pushing people's buttons.
I'm used to it.
- Well that doesn't mean it's okay.
- Hey, this is our last weekend together.
Do you really want to spend it
arguing about Sal?
- Don't say that.
- Don't say what?
- Last weekend.
You make it sound like we're never
going to see each other again.
- Hey, Montreal's a long way from here.
This is a big deal for me.
- You don't think it's a big deal
for me, too?
- Look, let's not talk about it now,
okay?
You're not afraid to fly, are you?
- Pantheon 520, wind is 330 at 7,
turn right onto taxiway bravo and hold.
520, additional traffic
will be departing shortly
runway one five left.
Six Echo Whiskey,
cleared to land runway three.
Be aware of departing traffic
at your one o'clock.
- Sara!
Is it always so noisy?
Sara!
- What?
- Is it always this noisy?
- I don't want to have to dub everything.
- It won't be so bad once we're up.
- Dub everything?
Are you serious?
I just want some better material
for my reel.
- What, and this is better material?
- Don't worry, I'll edit you out.
- By any means necessary.
- You got it.
- Malcolm X, right?
- Very nice.
- Actually, it's from Dirty Hands,
the Sartre play.
Jean-Paul Sartre, the existentialist?
Man is what he wills himself to be,
hell is other people...
- I will myself to be awesome.
- So does Sal. Right, babe?
- Yeah.
Get that fucking thing away.
- Philistines.
- Pantheon 520 is released.
Contact Lakeview Centre
11 niner decimal one.
- Harrisford Tower,
Yankee Zulu X-ray,
ready for take off, one five left
- Yankee Zulu X-ray hold short,
one five left.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray, holding short.
- Hey, Capitan.
What's our ETA?
- Ah, with a good tail wind,
it's about a 90 minute flight.
Nice, plenty of time to
get shitfaced before concert, huh?
- Well, you're well on your way.
- You guys want one?
- No.
- All right, more for me.
- What are those for?
- Um, motion sickness.
- Yeah, try not to yak on me
on this flight. Okay, sweet cheeks?
- Thanks for being so supportive.
- At least it's only like an hour
and a half flight.
The drive up there was brutal,
remember?
- We might get a decent camping spot
this year, which would be amazing.
- I don't know, there's supposed to be
like twice as many people this year.
- How 'bout you relax,
there's going to be room.
- Hey, that's what you said last year.
- So?
- So, we ended up sleeping in a ditch.
- That's funny because
I don't remember being in a ditch.
- I'm surprised you remember
your name after all that tequila.
- Ah, yeah.
- How many times have you done this?
- You mean soloed?
- Yeah, no instructor,
no co-pilot, just you.
- Plenty. You need a lot of hours
before they let you fly a twin.
- How about in this plane,
how many times in this plane?
- Well, never, because it's a rental.
- No, you know what I mean,
like this type of plane.
- Enough.
Okay? Enough.
- Whoa!
Look what we got here, huh?
- Is that what I think it is?
- Whoooaa!
Yeah! It's a parachute!
If anything happens,
we got this, right?
Whoooo!
Bail out, bail out!
- Be careful with that.
- Alright, alright, just playing.
- Well, play with something else.
- Oh, okay.
You like that shit?
- Don't encourage him.
- Oh yeah.
- Very good.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
cleared for takeoff, one five left,
to 1000 feet,
contact Lakeview Centre,
one niner decimal one.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
cleared for takeoff, one five left.
Okay, here we go,
buckle up back there.
- Whooo!
- Please insert tab into buckle.
- Okay line-ups, cowl flaps open,
mixture rich, props forward.
Transponder alt, lights on,
fuel pumps on,
DG set,
power set.
- Whooo!
- Hey!
- Let's do it, ha!
- That's so not okay.
- Whoooo!
- Gauges green.
Air speed alive.
- Whooo!
- 85 knots.
85 rotate.
- Yeah!
- Whooooo!
- After takeoff checks, fuel pumps off,
engine gauges green.
Beautiful, isn't it.
- Wow, Sara, this is amazing.
- Seriously?
- That was fucking disgusting.
- If you puke in here,
you are sleeping alone tonight.
- That's an empty threat.
- That's what happens
when you drink and fly, kids.
I don't recommend it, do you?
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
Harrisford V.O.R.
out of 2,200 for 5,500
en route to Green Lake.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
squawk 5247 and ident,
cleared 5,500.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
squawk 5247 cleared 5,500.
you're radar identified,
Green Lake altimeter
is two niner, eight niner...
- Yankee Zulu X-ray, roger.
- What's happening?
- Um, I just told them who we are
and what we want to do
and they assigned us
a new transponder code
so radar can identify us.
It's all routine,
there's nothing to worry about.
- So Sara, what's with you
taking the train to McGill?
- It was my dad's idea,
he thought I could see more
of the country that way.
- Do you still need a ride
at the ass crack of dawn?
- No, it's okay, I've got it covered.
- Um... actually my dad
really wanted to see me off,
so I told him he could drive.
- Whatever, just let me know.
- Yeah, but I thought that...
Never mind.
- Someone take this, take it.
- Ah, great.
This thing always gets out of tune.
- Tune it up.
- What are you doing?
- Filming you.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- Right...
- So you gonna shoot that video
for my band or what?
- It depends,
do I still get final cut?
- Whatever you want,
as long as it got hoes in it.
- Classy, I like it.
Speaking of hoes,
how's the love life?
- Whoa, getting a little personal,
don't you think?
- Come on, you can tell me.
Anybody special?
- There might be.
- It's a dude.
- Oh yeah?
Anybody we know?
- Um... I'd better not say.
- Why not?
- She's got a boyfriend.
- Funny guy...
Funny guy.
- Shouldn't you keep your hands
on the wheel?
- It's okay, that's what
the rudder pedals are for.
- You forget something?
- No, just making sure
my gift's not getting crushed.
You brought it?
- Of course I did.
- What gift?
- Just a little something.
- Oh yeah, what'd you get him,
a personality or something?
- Show us.
- Nah, it's just a... comic book.
- The guy at the store said
it was pretty rare...
and since Bruce was a collector.
- A comic book?
You're one of those guys.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Nothing, buddy,
come on, let me see it.
- Yeah, come on.
- Come on, let me see it.
- You can't right now,
because he is flying the plane.
- Whoa.
- Sara.
- Sara, can you please stop
screwing around with this guy.
That'd be great.
- Our lives are in his hands.
- Just, just relax, okay?
She knows what she's doing.
- You're doing fine. See?
It's not that hard.
- Woo, jeez!
- Shit! Shit!
- I think we get the point now,
take back the controls,
please, Sara!
- Just a little bit of turbulence.
Pull back slowly.
- I can't!
- Pull back slowly.
- I can't.
- Sara, this isn't funny anymore, okay?
- Come on, pull back.
- I think we'd all be more comfortable
with Sara flying the plane.
- Hey, Sara, come on, huh!
- Jesus, Sara, God.
- Next time I wanna be in front.
- Are you alright?
- Fuck this shit, gimme this!
- Hey!
- Sal! Come on.
- What you gonna do, punk, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry, is this yours?
Oooo, Weird Stories.
Oooo, creepy!
- Dude, d'you mind?
- Guys.
- You want it?
- Give it back.
- Be careful!
- Take it easy, guys.
- Careful, careful, it's a comic book.
- Sal, just give it back.
- Oh my God, I'm taking it out
of its protective case thing...
Oh my God...
great condition.
- Sal.
- You're so not funny, stop it.
- Dude.
- Oh... it's ripping...
- Sal, what are you doing?
- Oh my God, this looks
pretty important to the story.
- Seriously?
- Ah!
- What are you, seven years old,
reading comics?
The next time
you try and get us killed,
I'm wiping my whole ass with it.
- Hey, Sal, that's enough!
Okay, just give it back to him.
- Fucking little kid,
still reading comics.
- Give it to him!
- You want your comic?
You want your comic?
Take your fucking comic!
- Come on, Sal.
- It's okay.
- What's that?
- It's a...
a bus ticket to Montreal.
- Montreal, isn't that
where you're moving, Sara?
Sorry, man.
- I was gonna tell you.
- When exactly where you going
to tell me?
- Um...
- We'll talk about this later.
Centre, Yankee Zulu X-ray.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray requesting
10,500 for weather.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray,
you're cleared at 10,500,
negative traffic.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Um, we've got weather ahead
and I'm not instrument rated.
So we'll have to climb above it.
- Whoa, what does
'not instrument rated' mean?
- It means I have to visually
maintain separation
from the ground at all times.
- Translation, it means,
she can't fly through clouds.
- Clouds.
Are you kidding me?
- Will you shut up?
- How high does this thing go,
anyway?
- Service ceiling is 24,000.
- 24,000...
- Look at it this way,
commercial airlines fly at 40.
Sorry about that, guys.
It's just a little bit of unsettled air.
- Unsettled air?
- It's the third time.
- 10,000...
- Aren't we supposed
to level off or something?
- I'm trying.
- What you mean, you're trying?
- It means, I'm trying.
- Quit screwing around, Sara!
- This isn't a joke!
The elevator's not responding
for some reason.
- There's an elevator?
- Not that kind of elevator!
- You see that part on the tail
that's sticking up at an angle?
- Which part?
- The hinged section
- Yes.
- When air goes over it,
the tail goes down, making us go up.
I don't, I don't know,
something's jammed it.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Come on.
- What do we do?
- Mel, put the camera away!
Ten minutes!
- Centre, Yankee Zulu X-ray, I, uh,
I think I have a problem here.
- Yankee Zulu X-ray, Centre,
are you declaring an emergency?
- Yankee Zulu X-ray... uh...
Not at this time.
- Not at this time?
I thought you said we couldn't level off!
- No, there are procedures for this.
Okay, I'll just reduce power.
- You should tell him that then, Sara.
- Hey!
Who's the pilot here?
Everyone just relax, okay?
- Oh no.
- Oh, shit.
- We should probably turn around.
Turn this thing around.
- Sara, we need to go back!
Let's turn around, now!
- Yeah.
What the hell?
- This is bad.
I'm pretty sure this is bad.
- Everybody just stay calm, okay?
20,000...?
That's impossible.
- 20,000 feet?
Is that right?
- Can't be, there must be
some kind of glitch.
Centre, Yankee Zulu X-ray,
my elevator's jammed
and my instruments are malfunctioning,
I am climbing and have lost position
in cloud, please advise.
Centre, Yankee Zulu X-ray!!!
- Hey, what the hell is going on?
- I can't raise anybody.
- What do you mean
you can't raise anybody?
- Mayday, mayday, mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray,
approximately 15 miles
east of Patterson V.O.R.
Altitude unknown, instrument failure,
please respond.
Mayday, mayday, mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray!!
- Sara?
Sara?
- No one is answering.
There's nothing.
Just dead air.
- Jesus Christ.
- So what do we do?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
You're the pilot!
Get us out of this!
- What about the procedures?
You said you wanted to reduce power?
- I can't risk it now, visibility is zero
and without instruments, we could fly
straight into a mountain.
- Hey, what did you do?
Huh? You let him fly the plane.
He probably fucked something up.
- He didn't do anything!
- Yeah, well somebody did!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you know he's right.
This is your fault Sara.
- This is not my fault!
- How long have you had your license?
- Long enough.
- You only checked out on one
of these things like a week ago?
Jesus Christ, I can't believe
I was stupid enough--
- Sal! Will you just calm down?
You're not helping.
- Maybe I missed something
during the pre-flight, I don't know.
- You missed something?!
- We need to contact traffic control.
If they still have a radar fix on us,
they can talk us down.
Cell phones,
does anyone have a signal?
- No. Wait, wait...
Fuck, I got nothing.
- Same here.
- Oh, think.
Something's wrong, we're stalling.
I have to go to maximum power.
Bruce?
Bruce! Goddamn it!
There's a pilot operating handbook
underneath the seat,
can you give it to me?
Please.
- I thought you knew
how to fly this thing?
- Just give it to me, please.
Give it to me!
Go to section five.
- Now what?
- The maximum takeoff weight,
it should say somewhere.
- Uh... 6,500.
- Okay, if we're over that,
the stall speed will change.
What's the basic empty weight?
- Uh, 4891.
- Sal, how much do you weigh?
- What?
- How much?
- Uh, 170, why?
- Mel?
- 110.
- 155.
- Bruce?
Bruce, please!
- Uh, 150.
- Okay, I'm 110,
plus a 100 for baggage.
1,000 for fuel. Um...
- 1,800.
- 1,800?
We're too heavy. We should get rid
of anything we don't need.
- You kidding me?
- I look like I'm kidding?
- I'm not throwing
my stuff out of the plane.
- I'll do it for you.
- Sal! No!
No!
- Sit down!
- You want me to open the hatch?
- Be careful... please.
- You know I will.
Are you guys ready?
- Yeah.
I know, I got you, I got you.
- Got me?
- Alright, I'm opening.
- Be careful back there.
- Ready?
One... two... three!
- I got you.
- I'm good, I'm good.
- Are you ready?
- Can't keep this thing in tune anyway.
- And you play like shit.
- What's next?
- You got it, you got it?
Your bag, I'll get the other one.
- What the fuck?
- What is it?
What's going on?
- Sal, what's wrong with you?
- I just, I just saw something.
- What?
- I don't know!
- Guys!
- I need you, okay?
- Focus!
- I know, I know!
- Uh... I think that's it.
- Okay, you're next, go!
- What are you holding out on us?
- Look man, that stays, alright?
- Alright, well I'm keeping
something too, huh?
- That's it, come on!
- Is it better?
- Maybe, uh, I don't know.
This doesn't make sense.
The systems aren't supposed
to fail like this.
- So how long do we have?
Sara.
Sara, how long do we have?
- We'll be out of fuel
in less than an hour.
- What are you saying?
- When we took off,
the tanks were only half full.
- We're going to draw straws,
and the winner gets the parachute.
- Oh, come on.
- It's a good idea.
- What?
- He's right.
- I can't believe
you're even talking about this.
- You guys, it's too dangerous.
- Too dangerous?
- Is that a joke?
- We don't know who put that chute here,
or if it's packed properly.
None of us have even skydived before!
- Well how hard can it be?
- We could be at 10,000 feet,
or at 1,000.
You jump when we're too low,
you're gonna hit the ground
before your chute opens,
if it even opens.
Are you crazy?
- Too low?
We've been going up the whole time.
- Have we?
The first thing they teach you
at flight school is just
how disoriented you get
when you can't see the ground.
There's no way
that we're putting that on.
There's no way.
- You know what? Screw this.
Mel, take it.
- What are you doing?
- You're putting it on.
- What are you doing, man?
- I'm saving her life, man.
Take it.
- Hey, back off, Cory.
- No.
- I'm not going to let you die.
- Look man, I said back off,
we're drawing straws like I said before.
- She's your girlfriend, man.
What, you're going to let her die?
- Yeah, she's my girlfriend.
I'm gonna decide.
- Decide what?
- God, you're a fucking asshole,
you know that?
- Oh yeah, I'm the asshole here, right?
- Stop it! Quit it!
- What the hell is going on
back there?
- Stop it!
Both of you, stop it!
- That the best you got, man?
That what they teach you in school?
- Fuck off man, fuck off.
- No wonder you lost
every wrestling match.
- Fuck you!
I didn't lose every match.
- Shit.
- Un-fucking-believable.
Gimme that!
- Stop!
- No!
- Gimme.
- Let go!
- Leave her alone!
- Stop it!
Everybody, stop it!
Do you want to get out of this alive?
Do you?
Well then I'm the pilot
and what I say goes.
Is that acceptable to you?
Is that acceptable, yes or no?
Is that acceptable?
Good.
Everyone just stay in your seat
and shut up.
- We're going to die like them.
We're going to die like them.
- What do you mean?
- We're going to die like them.
We have to get down.
- Bruce, we're all scared, okay?
Just take it easy.
- No, we have to land the plane.
We have to get the plane down.
- Just relax.
- No, we have to get me down.
We have to get down!
We have to get me down!
Get me down!
- No!
- I'm not gonna die like them!
I'm not gonna die like them!
- Relax alright!
Just relax.
There we go, there we go.
- Sal, what are you doing?
- There we go. There it is.
- Who's flying the plane?
- The autopilot.
- Is he breathing?
- He'll be fine,
I just put him to sleep.
- What was all that shit he said
about people dying?
- His parents died in a car accident.
- Are you sure?
- You know, if he's so afraid of flying,
why'd he come?
- Because I invited him.
- You know what?
That's right, I forgot.
He's a freak and he's in love.
- We're not in love.
- Yeah?
Does he know that?
What are you gonna do?
One last weekend of pity sex with him
and trash him like a leaky rubber?
Is that what you're gonna do?
That's cold.
That's cold, sweetie.
- You don't know a thing about me
or what I want.
- Yeah, whatever.
We better tie him up.
- Tie him up?
Isn't that a bit extreme?
- You want him to go all kamikaze
on us again, huh?
- You got a blade, man?
- Alright.
- Ah!
- Sara.
It's getting really cold in here, Sara.
- I'm sorry,
this cabin isn't pressurized.
- Isn't there a heater?
- Yeah, there is, but we can't use it.
- Why?
- It runs on the main fuel supply
and we need every last drop
for the engines.
Oxygen is the real problem.
- What do you mean?
- Above 13,000 feet, we're going
to start suffering from apoxia.
- Apoxia, what's apoxia?
- It's, uh, oxygen deprivation.
Shortness of breath,
headaches, nausea.
- I thought you said this thing
could go to 24,000 feet.
- It can, but most people
don't bring it above 10.
That's why there's no breathing gear.
Dammit! If my elevator worked,
I could do a controlled descent
and we could all get our bearings.
- Is there a way that we can clear
the jam, like an access panel, or...
- There's nothing we can do from here.
Somebody would have to go outside
and do it manually.
- What do you mean go outside?
On the tail?
- No, no, no.
Screw that, we're not doing that.
It's ridiculous.
- That's your attitude for everything,
isn't it? Just give up.
- What, do you wanna go out there?
Huh?
Be my guest.
- Oh no...
- What now?
- The de-icing boots are malfunctioning.
- What?
- They keep ice
from building up on the wings.
- Aren't you supposed to check
all this shit before--?
- I didn't know we were going
to be flying this high.
- So ice builds up,
what does that mean?
- It means we don't generate
enough lift.
And if it blocks the ailerons
then we're really screwed.
- Oh, perfect.
- Mel, what's wrong, you okay?
- Just a... headache.
What are you doing?
- You heard her,
we just ran out of options.
- Cory, you're not going out there.
- Beats sitting in here waiting to die.
- No, Cory, you can't go out there.
Nothing to hang onto,
you'll be blown right off.
- That's what the rope's for.
- Listen to her okay?
She knows what she's talking about.
- Look, take this with you at least.
- The parachute?
Look, I've been free climbing
since I was 12, okay?
It'll only slow me down.
- My hero.
- Do you want to go out there?
Huh? Feel free.
- Be my guest.
- It might not even work.
- What?
Look, will it or won't it?
Sara, you're the expert here.
Will this work?
Or won't it?
- Enough pressure on the elevator
will be able to free it.
So, yeah.
- Okay.
- Alright, can you slow us down?
- I'll try.
- Help me!
- There's gotta be another option.
- No, there isn't.
- There's no other way, you heard her.
See that rope back there?
Get it and tie it to something.
Make sure it's tight.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
Piece of cake.
Who taught you how to tie a knot?
- It's a knot.
- What?
Like this.
Sure you're ready for this?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means you've been drinking, fuck-o.
- Oh my God, come on.
- Not now!
- I just need to know if I can trust you.
Gimme this.
- Is this enough for you, huh?
Are you satisfied now?
- Okay, okay.
- Let's fucking do this...
- Let's do it.
- Okay, I'm reducing power.
- Okay.
- Cory, come here.
- Yeah?
Yeah, what?
- Come back.
- Okay.
- No, promise me, you'll come back.
- I've done this a hundred times.
Okay, just not quite this high.
It's fine, fly okay?
It's okay, okay?
It's alright.
Just keep me in focus, okay?
Alright? Okay.
Okay, let's do it!
Come on.
Rock and roll.
- What's wrong?
- Our weight distribution's off.
We're not balanced.
- Cory!
- Jesus Christ, Sara! Come on!
- Sara!
- Come on. Okay.
Ooooh. That's better.
How's he doing?
- He's good, he's all right!
He's alright, right buddy?
- It's too far!
I think I gotta jump.
- What?
Are you crazy?
No!
Jesus...
There he is, he's here.
- Come on, Cory!
- There we go. There we go.
He's on the tail!
He's on the tail.
Come on...
- Come on, Cory. Come on.
- I've got control back!
- He did it.
You did it bro! Ha ha!!!
Put that thing away
and come help me!
Come on!
- Okay!
- How's he doing back there?
- He's not going to make it,
he's freezing!
Gimme your hand!
Come on, Cory!
For Chrissake, Sara,
keep it steady!
- I'm trying!
- Come on, Cory, I'm right here,
on the count of three,
you're gonna take my hand, alright?
Alright, ready? One...
two....
...three!
No!!
Jesus! Fuck!
Roll on!
Ah, shit!
Oh, my God!
- Do you have him?
Sal, what's happening?
- Oh, shit!
- Somebody talk to me.
Sal.
- He's gone.
- What?
- No, no.
- The fucking rope broke.
He's gone.
No... oh, no.
- I saw something.
No, no, no.
- I thought I saw it before,
now I know.
- No, no.
- Could you just shut up and listen?
Shut up and listen to me.
It got him, I saw it.
It was huge, it was fucking huge.
It was black.
You didn't see it.
You didn't hear it.
Look aren't you listening to me?
It fucking grabbed him, I saw it!
- What does it matter?
Cory's dead.
- Yeah, well better him than us.
Just get us down now, right now.
- No.
- Just land this plane now.
Get it down, Sara!
- I will, I will.
- Right now....
Right now.
- Can anybody see anything?
- More goddamned cloud.
- What happened?
Where are we?
Why the hell am I tied up?
- It's for your own good.
- We're not climbing anymore.
- That's right.
We're going to be okay now.
- We are?
- Where's Cory?
Sara?
- You killed him.
He trusted you,
and you... killed him.
- What are you talking about, Mel?
- This didn't break.
It was cut.
- Are you listening to yourself
right now?
Huh?
You sound fucking crazy!
- He saved our lives!
- Where were you when I needed help
pulling him in, huh? Where were you?
- I was there.
- Oh well, I must have blinked.
- I hit my head.
- I'm sure you did.
But you know what?
None of that matters now.
Your boyfriend is gone.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Mel, it was an accident.
Okay? You know it was.
- You're fucking crazy.
- I'm the crazy one?
You just accused me of killing someone!
- Guys! Stop!
- Someone please tell me
what happened to Cory.
- He went outside on the tail
to fix the elevator.
Sal thinks something grabbed him.
- Look, I know what I saw.
Okay, I know what I saw!
It was real.
- What was? What was real?
- We don't know.
- Bullshit.
Bullshit! Bullshit!
There's a monster out there!
- Just shut up, okay?
Just shut up.
- How long are you going
to keep me tied up for?
- Until we know we can trust you.
- Of course you can trust me.
- Can I really?
- You completely lost it earlier
and you lied to me.
- About what?
- Your parents weren't killed
in a car crash, were they?
Were they?
- No.
- Mel, can you come up here, please?
Keep an eye out.
- For what?
- Anything.
You know how I said we were going
to have that talk later?
Look at me!
We're having it now.
- I knew your mother.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- I was there when it happened.
- When what happened?
- I was one of the passengers.
When they pulled me out of that lake,
half my bones were broken.
I spent six months in the hospital
just trying to walk again.
- So you're saying,
you're the Taylor's kid?
- I thought you said your last name
was Parker?
- The Parkers are my foster parents.
- So, you knew who I was
when we first met?
- I didn't want it to affect things
between us.
I, I knew you would freak out.
- Jesus, man.
Freak her out?
God, you guys are fucking
death magnets!
Jesus, we're so fucked!
We're so fucked!
- What did you think would happen
when I went off to McGill?
You think I'd fly home every
other weekend to see you?
Our lives are going
in different directions.
You're so different
than I thought you were.
You're a liar.
You make up this story
like you know my mom.
That's a sick, bullshit fantasy.
You had to know that this,
this couldn't last.
You had to know that,
tell me, you knew that.
- Fantasy?
A fantasy?
Your mom killed my parents!
My life is so screwed up!
Your mom destroyed my life!
- You don't know shit.
- I figured it out though.
- Figured what out, Bruce?
- We're meant to be together, Sara.
- Meant to be together?
Are you crazy?
- I love you.
What did you just say?
- Don't say that.
Don't say that.
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray.
Position and altitude unknown,
can anybody read me?
- Can someone please
untie these ropes?
- Sure, I'll get right to it.
- Mayday, Mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
- Let us hear it.
It's that thing.
It's that thing, it's back.
It's back.
- No, it's distortion.
It has to be.
- Oh, come on.
That's not distortion.
- Well, whatever it is,
there's a rational explanation.
- Well good, 'cause I think
we'd all like to hear it, Sara!
- What do you want me to say?
Okay, apoxia makes you see things,
or hear things.
- But not the same things.
Look, the altimeter says
we should be in outer space.
How do you explain that right now?
- Some magnetic interference.
- Sara, you heard it, it's not normal.
- Yeah, I heard something.
It could be crosstalk or interference
with sunspots, something.
- Oh my god, sunspots?
Are you kidding me?
- You're not a radio expert, Sal!
None of us are.
- Alright, alright, let's just be real.
I think there's something we all need
to admit right now, don't you think?
- Admit what?
- Come on, Sara.
We've been going down
for what, like 20 minutes?
Tell me you're not thinking
the same thing I am!
- Spit it out.
- Where the hell is the ground?
- Sara.
Sara, your dad,
he works on secret projects, right?
- Yeah, Mel, what--
- Like for the Air Force?
- Yeah...
- Yeah, good point.
Yeah, remember the mechanic we saw,
the camel jockey?
Well, maybe, just maybe,
he rigged the plane
to kill the Colonel's daughter.
How's that?
- Look, that's not what I meant.
Okay, what if we don't need
to come down?
What if we never took off?
- Mel.
- Just hear me out, what if we're just
part of some big experiment,
you know, something to see
how people react to stress.
- Mel, that's impossible.
- Why?
- Because he doesn't even know
we're here.
- What?
- He thinks we were driving
to the concert.
He doesn't even know
I have my pilot's license.
- Are you shitting me, Sara?
- He's paranoid!
He's convinced I'll end up
the same way my mom did!
- Well, Jesus!
I wonder what gave him that idea!
- It has nothing to do with that okay?
The point is, it's not some giant
government conspiracy.
- Why not?
- This doesn't happen in real life.
- There wasn't any information
released on the plane that hit us.
- What plane?
- The one that killed her mom
and my parents.
There's no record of it,
it just appeared out of nowhere.
- The ghost plane theory? Really?
- It's just that we're trapped
in a hanger,
we're plugged into some sort
of simulation or...
maybe it's drugs, you know,
like those LSD tests they did
back in the '60s.
- One of hell of a bad trip we're having.
- It makes more sense
than anything else!
- Well shit, I say we find out.
- How?
- I don't know... jump!
I mean, in dreams, I don't know,
you're falling and you wake up,
Maybe it's the same
in this situation, huh?
Maybe it's the same.
- You know what?
I think you're onto something,
why don't you go ahead
and give it a shot.
- Well maybe it's just
the booze talking, I don't know.
I don't know!
But right now, right now,
it's saying shut the fuck up
and drink me.
So you know what?
I'm gonna do just that.
Cheers.
- Ahh!!!
- Wake up, Sara...
Sara...
Wake up, Sara.
Sara, wake up!
Sara!
- Sara!
Sara, wake up!!!
Sara!
Something hit us
and we need you to fly the plane.
Sara!
Come on, quick!
- Jesus...
- Come on!
- Ah!
- Sara!
I can't take this.
I can't take this anymore.
- No, no, Mel, stay with me,
stay with me.
Mel.
It's going to be okay.
I promise.
Okay?
It's going to be okay.
- What's that?
- Oh no...
- What? It's got us!
- What is it?
- Sara!
- Am I the only one
that's gone completely insane!
Did anybody else just hallucinate
something attacking us?!
- Calm down, Sal.
- Calm down?!!!
That thing's going to rip us apart!
- Well whatever it is, it's gone, okay?
Just relax.
- You would say that,
'cause you put us in this situation.
- This isn't about me, okay?
This isn't my fault.
Bruce, what are you doing?
Bruce, stop it, I'm serious.
- Sal...
Sal, I think I took too many,
I think I took many...
- Mel... Mel!
Mel!
Mel, Jesus Christ, Mel!
Oh come on, no, no,
don't do this, come on.
Come on... baby, baby.
Something's wrong with Mel!
- What happened to her?
- Don't know.
I, uh, can't feel a pulse.
I think she OD'd!
- OD'd on what?
- On her fucking pills,
what do you think she OD'd on?
Mel... oh baby oh, no, no, no...
- We got to get her breathing!
- Mel, come on!
- Please, please help her!
Please!
- What the fuck are you doing?!
- Move, move!
- Don't you fucking hurt her!
- Please.
- Jesus Christ, Mel!
- Come on. Come on, baby!
Come on. Come on.
Don't you fucking hurt her!
Don't hurt her!
Don't hurt her.
- Yeah, yeah, it's okay.
I'm here, I'm here.
Come on, I'm here.
- Oh, thank God.
- Here we go, here we go.
You're okay, come here.
There you go, baby.
You're okay.
Look, baby, I never...
I never meant to say those things.
I didn't mean it, I didn't mean it,
I swear.
I didn't mean those things
I said to you.
- Sal...
- What, what, baby, what?
It's okay, what?
- About Cory...
- No, we don't need
to talk about that now.
We don't need
to talk about that now, baby.
- Yes, we do.
- No, we don't, no we don't.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay, it's okay, baby.
I never meant to hurt you...
- Mel!!!!!
- What the hell was that?
- It got her, it fucking got her,
and it's gonna get us too...
It's gonna fucking get us too!
- There's no way... it can't be...
There's no way.
- What did you do?
What did you do, you fuck?!!!
What the fuck did you do,
you fucker?!
- Sal, Sal...
- I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- No, no, please no!
- No! Sal!
- I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- No!
Sal! Let him go!
Sal!
- I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- Stop it, Sal!
- You fuck!
- Sara, help me up!
Don't let go of me!
- Come here.
Please, don't let go of me!
- I got you.
- Nooo!
- They're dead.
They're all dead.
God, what have I done?
What have I done?
- It's not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
I'm the pilot.
I'm responsible.
He knew it.
My dad knew it.
He knew it from the day we buried her.
I wasn't allowed to see her body.
All I remember is the flowers
on her casket.
Tulips.
Tulips were her favourite.
God, I miss her.
I miss her so much.
I never believed she was really gone.
I thought, thought maybe
she was lost somewhere up there,
and that, if I learned to fly I could,
I could find her and bring her home.
I want her to come home.
- This happened before
and it's happening again.
- No.
Bruce, no.
This isn't about your parents,
or my mom,
or any conspiracy, okay?
It's not about that.
- You're right, Sara.
I know that now.
- Then what?
- It's me.
- What are you talking about?
- Ten years ago on that plane,
I saw...
I saw something... I...
There was a storm...
Turbulence...
The cover of a magazine.
I was scared.
I imagined it happening to us.
It did.
- No, that's insane.
That's just a coincidence.
- Then what do you call this, huh?
- What?
The comic?
- Just look.
- What?
- We should probably turn around.
- I'm trying.
- 20,000 feet?
- Where the hell is the ground?
- You killed him.
- This didn't break, it was cut.
- What are you saying?
This is... this is some kind of curse?
- Aren't you listening?
I made these things come true
just by thinking about them.
I should have never gotten
on this plane.
- Why, because you're scared to fly?
- Don't you get it?
That's when it happens,
when I'm really scared.
- So you're telling me that this is
some kind of fantasy world come to life?
- Sara, look around,
this isn't a fantasy,
it's a nightmare.
- I'm not gonna let us die!
- You're never gonna outfly it!
- We'll see. Hang on!
- Oh shit.
Shit... shit!
Another hit like that and we're dead.
- I told you, I told you, I told you...
- Are you really causing this?
Is this really because of you?
Then prove it.
Make that thing go away!
- I don't know how.
- Make it go away!
- I don't know how!
- Bruce...
Man is what he wills himself to be.
Sartre, right?
Stop being such a pussy
and face your fears.
Face your fears!
Bruce!
Bruce!!
Jesus...
it is you.
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray,
can anyone read me?
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday,
Yankee Zulu X-ray.
-... This is Lakeview Centre,
received your Mayday.
What is your emergency?
- I just got through to ground.
We're gonna make it.
- You didn't mean it, did you?
- Mean what?
- That kiss.
- I care about you, Bruce.
You know that.
Bruce.
Bruce!
- I can't help it.
- Yes, you can!
Oh, no!
Bruce! No!
Get us out of here!
- It's not that simple!
- Why not?
Just think us somewhere else!
- You don't understand, I've never made
anything good happen in my life.
What if I can't?
Sara!
Nooooo!!!
- Bruce!
- Sara!
- Bruce!!!
- Sara!!!!
- Your parents, Bruce!
Think of your parents!
- My parents?
- They wouldn't want you to die
like this, they'd want you to survive.
Don't you understand?
You can be with them again,
all you have to do is imagine it!
- Sara!
- Imagine it!
- Nooo!!!!
- What happened?
- I did it.
I thought us somewhere else.
- Oh no!
- Where the hell did he come from?
- Was that...?
- I think so.
- Did we just...?
- Yeah.
- If you're gonna do your thing...
now's the time.
- It's already done.
- Mom! Mom!
- I'm okay, sweetie.
Everybody gets one near miss, right?
- Do you think they made it?
- I hope so.
- Hi, I'm Sara.
- Bruce.
Dan4Jem,
ADMMX
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org