Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
I love love
I love being in love
I don't care
what it does to me
Sing I love love
I love being in love
I don't care
what it does to me
I love love
I love being in love
I don't care
what it does to me
These pills are fine
to pass the time 'til I find my new drug
We'll take our chances
we'll last a month
We'll never speak again
How I love being in love
May I help you?
Huh? No.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I'm just browsing.
- Thank you.
- So let me guess.
Big night tonight?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, actually. Actually, the biggest.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Menage a trois?
- Pardon me?
I'm kidding.
Oh, a menage a trois.
French for, "Who's that dude?"
So you're looking
for something for your girl?
Well, not just any girl, okay?
The most...
The most beautiful and incredible
and amazing and...
Well, girl I've ever met.
Okay. Well, if you have any questions,
my name is Claire.
Okay. Actually, yeah.
Does this come in red?
- I can check.
- Also, Claire, does it come any larger?
Much, much larger.
Oh, no.
Hey. Is she in there?
- Yeah, she's in there.
- Good.
How do I look?
I see your balls.
Are you crazy?
Come here. Come here. Up here, up.
- What's the matter with you?
- What?
This? This is the big idea?
Yeah. Yeah. She's gonna love it.
- She's gonna hate it.
- She's gonna love it.
- No, she's gonna hate it.
- Love it.
No, she's gonna hate it more than I hate it,
and I really hate it.
You know what your problem is, Ted?
You just...
You don't understand true love.
Oh, and you do?
I understand that there's a girl
that I love waiting for me in there.
And you know what? She loves me, too.
I still see balls.
Can I get you a drink
while you wait for your friend?
Hopefully, in a man's life,
you do this one time.
Well, I want my one time
to be unforgettable.
I want tonight to be a story Vanessa
and me will be telling our grandkids.
You almost done with that baby oil?
Yeah. That's it.
Get it in there. Soak those abs.
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Thanks, buddy.
- What's up, ladies?
- Oh, goodness.
There you go, beautiful.
I brought you some c-rations on the house.
Some what?
Oh, sorry. That's Special Forces talk.
Are you in the Special Forces?
That's not something
I'm at liberty to discuss.
Anderson, I sell cars.
My job is to close a deal.
- Trust me. This is not gonna close a deal.
- Give me the ring, Ted.
No. I can't let you do this.
- Give me the ring!
- No.
- Give me the ring, now!
Give me the ring!
Just give me the ring! I just want the ring!
I've got to propose!
Okay. Hey, watch the wings!
Watch the wings!
I'm not gonna lie to you, Vanessa.
Special Ops,
it's a deadly game.
But as a very brave person once remarked,
"Life is either daring or it's nothing. "
Do you know who that brave person was?
My personal hero, Helen Keller.
Helen Keller.
Excuse me, Vanessa.
I think table 16 needs more garlic knots.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention, please?
I am Cupid, god of love.
Dear God!
Shooter! Shooter! We got a shooter!
Down! Everybody, down!
Down! Down!
Anderson!
You know this perp?
He's my boyfriend.
I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
Anderson, get up! Get up!
You could have gotten yourself killed!
Vanessa, I...
I wrote you a poem.
"I am Cupid, god of love
"I come from skies far above
"Bringing love to all I see
"Now I have found some love for me"
Fag.
"And so I get on bended knee
"To ask, Vanessa, will you marry me?"
Vanessa?
Oh, my God. She's...
Nessy?
I stopped to think about
the bad times that I've had
It puts a smile on my face
Curled up with nothing to do
Why is the sun always out
when I'm feeling blue?
It must be you
Oh, it must be you
When I took
my first drink of alcohol
I saw the Angel of Death
floating over us all
With a smile on my face
I just wept
How does a grown man laugh
in the face of death?
It must be you
Oh, it must be you
Hey, you hungry?
Did I ever tell you what she smelled like?
- What?
- Dew drops.
- She was perfect.
- Nobody's perfect.
Okay. Like, you know how most people
have wrinkly knees?
Okay? Hers were perfectly smooth,
like billiard balls.
- You know what I used to call her?
- What?
- Billiard ball knees.
- You know what might be fun?
Not talking about your dead girlfriend.
Huh?
I still see her sometimes.
- Here?
- Just forget it.
You know, I'd like to, Anderson,
I really would,
but you won't shut up about it.
She's been dead twice as long
as you knew her. Get over it.
- I'm sorry, "Get over it"?
- Yeah.
How do you get over perfection?
You look around.
Maybe there's
another perfect somebody out there.
Here we go.
Don't talk to him like that.
- Eat that goddamn spaghetti.
This is just what the therapist
was talking about.
We're wasting enough money
on that therapist.
I don't believe you.
Who wanted to come here? Not me.
I am so sorry. What did you just do?
What did you do?
Satisfied? I looked around.
I'm just saying,
don't throw your whole life away
'cause you killed your girlfriend.
- Fiancee.
- Technically, she never said yes.
Anyway, I don't know
if you're gonna find anyone else
whose butt smells
like gumdrops or whatever,
but I know you won't unless you try.
So is that it? Is that it, huh?
You want me to try?
One time. That's all I'm saying.
- One time. I try, you get off my back.
- You have my solemn word.
Fine.
Fine, Ted. I'll try. I'll try.
Hey. Can I get you guys anything else?
That's what I'm talking about.
Back on the horse.
Is there anything else I can get for you?
Will you marry me?
Excuse me?
Stuart, you're flapping...
All right. Pigs? Three little pigs?
A banjo? And piggies?
Deliverance!
- Oh, my gosh! Like a machine.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, my God. Oh, you guys are so fast.
- That was great.
Okay. It's my turn,
and this is a really good one.
So I need you all to pay attention.
Especially you, mon amour.
Give me the little hand.
- Isn't he the cutest thing ever?
- Hey, I resent that.
Isn't it getting kind of late, you guys?
Oh, what's the matter, Cinderella?
You're not gonna turn into a pumpkin,
are you?
Do I know how to push her buttons,
or what?
I am pushing your buttons.
Honey, do your charade, okay?
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Aye, aye, Captain. Okay.
Oh, wait. We can't do this...
Incoming.
Here we go. Last one.
- Four words. First word.
- Me... Me...
- Shazam.
William! William! Shorter. Willie. Will!
- Will.
- Will. Okay.
- Second word. It sounds like...
- Second word. Sounds like...
- Rockette. Boot. Shoe.
- Shoe.
You.
Fourth word.
- Me, it's me again... Me?
- Me?
- Oh, it is "Me. " Okay.
- Will you blank me?
Hey, buddy, there's ladies present.
All right, well, you know,
that's just tasteless, Stuart,
- for God's sake.
- Sorry.
All right. Will you blank me?
Third word.
Saunter.
- Marry?
- Stuart, he's proposing.
Katie, will you marry me?
Yes! Yes! She says yes!
- Honey?
- Katie!
Katie!
Honestly, Katherine,
do you have any idea how embarrassing
that was for me last night?
I didn't say no, Mom.
I just said I needed to think about it.
What's there to think about?
That boy is a catch, and he's crazy
about you. God knows why.
Just tell me, what is it you want?
Because William is perfect.
For one thing, he's just about
the most attractive orthodontist
I think I've ever seen.
And he's incredibly romantic.
Mom, I know he's perfect.
I just need a little time.
Will you talk to her, Stuart?
Not to toot my own horn,
but William reminds me a lot of me
when I was younger.
Are you listening to your father?
He is not my father.
This man is more of a father to you
than your father ever was,
God rest his soul.
- Dad is not dead.
- He's dead to me, the son of a bitch.
- Don't talk about Dad that way!
- Don't you raise your voice to me!
- You're getting emotional, Lois.
- I am not getting emotional!
All right.
I am leaving this house in five minutes,
and if you want to be on that bus,
I suggest you pull yourself together.
Sometimes I wonder if you still love him.
Who?
- Dad.
- Are you crazy? Are you out of your mind?
Well, you must have loved him once.
Honey, I was 18 when I met your father
and about as dumb as a piece of ham.
What did I know about love?
All I knew was...
He was the hottest thing
that I had ever seen.
Oh, he looked like a panther,
a sex panther.
Sounds like love to me.
Well, there's a big difference between love
and mindless, animalistic, carnal lust.
And what do you have with Stuart?
What I have with Stuart is what I want
for you and William.
- A mature, stable relationship.
- But are you happy?
Of course I'm happy. I'm very happy.
Very, very happy.
No, no. Very happy.
Very happy.
- I gotta go. The bus is here.
- All right.
Very happy.
There she is. There's my beautiful girl!
Hey! Keep it down.
I will eat your head!
I will tear it off, shove it up your ass,
pull it through your mouth,
brush my teeth with it, and then eat it!
- I will eat it.
- Smitty!
I'm not finished. Eat it!
- Dad.
- What?
- Apologize to him.
- Oh, come on.
I'm serious, Dad. It's just rude. Now.
Do it now, Dad.
Hey, Dave. I'm sorry.
Smitty, I'm working
on my appeal over here.
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
You see, that's why
I love you so much, Baby Bear.
You got your mother's good heart.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
William asked me to marry him.
But that's good.
That's what you wanted, no?
Yeah.
No.
Oh, Dad, I don't know. I just...
I mean, how are you supposed to know
when you're with the right person?
Just listen to your heart, Baby Bear.
You'll know.
Hey, do you know what I do
when I'm feeling blue?
Yeah. You drink homemade toilet wine.
No!
Well, yeah.
But I also write in my gratitude journal.
And every day, I write about the things
that I have to be grateful for,
like you and your mother.
Oh, here.
"December 25th, Christmas Day.
"I am grateful that somebody finally
stabbed that cocksucker Rodriguez. "
Dad.
I'm gonna say yes.
Yes!
I mean, we get along so well, right?
He's so funny. He cracks me up, you guys.
I'm gonna say yes.
That's great. Right, Matador?
I think William is kind of a turd.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But he's like a turd
with a piece of candy in it.
Marriage isn't in our blood.
We're circus folk.
Gypsies roaming from big top to big top
on the open road.
You guys have been working in the diner
since I've known you.
Not in here, Katie. Not in here.
Gentlemen, observe.
Can I get you guys anything else?
Will you marry me?
- Excuse me?
- Will you marry me?
Seriously.
Think about it.
What could possibly be more romantic
than throwing away your entire life
and running off with some handsome,
dark-haired stranger
you spotted across a restaurant?
I'm sorry. He's had a lot of syrup.
- Okay.
- Okay, he's had a lot of syrup?
Okay, I'll marry you.
What?
Yes. Yes.
I'll marry you!
Jane! Jane! Will you cover for me?
Where're you going?
I'm getting married! To this guy!
Come on. Come on!
Go. Get out of here. I got the bill.
Oh!
Anderson.
- Katie.
- Katie. Hi.
Two kisses.
Big rig. Watch this.
Stick that arm up your ass!
Got a brand new roof
above my head
All the empty boxes
thrown away
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah. Yeah.
So years from now,
when we're celebrating
our 37th wedding anniversary
and one of our friends
asks us about our first date,
is this what we'll talk about?
I guess it is. Yeah. Okay.
And... And then I'll tell them
the funny part.
What's the funny part?
That after we talked about it,
you stepped in dog shit.
- Oh! I stepped in dog shit!
- Yeah.
Why didn't you warn me?
You could have warned me.
That would have ruined the story.
Ah, man. Can I borrow your...
Oh, God! Cut it out!
Okay, careful, careful.
I've never been up here before.
Yeah, it's a cool place to come if you want
to get an old refrigerator filled with vomit.
I was looking for one of those.
Yeah? Well, I think
it's two-for-one day, so...
Look what I've got.
Tetanus?
- This is stupid.
- What?
You know, this. Us sitting up here,
pretending we're doing something.
It's just stupid.
It is, right?
I mean, obviously
we're not getting married.
Obviously.
- Strangers don't get married.
- Well, in some cultures they do.
- They do?
- But not ours.
Not ours.
Other cultures, far-away cultures.
The Kalahari bushmen is one example.
- And my parents did. They did.
- They did?
My mom barely knew my dad,
and she got pregnant with me,
and they eloped
to this weird little place
called The House of Wedded Bliss
in Atlantic City.
The House of Wedded Bliss?
Yeah.
Doesn't that sound incredibly romantic?
Sounds like a bad Chinese takeout place.
Yeah, well, I mean, just because they did,
doesn't mean that we are, right?
You probably weren't even serious
when you asked.
Were you?
Of course not.
You see, that's what I'm talking about.
I mean, this whole thing is just...
It's stupid.
- Wait.
- I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait. What's happening?
I'm just such an idiot.
Are you crying?
- No.
- Why are you crying?
I am not crying.
It really looks like you're crying.
Yeah, well, I'm crying now.
Are you satisfied, you asshole?
Hey. Hey, hey.
Hey. Hey, you.
Hey! Hey.
Are you okay?
I can't remember the last time I did that.
I don't think I've ever done that.
- Do you want a tissue?
- No, I'm fine. I feel incredible.
Really?
Why is that?
- You sure you don't want a tissue?
- No, I'm fine.
Anderson, when you asked me
to marry you,
you probably picked the only girl
in the whole world that would say yes.
I don't think that's a coincidence, do you?
I don't know.
- Do you believe in fate?
- No.
Neither do I.
You see, this was meant to be.
Will you marry me?
You said yes?
- Yeah. Well, why not?
You know, I think this is exactly
what I need to get my life back on track.
I mean,
why can't two strangers get married?
- I don't know. Because it's retarded?
- Look, you said it yourself.
You said I need to get back out there
and meet people. Right? So...
Yeah, meet! Meet! Not marry!
Why can't you just date her for a while
like a normal human being?
Look, don't worry. Okay? It's not...
You know, it's not like
we're getting married today.
We talked about it,
and we decided to take things slow.
- So what's next?
- She's moving in with me.
I gotta go.
Okay. Well, good luck with that.
I don't care
whether you hear this
I don't care if I'm alone
here singing songs to myself
There's nobody else around,
around
Meet you up
at the Indian part of the town
The town's shut down,
the people left with their bags
Their kids so there's not
a sound, a sound
But I must get
from there to here
There's a small voice crying
on the other side of the river from here
It's too late
to phone her now
William, I have some weird news.
It's good news for me.
I can't marry you.
I'll explain everything later. I'm so sorry.
I love you... As a friend. Okay, bye.
Just a minute
close your eyes
If we settle
for this compromise I'll stay with you
The river looks
so good tonight
Can I leave a message for 99138?
I don't know
what's with your friend
Phone message, Smitty.
She said she'd had enough
of playing games
It's from my daughter.
She's getting married.
Oh, yeah?
It's too bad you're not gonna be there
to walk her down the aisle, big guy.
- What is this?
- I'm getting married!
- No, this.
- It's a diaphragm.
I know what it is. Not in front of...
Please. Please.
- It's her diaphragm.
- Stuart!
- Damn it!
- Jeez.
- Where are you going?
- I told you. I'm getting married.
- You said yes!
- Not to William.
Not to William?
His name's Anderson.
I met him a couple of hours ago.
A couple of hours ago?
What kind of... What about William?
What kind of name is Anderson?
- Use your head here, Katie.
- He's black, isn't he?
I have to go.
Don't you think
you're being a little impulsive?
Yes! That is exactly what I'm being.
And guess what? It feels great!
- You ready?
- Oh, my God.
Hi.
Hey, there, dude. You must be Anderson.
- No.
- Matador.
This is my friend, Matador.
He's just giving me a ride.
I like your Jew hat.
Bye, Mom. I'll bring him by
for you to meet him tomorrow!
- Can you see?
- No.
No problem.
You know, this happens all the time.
How can you see?
Just be patient!
This will clear up in a second.
Okay, slow down.
- What?
- Slow down.
Oh, my! Oh, my!
Oh, my!
I killed that fellow.
I killed that fellow with my car!
- Oh, my God, not again.
- Anderson?
Vanessa?
Anderson?
Am I dead?
You're just unconscious.
Does it hurt?
Not really.
Now does it hurt?
You're getting married?
No! No! No! We're not getting married.
We're just...
We're just moving in together.
I thought you loved me.
I do, Vanessa. I do.
I'll never love anybody but you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Of course.
Then dump her.
Promise me, Anderson.
I promise.
Touch my lightsaber, Luke.
Touch it!
- What is that? What is that?
- It's just ice.
Okay.
Hello.
Katie, would you like
to make the introductions?
I hit you with my car.
This is Matador.
Matador.
Here. I got you a small gift.
I didn't have time to wrap it.
It's a Discman.
This is my Discman.
Did you take this from my drawer?
Yes, I did.
Okay.
Matador, could you do me a giant favor?
Yeah.
Is there some way that you could not
press your balls into my shin?
- Can do.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Are you okay?
Well, I thought he was abrupt,
but I'll be fine.
Yeah, I think... I think I'll be okay.
Matador.
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry. Very good.
Okay.
Take care, now.
I will.
He seems nice.
- Does it hurt?
- No, it's fine.
- You're so brave.
- Listen. Listen, Katie...
- Hey, where's your bedroom?
- Bedroom?
Yeah. I need to put this somewhere.
- What's this?
- My clothes.
- Your clothes?
- Yeah, you know, for wearing.
Oh, clothes.
Right. I thought you said "cloves. " Cloves.
And I was like,
"Cloves, that's a weird thing to pack. "
Okay, yeah. You found the bedroom.
So, yup. So this... This is the bedroom.
This is the bedroom.
I should probably clean up a little.
Good. Good.
So listen, I was thinking about everything
and how great this is,
but it's all happening so fast,
and I was afraid
that maybe you thought it
was happening too fast.
That's what makes it so exciting.
Exactly. Exactly.
That's what I was exactly going to say.
Because personally,
I couldn't be more thrilled.
Well, you seem really nervous.
Really? No, no, no. I don't...
That's weird. I don't get nervous.
I just express joy by sweating on occasion.
- Who's Vanessa?
- Who?
You said "Vanessa"
right before you passed out.
- I did?
- Oh, is this her?
No. No, that's not her.
I don't know who that is.
That's... That picture came with the frame.
But you're in the picture.
Yeah, there I am, right there. I know.
That's because I used to do
some modeling when I was younger.
- Really?
- Yes, I did.
I did some picture frame modeling
back when that whole "regular guy" phase
was sweeping the picture frame
modeling industry.
- That is so cool.
- Yeah.
The telephone's ringing.
Should I get it?
No. No, no, no.
It's my mom. I'll call her back.
- Oh, should I say hi?
- That's okay.
No, really, it's weird.
I mean, I should say hi, right?
No, no. That's... I got it. I got it.
Hello, Mom? Hi. Hi!
Oh, same old, same old.
How are you guys?
If she wants to talk to me,
I'm here.
Yeah, listen. No.
Everything is... Everything is...
Everything is good.
Okay, sweetie.
Yeah.
I gotta go, Mom. I love you.
Yeah. Love you. See you tomorrow, then.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
How's Anderson?
Fine, I guess.
He says he has a surprise for us.
He's coming over tomorrow.
What's he doing tomorrow?
Coming.
He's what?
I can give you what you want
I can make
your heart beat short
I'm scared.
Give me that, little girl.
I'm just a little girl. I'm a little girl.
- Anderson?
- Just a minute! Just a minute.
I can be the sauce
you crave
I can spell
what you can't say
Chocolate flavored
love theme treat that treats you so mean
Covering your
nights and days
Let me give you
what you'd like
I can make your mouth
run dry
Drink me like a liquor,
c'mon and dip your dipper
Show me
what you're here for, guy
- Anderson? Anderson?
- Coming.
Okay.
Listen. Listen, Katie.
I think you're really neat. Okay, I do.
But I just...
I can't. I can't,
'cause I made a promise to somebody.
And...
"I think you're really neat"? God.
What you want
I can give you what you want
I can
Oh, God! I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry.
No, Anderson. It's okay.
Turn around.
So what did your mom say?
Oh, yeah. Well, she...
I was thinking that we could go over there
and meet them before we...
Get married?
If you want to put a label on it.
Great, 'cause I told my mom
we'd go over to visit her tomorrow, too.
Great. That's great.
I was thinking we could take a bus over
to my folks' house.
- I like buses.
- That's good. 'Cause it's a bus. It's a bus.
Minty.
Well, that's toothpaste for you.
That's just classic toothpaste.
Oh, God!
- It's in my eye! It hurts!
- I'm sorry. I swallowed some. Sorry.
It's really burning.
Did you wanna go in...
The bathroom's right there.
- Where?
- Yup, this way. Yes. Yeah, you got it.
Maybe I should go out
and get some saline solution.
No. I'm fine.
Yeah, but maybe I should go, you know,
get some saline
or eye drops or something.
No, really.
I'll go get some saline.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Okay. Slow down. What's the problem?
I think she wants to have sex with me.
I'm gonna call 911.
I'm so embarrassed.
I mean, I feel like such an idiot.
- Maybe you just came on a little strong.
- Oh, God.
A couple hours ago, she was moving in.
All your problems were solved,
rainbows were shooting out of your ass.
What happened?
Nothing. Nothing. She's great. She's great.
It's just...
What?
- What would Vanessa say? Huh?
- Oh, buddy.
I was just trying to be spontaneous,
you know?
He probably thinks I'm such a freak.
No. Trust me. You're not a freak.
Hold on. Help. Help. Help me.
I've got to go. He's here.
- Hi.
- Hi. Hi.
They were out of saline,
so I got you some Q-tips
and some zit cream.
So you can do with that what you please.
How's your head?
- Oh, sorry.
- No, it's okay.
My eye is fine.
Right. How's your eye?
- It's fine.
- Good.
Wow.
- Wowee.
- Wowee dowee doo.
Doowee wowie booby.
Well, I think we better get to bed.
I think it's time for...
Not... I mean, not that kind of bed.
Not that kind of bed.
I mean... I mean, like,
sleepy time. Sleepy bed.
'Cause...
'Cause I... You know.
'Cause your eye and my head and...
Well, if we have
any more physical contact,
I think one of us might actually die. So...
So the weekend
came and went
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
- It's all right.
- Go back to sleep. I'm sorry.
Sunday afternoon's
a memory
She was just lying there
Sleeping softly in a chair
Are you almost ready?
I told Mom we'd be there in,
like, half an hour.
She's gonna love you!
Fourth word!
You're holding hands.
You're with friends. You're skip...
Wizard of Oz! The Wizard of Oz!
Diving? The Greg Louganis Story?
Flashdance!
Airplane!
Him?
Her? When a Man Loves a Woman!
Sound of Music!
Philadelphia!
Deep Throat! Deep Throat!
Oh, sorry.
Okay. You know what?
You know what, dear?
We give up. Why don't you just tell us?
- That was The Apple Dumpling Gang.
- Oh.
It's not an easy one. So...
It was really good.
Thanks. Thanks. Thank you.
I'm sorry... Thanks.
- You're so good. Yeah. It was hard.
- I thought it...
- I thought it made sense.
- It was good.
- It was a tough one, so...
- Yeah.
And then a few years ago,
I was in a toy store and I had a thought.
What if there was a line of stuffed animals
specifically for Jewish children?
And that's when the Jewnicorn was born.
Listen.
Well, Anderson, what do you think?
Wow.
I think it's very...
Specific.
In a good way, of course.
So, Anderson, what is it you do?
Oh, Anderson's
between jobs right now, Mom.
- Oh, he's between jobs?
- Yeah.
I see.
You know, maybe you'd like
to go downstairs to the basement
and see where Stuart makes
all his little toys.
- Mom, no. Why?
- Well, yeah. Yes, yeah.
Oh, I think he'd be interested.
Especially if you like googly eyes.
- As a matter of fact, I do like googly eyes.
- Okay.
That does it. Follow me, young man.
Santa's not the only one with a workshop.
- Wow.
- What do you think?
- What is this?
- Jewla-Hoop.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org