Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Yeah, I know that...
and for every 9 stocks
that fell, 8 advanced...
stop acting like it's
fucking Black Friday.
Yeah... alright, well then,
why don't you go back with that...
huh, what's his name? That... huh, asshole
who talked you into going on with Enron.
Yeah...
you know what?
Fuck you, too.
Della?
Della, honey?
What?
What's the matter?
Honey, you wanna tell me
what it is you do all day?
- What do you mean?
- Well...
Honey,
look at the goddamn place, okay?
There's kid-shit all over the place,
wall to goddamn wall.
We do the best...
we do the best we can, I mean...
The best you can? Why don't you
just do what I tell you to do?
- Stop.
- Can I ask you a question?
- What in the hell happened to you?
- Stop.
You don't even try
to put yourself together anymore.
I don't know what you
want me to say? We've got kids.
Look, I want you to hear this,
I want you to keep the house clean!
Oh... god.
Terry got an "A" in math.
- Goddamn it, Della!
- Don't.
- Don't what?
- No! It's her favorite doll.
- What?
- You'll have to fix her.
I have to what?
- I will have to what?
You'll have...
That's all you worry about.
Is these kids.
I will have to what? Would you look
at me when I'm talking to you?
Stop it!
Why don't you stop it? And don't you
tell me what the fuck to do! Okay?
- Stop it.
- You understand me?
Do you hear what I'm saying to you?
Don't break my arm.
Don't tell me what to do!
Why you fuck with me? And you do
that every fucking time?
So, what're we supposed to do now?
I'm... um...
I'm out of wrapping paper.
It's okay.
Come on, it's okay.
Okay, it's okay!
How are you doing?
I want a Nintendo Wii
for Christmas, mom.
It's only a few hours
till Christmas.
- Can I get an American Girl doll?
- Oh, guys.
You wrote your letters
to Santa already.
I don't think another letter
will make it to the North Pole.
- We will be okay, right?
- We're always okay.
We're always okay.
- No matter what happens.
Okay.
Alright...
Okay... I'll be back
in just a little while, okay?
- Okay.
- Alrighty.
Now, promise me one thing, that...
Listen... listen, hey, you... you...
you have to brush your teeth.
And I want you in the bed
after your treat, all right?
- Okay
- Okay...
I'll see you later.
Mom!
I made a secret drawing for you.
- Oh, I love your drawings.
- Don't look at it yet!
Okay. I'll save it for later.
How about that?
Bye, sweetie.
And you can kiss my ass, Kenneth.
Cellular 411 connect.
How may I direct your call?
- Spring Street Learning Academy, please.
- Hold, while I connect you.
Thank you for using
411 Information.
Learning Academy.
Meghan speaking.
Hi, Meghan.
It's Della Myers.
Hi.
Are you calling about Spanish?
It's been cancelled.
No, no, I knew about that.
It's about next week's
mechanics class.
Would you just pass on to Mike,
that I won't be there just this once?
No problem.
- I'll make sure he gets that.
- Great.
- Hi. Della?
- Hey, what's up, Cassie?
I'm over at the mall. What is
it we need to get for Pilates?
One of those rubber bands.
I'm headed over there myself.
Do yourself a favor. Turn around.
It's hell over here.
Hey, my cell's dying.
You know, I... I... damn!
You know, I left... I left
the charger in the other car.
Silly you. Let me pick you up
something. Save you the trip.
- No, I mean...
- Are you sure?
No, no... it's okay.
Cassie... um, can we meet...
huh, for a drink?
You still there?
Your phone is breaking up.
Damn.
You're kidding me.
My God!
Damn it!
Damn!
Come on.
You think you're gonna
take my spot, think again!
I've been waiting now
for 3o minutes! It's Christmas!
Excuse me. You know where
I can find a parking space?
I mean this is ridiculous!
Ma'am, there is absolutely
nothing close by.
Even the valet's backed up.
- You might wanna try further up.
- Where? Over there?
Yeah...
Now, please keep it moving.
Let's go. Come on.
Go!
Come on!
Jerk!
What a jerk!
Over there.
Smile.
Good girl.
Merry Christmas!
- Would you like to try Chanel No. 5?
- No, thank you.
We're breaking up,
you hear me?
- Can I help you with that?
- No.
No, I was just looking.
Thank you.
Hi.
Could I have a hot tea, please?
And one chocolate biscotti.
Huh, milk with dark chocolate?
No, just the tea.
Name?
Oh, Della.
Two "L"s.
2 dollars and 65 cents.
Thank you.
Della?
Is that you?
Lynn? Lynn Monroe.
- Hi.
- I haven't seen you since college!
Right.
You married that handsome jock
and we never heard from you again.
You live around here?
We just bought this divine house
in Pleasant Valley. You know it?
Yes, I do.
It's perfect for the kids.
They practically walk to school.
We've got a great backyard.
We're thinking
of putting a pool in it.
They'll love that!
Enough about me.
How are you?
Fine.
I have two children,
Terry and Tammi... Twins.
Oh...
We're celebrating tonight.
David just been promoted.
So I... had to buy this
gorgeous black teddy.
Oh...
It is... It's gorgeous.
- It's been nice talking to you.
- You too.
I've got to get my hair done.
- See you later.
- Yes.
See you.
Mitch!
Here you are.
- Which one would you like?
- That one.
That one?
That's the one?
- Thanks.
- Thank you. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas!
- Hello.
- Hi.
21 dollars and 69 cents, please.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's been declined.
Do you have another card?
Um... no, I don't.
Um...
Seventeen...
twenty-one...
There.
It's Christmas Eve,
and the mall is now closed.
Happy Holidays, everyone.
This day is borne a Savior
Of a pure, virgin bride
To free all who trust in Him
From Satan's power and might
Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Oh, tidings
Of comfort and joy
Shit.
Shit. What now?
Excuse me?
I've got a gun.
How's about I aim it
at your pussy first?
Why don't you just back the car up?
That's not gonna happen.
What... what're you doing? Or what're
you playing? I don't know this game.
Trust me, it's not a game.
That's right, how about you
shut up, bitch, and eat a dick?
When you're done eating, we're gonna
staple your bitch-mouth and close it.
Right, Chuckie?
"Chuckie"? Is that for real?
At least your parents
had a sense of humor.
I don't have any parents.
I named myself.
Do you have a beef
with us, honey?
Because slipping an insinuating
note underneath my wipers...
is an invitation to war
to me and my soldiers.
You had to park
like an asshole now...
we wouldn't be
standing here, would we?
- Watch your mouth, lady!
- Get away from me!
You know you're just digging
your grave deeper.
- Where you going?
- Fuck you!
- No way, fuck you.
- No, fuck you!
Is any trouble here, ma'am?
Not if these punks
move their car!
Yeah, what's the deal, Barney Fife?
Okay, boys. Let's back the car up
and let the lady out.
How's that sound, squirt?
No, we're not in the mood.
In fact...
why don't you mind
your own fucking business...
go direct some traffic
or something, huh?
I'm gonna make this my business.
Now, why don't you kids, pile back
into your piece-of-shit car...
and get the fuck out of my mall?
Didn't you hear what I said?
You hear me?
You hear me, daddy?
Get the fuck outta here!
- Put the gun down.
- Get the fuck outta here!
- Put the gun down!
- I said, get the fuck outta here, bitch!
- You want me to put it down?
Make me, bitch!
I said make me...
- Shit.
- Motherfucker.
She's getting away!
Fuck, man! She's probably on the
phone with 5-0 already, Chuckie!
What the fuck!
We're going down for this shit!
Don't worry about it, nigga.
Don't worry! Don't worry!
Don't fucking call me "nigga", Chuckie.
You ain't earned the right.
That goes for all you niggers.
Huey, Huey, take it easy, we got it.
Take it easy.
We got it!
The world's like this.
Come on, get in, get in the car!
Now.
Move over, Thomas!
Come on! Move!
- The cop went down hard.
- Goddamn it, Thomas. Shut up!
My God.
Oh, God.
Hell, no.
- Damn!
- What?
My new Keds they're all dirty, man!
Get up there and push!
The car's got nowhere else to go, Chuckie,
the road ends just up ahead.
There's nothing but half build
houses and trees.
Ditch the car, man.
We've got a witness on the loose.
Trust me.
You won't hear a peep outta little
miss red, after tonight, alright?
She's going down, execution style.
What if she's gone already?
She's not gone.
There's no place for her to go.
Damn. She took out that barrier.
It's gonna be impossible to
find her, even if she is around.
Come on, guys. Let's go!
Maybe we can hotwire the truck.
I think, I'll find you now, cunt!
Well, we're caught up with them things,
like... like in a soap opera.
We need to just bail, blast out of town,
act like we was never even around.
- Vingh, get over here.
- How much "Kill" you been smoking?
Come on, man. No one cares
about a fucking Rent-A-Pig!
He's just collateral damage
to the people at the mall.
She's the only witness!
Come on, if we hit the road
right now...
we could be miles away
before they find you.
We could be sipping cold beer
swimming in the Atlantic,
just like you promised me.
Huey, come here.
Come here.
Remember how I broke
you outta that home?
I was there for you, right?
I was there.
You trust me, right?
- Right?
- Yeah.
All we gotta do is find that bitch...
and we're outta here, I promise. okay?
That's it.
There's her Ford!
Somebody tell her mom
to lay out her black dress.
Why? Is she dead?
No, I looked,
she went through her trunk.
She's here.
She's hiding somewhere.
She left her purse.
It's all in here. Her cell phone.
Where are you?
- Her battery gave out.
- We're gonna find you!
There she is!
Go that way! That way!
Fuck!
- You see her down there?
- No, man.
- She must have gone around.
- She vanished.
Check each one of these houses.
Split up. Spread out!
Della!
We know who you are!
You can't hide, honey.
We're not gonna give up,
till we find you, Della.
You're trapped, Della.
We're gonna find you!
Where's Little Red Riding Hood?
You all hear that?
Check the house next door!
Move it!
Yeah.
Ah'ha...
There she is!
- Hey there, we got you.
- You're dead, bitch.
Time to say goodbye.
Hey!
Shh...
You hear that?
Did you hear that?
The sound of the waves!
You hear that? Sounds good, right?
Yeah, Chuckie.
Sounds great.
Don't worry.
When we're done with you, we'll send
you back in your junk to mister...
You won't play nice?
You fucking wanna play?
Back off! Hold back!
Give me a minute.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
You okay?
Chill out.
You all right?
Hey, settle down!
Settle down!
You all right? Settle down.
You must be wondering,
how we know your name?
You messed up, Della.
You left your purse in the car.
Give me that.
Your photo
doesn't do you justice.
He's right.
- You look better in person, ma'am.
- You do.
You look good.
You're not gonna
need it anymore.
What's in that box, Della?
Huh?
What's in the box?
What's in the box, girl?
What's up, Chuckie? Do you think
she's carrying some cash?
Some jewelry or something?
I don't know.
Maybe she cashed in
her life savings.
Planning on running away?
Start a new life?
Is that it, Della?
You got enough scratch
in there to buy us off?
Huh?
Open the box.
Open the box!
- Open it!
- Okay.
Why don't you take the box.
We're gonna kill her anyway.
No...
I'll open up the box.
You know what, man?
She ain't got nothing.
Just take that pussy
and get going.
I got her!
Go down here!
Look out, Huey!
- What the fuck, nigga?
- Shut up!
- What, Chuckie?
- I said, shut up!
Don't use the N-word.
You ain't representing.
Huey?
- What did you do?
- What'd you mean?
- Yeah...
- Stop fucking around.
- Hey!
- Huey?
- What's up, brother?
- Please, forgive me.
Quit goofing around.
Huey?
Hey!
Hey, Huey.
What's up?
Oh, Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Huey?
- Huey?
- Hey, man, come on!
What the fuck did you do?
Get off him!
- I didn't kill him.
- Huey?
You fucking
stepped on his face, fucker!
Don't fucking touch me!
- I didn't kill him! She did.
- Get the fuck off!
God! Huey!
- I'm gonna get that bitch!
- You let her go!
You piece of shit!
Where the fuck is she?
Fuck.
Della!
I guess you are right
When we talked in the heat
There's no room for the weak
No room for the weak
Where will it end?
This is the room
The start of it all
They're talking to you
I remember it all
I've seen the night
Filled with blood and pain
And the bodies obtained
What're you doing?
It's a tribute.
A gesture.
Where will it end?
That'll wake up every
fucking cop in Podunk county!
It's for him.
It's for Huey.
I didn't mean it, Huey.
What did you say?
What?
I... I didn't mean to kill him.
Get away from him.
Get the fuck away from him!
Get away from him!
Get away! Get the fuck away!
- Get away!
- Fuck you!
I'm gonna fucking get you!
Do you hear me, Della?
God.
MOMMY WE LOVE YOU
Della!
Della?
- Wait.
- Huh?
It's "Bulgari".
- What's "Bulgari"?
- It's a perfume, dude.
It smells more
like that No. 5 shit.
- "Chanel".
- No, it's "Bulgari".
My dad's bitch bathes in it.
It's blood.
It's her blood.
Maybe she's hurt.
This way.
Go, go, go!
Watch out, dude.
Look out!
Damn!
- Oh, shit!
- What happened?
I stepped in the fucking stream!
- That is raw.
- Who cares, man?
Nobody gives a shit
if we live or die.
Quit playing with the fucking flashlight.
We are stumbling around in the dark!
He who finds it, shines it, Chuckie.
- Let's go!
- Where the hell is she?
- Shut up and move it!
- Damn!
Let's go, guys. Come on!
There she is!
Don't let her get away!
Huey?
Is that you, Huey?
I saw him
in those trees, right there!
Sure you did.
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna get you now, bitch!
You're ain't putting
anything over on me!
You fucking bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Time's up, you bitch.
God!
Thomas!
Shhh...
Quiet.
Thomas is gone, Chuckie.
I can feel it.
He's probably got her strung up
on her Penada by now.
There's something over here.
Looks like a body.
It's a tree stump,
you dumb Wonton.
Thomas...
She's gonna kill both of us too.
We're all gonna die here.
No gun can kill
a spirit gone bad.
She's gone bad.
Gone bad.
I'm gonna get this girl.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Where are you, God?
Where are you? Where are you?
All I wanna do
is see my babies!
Where are you?
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck!
Over there, Chuckie!
You're going down!
Slow down, bitch.
- Fuck off.
- Get outta my way, Vingh!
Get up!
- Get up Vingh!
- She's going now!
I don't feel so good, Chuckie.
I think I got hypothermia.
You'll be fine.
It ain't natural how she
keeps getting away every time.
Let's get this over with.
You go up there.
I'll cover you.
I ain't going up there without
a gun. End of story.
I never pegged you for a pussy.
Even when Thomas called it,
I always defended your ass.
No one ever called me a pussy.
She couldn't weight more than 120.
If you'd fuck her,
you could break her in half.
- Thomas never called me a pussy!
- Okay, fine.
You don't wanna go? Don't go.
I'm going up, I'm gonna go get
this bitch for Thomas, for Huey.
If you go up.
I'm gonna go around the side.
On power...
No limits.
Vingh?
Della?
It's just you and me left now.
I saw a little trail
of your blood back there.
You must be hurt.
I'm hurting, too.
You busted my collarbone.
I know you can hear me.
I can smell your sweat.
I can smell your blood.
I know you're close.
After what went down tonight,
you and me got a special bond, Della.
You might as well come out now.
You want a cigarette?
I'll save one for you,
for when you decide to come out.
You are one tough bitch!
And that is hot.
Well, well.
And they're really cute.
Twins, huh?
A woman's purse can
tell her whole life story.
You sure you don't want
a cigarette now, huh? Della?
Honey?
Now I know where they live.
Maybe I'll stop by and say hi.
No... No...
I figured that'd help
to find your voice.
Don't worry.
I wouldn't hurt them.
It's wrong to hurt kids, right?
The game's over, Della.
You won.
You took him from me, Della.
He was like my little brother.
All he ever wanted to do
was see the ocean.
But he never got to see it.
No, he never got to go.
They're all gone now.
Let's see here.
Monday, Pilates.
Tuesday, Spanish.
Wednesday, Mechanics?
Thursday, Friday...
Face it, Della.
You're no suburban housewife.
You bought into the big lie.
You even tried to live it.
Husband...
house...
security...
every woman's dream.
But not yours, Della.
You know there's no
such thing as security.
I reckon I know what you've been
dreaming about, Della.
What you've been aching for...
all these lonely years.
The wind in your hair.
The dirt of life
between your fingers.
Taking what you want from life.
Right, Della?
Don't tell me you
haven't thought about it.
It's in your blood.
I bet your husband
doesn't treat you right, does he?
He takes you for granted.
You can't go back to that, Della.
You don't wanna go back to that.
Let's go pick up your kids.
Right now.
And we'll get rid of him.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Della!
It's okay.
Come here.
Hell of a night, huh?
Hey! Hey!
Close your eyes.
You're amazing, Della.
So beautiful.
You've been a bad girl.
I don't care.
You're a bad girl.
Fuck me.
You can count on me
Please have snow and mistletoe
And presents under the tree
Christmas Eve will find me
Where the love light gleams
I'll be home for Christmas
If only in my
Dreams
You wanna tell me where in the
hell you've been all night, honey?
Don't ever call me that again.
What?
You can't even take
your shoes off at the door?
The Japanese do it!
I do it.
I see you got wrapping paper.
What'd you get me?
What did you get me at the mall?
Nothing.
In every dream home
A heartache
And every step I take
Takes me further from heaven
Is there a heaven?
I'd like to think so
Standards of living
They're rising daily
But home, oh, sweet home
It's only a saying
From bell-push to faucet
In smart-town apartments
The cottage is pretty
The main house a palace
Penthouse perfection
But what goes on?
What to do there?
Better pray there
Open-plan living
Bungalow ranch-style
All of its comforts
Seem so essential
I bought you mail order
My plain-wrapper baby
Your skin is like vinyl
The perfect companion
You float in my new pool
Deluxe and delightful
Inflatable doll
My role is to serve you
Disposable darling
Can't throw you away now
Immortal and life-size
My breath is inside you
I'll dress you up daily
And keep you till death sighs
Inflatable doll
Lover ungrateful
I blew up your body
But you blew my mind
Oh, honey
Dream home heartaches
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org