Back! Get back!
Spray!
Get off!
Hurry!
Run!
Okay. Pull him up!
Pull him up!
Come on.
Get this to the lab. And hurry!
Move!
Let's go.
509, unpack, and help him.
502, the computer,
and you check with the team.
Yes, sir.
Get ready.
Target is approaching!
Here. Get down there!
What's this stuff?
Can't move!
Come on, move it!
Let's go.
Keep moving!
Come on.
Ok. You get up here.
Attention!
What's your name?
Don't know, sir!
Where are you from?
Good. No names, no background.
But highly disciplined.
Mission is over, go have some fun.
Thank you, sir.
Ok. Dispose your weapons,
dispose your equipment.
523.Yes.
Go! Collect. Go!
To the main helicopter. Go!
Go! Move it, go!
Ok. Dismiss.
Sorry, sir.
So sorry, I’ve to do this.
Don't move.
Sorry soldiers,
we've got only two parachutes.
What the hell is going on?
Have a nice flight, bye.
Let me go.
What are you up to do?
Say it.
Here's the control. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Jacky Chan,
one of our best agents in Hong Kong.
Is also missing in the African action.
The three men they hijacked
are the scientists responsible.
For the comet research project recently
launched by the African state.
Lights!
We have a serious situation on our hands.
The operation was carried out
with clinical precision.
Using united states air force helicopters.
They seized the meteorite fragments
along with the three scientists.
And until now their
whereabouts are unknown.
If they knew the transport schedule.
Someone must have leaked the information.
How many C.I.A.
Staff knew about this project?
I know where you're heading
with this, Norman.
And I don't like it.
How can you be so sure it
wasn't one of your own people?
Why the hell would my guys
break into a hangar.
They already have access to and
steal their own aircraft?
Because it's a perfect cover
and no one would suspect them.
And remember, general.
The C.I.A. Pulled out of
south Africa over a year ago.
Only the essential staff remain.
Right now, our first concern.
Should be the retrieval of
the scientists and the fragments.
Agreed. There could be serious
military ramifications.
If the wrong people get a
hold of this formula.
We've got to find out who's
behind this pulling the strings.
Agent Morgan.
Yes, sir.
You used to head up our
south African operation.
You know the terrain,
you know the locals.
Take 3 agents and hop
the next flight over there.
I want to see positive results.
And fast.
Consider it done, sir.
Thank you, terry.
Bye.
General Sharman.
Hello, Norman.
I hear you're retiring a few days.
Yes, I am.
Congratulations on your retirement,
general Sharman.
Thank you.
I bet you're going to miss being
in the middle of all the action.
Norman, I'm going to take that
fat pension check of mine.
And head for my favourite fishing hole.
I want a black op assigned to this case.
Are you saying
we can't trust our own people?
Better safe than sorry.
Shall I select them
from Washington or.
From one of the outside branches?
Outside.
Sir, Mr. White is here.
Thank you. Send him in.
And tell them to
report to me directly.
Yes, sir.
Your plan worked,
mission completed.
What's wrong with him?
How is he?
He's just woken up.
My friend!
You gave us quite a scare.
We're happy you've woken up.
Welcome to our land.
Where am I?
How did I get here?
These men found you in the mountains.
Now, I want to know,
where do you come from.
And how did you get here?
I don't know your language.
Does anybody speak English?
I am the chief. Me. The chief.
And who are you?
What is your name?
Who am I?
His name is who am I
Your name is who am I?
Who am I?
Who am I
Who is he?
Hello.
Hey! Looks like you're
getting better, my man.
I knew he would.
What are you doing
on this search, sir?
Langley must be serious
about finding these guys.
They're traitors.
They've stolen a discovery.
Which could keep our nation on top.
In the 21st century.
Yes, sir.
Baba.
Who am I, we have seen a
miracle over the mountain.
There was iron that had been burnt.
We buried 8 bodies wearing
same clothes like yours.
You mean come with you? Go?
Yes. Let's go!
Go!
Look at that!
Yvirorich, Russian.
Jakol, Israel.
Hans, German.
Thailand.
Tachi, Japan.
Korea.
Who am I, come quickly! Come!
I'm sorry. I don't know.
What are you saying?
See! There it is.
The fire I told you about.
A light!
I can go! I can go!
Yes! I can go!
When we found you.
You were wearing the same clothes.
Am I right?
Yes. We wear the same clothes.
Eleven done one too many.
Baba. Never play with
dead people's belongings.
I know this is bad luck
for your culture.
I'll go on alone.
Thank you.
Go well!
Baba.
Can I borrow your compass?
Can I take it?
I bring back, I promise.
I promise.
Please come back soon.
I will miss you.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Take care, my friend.
You will succeed!
Somebody! Help us!
Are you okay?
We're over here! Help!
Look! Somebody! Help us!
Oh, my god!
Get away from him!
Stop eating my brother,
you animal!
Leave us alone!
Don't move!
Don't move! You know this?
This is a gun!
You know, I can bang you!
You know, I can shoot you!
I can bang you, you know?
I know karate! Karate!
Medicine!
It's medicine!
My brother!
Your brother?
You're helping my brother!
You understand English?
Say something.
Those medicine make my mouth numb.
You speak French?
I understand a little, do you?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I don't understand your language.
But, is my brother okay?
Is he all right?
Amazing!
You navigate, and work the G.P.S., ok?
You want to drive?
But do you know how to drive?
I think I better, you know
Nine o'clock. Turn this way!
Okay. Just go straight ahead.
Aiji, how are you feeling?
Feeling better. I.V. Is helping.
Good!
Please help us! We need a doctor!
Look! Here's the driver!
Back a little bit! Back!
He's very lucky.
The natural herbs on his
leg neutralized the poison.
And that coconut I.V... The only people
that use it are elite military units.
Who applied it?
Here.
That's him over there.
Amazing. Very talented native!
Say again? What?
Give us a story!
Where are you going?
What?
What's he on about?
Oh, it's okay. Speak to him.
He understands English.
One of them is still alive.
What?
He's all over the local paper.
I want to know if any of
the others survived.
I want every one of them liquidated.
Including this one.
That's a bit difficult with these,
C.I.A. Boys scout on my tail.
That's not your problem, Morgan.
We've other people to take care of that.
You just find him.
Who am I?
Yes.
I'm Christine spaak.
I work for the south African tribune.
I saw you on TV...
What a great story! That was!
I want to do an in depth article on you.
Huh?
I want to do an article on you.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm very busy right now.
Maybe some other day.
But you don't understand!
You're a hero!
Everybody wants to know who you are!
They do?
So do I
Who am I
Excuse me.
Wait! The article. Wait!
Wait, wait!
Hi, who am I
Don't you want to be a hero?
Everybody wants to know
what happened in the rally.
Christine. Reporter.
How's your brother?
Oh, he's going to be fine.
And the doctor's ready to see you.
I think she wants to interview you.
Oh? So you're the journalist? Yeah?
You know my name? My name is yuki.
It's Y ­ U ­ K ­ I
Our x­rays show that you experienced
a severe blow in this area.
It's very sensitive.
It controls your reason,
logic and memory.
That's why you're feeling confused.
I'm not mixed up!
But if I am,
is there any cure?
That's what they all want.
There is no immediate cure.
Why don't you contact the police?
Perhaps missing persons will have some
information that will jog your memory.
So where are you going now?
I'm going to the police station.
The police station?
Yes.
I'll see you later then.
Yeah. Bye.
Did it work?
Do you remember anything?
What do you think you're doing?
This is a hospital!
I was just helping my patient.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir.
Agent lee, C.I.A
C.I.A?
Our superior would like to speak with you,
just a moment.
Nothing serious. Just a quick chat.
Would you mind coming with us?
Thank you.
Feel free to use this room.
It's all yours.
Are you looking for me?
Yes, I am.
Who are you?
Have we meet before?
Not that I recall.
Morgan, C.I.A
Chief operative, southern Africa.
Pleased to meet you.
Have I done something wrong?
Do you know about my past?
Yes, I do.
I know you came out of the desert.
I know you lost your memory.
And I believe you can help us.
With a highly classified investigation.
Me?
Are you sure you saw eight graves?
Yes, I'm sure.
And a skeleton hanging from a tree?
Yes. From a parachute.
Good. This information could be
highly valuable to us.
Of course we'll have to verify it.
And remember, this is top secret.
Not a word to anyone.
I mean, no one.
Yes, of course.
Mr. Morgan, if you find out
anything else about me.
Please let me know
Sure. I'll be in touch.
Thank you.
Very soon.
Mean anything to you?
What?
Good. Keep well.
Close, but no cigar.
It's not him?
No. Striking resemblance though.
Mr. Morgan, wait.
If I remember anything,
how can I contact you?
You have a business card?
I'm sorry. I don't.
Here. You can use mine.
No!
Use this. It's better.
The C.I.A. Will put
you through immediately.
It's a phone card.
You can use it anywhere in the world.
Thank you.
The poor guy can't remember a thing.
So put him out of his misery.
I'll make sure he doesn't enjoy
the African sun. Leave it to me.
Get to work, and running!
We're at a very delicate stage of testing.
The process should be gradual.
I can't guarantee.
And I can't guarantee
your family's safety.
Now get it started!
Work!
Activate the accelerator!
All set!
How can a tiny fragment
power up a whole city?
You don't understand the
power of this fragment!
You! Keep working!
Initiating bombardment!
Watch the levee!
What's the flow rate?
Forty thousand joules and climbing!
It's working! It's working!
Yeah!
Yes!
Look out!
Go! Check it out!
What's going on?
The voltage is too high!
Abort! Abort!
Don't abort! Keep going!
We told you it was too soon!
The core's expanding!
Come on!
Move it!
Quick!
Let's go.
Oh, my god!
Move it!
What was that?
I don't know. Let's take a look.
Officer! Officer!
Officer!
Sergeant actually!
Sergeant. What about my case?
I've been waiting two hours.
I'll get to you when I can.
Everybody is waiting!
The power station has just blown up,
and it's chaos everywhere!
What are you doing
standing in front of me?
If you're a missing person,
what are you doing here?
Have you seen a doctor yet?
I've already seen the doctor, officer.
Sergeant!
Look, have a seat.
As soon as we have sorted out
the problem with computers.
You'll be first on my list.
Okay?
Pullen.
What?
Yes, sir.
More coffee?
No, thank you. Five is enough.
I insist.
Thank you.
What am I waiting for?
Computers.
Thanks for popping in.
I've been dying to meet you.
What's going on?
Internal security!
I've got a couple of questions,
I want to ask you.
Go!
You two stay.
The rest of you come with me.
We have the suspect. Keep guard.
Get me the stuff.
Have a seat.
28th of march, you and your group.
Spent the night in this
deserted exhibition hall.
On the 29th,
your friends disappeared.
On 30 march, 3 very important scientists
from my country were kidnapped.
And their whereabouts is still
a mystery where have you taken them?
Now listen, my friend.
We witnessed five guys.
And the scientists at the power station.
Then, mysteriously it blew up.
Now if you're not a terrorist.
Why the hell did you blow it up?
Who are you working for?
I don't know
Now on the day that our
scientists were kidnapped.
We discovered extremely high-Tech.
Lethal weaponry.
The likes of which we've never
been seen in Africa.
Now only a first
world country has got the money.
And the technology to make
something like that.
So, I want to know from you,
my friend, who are you working for?
The Japanese, the Chinese,
or the Americans?
Or maybe somebody else?
And tell me, eleven done one too many.
What does it mean?
I don't know who saved my life.
But I thank you.
Yvirorich, Russian.
Jakol, Israel.
Hans, German.
And you, what's your name?
I'm Paul, France.
Muhammad, I'm Malaysian.
Yubicha, Thai.
Tachi, Japan.
Dick sing, Korea.
My name is¡­
Gentlemen, what a great combination
we've got here.
Who are you?
You want to know who I am?
I want to know who I am.
We found 54 different passports.
That makes 6 for each of you. Why?
Where are your friends?
Who are your friends?
Well, there's no point trying
to cover for your friends.
And don't you think you're in deep trouble now,
you ain't smelt nothing yet?
Talk to me. Now!
They're all dead.
Quite a tough guy!
We know about your special training.
But we've got special ways
to make tough guys like you crack.
I'm waiting.
I told you, it's no use.
I lost all my memory.
With this attitude,
you're going to lose more than just your memory.
Get my drift? Book him.
On terrorism, espionage.
...and attempted murder.
If any of his friends arrive,
I'd like to have a little chat with them.
Let's go, smart ass!
What's happening in here?
You idiots! He was handcuffed! That way!
Go around the back!
How did he do this?
Don't just stand there.
we're losing him!
Thank you, I'll be back.
He's on his way in.
Room 1954
- Certainly, sir
- Thank you.
Who Am I, Christine, South African Tribune.
Remember me?
Here, take one of my cards.
I finally found you!
It's amazing how hard it
is to track you down.
My editor's been asking.
Excuse me. Could you do me a favor?
My taxi's waiting outside.
Can you pay for it?
Then the interview. Okay?
OK, no problem. But remember the deal.
The interview as soon as I get back.
I trust you.
Check her out.
Thank you.
Police, step aside, please.
Police?
I didn't even see your I.D!
He's gone that way!
What did you give him?
My card. I told you I'm a reporter.
I'm doing a story on him.
Sure. Story. Right.
Come in, come in.
What's going on?
What?
Go! Go! Go!
Stop!
Start the car!
How?
I'll shift the gears!
What?
What's going on?
Come in!
Wait! Are you crazy?
Slow down, come on! I'm not in yet!
Come on, move it, get on!
Third, fourth gear.
Which gear you run?
I don't know
Look out!
Watch out!
Be careful!
You stop messing the gear!
Find a better road!
Let me.
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, no! We can't move!
Do you know how to drive?
What do you expect?
I only have one arm.
Move, I drive.
We're stuck!
Don't worry, I can figure out.
Do something.
They're right behind!
Back to the car.
Car 54, in pursuit.
- Hey! Watch out!
- I'm driving.