Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
- What time did you get back?
- You don' t want to know.
Was it worth it?
Did he sign the contract?
- Yes.
- What a genius. How did you do it?
I did it the old-fashioned way.
I begged.
Good morning, Roy and Mary.
What time' s my doctor' s appointment?
I had no idea you had one.
- Coffee, Roy?
- Yeah. Are you sick?
- A wolf bit me.
- I just asked.
- Are you going to Alden' s party?
- Probably.
He invites everybody over to let
them know if they still have a job.
You have no appointment.
But he' ll see you before 12.
If you get the axe tonight,
I go with you.
- So do I.
- Listen, you need your pay cheques.
I forbid you to take any action
if I' m fired.
Right. Maude Waggins
is waiting in your office.
I cannot write for a conglomerate.
Protect me.
Raymond Alden isn' t a conglomerate,
he' s a billionaire.
And I' m not sure if I' m going
to be here after the takeover.
You' re the senior editor.
Your name, your reputation ...
My reputation has been in question
ever since I told Judith Krantz -
- that no 14-year-old
would read her fiction.
- Bullshit!
- Sit down. Maude.
The good news is that the head of
marketing is my friend and protege.
lf I leave. he' ll leave with me.
I know they don' t want to lose him.
That may give me some leverage.
I' ll leave with you, too!
How' s that for leverage?
Let' s go and see your protege.
Willie,
just the man I wanted to see.
Maude Waggins.
You saved my life. While reading
"What About Us Girls?" ...
- You realised you had to write.
- No, I stopped.
I realised that if this was talent.
I had none.
- How nice that it should stop you.
- I adore you.
- I taught him to do that.
- I used to hit my authors.
Maude wants in if we leave. Do you
know what her contract calls for?
She' s obligated to one more book.
We get first look at her next two.
How about an 80-page reminiscence
of all the restaurants I' ve loved?
There are no specifications
in the contract.
I' ll start eating out right now.
You are a rarity. A loyal man,
with a great taste in authors.
Bye, Will. I' ll see you at Jason' s.
You' re such a polished ass-kisser
it takes my breath away.
I kiss' em like I see' em.
A wolf in Vermont.
I don' t think so. Will.
You weren' t there.
You sure it wasn' t a husky?
After all, it was dark out.
There was a full moon.
It was a wolf.
I was staring straight at it.
You don' t confuse a dog with a wolf.
I see. Funny, this isn' t the first
rabies shot I' ve given recently.
My wife' s sister-in-law in Oneonta,
a raccoon bit her in the ass.
My friend' s son sustained
brain damage from a snake bite.
He was by the pool,
next thing he has brain damage.
- Is he all right?
- No, you idiot, he' s brain damaged.
I see Time-Warner
as a bunch of decent caring people.
Money doesn' t always imply
ruthless ambition. Am I insane?
I would say so, yes.
He' s so charming.
Because the rainforest
is being destroyed so rapidly, -
- all these viruses
are going to colonise the world.
They' ll kill off the population.
I' m only quoting "The New Yorker" .
Everyone' s trying to say the world
will end if we have no rainforests.
You could make a case that the world
has already ended. That art is dead.
Instead of art we have
pop culture and daytime TV.
Women who' ve been raped by
their dentists confiding in Oprah.
An exploration in depth of why women
cut off their husbands'  penises.
- Time to fill up the glass.
- Yes. let' s have a drink.
Relax. Eat something.
At least get a meal out of this.
I didn' t like the food.
All that red meat dripping blood.
- You' re fun to eat with.
- Mr. Alden would like to see you.
"Never send to know for whom
the bell tolls. It tolls..."
Will... just remember who you are.
Charm him. You can be charming
when you want to.
- Why is he doing it this way?
- It' s kinder face-to-face.
- Cigar?
- Don' t mind if I do.
I want you to think about Europe.
Eastern Europe, particularly.
There' s a whole new market
opening up there.
God and currency willing,
the entire continent will cohere.
Both economically and culturally.
I want that to be your area.
I see...
Then my area will no longer be
editor-in-chief after the takeover?
There' s nothing personal,
you know that.
You' re clearly a man
of taste and individuality.
But these days,
all around the globe, -
- taste and individuality
are actually a handicap.
Then what of my successor?
Is he a vulgar conformist?
Drive. Hustle. Drive
and 52-carat ambition.
He nagged me day and night
until I gave him your job.
Well. for what it' s worth. here' s
what I' ve learned in 30 years:
Treat the authors as human beings.
Don' t stint on review copies.
Don' t hold them to deadlines.
They' ll only turn in rough drafts.
Thank you, I' ll remember that.
You' re a nice person, Will.
Thank God I replaced you.
I hope you give
Eastern Europe a shot.
You' d better put that out.
Horses don' t like it.
- I think I' ll finish it.
- Go ahead. Good cigar, isn' t it?
This is the prize. Fort Knox.
Drink it.
Good boy.
I' m afraid I...
finished your drink.
What are you?
The last civilised man?
I' m...
... just embarrassed.
Half the people here use Thorazine,
so a little anxiety is okay.
- You' re very kind.
- No. I' m not.
I' m Laura Alden. Alden is my father.
- I' m Will Randall.
- Nice to meet you.
- You don' t seem surprised.
- Not tonight.
- He just fired you, didn' t he?
- Demoted is the word.
I have a choice between no job
and a job no one would want.
- What will you do?
- Take the job no one would want.
I don' t have the courage
to be jobless at my age.
Old guy?
Yeah... Old guy.
Well... I' d better get back.
Was that on purpose?
No... You' re perfectly safe.
I' m married.
- And that makes you perfectly safe?
- Yes...
You better clean yourself up
if you' re gonna face the crowd.
Here, wipe your face.
It' s all sweaty.
There you are, dear.
All ready for company.
Thank you.
How did it go?
Speak, we' ve been going nuts.
First, let me say congratulations
on being the new editor-in-chief.
What ..? Alden said that?
What did he say?
He called this evening and told me
he wanted me to take the job.
I said that it was your job.
I didn' t know if he was serious.
I didn' t ask for this.
Say the word, I' ll turn it down.
- What should I do?
- That' s up to you, Stewart.
No, it' s up to you.
I' ll do whatever you say.
You' re asking the one person
who can' t advise you.
Shit! I' m sorry you said that.
That son of a bitch! Prick!
I had no idea
he was offered your job.
Alden must have made a good offer,
but he could have told you.
Why didn' t you say something?
You let him walk away guilt-free.
Charlotte, please...
I can' t talk now.
May I just say
one more thing about it?
No.
Will, come on, it' s 7:30.
Give me till eight.
Will?
It' s 7:40.
I asked you to give me till eight.
It' s 7:40 at night, you dope.
You' ve slept all day.
Are you all right?
How do you feel?
I feel...
... good.
I said, "Why assign me mastectomies
and oestrogen therapy?"
"Let me do genetic engineering.
Give Pete mastectomies."
You know what he said? "You' ll do it
so much better, you' re a woman."
l said, "That' s like telling
a black food-writer..." Hey!
what are you doing?
l have to catch up.
l haven' t eaten. l haven' t drunk.
l haven' t made love in a long time.
A very long time.
Do you think we ought to do it
right here in front of the church?
- What else do you do without hands?
- You' ll see.
What was in that stew?
- Good morning.
- It' s a bit early to be drinking?
- How the fuck did you know?
- You can smell it a mile away.
- Mr. Randall, are you all right?
- Perfectly.
I heard about Alden' s decision.
I' m so sorry.
- Was Stewart just in here?
- Not just. About an hour ago.
That' s how I found out.
Are you all right?
I' m fine.
- I want to say I think it sucks.
- Thank you, Roy.
What did you do, get contacts?
I' ll be damned...
You' ve edited about 60 pages
since Monday. What are you on?
Nothing.
I just caught up on my sleep.
I got 20 hours of sleep
and I feel 20 years younger.
And so now
you can see without your glasses?
Yeah, you' ve got a point.
You know what he said?
"How could you drink this early?"
I put some tequila in my coffee
and he said he smelled it.
- Alden replaced Randall.
- Are you sure?
It' s official. Will Randall' s out.
Stewart Swinton' s in.
Get me Gary on the phone.
- A manual on owning animals?
- No. Animal possession.
Demonic possession.
Possession of the spirit by animals.
Give me a minute.
- How many do you want?
- One, the most respectable.
Vijav Alezais
wrote "Something Wild" in 1948.
- Old but breathing.
- He' s not some kind of mystic?
No, he has letters after his name.
ln fact, he' s Doctor Alezais.
Thank you.
Give his number to Mary, please.
And, Gary, don' t tell people
you had tequila with your coffee.
You didn' t have coffee
this morning.
Hi, I made it to New Haven.
l' ll be home tomorrow.
lf you get hungry,
there' s some leftover stew.
Let' s see if it still works,
you animal!
- Yes?
- It' s Will.
l' ll come down.
Hey, Will. What' s going on?
What is it?
What' s wrong?
What did he...
I' m sorry.
I' ll get dressed.
- Good morning, Mr. Randall.
- I' ve moved to the Mayflower.
- Is that permanent?
- Yes.
Call legal and find out
if the deal with Alden is closed.
Get Roy to come over with a list of
every author he' s ever worked with.
And a list of every author
I' ve ever worked with.
Call Alden and get me
an appointment this afternoon.
Is the worm turning?
- The worm is now packing an Uzi.
- It' s about fucking time.
Shall I resign today? Promise
never to see Charlotte again?
- Just tell me what to do.
- Resign today.
I can' t do that.
So why did I say it?
I guess it' s just a way
of telling you...
... how bad I feel
about being such a shit.
I love you, Will.
I know how that sounds, but I do.
I know how much I' ve hurt you
and it kills me.
I know I can' t...
- You' ll never forgive me, will you?
- No.
I' d still like one thing.
Your permisson to call Alden and
tell him to forget Eastern Europe.
To keep you on as a consultant.
May I do that for you?
I' m gonna get you, Stewart.
The deal is not officially closed.
Mr. Alden will see you at 12:30.
Roy, ask your list of authors about
forming a publishing partnership.
Tell them
we' re leaving MacLeish House, -
- whose new policy is to bury
everything that doesn' t sell.
- Tell them we' ve got investors.
- Two things.
- How many investors do we have?
- I don' t know.
But I say it anyway.
Is any of this true?
- Not yet.
- You' re my God.
You' d better start calling writers.
Begin with Maude.
Mr. Randall.
I wanted to tell you that
I' m turning down Eastern Europe.
I more or less
thought you would.
Nice seeing you again, sir.
- Are you all right?
- Are you crazy?
Stay away from animals when
you know they' re frightened of you!
Didn' t you realise that on Monday?
Your presence disturbs them.
- I just wanted to say hello.
- You haven' t fallen in years.
Here you still are.
Did you get lost?
- No.
- We were talking.
Henry and Caroline are here.
I told them you' d join us.
Did you? What a pity,
I' m having lunch with... Will.
lt doesn' t really matter to Laura
what your name is, Mr. Randall.
What is important is that you' re
unemployed and I disapprove of you.
- We' re going to miss your company.
- Yes, I know.
Shall we start cooking?
Your place?
A guest house.
I stay here when I' m in town.
I only have peanut butter and jelly.
We' ll have to cancel lunch.
Peanut butter and jelly
is mother' s milk to me.
Whatever you think
is going to happen, isn' t.
Don' t take anything for granted
because we exchanged a few words.
I don' t take anything for granted,
except perhaps a little civility.
So what do you do?
Why do you care?
I don' t. I was just making
polite conversation.
I' d rather not discuss what I do.
I think I understand
what you' re like now.
You think men are only interested
in you because you' re beautiful.
But you want them
to be interested in you.
The problem is
that you' re not very interesting.
You' re rude, you' re hostile,
you' re sullen, you' re withdrawn...
I know you want someone to look
past all that to what' s underneath.
But the only reason anyone would
bother is because you' re beautiful.
Ironic, isn' t it? In an odd way
you are your own problem.
Sorry, wrong line.
I' m not shocked by your keen insight
and suddenly challenged by you.
Shall we have the rest of our milk
in the living room?
Are all these you?
Yes, my father keeps this cottage
empty just for me, -
- so I can stay
as far away from him as possible.
The pictures were thrown in by the
decorator. He had a mawkish side.
- Is this you?
- My mother. She died when I was 12.
I' m sorry.
And this?
My brother. He died last year.
Yes... I remember.
He had some kind of an accident.
No, he killed himself.
He was diagnosed
borderline schizophrenic.
I guess he got tired of the title.
He lived with me on and off.
- Nice face.
- Yeah...
He was pretty nice
for a little brother.
This is really something.
Isn' t it?
This is where I used to come
to bury my pets.
And this is where I realised
that one day I would die.
Standing right here on this spot,
I realised one day I would be over.
I want to tell you something.
A few days ago,
something happened to me.
I was driving in New England
and I hit an animal.
- A wolf.
- In New England? Are you sure?
I' m positive.
When I tried to touch it, it bit me.
- Did you get checked for rabies?
- Yes, I' m fine.
This will really sound insane.
The wolf passed something on to me.
A scrap of its spirit in my blood.
My senses are suddenly so acute.
I feel just so... great.
I' m just not the kind of person
who walks around feeling great.
I' m more alive. Stronger.
- It sounds strange, but...
- It' s better than living in Bosnia.
No, I wasn' t going to say that.
I was going to say that...
If you feel great, maybe you
should just accept it as a gift.
I' m afraid it will have a price.
There is that.
Would you like to stay for dinner?
If not peanut butter and jelly,
and I won' t tell my father.
Yes.
- Let' s get back before it' s dark.
- Are you coid?
No, but we will be.
What is it?
- Here, sit down.
- I think... I want to get inside.
It' s not that far.
Here, lean on me.
Listen, I' m an almost-professional
psychiatric nurse.
Elevated, but you' ll live.
Is this another attack?
I don' t know.
Don' t be upset with me
if I tell you this, okay?
You are beautiful.
And the nicest girl...
Can I get you something to eat?
- I can' t eat.
- Then go to sleep.
The next thing you know it' ll
be morning and I' ll make coffee.
- Eggs and toast.
- Bacon.
You think I can' t get bacon?
I just may surprise you.
- I don' t know where I' m going.
- Some place nice.
- Any idea how this happened?
- None.
- Do you ever sleepwalk?
- Not that I know of.
It sounds like you took a walk
in your sleep and fell down.
There' s some lacerations back here.
Nothing bleeds like the scalp.
I' ll have you in
for an EEG and a CAT scan.
- You' ll have to be in overnight.
- Impossible.
You could have a concussion.
No one feels this good
with a concussion.
So good to see you again
so soon. sir.
It' s nice to see you too, Will.
Robert Keyes, my counsel.
- Counsellor, nice to meet you.
- Sit down. Will.
You' re deliberately goading
some of our top writers -
- to become part of some
totally improbable scheme.
And being writers,
they' re too damn stupid to know it.
They might not succeed,
but it won' t hurt them to try.
And if they fail, any publisher
will be glad to get them.
It doesn' t matter if we start a new
publishing house or go to another.
At least seven top writers
are going to leave MacLeish House.
My press release in the morning will
see this firm' s reputation collapse.
- You' re worse than Stewart.
- Yes.
But I have two big drawbacks:
Taste and individuality.
Maybe I can overlook them.
All right.
Call it off. Keep your job.
I' d never have fired you
if I' d known you were this ruthless.
I want a deal memo granting me
additional powers and monies.
By tomorrow morning.
- I won' t agree to that.
- You will. I' d do the same.
- I' ll tell Stewart.
- Wait until the deal is signed.
Then I' ll tell Stewart.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org