Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Ah, what the hell. Guys like
me shouldn't dream anyway
I'm alive
And the world shines for me today
Suddenly I am here today
Seems like forever from today
Thought I could never feel this way
Is this really me
I'm alive
And the dawn breaks across the sky
And the sun rises up so high
Lost in another world far away
Never another world from today
But what can I say
I'm alive
Suddenly came the dawn from the night
Suddenly I was born unto light
How can it be real I'm alive
I'm alive
And the world shines for me today
Suddenly I am here today
Seems like forever from today
Thought I could never feel this way
Is this really me
I'm alive
What the...
Hey, Sonny... Never thought
we'd see you back here again
I'm not exactly thrilled about it
You said this place made you crazy
I decided I'd rather
be crazy than hungry
"The calculation is sensitive to
the time you plan to own your house
The factor increases if you pay
off your mortgage in five years"
Five years?
He'd be lucky if he
paid off the movers
Who could pay off a
house in only five years?
Rock stars don't even need
that long. They pay cash
A million dollars, man? See
my manager. I'm busy, you know?
- Last one in, first one home
- Hey, it's Sonny
It's Michelangelo Malone
Michelangelo,
the ceiling needs painting
All right, that's enough
The great Sonny Malone
returns to AirFlo Records
welcomed by cheering
throngs of thousands
Art world fails to suffer.
News at 11:00
Cut it out. You know I wouldn't
come back unless I had to
- We were all really pulling for you
- Yeah, like one of us breaking away
Really doing it
Yeah, no paint by numbers, no
assembly line art. What happened?
It's what didn't happen. No bread
- I fought it, that's for sure
- Don't worry
I spend my whole life paintin'
what other people want
I paint his van...
I paint somebody else's mural...
I paint Simpson's album covers
Then when I finally
quit to freelance
not only do I almost starve to death
but I can't figure
out what I wanna do
- You can try again
- You will, won't you?
Ah, look who decided to drop in.
Where's your white flag?
You have a way with words,
Simpson. You know that?
Same old wiseass attitude. I thought
we discussed this on the phone
when I decided to take you back
We did. But I have one question...
Why the hell did you take me back?
Simple. You're good. And you're
the fastest painter around
But this time no more artsy-craftsy
Sonny Malone touches, huh?
Just enlarge the album cover
the way I give it to you
Am I coming in loud and clear?
- Yeah
- Good. Here
You're on your way to your
next masterpiece. Get started
That's great, isn't it? Picasso
only gets to be called a genius
I get to be called the
fastest painter around
Hey, Sonny, I have this
terrific friend. You interested?
Not right now. Hey
Ooh, she's great lookin'
I think that's this crazy
girl. I just ran into
- Yeah?
- I was walkin' through the park
She nearly ran over me.
Then she kissed me
Let's hear the X-rated version
- What did you do?
- Nothing. She took off
She took off? Come on! Is
this the same Sonny Malone
that drives women crazy?
I'm gonna find out who she is
- You mean right now?
- You're gonna be a successful artist
- You're nuts!
- Simpson's gonna kill him
Listen, Sonny, I told ya.
I don't know who she is
She never filed a W-2
and she never got a cheque
If I never paid her,
she doesn't exist
What do you mean? I'm lookin' at
her. She's on the Nine Sisters' album
Not if I didn't pay her she isn't!
Down here at me.
Now look to your right
Yeah, that's good. Listen,
Sonny, I don't know who she is
How can you not know?
You took the picture
Listen, this sounds strange
but there wasn't supposed
to be a model on this cover
I snapped maybe 100 shots
In one of them this girl
just jumped into frame
The next time I saw her
was on the contact sheets
I liked it, so I used it.
That's the whole story
- She just appeared?
- No, appeared then disappeared
Don't go spreading this around.
This is one of my best covers
Why do you want to know
who she is, anyway?
I like her
Hey, Lou...
You seen her around here?
No. Pretty Hey, you're single, right?
Let me show you my daughters
That's great. I'm gonna go look
where. I saw her this morning
Get a balloon
Seventy-five cents
- I'll meet you later
- All right
- Hi I'll take one, please
- Hi
- There you go
- See ya
All right, come on now
Hey, mister. What are
you doin' up there?
Hope you don't mind a
little noontime music, kid
A little lunchtime serenade?
I don't mind. It's kinda nice
I'm just wondering where
they laid out the body
I mean, you got something
a little more upbeat?
Sure
- Better?
- At least it's faster
- Here, give me a hand
- Sure
Boy, they sure don't make
rocks like they used to
- Want some popcorn?
- Yeah, thanks
- You work around here, kid?
- Pretty near. I'm at AirFlo Records
You in the music business? Are you
a record producer? A sound engineer?
No. I'm sort of a painter
You, you paint at a record business?
Not exactly. What I do is a...
I duplicate record covers
Why?
I make album covers bigger
so you can hang them
outside of record stores
Promotion. Sounds like
an interesting job, huh?
Yeah. Sounds like you should
take real long lunch hours
- You got it
- I used to be in the music business
Now I'm retired
It's a refined name for "bum"
I don't believe it
Hey, wait a minute!
- Hey, kid, wait up!
Where are you goin'?
Hey you!
Come on! Hold on!
I gotta borrow this.
I'll bring it back
- Sure
- If you bring it back in person
You got it
Hey!
Hey, wait a minute!
Where are you going?
Take that bike off the pier!
Holy shit!
Whoo!
You're a real Errol Flynn, kid
What other stunts do you do?
Man, this whole thing
is screwin' me up
- What whole thing?
- Ah, nothin'
Come on, have a cup of coffee
Sometimes the best person
to tell something to is a stranger
Go on. What's on your mind?
Okay
I run into this girl this morning.
Never saw her before in my life
She kisses me and disappears
- So what's so weird about that?
- What's weird about that is
ten minutes later I see her on an
album cover I'm supposed to paint
I mean, that's crazy, right?
If I said it sounded crazy,
would you stop looking for her?
- No
- Then why ask?
So I'll keep lookin' for her
Okay, but take a tip from me
What's that?
Don't look underwater any more
Thanks a lot
- Hey, Al, where you goin'?
- Sonny,
- it's good to see you, man
- How you doin'?
How could I go wrong with
the paint job you did on my van?
And the chicks love it
It's one of the finer
examples of my work
- It's beautiful, man
- Where you headed?
- Eas. Where you goin'?
- West
- I'll give you a ride
- No, that's cool
- Forget it. I owe you one
- All right. Okay, hit it
Relax and enjoy it.
We're taking the scenic route
Yeah, just don't forget
I'm back here
Hey, that's the place
on the album cover!
Slow down, I wanna get off here
- Here?
- Thanks for the ride
Anytime, Sonny
I've always been in your mind
You know I will be kind
I'll be guiding you
Building your dream
Has to start now
There's no other road to take
You won't make a mistake
I'll be guiding you
Wow
We have to believe we are magic
Nothin' can stand in our way
Don't let your aim ever stray
And if all your hopes survive
Destiny will arrive
Bring all your dreams alive
For you
You
Me
Hey, I've been askin'
about you all day
You may not believe this,
but I'm paintin' an album cover
- and you're on it
- Why shouldn't I believe it?
Because before today,
I never laid eyes on you
Now I've seen you
three times in one day
- That's too coincidental
- Sounds like you don't believe it
With all that's happened to me today
to tell you the truth,
I don't believe it
You're right. It's too coincidental.
Someone must be setting us up
What do you mean?
Hey, wait a minute!
I didn't have anything
to do with this!
- Really?
- Yeah, really, I didn't
Hey!
Who said I was talking about you?
You come here often?
Yes. I can practise my
skating and no one bothers me
- You must live around here then
- Sometimes
- Say, you think we could, uh
- See each other again?
- Yeah. Would you like that?
- Why?
I don't know... I don't
have a very good reason
I'd just like to see you again
Where are you? I don't know
where I'm supposed to look
Bring all your dreams alive
For you
We'll see each other again.
Bye, Sonny
How'd you know my name?
Hey, wait a minute!
I don't know your name
Kira
- I was in big trouble
- What did you do?
- Nothing
- Hi, Sonny
What are you doin' here?
It's early
Yeah, it's really early
I'm workin'
- Well, that's wonderful
- Oh, hello there
Do you know you bear
a strong resemblance
to a fellow by the name of Sonny?
He works here
Always comes in late, though.
Say, that's pretty damn good
It is. It's too good.
That's what's wrong with it
It is supposed to look exactly
like the album cover I gave you
- Is that too difficult?
- If you want me to work, I'll work
If you want to argue,
I can get into that too
Don't be a wiseass, Malone
What are you wasting all
this time on a girl for?
Because that's how she really looks
I don't give a damn
Just get it finished.
When are you gonna have it done?
Well, I'd say it
probably will be done...
when it's done
But that's only an approximate guess
Five minutes, my office.
If it's six, keep walking
Sonny, what did you do?
Nobody likes it, but we all
say "yes" and then forget it
- It goes with the job
- Four minutes
What difference does it make?
I'll say it's Tuesday,
he'll say it's Wednesday
Big deal. Tell him it's Wednesday.
What does it cost?
Oh, nothin'.
Maybe just the truth
Just go in there and agree
with him. That's all he wants
You want me to say
Tuesday's Wednesday?
- Uh-huh
- Three and a half minutes
All right!
I'll be right back
Sit down
You think you're pretty
special around here, don't ya?
- I never said I was special
- Well, you're not
I mean, you didn't discover art.
Who do you think did that?
- I did. Surprises you, doesn't it?
- No, not really
Now I've got an office
I make a lot of money.
People respond when I call
That's because I smartened
up and I gave up art
I think you made the right decision
I want you to smarten up too.
Start doing things the company way
Sometimes I see more in these
covers than what's really there
That's art. Just paint
what you're told to paint
If you start making changes, then
other people start making changes
Before you know it, you got
people doing what they want to do
That's not a company.
That's chaos
Now, I want you to hang
some of your precious covers
Pick up the van and hustle your
butt over to the Platinum Palace
Tuesday's Wednesday
Hey, clarinet. How you doin'?
Hey, kid. What're
you doin' up there?
Trying to get down.
Grab ahold of the ladder
Sure
We might as well
introduce ourselves
- Sonny Malone
- Danny McGuire
Malone and McGuire.
Sounds like a vaudeville team
- What you got there?
- A real gem
- I've been waiting months for it
- Ah, Glenn Miller
You wouldn't know about him.
He was before your time
So was Beethoven,
but I know who he is
You like Glenn Miller?
- You like rock'n roll?
- I love rock'n roll
I love Glenn Miller
This place is incredible
It belonged to a silent movie star.
They did things big in those days
What do you do with
all this space?
Nothing really
This room makes
my records sound great
I've only got one thing to say:
Remember, I gave you some popcorn
Okay. But you came here
to listen to Glenn Miller
All set up. There he goes
Nothing like that sound.
That sound was a miracle
- Hey, Danny, that's you
- Yeah
This girl. Danny, there's this girl
Shh, listen
That's me
Hey, that's all right.
You got any more surprises?
This is what I call my
memorabilia room
The story of Danny McGuire
Tommy Dorsey, Benny Goodman...
You really knew those guys?
We used to hang out together
After I toured with Miller
I got my own band and my
own club. West 51 st Street
It was small and jam-packed
Everybody in town would drop by
Sometimes they'd sit in
for a set or two
Now it's a parking lot
- Why did you give it up?
- Oh, it was one of those
turning points where you
turn in the wrong direction
- It was a girl
- The girl in the album
Yeah
The singer with the band
When she left,
I figured she'd be back
I wasn't about to run
after her, right?
Hmm! Boy, did I teach her a lesson
Never saw her again
After that, the heart
went outta my music
I went into the family
construction business
and became what
they call "comfortable"
Three cheers for comfort
You ever think about
going back into music?
Oh, only about 20
or 30 times a day
So, you gonna do it?
Well, I can't play clarinet
like I did in the old days
But you know something?
I'd love to open up
another joint again
Why don't you?
I've had real estate agents
looking for two years
They can't find the right place
If it's just a place you want,
that seems pretty easy
No, it's not easy.
It's like falling in love
You gotta feel a special attachment
- Like you and your friend
- Kira
Kira Hey, why don't you
help me look?
Maybe you can
come up with something
- Me?
- Sure. You've got a good eye
- Stranger things have happened
- Yeah, I guess they have
- Listen, I gotta go
- I understand
- I'll let myself out?
- Sure
So long. See you around
Now how'd that kid
figure out about us?
You made me feel so bad
I guess it still shows on me
You made me sigh for you
I didn't wanna tell ya
You're gettin' old, boy
Didn't wanna tell ya
I'm gettin' old, babe
I want some love
You wouldn't even know me now
That's true
Yes, I do, indeed I do
But I'd know you
You know I do
Gimme, gimme
Yes
What I cry for
I'd certainly know you
You know you've got
I remember
The kind of kisses
That I'd die for
everything
Oh-ho
You know
How I remember it
You made me
Love you
No other face could
take you off my mind
You're so refined
You're much too kind
I have to warn you
I'm never gonna set you free
'Cause I was born to
Love you for eternity
Whenever you're away from me
Wherever you go
You're never far away from me
I want you to know
I only have to close
my eyes, dear
And suddenly I'm where you are
You better never stray
'Cause I'll never be far away
On every breeze I seem
to hear your name
My heart's to blame
I feel the same
I'd fall apart, dear
If you'd let the feelin' end
Don't break a heart, dear
Nobody else could mend
Whenever you're away from me
Wherever you go
You're never far away from me
I want you to know
I only have to close
my eyes, dear
And suddenly I'm where you are
You better never stray
'Cause I'll never be far away
'Cause I'll never be far
A way
- Hello. Oh, I'm sorry
- Hey! You scared the hell outta me
I'm sorry if I disturbed you.
I tried to be quiet
- How long you been standin' there?
- Just a few seconds
- Should I go?
- No, stay
You paint beautifully
This is the first time
I've cared about
what I've painted in a long time
It's a shame. It must be frustrating
to waste your talents on things
- that don't really matter to you
- Yeah
I met a guy. He told me
I should take long lunch hours
- A guy?
- Someone I met at the beach
He's got this crazy
idea to build a club
He asked me if
I'd help him find a place
All the real estate agents
in this town, he asks me
That's not a crazy idea.
You've got a good eye
That's what he said
If it's a place you want, what about
this one? My place, where we met
That? Forget it
I think it has a very
special aura about it
It's a dump!
You're supposed to be an
artist. Use your imagination
Thanks, I'm all out
You know, I really think
you believe that
I've had enough for tonight
- Come on, let's get out of here
- Okay
- What's this?
- Shh, be quiet
I thought we were going skating
I wanna show you
the special studio first
Only the biggest groups
get to record here
- It's really kinda magic
- Hmm?
They flash all sorts
of pictures on screens
Really? Can we see it?
Straight ahead
But pictures in a
recording studio? Why?
- For inspiration
- Oh, inspiration. Sounds perfect
I've only watched them do this
a couple of times before
Let's see. Turn on
that one. And this
I don't know how to make
the whole thing work
- Press 'em all
- I don't wanna break it
- Press them carefully!
- What the hell
I didn't like the job anyway
Let's see
Now will we see the magic?
Sure. Come on
Careful
She walks in
And I'm suddenly a hero
I'm taken in
My hopes begin to rise
Look at me
Can't you tell I'd be
so thrilled to see
- The message in your eyes
- You make it seem
I'm so close to my dream
And then suddenly it's all right
Suddenly the wheels
are in motion
And I
I'm ready to sail any ocean
Suddenly I don't
need the answers
'Cause I
I'm ready to take
all my chances with you
And how can I
Feel you're all that matters
I'd rely on anything you say
I'll take care
That no illusions shatter
If you dare say
what you should say
You make it seem
I'm so close to my dream
And then suddenly it's all right
Suddenly the wheels
are in motion
And I
I'm ready to sail any ocean
Suddenly I don't
need the answers
'Cause I
I'm ready to take
all my chances with you
Why do I feel so alive
When you're near
There's no way any hurt
Can get through
Longin' to spend
every moment of the day
With you
Suddenly the wheels
are in motion
And I
I'm ready to sail any ocean
Suddenly I don't
need the answers
'Cause I
I'm ready to take
all my chances with you
Ah-ah-ah-ah
Hey! What the hell's
goin' on in here?
Malone! Is that you?
Yes!
No, it's not me.
It's somebody else
Do you have any idea how much
this equipment costs? Huh?
- Oh, shit!
- That was great
- You were great
Our first dance together
Followed by our first
being-kicked-out together
- Now I want to go somewhere else
- Where?
Find out more about you
You know enough about me.
I wanna know about you
- I'm serious
- So am I
After all that, do you think you'd
let your imagination roam a little?
I won't even
start in on that one
What are you doin'?
- What do you think you're doin'?
- Oh, nothing
Oh, ha. Well, well, well.
What a coincidence
Look where we
just happened to end up
- You think you're
clever, don't you?
I just didn't want you to close
your eyes to any possibilities
You really think this
could work out for Danny?
I think this place could be
anything you want it to be
See, it's simple.
Your friend has a dream
and you want to be involved in
something you really believe in
Maybe his dream is big
enough for the both of you
So here we are. Someone who believes
that dreams come easy, and...
Someone who doesn't know
what they believe in
So just think about it, okay?
Just think about it
You gotta be kidding. This place?
They used to have wrestling here
It's got a history of success
It needs some fixin' up.
It could look terrific
So could the Titanic
Kid, you don't need a builder.
You need a demolition team
I know it's a wreck now, but I
can see it coming to life again
Just check it out, Danny
- What put you onto this?
- A girl
Oh, that explains everything
Hey, Danny, don't you think
there's a certain kind of...
aura about this place?
Well, if that's what you call it,
it's got it all right
Let's see the rest of it
Course, it's not small and
intimate like my club in New York
But then again, that was back
in 1945 and things are bigger now
And this place. Whoo! Sure is big
- Yeah, it is
- Well, I don't know
Naturally, I can't take
all this too seriously
But if I were going to do
something. And I can't say I am
I'm a builder and a builder has to
take his time deciding these things
If I were going to do
something about it
speaking hypothetically,
it just might work
- You think so?
- Might. If I planned it right
Let's see, uh.
Stage over there
Stairs there and there
and back there
- Can you imagine it?
- Imagine what?
A bandstand right over
there in that corner
And a big band,
like in the '40s
No. Bandstands went out
with running boards. Over there
A great rock 'n' roll band.
This is the '80s
Real smooth dancers...
Wild trombone
The band decked out in tuxedos
Six guys wearin' electric orange...
Synthesizer, heavy
percussion, electric guitar...
Lots of glamour. Everybody
dressed in elegance and style
Do it, Daddy, do it
Anybody blue
Anybody needin' someone too
Anyone feelin' cold
No one there you can hold
Don't wait to get old and grey
I'm gonna blow
all the clouds away
'Cause there is nothing
I would rather do
Ooo-ooo-ooo
Forget about the blues
tonight. Sweet thing
Forget about the rules tonight.
Sweet thing
I want to dance with you
Until the sun comes
creepin' through
I want to dance with you
I won't stop pleasin' you
Ahh-ahh-ahh-ahh
Honey, for a while
Give a girl a chance
to show some style
If you've got no love to spare
Tell me lies
I don't care
You better believe that I
Know some moves
that we've gotta try
'Cause there is nothing
I would rather do
Ooo-ooo-hey
Forget about the blues tonight.
Sweet thing
Forget about the rules tonight.
I want to dance with you
Until the sun comes
creepin' through
I want to dance with you
I won't stop pleasin' you
Ahh-ahh-ahh-ahh
Lover, I wanna let you know
I won't take a backseat
Ain't willin' to let you go
Don't wanna hear what you want
It's gotta be all my way
And I'm makin' sure
you stay to see
I'm really a selfish man
I gotta get right to it
Lover, tonight
I'm thinkin' of me
Lover, I won't take a
backseat tonight. Ooo-ooo-ooo
Lover, gettin' on my
two feet tonight. Ooo-ooo-ooo
Got some dancin' to do
Can't let anyone dance with you
I won't take a backseat
Let me show you what I can do
Ain't funny to fool with me
I'll be a bad loser
You're gettin' me mad.
Usin' me
Tried puttin' a spell on me
'Cause I had a strange feelin'
You better get down
to healin' me
Lover, I won't take a
backseat tonight. Ooo-ooo-ooo
Lover, gettin' on my
two feet tonight. Ooo-ooo-ooo
Got some dancin' to do
- Got some dancin' to do
- Wha-aah!
Got some dancin' to do
Ahh-ahh-ahh-ahh
- Forget about the blues
- Lover
I won't take a backseat tonight
- Forget about the blues
- Lover
Gettin' on my two feet tonight
- I want to dance with you
- Got some dancin' to do
Until the sun comes
creepin' through
- I want to dance with you
- Got some dancin' to do
- I won't stop pleasin' you
- Forget about the blues
- Lover
I won't take a backseat tonight
- Forget about the blues
- Lover
Gettin' on my two feet tonight
- I want to dance with you
- Got some dancin' to do
Until the sun comes
creepin' through
- I want to dance with you
- Got some dancin' to do
- I won't stop pleasin' you
Ahh-ahh-ahh-ahh
Hey
I love it!
I'll do it!
Maybe I'm crazy, but what the hell!
I haven't been crazy
for over 35 years
And, kid, I'm giving you
half the place
You're gonna be my partner
I can't do that, Danny.
I can't take that
Why?
I don't know the first thing
about being a partner
It's easy. We share the
responsibilities and we argue a lot
It's like being married
without the good part
- Come on, kid. Is it a deal?
- Okay It's a deal
- What do you know!
I'm back in show business
I can't wait. I gotta look over
every inch of this place
- I wish we could see better
- I got a flashlight in the car
- Will you get it?
- Yeah
Our first collaboration as partners
Oh, partner?
Partner, what'll we name the place?
Yeah. What, what
the hell to call it?
"In Xanadu did Kubla Khan,
a stately pleasure dome decree:"
"Where Alph,
the sacred river, ran
through caverns
measureless to man"
"Down to a sunless sea"
Yes, Xanadu
- I'm Kira
- Of course
You're Kira
- But, uh
- But?
I mean... don't I know you?
I don't think so
- Are you sure because...
- Because?
Well, I mean... I don't know.
I was thinking that I ge...
Oh, I'm sorry. Forget it
So you're gonna do it?
Yes, we-we're gonna do it
- Total insanity
- Only if you think so
Well, even if it is,
it's worth a try
Xanadu... How do you think
that'll look on a marquee?
- Mmm, wonderful
- Hey!
- When did you get here?
- Just a minute ago
What'd I tell you, Danny?
One minute she's here, the
next minute, who knows?
Guess what you
own half of, partner
What?
Xanadu
- Xanadu
Hi, guys
- Hey, Picasso
- Hey
How ya doin'?
Let's see, what's first
on the agenda?
- Who are you calling?
- Leave a dime on the counter
- Hello, Simpson? Sonny Malone
- I wanna see you right away
- What's goin' on here?
Who cares? Just get out
before he gets here
I'll fix everything up.
I'll tell him it was a joke
- Wait a minute. Relax
- Are you loaded?
When you sober up,
you're gonna be sorry
- He should be coming in about now
- Malone, what the hell is goin' on?
Simpson, I've worked like a dog
tryin' to make Tuesday Wednesday
I couldn't do it.
I must be a failure
Is he straight?
You told me if I didn't
do things right, I'd be fired
- Well, you were right
- Huh?
I'm fired!
Malone, I want you
out of here in five minutes
That's five minutes, Malone
and if it's six, just
keep walking. Got it?
I'm doin' it I'm doin' it
I'm doin' it!
You know that dream of
mine to get out of here?
It's happening,
and you're all invited
Opening night, whatever you want
it's on the house
You know, I always
wanted to say that line
Shit
Okay
- To Xanadu
- To dreams
I couldn't have done it without you
- How is it?
- Heavenly
You're the one
that's heavenly
No, don't
What's the matter?
Did I do something?
No
You know, I don't know
anything about you
Where you live,
where you were born
There's nothing to know
- Where do you live?
- With my sisters
- Where?
- In an apartment
- Yeah, but where's the apartment?
- On the second floor
Look, I don't even know
how to find you
- Yeah, but you always do
- Okay
That's a dead end
- What's your last name?
- Same as my father's and mother's
- Yeah, but what is it?
- What? My father's or my mother's?
- I don't care. Either one
- Same as mine
Okay, I get it. No questions
- No questions, no lies
- No questions, no truth either
Listen, you know
enough about me already
Any more, you're
gonna get a headache
- Are you living with somebody?
- Yes
I'm living with my sisters.
I told you already
Yeah, I know, in an
apartment on the second floor
Why do I say
Don't walk away
You'll be the way
you were before
When you don't
want me any more
Don't turn around
Don't ever leave
A lonely room where empty days
Are gathering to meet me
When you're gone
Gone
How in the world will go on
Don't walk away
All you gotta do is stay
- Don't walk away
- Don't say goodbye
- Don't turn around
- Don't let it die
- When shadows fall
- When day is done
- All through the night
- All of my life
All of my life
Don't walk away
- Don't walk away
- Don't say goodbye
- Don't turn around
- Don't let it die
- When shadows fall
- When day is done
- All through the night
Come on, you guys,
does anyone want some more?
Gimme a break. It's only
the end of the first week
So what? We're gonna celebrate
at the end of every week
- I won't argue with that Cheers
- Two cheers. Two cheers
You know, when you guys told
me you were buildin' a dream,
- I thought you were crazy
- Yeah?
Most people want skyscrapers
you put up in 20 minutes
- It's gonna be beautiful in there
- Thank you
- See you guys next week
- You bet
Hey, Sonny, I thought we
should haveone special toast
just the two of us
I've never had a partner before
I've never watched
a dream come true
Hey, there's not much
left. But, still vintage
Only the best
- T o Sonny Malone
- Danny McGuire
- And Glenn Miller
- Hello
- How's it all going?
- So far so good
Kira, I want you
to promise me one thing
Anything
Opening night,
I get the first dance
- Okay
- You're gonna dance?
Oh, I've been known
to twinkle a toe or two
Listen, if you're gonna dance,
you have to wear something
Uh, that looks special
- You need some, uh
- Glitz
- "Glitz"?
- Something sharp looking
You know, something
with a bit of pizzazz to it
- Hot
- Oh
- Well, if I need some Wha-Wha-Wha
- Glitz
Glitz, uh, then I gotta go get some.
Where do you go to get it?
- At a franchised glitz dealer
Well, wherever it is
you go, let's go
Ooo-ooo-ooo
Everybody all around the world
Gotta tell you what I just heard
That there's gonna be
a party all over the world
I got a message on the radio
But where it came from
I don't really know
And I heard these voices callin'
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Everybody, everywhere
is gonna feel it tonight
Tonight
Everybody walkin'
down the street
Everybody movin' to the beat
They gonna get hot
down in the USA
New York - Detroit, LA
We gonna take a trip
across the sea
Everybody come along with me
We're gonna hit
the nights down in gay Paris
See the Duke.
Then we'll pick up the team
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Everybody, everywhere
is gonna feel it tonight
All over the world
London, Tampa, Hollywood
New York, Hong Kong, Tokyo
LA, New York, Amsterdam
Monte Carlo, China and then
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Everybody, everywhere
is gonna feel it tonight
Ooo-ooo-ooo
Everybody all around the world
Gotta tell you what I just heard
Everybody walkin'
down the street
I know a place where
we all can meet
Everybody gonna have a good time
Everybody will shine
till the daylight
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Everybody, everywhere
is gonna feel it tonight
Ooo-ooo-ooo
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Everybody got the word, word
word, word, word, word, word
All over the world
Everybody got the word
Yeah, that's right.
We're opening tomorrow night
You can bring your
TV cameras if you like,
but we're not gonna do
any of that celebrity stuff
No, no, just, just people
Anybody who shows up. Okay,
we'll see you tomorrow. So long
I wonder what would have happened
if I got that al bum to paint?
Don't worry.
Your turn will come
Everyone gets at least
one chance at feeling like that
- Mmm, yeah. That's what they say
- That's what I say
All right, what's next, boss?
Well, we're down to little details.
Fountains, yes
The mirrors, yes. Uh, next,
we need those new parking signs
The signs are here.
We haven't put them up yet
Let's get' em up. I'll be
right back. I wanna talk to you
- about the sound system
- Sure
You've made the place
look beautiful
Just did what the kid said
Oh, I see a little Danny
McGuire here and there
Oh, just here and there.
Don't tell anybody, but...
- I'm nervous
- What about?
Well, I haven't had an
opening night since, uh, 1945
Wow! I guess I got the jitters
Well, just pretend we're
back in 1945 all over again
I don't have to pretend
It is 1945 all over again
Well, that takes care of that
Sonny, don't worry
about that sound system
I looked over it
twice today and it's fine
You kids go on home
Bye, Danny
You did it. Tomorrow's your big
day. It's all gonna come true
Tomorrow's gonna be the most
beautiful day in the world
Kira
I love you
I love you, Sonny
- What's the matter?
- All of it everything
We can't go on pretending
this is for real
I know, it is hard to believe
Oh, I can't have
these kind of feelings
It's beginning to hurt...
Oh, this part of it was
never supposed to happen
I don't understand
What do you mean, "hurt"?
I know... I shouldn't but
I do, and it's crazy
Sonny, there's something
I have to tell you about myself
- I know all I need to know
- I have to tell you. I have no choice
All I was sent to do
was to make Xanadu happen
I don't get it
Sonny, you have to
believe me when I tell you
that I never wanted to hurt you
That was the last thing
I wanted to happen
I'm not as I appear to you
Have you ever heard the
expression, "Kissed by a muse"?
That's what I am.
I'm a muse
I'm glad somebody's
havin' a good time
Please don't make a joke
I'm serious
I come from Mount Helicon
I'm the daughter of Zeus
I have eight sisters.
My real name is T...
Are you telling me
that's not real?
I'm trying to tell you the truth.
Why don't you believe me?
Look up the word "muse"
in the dictionary. Go on
- Page 728. Read it
- Okay
All right, I'll read it
- "'Muse' Any of the nine sister"
- Like the album cover?
Hmm?
"Any of the nine sister
goddesses in Greek Mythology
presiding over song and poetry
and the arts and sciences
And do you believe me
now, Sonny?"
How'd you do that?
What's goin' on?
The television
Well, well, look who's here
Who's chasing you this
time, Vargas? The cops?
- Or the mob?
- Don't get smart with me, Nick
I told you to stay away
from Brenda Trent
Ah, yes, you did tell me.
What should I do, Sonny?
Dive at him
or, uh, make a martini?
What?
Who you talking to?
Sonny Malone. He doesn't
believe Kira's a muse
How can you be talking
to me? You're a movie
I ain't got time for this, Malone
Brenda's the only one
that saw me at the racetrack
Now if the lady says
she's a muse she's a muse
Who's that? Brenda!
Kira
Sonny
I think he needs a drink
It's okay I'll take care
of it. Thanks
Good luck on the
opening of your joint, kid
Wish I could be there
Oh, wow!
Oh, Sonny
We've been painted by Michelangelo
Shakespeare's written
sonnets about us
Beethoven's played music for us
We're not supposed to feel
emotion or show any feelings
Muses are just
supposed to inspire
I fell in love
You did?
Well, what do you think
happened to me?
It was a mistake.
I broke the rules
Well, now what
the hell do we do, huh?
- Answer that, muse!
- I don't know
I'm sorry. It just never
should have happened
- Well, it did
- I love you, Sonny
Kira
I'll love you forever
I will
Kira! Wait!
I'll love you forever
Hey, painter! I've been
lookin' for you. Where you been?
- Here
- Well, how do I look?
Aren't you gonna say
anything about my new threads?
Hubba, hubba
Well, uh we're gonna
miss you tonight
- It won't be any fun without you
- I told you
I can't go
Xanadu doesn't matter any more
What do you mean it doesn't matter?
How can it not matter?
This was our dream.
Well, well, wasn't it?
There's no Xanadu
'cause there's no Kira
- She made it real
- So find her!
Bring her back!
- Dreams die
- No
No, no, no. Not by
themselves. We. We kill them
Now, if you give up,
you'll be sitting on that rock
30 years from now
just like I was
I know how you feel, kid.
I felt the same way once I did
I didn't know
how important love is
But let me
tell you something
Somehow, somewhere,
there's a way to get her!
If she got here, there's
a way to get there
Believe me, kid,
it's up to you
It's-It's up to you
I see the early glow
I hear you say hello
I watch the shadows fall
I don't see you at all
- It's a lie
- Don't believe it's so
It's a lie
I see the autumn rain
Falling on my window pane
I hear you say goodbye
I see a tear in your eye
- It's a lie
- Don't believe it's so
It's a lie
Our love couldn't go wrong
How could I know
I was only dreaming
And now... Now that you're gone
I will go on really believing
I'll take the fall
I see you in a dream
You turn and start to go
I call to you once more
Guess that I'm takin' the fall
- It's a lie
- Don't believe it's so
It's a lie
Our love couldn't go wrong
How could I know
I was only dreaming
And now now that you're gone
I will go on really believing
I'll take the fall
Kira
Sonny. How d id you get here?
You didn't think I'd let you
get away from me, did you?
- You'll have to go back
- Okay, I'm ready. Let's go
I can't go with you
But you have to get
out before it's too late
Too late for what?
Oh, please, you took
a big chance coming here
What's going on here?
I'm taking you back with me, Kira
It can't be done. Nobody's
ever taken anyone out of here
Not in the whole history
of the whole history
I'll make 'em let you go.
Hey, Zeus!
- Zeus, you hear me?
- Oh, God
I wanna talk to you
We don't use those
old-fashioned names any more
In any case, it's me
you want to speak to
I've come to get Kira
She's not leaving!
It's impossible!
- That's what you think
How'd you know
I was gonna say that?
I'm a good guesser
What else do you know?
- Everything
- All right, then. You know this
I'm sticking to this place
till hell freezes over
Sonny!
You'll leave now and
you'll leave without Kira!
- Why?
- Because other people have dreams
So send another muse You got muses
running around all over the place
One dream, one muse
Wait. Wait a minute.
Just listen to me, okay?
Kira and I love each other
Now I don't know how often
that happens in this kind of place
but back on earth,
it's pretty rare
- We need to be together
- All right, that's enough
You're leaving Kira's staying.
No more discussions
Those are the rules and
that's all there is to it
On the other hand, dear,
rules were made to be broken
We'll talk about that later
Which is later and earlier?
- I keep forgetting
- Just a minute!
Isn't anyone interested
in my feelings?
What do you mean, "feelings"?
Oh, you remember, pet.
We learned about feelings
- in our mortal history class
- Yes, feelings
I guess that's what you call 'em.
I've never really had them before
I've never felt this way
about anyone before
And I've never asked
to leave here. Not ever
Not once in the whole
time. I've been here
It's true, dear, she hasn't.
Not in all these centuries
Or is it minutes?
I do keep mixing them up
Please, can't we just have
this one night? Just one night?
No, no, it's just not possible.
Goodbye, Sonny Malone
- Hey, Kira?
- Just one moment
Goodbye, Sonny
Kira!
A child and a fool in one
So sure I could need no one
My heart always on
the run to nowhere
Now as you're holding me
My heart is reminding me
That now I could never be
Without you
But how can our love succeed
A miracle is what we need
And so I appeal to you
To keep me suspended
in time with you
Don't let this moment die
I get a feeling when
I'm with you
None of the rules apply
But I know for certain
goodbye is a crime
So, love, if you need me
suspend me in time
Ahhh
Wasted the time away
Holding our love at bay
Now I can't last a day
Without you
Your smile is a thrill to see
Your eyes hold me tenderly
They'll shine in
my memory forever
But how can our love succeed
A miracle is what we need
And so I appeal to you
To keep me suspended
in time with you
Don't let this moment die
I get a feeling when
I'm with you
None of the rules apply
But I know for certain
goodbye is a crime
So, love, if you need me
suspend me in time
In time
Maybe just one moment, darling
Well, maybe just one moment
or forever
I keep getting them mixed up too
All right, everybody, let's skate!
Let's skate!
Everybody! Come on!
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
I don't even know yet
U- U-Up!
Hey!
Xanadu!
Ho!
A place
Where nobody dared to go
The love that we came to know
They call it Xanadu
It takes your breath
and it'll leave you blind
And now
Open your eyes and see
What we have made is real
We are in Xanadu
A dream of it we offer you
A million lights are dancing
And there you are
a shooting star
An everlasting love
And you're here
with me eternally
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Xanadu
Your neon lights will shine
For you in Xanadu
The love
The echoes of long ago
You needed the world to know
They are in Xanadu
With every breath you drift away
The dream
That came through
a million years
That lived on
through all the tears
It came to Xanadu
The dream you dream
Well, it will happen for you
A million lights are dancing
And there you are
a shooting star
An everlasting love
And you're here
with me eternally
Xanadu
- Now we are here... Xanadu
- In Xanadu
Xanadu
Now we are here
In Xanadu
Xanadu, Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Way to go!
Fool
Whatever you do
you're reminded
Fool
Wherever you go
you won't find it
I'm really down on love
so save all your smiles
Ooo, I won't be needin'
any love for a while
I'm really down on love
so save all your smiles
Ooo, I won't be needin'
any love for a while. Ooo-ooo
- Ooo Ooo
- Ooo-ooo
Ooo
Uh-uh
O- o-oh wherever you go
you're a loser
Such a fool
I want you to know
you're a loser
I'm really down on love
so save all your smiles
Ooo, I won't be needin'
any love for a while
I'm really down on love
so save all your smiles
Ooo, I won't be needin'
any love for a while
Fool
I'm sure I should pass
a law laid down
Yee-haw!
Declare you will never wear
Your face in a frown
Obey or be on your way
Get on the first stage
out of this town
There's me and my deputies
to chase you down
If you don't grin
we will take you in
So spread some sunshine around
Obey or be on your way
Get on the first stage
out of this town
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Xanadu
You have to believe we are magic
Nothing can stand in our way
Don't let your aim ever stray
And if all your hopes survive
Your destiny will arrive
I'll bring all your dreams alive
- You doin' okay, kid?
- Yeah, I'm all right, Danny
Have a little somethin'.
It'll cheer you up
- Nah, no thanks
- Uh, Miss, uh
would you bring
my friend a drink?
Thanks
- Wait a minute
- Yes?
I mean, I'd just like to talk to you
A place
Where nobody dared to go
The love that we came to know
They call it Xanadu
It takes your breath
and it'll leave you blind
And now
Open your eyes and see
What we have made is real
We are in Xanadu
A dream of it we offer you
A million lights are dancing
And there you are a shooting star
An everlasting love
And you're here with me eternally
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Xanadu
- Now we are here
- In Xanadu
Xanadu, Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Now that I'm here
Now that you're near
In Xanadu
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org