Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS.
[RUMBLING]
[HONK]
MR. ROBERTS?
WILLIAM ROBERTS?
THOUGHT
YOU LOST ME.
YOU WEREN'T KIDDING,
WERE YOU?
UH!
CHARLES PHALEN, SIR.
STACKPOLE, McFEE,
LASSITER, AND PHALEN--
ATTORNEYS AT LAW.
HOW YOU DOING?
[HORSE SNORTS]
UH!
SO...
WHAT IS IT
I CAN DO FOR YOU, SIR?
I'M DYING...
AND I WANT TO GO
BEFORE THE GOVERNOR.
I WANT TO BE
PARDONED.
PARDONED?
FOR WHAT?
FOR THE KILLING
OF 21 MEN.
I WAS PROMISED
A PARDON
7O YEARS
AND 3 MONTHS AGO,
AND YOU TELL HIM
THAT YOU'RE BRlNGlNG lN
RlCHARD "BlLL" ROBERTS,
ALIAS WILLIAM ANTRIM,
ALSO KNOWN AS
WILLIAM H. BONNEY.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WILLIAM H. BONNEY?
ALIAS BILLY THE KID.
BILLY THE KID, HUH?
BILLY THE KID
WAS SHOT AND KILLED
BY PAT GARRETT.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
IT'S COMMON KNOWLEDGE.
UHH...THERE ARE
OTHER LAWYERS AROUND,
YOU PIECE
OF CHICKENSHIT.
GET BACK IN YOUR VEHICLE
AND DRIVE
BEFORE I MAKE IT 22
JUST FOR THE GOD DAMN
HELL OF IT!
CAN YOU SHOW ME
SOME EVIDENCE?
SCARS OR SOMETHING?
I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU HAVE ANY SCARS?
[BIRD SCREECHES]
WHAT I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
IS HISTORICAL FACT.
IT TOOK PLACE A YEAR AFTER
THE GREAT McSWEEN FIRE OF 1878,
WHAT SOME CALL THE END
OF THE LINCOLN COUNTY WAR.
THAT'S HIM.
WHEN THEY ASK
WHO DREW FIRST,
I GOT THE DROP ON HIM.
SAY WHAT YOU WILL.
I FIGURE
TO GET AT LEAST 1OO DOGIES
FOR HIS TRIGGER FINGER.
BOYS!
[HORSE NEIGHS]
UH! UH!
WAIT.
DO I KNOW YOU?
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW ME.
YOU DO.
YEAH.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
TRAVERS...
FROM TULAROSA.
TRAVERS.
NO.
WHY YOU JUST DIDN'T
WANT TO HIDE OUT
UP IN THE CANYONS
DON'T MAKE THE SENSE
GOD GAVE A MULE.
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, NOW...
THIS HERE'S A DANDY.
AH!
UH!
I'D TAKEN UP
WITH ARKANSAS DAVE RUDABAUGH
AND PATRICK FLOYD GARRETT.
ME AND GARRETT
HAD A COMMON INTEREST
IN THE HORSE
AND CATTLE TRADE.
CONTRARY TO WHAT THEY SAY,
I LIKED
THE SON OF A BITCH.
NOW, MOST OF THE BOYS
THAT RAN WITH ME
DURING THAT LITTLE WAR
ARE DEAD OR GONE OR HIDING,
BUT I NEVER LET THEM
PUSH ME OUT.
NEW MEXICO TERRITORY
WAS MY HOME.
WELL...
SHOULD WE GIVE HIM
A PROPER BURIAL?
YEAH. WHY NOT?
AND I WAS MAKING
ONE HELL OF A NAME FOR MYSELF.
[GUNSHOT]
HA HA HA!
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
UH...FRIDAY?
GOOD.
VERY GOOD, PIETRO.
OK. SO, WE HAVE FRIDAY.
FAMILY.
FULMINATE.
WHAT ELSE?
OVER THERE!
WATCH?
WATCH. VERY GOOD.
UH...
WOBBLY!
[BREAKING GLASS]
DON'T MOVE.
[MEN SHOUTING]
HEY, DAVE.
PUT YOUR LIPS
AROUND THAT.
YEEHAH!
YAHOO!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
HOW YOU DOING,
BEEVER?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU?
JUANITA.
PATRICK.
MILITIA'S BEEN THROUGH,
AND THE CAVALRY,
AND THEY KEEP ON
COMING.
WHEN YOU WAS
IN THE GUADALUPES,
THEY SENT A NEW GOVERNOR
TO CLEAN UP.
HE'S GOING THROUGH
THE TERRITORY LIKE THE POX,
RUNNING IN EVERYBODY
WHO FIRED A SHOT
IN THE LINCOLN WAR,
DRAGGING THEM ALL BACK
ACROSS THE WHOLE DAMN COUNTRY.
THlS SAYS,
"GENERALLEW WALLACE
HAS PROCLAlMED A STATE
OF lNSURRECTlON."
THEY'RE FIXING TO DO
A BIG EXTERMINATING,
AND KID, YOU'RE ON THE TOP
OF THEIR HANGING LIST.
THEY WANT TO PUT YOU DOWN.
ARE YOU...
BILLY THE KID?
NAH.
BUTIAM ARKANSAS
DAVE RUDABAUGH.
YOU EVER HEAR OF ME?
I KILLED 65 MEN,
NOT COUNTING MEXICANS
AND INDIANS.
YOU MUST HAVE
HEARD OF ME.
COME ON. RUDABAUGH!
GREAT.
I'D LIKE
SOME FRIJOLES
AND SOME COFFEE.
PLEASE.
GET OUT OF HERE, BOY!
IF I HAVE TO TELL YOU
ONE MORE GOD DAMN TIME,
I'LL PUT AN IRON TO YOU!
#QUIEN ES?
GOD DAMN VAGRANT!
CAME OUT
IN THE ORPHAN TRAIN.
EATING OUT
OF MY ASHCANS.
COME OVER HERE.
STEALING BREAD
FROM MY OVENS.
YOU KNOW
WHO I AM?
YES.
YES?
WHERE ARE YOU FROM--
NEW YORK?
PENNSYLVANIA.
WHAT YOU GOT
IN THAT SATCHEL?
EASTERN TENDERFOOT
SON OF A BITCH!
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
SHUT UP!
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU WANT TO JUST...
LOOK AT ME?
GO ON. HAVE A LOOK.
I WANT TO RIDE THE TRAIL
WITH THE KID...
BILLY THE KID,
PRINCE OF P...
PISS...
PRINCE OF PISTOLEERS.
HA HA! HEY, BEEVER.
HEY, BEEVER.
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
PRINCE OF PISTOLEERS.
HA HA!
I HAVEN'T HEARD
THAT ONE BEFORE.
YOU WANT TO RIDE
WITH BILLY THE KID?
HMM?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
YOU WANT LEAD SHOT
IN YOUR LEG LIKE THIS?
HUH? HOW ABOUT
IN YOUR SKULL?
HIDING OUT
IN THE DAMN BRUSH
LIKE SOME KIND
OF LIZARD,
EVERYBODY
IN THE TERRITORY
TRYING TO TAKE
A SHOT AT YOU.
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM!
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT,
MR. PENNSYLVANIA, HUH?
HUH? IS THAT
WHAT YOU WANT?
YES.
YES?
BEEVER...
PUFF WITH HIM.
I GOT YOU,
YOU LITTLE VAGRANT!
LET GO OF ME! GET OUT!
UH!
AND STAY
THE HELL OUT!
SOLDADOS!
ANDELE! ANDELE!
WHAT DO YOU KEEP
BOTHERING ME FOR?
CAN'T YOU SEE I RUN
A RESPECTABLE PLACE?
GO ON. BOTHER SOMEBODY ELSE,
WILL YOU?
SHUT UP, BEEVER!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU ONLY LIKE BOYS?
HA HA HA!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
HA HA HA HA!
[GUNSHOTS]
HEY! YOU BRINGING
SOMEONE IN?
GOT ONE!
THEY GOT SOMEBODY!
HEY, LOOK AT THIS!
WOO-HOO!
SCURLOCK!
DOC SCURLOCK.
OPEN HER UP, BELL.
WHAT YOU DOING,
BOY?
YEAH!
KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
DOING, BOY?
HA HA HA HA!
NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, DOC.
I GOT A FEW
OF YOUR FRIENDS
WAITING FOR YOU.
HA HA HA HA!
SCURLOCK!
I KNOW YOU!
YOU BEEN DELIVERED
INTO ME HANDS,
YOU STINKING
PRESBYTERIAN FILTH!
UH!
AH!
OH, CHAVEZ.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
"WHEN TROUBLES COME,
"THEY COME
NOT SlNGLE SPlES,
BUT lN BATTALlONS."
JOSIAH G. SCURLOCK.
I NEVER WROTE THAT.
I ALWAYS WANTED
TO TELL YOU.
WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE
WROTE IT.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
WHAT ABOUT
A DRINK, DOC?
HA HA HA HA!
WHERE'D
THEY CATCH YOU?
SEVEN RAIL DAYS
EAST.
WIFE?
CHILD.
CHAVEZ, WHERE
THE HELL IS HE?
[BREATHING
HEAVILY]
BILLY.
WHOA, WHOA.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HEAVY STEPS, PATSY.
HEY,GRACIAS.
A MESSENGER
CAME THROUGH TOWN TODAY
FROM THE NEW GOVERNOR.
HEE HEE!
HE WANTS TO MEET
WITH YOU.
HE CAN'T CATCH YOU.
YOU'RE MAKING HIM
LOOK A FOOL.
GO ON.
HE WANTS TO TALK TREATY.
YOU'RE BOSHING ME.
HE WANTS YOU
TO TURN STATE'S EVIDENCE
AND TESTIFY.
TESTIFY AGAINST WHO?
AGAINST THE MURPHY BOYS
HE'S GOT IN THAT PIT
IN LINCOLN.
YOU CAN HANG
YOUR OLD ENEMIES, KID.
IT'S THE ONLY CHANCE
YOU GOT TO SAVE YOUR NECK.
YOU GOT NO PLACE
LEFT TO HIDE.
SO EVERYBODY'S
LOOKING FOR ME.
HMM.
HEY. PAULITA MAXWELL
AROUND?
SHE LOOKING FOR ME?
GETTING KIND OF
LONELY IN HERE.
NO. I DON'T THINK
PAULITA'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
I THINK CELSA BACA'S
LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHOA! CELSA BACA!
YOU GOT TO BEAR GREASE
THE DAMN WALLS
TO GET THAT PIG
IN HERE.
YEAH? THAT'S THE ONLY THING
WE'D HAVE TO BEAR GREASE.
GARRETT!
WELL, GARRETT WAS RIGHT.
I WAS RUNNING OUT
OF PLACES TO HIDE.
AND HERE WAS
GOVERNOR LEW WALLACE,
THE SECOND BEST-KNOWN MAN
IN NEW MEXICO,
PROPOSING TO MAKE A TREATY
WITH ME IN LINCOLN.
THEN WHY GIVE UP THE SANCTUARY
OF A LITTLE VILLAGE
WHERE I WAS PROTECTED
BY MY FRIENDS?
BUENOS DIAS, IGNIO.
#COMO ESTAS?
HOLA, BILLY.
I FOUND HIM! HE'S--
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
'CAUSE $5OO
CUTS A LOT OF TIES.
AH, DAMN IT, IGNIO.
[GUNSHOTS]
COME ON!
MOVE IN!
ALL RIGHT!
GO AROUND BACK!
AH!
KEEP IT DOWN!
SERGEANT TURNER!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
AH! AH! AH! AH! AH!
RIDE, LITTLE CASINO.
COME ON!
GIT, GIT, GIT! WOO!
[GUNSHOTS]
GO, BILLY!
YOUR EXCELLENCY...
IT'S HIM.
HE'S HERE.
WELL, SHOW HIM IN.
HI.
MR. BONNEY?
I APPRECIATE
YOUR GOOD FAITH.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M GOVERNOR LEW WALLACE.
EXTRAORDINARY.
I WAS EXPECTING A RATHER ROUGH
AND OLDER FELLOW,
NOT SO SMOOTH OF FACE.
COGNAC, MR. BONNEY?
UH-UH.
WELL, THEN. TO THE POINT.
THE VARIOUS CRIMES COMMITTED
DURING THE LINCOLN CATTLE WAR--
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
IT WAS NO CATTLE WAR.
IT WAS A MERCHANT WAR,
IRISH AGAINST THE ENGLISH.
THEY KILLED MY EMPLOYER,
MR. TUNSTALL,
AND I MADE WAR.
THOSE MEN THAT KILLED
YOUR EMPLOYER,
THE GROUP THAT EVADED
THE REVENGE
OF YOUR SO-CALLED
REGULATORS,
THEY'VE BECOME
A RATHER ROUGH BUNCH
SINCE THIS MERCHANTS' WAR,
CUTTING
PROMINENT RANCHERS' HERDS
LIKE JOHN CHISUM'S.
YES, SIR. THEY HAVE.
AND YOU HAVE, TOO.
HOWEVER...
YOU'RE ONE,
AND THE MURPHY-DOLAN RUSTLERS
ARE MANY.
IF YOU CAN TESTIFY
AGAINST WHAT YOU SAW
IN YOUR LITTLE WAR,
I CAN THEN ELIMINATE
THE MANY.
WELL...
WHAT ABOUT THE ONE?
MY TERMS ARE SIMPLE--
YOUR TESTIMONY AGAINST THOSE
WHO MURDERED YOUR EMPLOYER
IN EXCHANGE FOR LENIENCY.
NO.
MY TESTIMONY IN EXCHANGE
FOR A FULL PARDON.
WELL,
I'M AFRAID THAT'S--
I TESTIFY,
AND I RIDE OUT OF LINCOLN
A FREE MAN.
IF NOT,
I RIDE OUT OF LINCOLN NOW.
ANY OF YOUR BOYS
TRY TO FOLLOW ME,
THEY'LL WIND UP
IN A PINE BOX.
IF YOU
WERE GIVEN PARDON,
YOU WOULD LEAVE
NEW MEXICO,
NEVER TO RETURN?
YOU GO ON THE STAND
AND HELP ME HANG
15 RUSTLERS,
AND I'LL GIVE YOU
PARDON.
HA HA HA HA!
OF COURSE,
15 MINUTES LATER,
THE MURPHY BOYS WILL SHOOT YOU
DEAD AS A MANGY DOG
IN THE STREET.
SO WE'LL ARREST YOU,
A STAGED ARREST
FOR YOUR OWN PROTECTION
BEFORE THE TRIAL.
BUT THAT'S FOR YOU
TO DECIDE.
CAN I HAVE
SOME OF THAT CAKE?
PENDLETON.
UH-UH, PENDLETON.
UH-UH.
THE, UH...
THE WHITE CAKE
WITH THE SWEET FROST.
SO...
SHALL WE PROCLAIM
OUR SECRET PARLEY
A SUCCESS?
IT'S A DEAL.
WHEN THE NECK IS BROKEN,
THERE'S ONLY A SHARP PAIN, FAST.
THEN IF THE OTHER PLACE
ACCEPTS YOU,
THE SPIRIT HORSE COMES.
IT TAKES YOU THERE
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
SO DON'T WORRY TOO MUCH.
WHEN YOU DIE, YOU'RE GONNA SEE
THE SPIRIT HORSE.
SHE'LL COME FOR YOU,
MY FRIEND.
GREAT. LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, CHAVEZ.
I DON'T REALLY WANT TO CATCH
A SPIRIT HORSE.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SEE
THE OTHER SIDE.
I SURE AS HELL DON'T WANNA
HAVE MY NECK BROKE
THROUGH A SHARP, QUICK PAIN.
THE ONLY THING
I REALLY WANT TO DO
IS GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
ME, TOO.
[APPLAUSE]
WELL DONE, WILLIAM.
SPLENDID PERFORMANCE.
HOWEVER, THERE ARE
THREE CANDLES LEFT
AND ONLY TWO BULLETS.
[GUNSHOT]
SPLENDID, SPLENDID!
WHAT DID I SAY?
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
MR. BONNEY...
DISTRICT ATTORNEY RYNERSON'S
HERE TO SEE YOU.
THE GOVERNOR
THINKS IT'S BEST
IF YOU HAVE
YOUR RESTRAINTS ON.
HEY, SHERIFF?
CAN YOU BRING THAT
FIDDLE PLAYER IN AGAIN?
HE WAS QUITE GOOD.
HOW ABOUT SOME MORE CAKE
WHEN YOU GET A CHANCE?
AND IT'S GETTING
A LITTLE NIPPY IN HERE.
COULD YOU STOKE UP
THAT FIRE?
THANKS, GEORGE.
YES, SIR.
I WAS STARTING TO GROW FOND
OF PRISON LIFE.
TOP OF THE MORNING
TO YOU, MR. BONNEY.
FINALLY IN CHAINS,
ARE YOU?
STILL TRYING TO
KEEP UP YOUR GAME?
WELL,
WE'LL BE SEEING YOU
ON THE FLOOR
OF THE COURTS VERY SOON.
I AIN'T BEING TRIED.
I'M TESTIFYING AGAINST DOLAN
AND ALL THE OTHER SWINE
WHO KILLED MY FRIEND
JOHN TUNSTALL. YES, SIR.
ARE THE BLOODY COCKS
STILL RUNNING THE COOP?
AH, TO BE SURE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HA HA HA!
HMM.
WHO GIVES TESTIMONY
IS STRICTLY
WITHIN THE DISCRETION
OF THE PROSECUTING
ATTORNEY,
WHO HAPPENS TO BE ME,
WHO HAPPENS TO THINK
NOT A BLOODY CHANCE
IN THE PIT OF HADES.
UGH!
YOU CAN'T BLUFF ME.
NO.
I'LL CHARGE YOU,
SENTENCE YOU.
I WILLHANG YOU...
BUT I'D NEVER
BLUFF YOU.
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
THE GOVERNOR'S ON HIS WAY
BACK TO SANTA FE NOW.
PARDON BILLY THE KID!
IMPOSSIBLE!
I SHOULD HAVE DUSTED
HIS EXCELLENCY'S REGAL ASS
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
HE DIDN'T EXACTLY
LIE TO ME.
HE JUST DIDN'T HAVE THE POWER
AGAINST THE IRISH POLITICIANS
WHO WERE STILL RUNNING
LINCOLN COUNTY.
GOOD DAY, MR. BONNEY.
GOOD DAY, MR. DUNG PILE.
HA HA HA!
AIN'T THAT A BEAUT?
ANOTHER HISTORICAL
AND BIOLOGICAL FACT
WAS THAT
I HAD SMALL HANDS
AND BIG WRISTS.
AND THAT HAS SAVED MY LIFE
MORE TIMES
THAN COLONEL COLT'S EQUALIZER.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GETTING
NEAR TO SUPPER TIME.
YOU BOYS HUNGRY?
I GOT TWO LOTS
OF NEWS FOR YOU--
GOOD AND BAD.
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE BAD NEWS FIRST.
ALL WE GOT FOR SUPPER
IS HORSESHIT.
HA HA HA HA!
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE GOOD NEWS?
Scurlock:
THERE'S TONS OF IT.
THE WORLD HATES
A SMART MOUTH, SCURLOCK.
OF COURSE, YOU'RE GOING
TO REALIZE THAT TOMORROW
WHEN YOU SWING
FROM THAT GALLOWS.
HEE HEE!
THAT'S IF THE LYNCH MOB
DON'T COME FOR YOU FIRST,
WHICH I HEAR TELL
THEY INTEND TO DO.
LET ME KNOW
IF YOU BOYS WANT SOME DESSERT.
HA HA HA HA!
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
HOWDY, BELL.
EVENING.
HOWDY, BOYS.
HEE HEE HEE!
IF THEY STICK THEIR
FINGERS UP AGAIN,
I'LL BLOW THEM OFF
LIKE I DID YOURS,
EH, MOFFAT?
IF THERE WAS ONE THING
AN OUTLAW FEARED
IN THE NEW MEXICO TERRITORY,
IT WAS LYNCH-MOB JUSTICE.
RIGHT ON TIME.
WITH NO PATIENCE FOR COURTS
AND TRIALS,
THEY DID IT
THEIR OWN WAY,
AND THERE
WAS NO STOPPING THEM,
MAINLY 'CAUSE
THE SO-CALLED LAW...
HOWDY.
HAD NO DAMN INTENTIONS
OF STOPPING THEM.
YOU'RE A BIT LATE.
VIGILANTES!
JEEZ! IT'S THE LYNCH MOB!
KID'S ESCAPED,
THE LITTLE WEASEL.
OH, I'M SURE HE DID,
MISTER.
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
OPEN THE PIT.
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
NO BILLY THE KID
IN THERE.
IT'S TRUE! HE'S GONE!
WE MIGHT
AS WELL GO.
WE GOT SOME OF HIS
REGULATORS THERE--
THE INDIAN
AND TENDERFOOT
RODE WITH THE KID
ON THE TUNSTALL-
McSWEEN SIDE.
HOW'D THEY BE?
AW, SHIT.
THEY'LL HAVE TO DO.
BRING THEM UP.
[YELLING]
HA HA HA HA!
PICK YOUR TREE, BREED.
STOP!
I ORDER YOU AS A PEACE OFFICER
OF LINCOLN COUNTY!
HA HA HA HA!
GENTLEMEN, I'M A SCHOOLTEACHER
FROM THE CITY OF NEW YORK,
AND THE BREED BACK THERE,
WELL, HE'S MY GUIDE,
AND I BELIEVE YOU'RE ABOUT
TO MAKE AN ENORMOUS ERROR.
WE KNOW YOU RODE
WITH THE BOY- DEVIL,
AND YOU'RE GONNA
HANG FOR IT.
I SWEAR TO YOU. I NEVER
EVEN LAID EYES ON HIM.
I WAS A SCHOOLTEACHER
FROM THE CITY OF NEW YORK!
"I'M A SCHOOLTEACHER
FROM THE ClTY OF NEW YORK!"
HA HA HA!
HOWDY, DOC.
HOW ARE YOUR DRAWERS?
NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, BILLY.
IT'S THE KID!
COME ON!
LET'S GET OUT!
JESUS! YOU SURE GOT
A LOT OF BOYS
RIDING WITH YOU
THESE DAYS.
THEM AIN'T MY BOYS.
IT'S THE REAL LYNCH MOB!
LET'S GET OUT!
HA! HA!
[GUNSHOTS]
YAH!
YAH YAH!
YAH! GIT, GIT, GIT!
WOO!
YAH! YAH!
LOOK OUT!
WHERE'D THEY GO?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY WENT OVER THAT WAY!
HEE HEE HA!
WOO!
UGH!
[CLICK]
UH!
YAAAH!
I THINK
WE'VE GOT HIM!
AH!
HEY! HEY!
HURRY!
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE!
COME ON!
[GUNSHOTS]
HOLD STILL NOW.
GOT THIS BUCKSHOT INFECTION
IN MY ELBOW.
MAKES MY RIGHT ARM
KIND OF...WHOA!
HOLD STILL NOW.
IAMSTILL.
JUST SHOOT
THE CHAIN, OK?
GOD DAMN.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU, DOC.
I KNEW
YOU'D COME BACK.
WE MADE A PACT,
REMEMBER?
YOU, ME, AND CHAVEZ.
PALS FOREVER.
BILLY,
THE CHAINS.
LOOK. I DON'T CARE
IF YOU GUYS
SWAPPED SPITTLE AND PISSED
IN EACH OTHER'S BOOTS.
I DON'T TAKE TO TENDERFOOTS
IN MY GANG,
AND I DEFINITELY DON'T TAKE
TO NO MEXICANS.
IT AIN'T YOUR GANG,
DAVE.
MEXICAN-INDIAN,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
OH! I'M SORRY!
HEY, TELL ME SOMETHING,
CHAVEZ.
WAS IT THE SAVAGES PUTTING IT
TO A MEXICAN WHORE,
OR WAS IT AN INDIAN WHORE
PUTTING IT TO
THE WHOLE GOD DAMN MEXICAN ARMY?
HO, HO, HO!
GOD DAMN IT.
REMEMBER SOMETHING,
DAVE.
THESE BOYS
ARE THE LINCOLN COUNTY
REGULATORS.
YEAH. WAS.
WERE.
BILLY, COME ON.
THE CHAIN.
YOU'RE RIGHT, DOC.
WERE.
THERE AIN'T NO REGULATORS
NO MORE.
NO ROOM FOR THEM.
NO ROOM FOR ME.
BILLY, PLEASE.
I'M TAKING
THE MEXICAN BLACKBIRD.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TAKING?
THE BROKEN TRAIL
THAT GO DOWN TO OLD MEXICO.
ONLY ME AND A FEW OTHER BOYS
KNOW IT.
TAKE THE TRAIL BELOW.
HEY, DOC...
ONCE YOU'RE DOWN THERE,
THESE BASKET MEN,
PAY THEM,
AND THEY'LL COME UP
AND GET YOUR BELONGINGS,
YOUR FAMILY,
WHATEVER YOU NEED.
COME HERE, BILLY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SHOOT THE CHAIN, OK?
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN HERE.
MOUNT UP.
WE'RE TAKING
THE MEXICAN BLACKBIRD, HUH?
OLD MEXICO. LET'S GO.
COME ON.
WHERE'D
YOU FIND HIM?
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
IT'S FOR YOU.
IT'S FROM NEW YORK.
IT'S FOR THE HORSE.
THAT HORSE
AIN'T FOR SALE, DOC,
BUT, UH...
HOW ABOUT MY BOOTS?
THEY'RE NICE
AND BROKE AND--
SON OF A BITCH!
WOO HOO HOO!
COME ON, BILLY.
KILL THAT TENDERFOOT
SON OF A BITCH!
GET ON TOP OF HIM!
COME ON!
COME ON. BREAK IT UP, BILLY!
I KNOW YOU,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU KNOW ME, HUH?
WELL, I KNOW YOU!
YOU KILLED HALF THE MEN
I GOT CREDIT FOR.
I SAW YOU WITH BLOOD
ALL OVER YOURSELF.
I SAW YOU KILL!
JUST BECAUSE YOU WENT
BACK EAST AND MARRIED,
PUT ON A SILK CRAVAT,
THAT DON'T CHANGE
WHAT YOU DID!
DAMN IT, CHAVEZ!
LET ME HAVE--
YOU REMEMBER
JOHN TUNSTALL?
REMEMBER THE STORIES
HE'D TELL US
ABOUT THE THREE CHINAMEN
PLAYING FAN-TAN?
SOMEONE RUNS UP TO THEM
AND SAYS, "HEY!
THE WORLD lS COMlNG
TO AN END."
AND THE FIRST ONE SAYS,
"WELL, I BEST GO
TO THE MlSSlON AND PRAY."
AND THE SECOND ONE SAYS,
"WELL, HELL!
I'M GOlNG TO GO BUY ME A CASE
OF MESCAL AND SlX WHORES."
AND THE THlRD ONE SAYS,
"WELL, I SHALL FlNlSH THE GAME."
I SHALL FINISH THE GAME, DOC.
WHOEVER'S GOING FOR OLD MEXICO,
WE RIDE NOW.
JOSIAH, THIS AIN'T
THE UNTAMED PRAIRIE
YOU USED TO
RUN FREE OVER.
I GOT A FAMILY
I GOT TO GET BACK TO, PAT.
THE NEW GOVERNOR WAS
THE GENERAL AT SHILOH...
HE'S GOT MILITIA,
HE'S GOT ARMY,
HE'S GOT MONEY
TO PAY GLORY HUNTERS
TO RUN YOU
DAY AND NIGHT,
AND THEY'RE
ON THEIR WAY,
AND THEY WILL
KILL YOU, DOC.
YOU TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF, PAT.
THEY'LL
CATCH YOU, DOC,
AND CATCH ME.
EVERYBODY BUT HIM.
THE VILLAGERS SAY
HE'S ADIABLERO.
HE CAN CHANGE
INTO A COYOTE,
DISAPPEAR, AND NEVER
GETS KILLED.
ME?
I JUST THINK
HE'S THE LUCKIEST
WHITE EYE IN NEW MEXICO.
BUT HE'LL CROSS
THE BORDER.
HE WILL.
CHAVEZ, I CAN'T RIDE
WITH HIM ANYMORE.
TRYING TO SPEND THE LAST YEAR
FORGETTING ABOUT HIM.
READ ABOUT HIM
IN THE NEWSPAPER
AND THEM DAMN
FIVE- CENT BOOKS.
JESUS CHRIST,
THE CHILDREN
IN NEW YORK CITY
IMITATE HIM
IN THE STREETS.
HE'S IN MY SLEEP.
YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING.
IT'S OVER.
WHEN THE SPIRIT HORSE COMES,
THEN IT'S OVER.
WELL, CHAVEZ KNEW
WHAT HE WAS TALKING ABOUT.
HE HAD SEEN THE SOLDIERS
MURDER HIS ENTIRE FAMILY,
AND HE'D BEEN HUNTED DOWN
LIKE A DOG
AND THROWN IN THE PIT.
HE KNEW HIS ONLY CHANCE
WAS TO SKIN OUT
AND HEAD SOUTH.
YAH! YAH!
BUT DOC,
HE DID HAVE SOMETHING ELSE
TO GO BACK TO,
AND ALTHOUGH HIM AND ME
WERE LIKE BROTHERS
AND HE REALLY WANTED TO
RIDE WITH ME,
HE JUST NEEDED SOME TIME
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
OH, NO.
OK, READY?
GRAB A HOLD.
LIFT HIM UP.
[PRAYING IN LATIN]
WHERE'S THE HAMMER?
LUKE,
GIVE US A HAND.
THAT'S IT.
GOT IT?
WHERE ARE WE GONNA
PUT THIS?
WE WANT HIS HEAD.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT,
SHERIFF KIMBEL?
I WANT YOU
TO GET ON YOUR HORSE,
AND I WANT YOU TO TRACK
THIS LITTLE FIEND
TO THE EDGE
OF THE EARTH.
I WANT YOU TO
ASSASSINATE HIM.
I WANT YOU TO DELIVER
HIS HEAD IN BURLAP!
I'D RATHER DRINK TURPENTINE
AND PISS ON A BRUSH FIRE.
I AIN'T
TOUCHIN' THIS ONE.
BILLY,
WHERE ARE THE MEN
YOU PROMISED US?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU HAD AN ARMY.
I DO.
HERE IT COMES.
JESUS...JUST ONE?
THAT'S ALL
YOU COULD FIND?
NO ONE
WANT TO COME.
EVERYONE AFRAID.
ARE YOU
A FARMER?
YES, SIR.
MY NAME'S
HENDRY WILLIAM FRENCH.
YOU EVER SHOOT
ANYBODY BEFORE,
HENDRY WILLIAM
FRENCH?
YOU EVER SHOOT
ANYTHING BEFORE?
SAGE HEN.
SAGE HEN!
AHH...
WELL, TELL ME
SOMETHING, HENDRY.
WHY IS IT YOU WANNA
JOIN MY GANG, HUH?
WELL, I AIN'T--
I AIN'T A FARMER
NO MORE.
UH...LOST MY WIFE
TO THE POX,
LOST MY LAND
TO THE MONEY MEN.
HEY, BIG CASINO...
WHY DON'T YOU SAW A FOOT
OFF OF THIS THING
IN CASE WE RUN INTO
GOVERNOR WALLACE ON THE WAY.
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA
MAKE THIS ONE, KID.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU GOTTA COME WITH US, PAT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
STAY HERE
AND SCRUB POTS FOR BEEVER?
I MAY HAVE OLD BEEVER
SCRUB THE POTS FOR ME.
I'M BUYING THIS PLACE,
TURNING IT
INTO AN EATING HOUSE.
THERE'S WILDCAT MONEY
COMING IN HERE.
I GOT TO STAKE MY PIECE
WHILE I STILL GOT
A FAIR ENOUGH NAME.
WHAT NAME?
YOU'D BE RIDING
WITH KNOWN MEN, PATSY.
YOU ALWAYS WANTED TO BE
A KNOWN MAN IN NEW MEXICO.
HELL,
I'LL BE A KNOWN MAN.
NEXT TIME
YOU RIDE THROUGH HERE,
THERE'LL BE
A BIG OLD SIGN OUT THERE
SAYS "GARRETT'S PLACE."
IT'S TIME
I GOT AN INCOME
THAT AIN'T
FROM STEALING HORSES.
WELL, YOU REMEMBER
SOMETHING, PAT.
I NEVER STOLE A HORSE
FROM SOMEONE I DIDN'T LIKE.
IF I DIDN'T LIKE THEM,
I JUST WOULDN'T
EVEN BOTHER WITH THEM.
NO. HE'D JUST KILL THEM.
HEY, COME ON, PAT!
YOU'RE ONE OF US!
YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN ONE OF US!
I ALWAYS WILL BE, BILLY.
WELL, GO ON, THEN!
GO ON!
WE DON'T NEED YOU, PAT!
WE DON'T NEED HIM.
AH!
SOAPWEED, I GOT YOU!
YOU WANT TO EAT
OUT OF MY ASHCANS?
GO ON. HAVE A CHEW!
GO ON! GO ON!
HOWDY, BEEVER.
GO ON.
SIT WITH THE BOYS.
WHAT THE HELL'S THIS?
THIS?
THIS IS THE PRINCE
OF PENNSYLVANIA.
MMM, MMM, MMM.
[SIGHS]
[CLANGING]
THE FIRST STOP
ALONG THE BLACKBIRD
WAS TO RAISE SOMEDINEROS,
AND JOHN SIMPSUM CHISUM
WAS THE RICHEST MAN
IN THE TERRITORY.
NOT ONLY THAT,
BUT AS ANYONE FAMILIAR
WITH THE LINCOLN WAR KNOWS,
HE WAS A FINANCIAL PARTNER
OF TUNSTALL AND McSWEEN,
WHICH MADE HIM AN ALLY.
OLD JOHN
ADMIRED MY PLUCK
AND LOVED ME
LIKE I WAS HIS OWN SON.
WELL, BY GOD.
YOU REALLY TURNED OUT
TO BE A SNAKE, BILLY.
WHEN THEY CATCH YOU,
THEY'RE GONNA DRY GULCH
YOUR STINKING BONES.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET
MY FRIENDS TO OLD MEXICO.
WE NEED SOME PESOS.
NOW, I'VE DONE
SOME FIGURING,
AND I FIGURE YOU OWE US,
MR. CHISUM--
$25O FOR THE FIGHTING
WE DID LAST YEAR
AND $25O FOR ME
LEAVING YOUR STOCK ALONE.
IS THAT
WHAT YOU FIGURED?
YES, SIR.
THAT'S WHAT I FIGURED.
WELL, YOU CAN TAKE
THOSE FIGURES
AND SHOVE THEM UP
YOUR ARROGANT LITTLE ASS
AND SET FIRE TO THEM.
I DON'T OWE YOU
A GOD DAMN THING.
NOW GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE!
I'LL BRING MY .5O DOWN
AND GIVE YOU A REAL GAME.
YEAH. WE, UH, WE SAW
SOME OF YOUR MEN
UP THERE
ON THE HIGH RANGE.
PASSED RIGHT BY THEM.
FINE BUNCH.
MR. CHISUM...
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE LINCOLN COUNTY WAR
IS OVER.
WE JUST WANT TO
GET OUT OF HERE,
GET DOWN BELOW.
OH, YOU'LL GET DOWN BELOW
ALL RIGHT, DOC.
YOU'LL GET DOWN BELOW.
YOU'RE BILLY THE KID,
TOO, YOU KNOW.
YOU ALL ARE
DIRTY LITTLE BILLY BASTARDS,
AND I DON'T OWE YOU
ANYTHING, DOC.
OR YOU, CHAVEZ...
YOU TOOK MY FARM,
MR. CHISUM.
YOU TOOK A LOT OF FARMS,
AS LONG AS BILLY THE KID
IS TAKING SOME BACK,
I'M WITH HIM.
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT,
MR. CHISUM?
YES, YES.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
UH...GO ON AND BRING
THE MEN IN,
AND WE'LL HAVE
A LITTLE FRESH COFFEE
WITH THE BOYS HERE.
YOO-HOO!
I'LL MAKE YOU FAMOUS.
MR. CHISUM, WHICH ONE
OF THESE BOYS
IS THE FASTEST
WITH THE IRON?
DON'T YOU DO IT,
BILLY.
THAT BE ME.
YOU.
DROP SAM COLT.
BILLY...
PUT HER DOWN NOW.
STEP AWAY.
YOU OWE ME $5OO,
MR. CHISUM,
SO WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
IS KILL ONE OF YOUR MEN
FOR EVERY $5.OO YOU OWE ME.
ONLY I'M GOING TO
DO IT FAIR.
HOW'S THAT FOR SQUARE?
NOW, WHEN I GO FOR MY GUN,
YOU START SHOOTING.
BUT I PROMISE YOU,
YOU WILL NOT MAKE IT.
READY?
YEAH, I'M READY.
DAVE.
OH, MY GOD!
495.
HENDRY.
OH, MY GOD!
49O.
YOU JUST KILLED YOURSELF.
BONNEY, YOU ARE A FOOL!
YOU CALL YOURSELF
THE SCOURGE OF NEW MEXICO?
WELL, BY GOD,
IAMNEW MEXICO,
AND YOU ARE DEAD.
HA HA!
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
MR. NEW MEXICO.
I WOULDN'T GIVE
A BUCKET OF PISS
FOR YOUR FUTURE.
SKIN OUT, BOYS.
YOU HAVE YOURSELF
A GOOD DAY NOW.
I WANT HIM DEAD.
WELL, THE PROBLEM IS
HE'S PROTECTED
BY THE SURROUNDING
COMMUNITIES.
THEY'VE
MADE A BLOODY HERO
OUT OF A HALF-WIT
COMMON HORSE THIEF.
THAT'S WHAT I SAY!
LET'S HIRE A THIEF
TO CATCH ONE.
NOW BRING HIM IN,
GOVERNOR,
AND MAKE THE OFFER.
PENDLETON.
IF I'VE BEEN BROUGHT HERE
TO BE, UH...
IMPLICATED IN ANYTHING,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'M A FAMILY MAN,
FIXING TO SETTLE
AND RUN A BUSINESS.
MR. CHISUM HAS INFORMED US
OF YOUR AMBITIONS,
MR. GARRETT.
NOW, WE KNOW THAT YOU'VE
BEEN WITH BILLY BONNEY
SEVERAL TIMES
WHEN HE CUT MY HERD.
NOW, PAT,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEBODY
WHO KNOWS HIS HAUNTS,
HIS, UH, HIDEOUTS,
SOMEBODY WHO'S FAMILIAR
WITH HIS PATTERNS.
YOUAREFAMILIAR WITH HIM,
MR. GARRETT.
YOU SEE, PATRICK...
CERTAIN CHANGES
NEED TO BE STRUCTURED.
WE NEED A SHERIFF
WHO CAN ELIMINATE
THIS PARTICULAR...
PROBLEM.
I DON'T QUITE FOLLOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
WE'RE SAYING
SHERIFF OF LINCOLN COUNTY.
SHERIFF PAT GARRETT.
NOW THAT OUGHT TO
MAKE YOU FEEL PRETTY GOOD.
AND WE'RE SAYING $5OO...
UP FRONT.
AND 5OO AFTER.
$1,OOO, MR. GARRETT.
AND ALL THE RESOURCES
YOU NEED
TO CARRY OUT
THE EXTERMINATION
OF ONE
WILLIAM H. BONNEY.
IS THAT SATISFACTORY?
WHILE PAT WAS THINKING
ABOUT THE SANTA FE RING'S
GENEROUS OFFER,
ME AND THE BOYS WERE BUSY
SORTING OUT OUR FINANCES.
WE FIGURED THAT IF IT WAS
TOO MUCH OF A HARDSHIP
FOR CHISUM
TO GIVE US ANY MONEY...
HOWDY.
WELL,
THEN WE'D HELP HIM OUT
AND JUST TAKE
A FEW OF HIS COWS.
I GUESS WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
YOU'RE CALLED KID,
AND RUDABAUGH'S
CALLED ARKANSAS DAVE,
AND, UH, I DARESAY
DOC'S CHRISTIAN NAME
AIN'T DOC.
YOU WANT A NAME.
YES, SIR.
I WOULD LIKE THAT.
I WOULD LIKE THAT
VERY MUCH INDEED.
YOU HAVE TO EARN IT,
HENDRY.
UNTIL THEN, YOU'RE STUCK
WITH PLAIN OLD HENDRY.
SORRY.
[RINGING]
[CLICK]
STILL TRYING TO GET
THIS RAG SHEET
OFF THE GROUND, ASH?
THE COPY IS GOOD.
THE MACHINE IS BAD.
I HEAR YOU'RE GOING TO BE
OPENING UP AN EATING HOUSE,
GARRETT.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SECURE
AN ADVERTISEMENT?
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
JEEZUM CROW.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT
THE SANTA FE RING HIRED--
NEVER MIND THAT.
I WANT TO HIRE YOU
FOR A JOB.
YOU DO?
I WANT YOU TO DOCUMENT
THE HUNT
FOR THE MOST FAMOUS MAN
IN NEW MEXICO.
I WANT
A BOOK WRITTEN ON IT
SO THAT THE PEOPLE WILL
UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION.
I WANT YOU
TO RIDE ALONG WITH ME
AND RECORD THE DANGERS
OF THE EXPEDITION.
RIDEALONG WITH YOU?
ON A HORSE?
OH, NO.
THIS I CAN'T DO.
I CAME OUT WEST
TO SAVE MY LAST LUNG.
I'M A JOURNALIST.
YOU'RE
A BROKE JOURNALIST,
AND YOU'RE A DRUNK.
THE COUNTRY WAS OVERGROWN
WITH WEED AND BRUSH
AND ENCUMBERED
WITH LOOSE ROCK,
MAKING IT
ALMOST IMPASSABLE.
I LIKE THAT.
THAT'S VERY GOOD.
MORNING, SHERIFF.
WE MET AT THE GOVERNOR'S.
JOHN W. POE,
CATTLEMEN'S ASSOCIATION.
THE GOVERNOR SENT ME
AND THESE MEN
TO LEND YOU A HAND.
ENCUMBERED BY IDIOTS,
WE PRESSED ON.
I LIKE THAT.
IT'S VERY GOOD.
WHAT DID THEY DO NOW--
SPELL YOUR NAME WRONG?
THEY GOT A NEW SHERIFF
ON US, BOYS.
GOES BY THE NAME
OF PAT GARRETT.
JESUS CHRIST!
WHAT THE HELL
DID HE DO THAT FOR?
MAKE HISSELF FAMOUS.
BE A KNOWN MAN LIKE ME.
HEY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
WHAT DID THEY SAY
ABOUT ME, HUH?
NOTHING, DAVE.
JUST PLAYING THE GAME,
DOC.
WE'LL GIVE HIM A GAME,
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, DAVE'S BOYS.
WE RIDE NOW.
WE ARE GOING TO GIVE
PAT GARRETT
THE RIDE OF HIS MISERABLE
TWO-FACED STINKING LIFE.
LET'S SKIN OUT! COME ON!
WELL, COME ON!
DO YOU BELIEVE THIS?
OK, TOM.
LAST ONE OUT OF HERE
DRINKS DIRTY DISHWATER.
COME ON!
SON OF A BITCH!
HO.
BURIAL GROUND.
WARM SPRINGS PEOPLE.
APACHE.
WE BETTER GET GOING.
WE'LL GO AROUND.
WHAT IS IT--
CHAVEZ, WHY DON'T YOU
GO PECK SHIT
WITH THE CHICKENS, HUH?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE PAYING
FOR APACHE BONE
IN SILVER CITY RIGHT NOW?
CHRIST ALMIGHTY,
THEY'RE MAKING...
THEY'RE MAKING ASHTRAYS,
THEY'RE MAKING COMBS,
THEY'RE MAKING
KNIFE HANDLES.
YOU GET 5O CENTS
FOR A GOOD INDIAN LEG BONE.
IT'S ALL OUT THERE,
SO DON'T YOU GO GETTING
SENTIMENTAL AND ALL THAT,
COME ON.
YOU GO IN THERE,
SMART GRINGO,
AND I'LL BURY YOU
THERE.
OK.
LET'S GO.
COME ON. YAH!
COME ON.
WHOA.
WHOO!
SILVER CITY,
HERE I COME!
AAAH!
NO!
YAH!
UGH!
UHH!
SHIT.
SON OF A...
I DON'T THINK SO,
DAVE.
THAT MEXICAN-INDIAN
MAY HAVE LOST HIS FAMILY,
BUT HE HADN'T LOST A TRICK
WHEN IT CAME DOWN TO
AN OLD-FASHIONED
PIG-STICKING MATCH.
YOU WANT
YOUR KNIFE BACK?
SHIT.
YEAH.
AND DAVE...
WELL, HE APPRECIATED
THE VALUE OF FAIR PLAY,
BUT HE ALSO APPRECIATED
THE VALUE
OF A GOOD BONE-HANDLED KNIFE.
AND WE WERE GOINGAROUND
THAT CEMETERY,
I PROMISE YOU.
THANK YOU.
GARRETT!
GET ME OFF
THIS ANIMAL!
I HAVE TO HAVE
A MOVEMENT!
YOU HAVE TO HAVE
A WHAT?
HE HAS TO HAVE
A SHIT.
I HAVE TO HAVE
A MOVEMENT.
THAT'S THE FOURTH ONE
TODAY.
AAAH!
SHERIFF, AT THE RISK
OF OFFENDING YOU,
YOUR NEWSPAPERMAN
IS HINDERING
AN IMPORTANT
GOVERNMENT OPERATION.
I HAVE TO REQUEST
THAT HE BE DISCHARGED
FROM SERVICE.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
TOBACCO POUCH.
IT'S HIS.
I GAVE IT TO HIM.
IT'S BUFFALO SCROTUM
FROM MY FIRST KILL,
BIG OLD BULL
NEAR FORT GRIFFIN.
THAT'S A PRETTY STORY,
SHERIFF.
WHY'D HE LEAVE IT
HANGING THERE LIKE THAT?
JUST TO SAY HELLO.
LOOKS LIKE HE'S SAYING
MORE THAN HELLO.
WHAT'S ''SCUM''?
WELL, TOM,
THAT'S BAD TYPES--
POLITICIANS, BANKERS,
CATTLE KINGS--
SCUM.
COME ON.
COME ALONG, MOTHER.
WELL, I'LL BE HOG-TIED
AND SENT TO HADES!
BILLY!
AHH!
WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
HOW ARE YOU, JANE?
WICKED BOYS!
4, 5, 6 WICKED BOYS.
WICKED AND WANTED
OR JUST PLAIN WICKED?
$1,OOO ON ME.
YEAH?
I HEARD $5OO.
WELL, YOU HEARD
WRONG, JANE.
I ALSO HEARD YOU AIN'T LONG
FOR THE TERRITORY, BILLY.
WE'RE NOT. WE'RE GOING TO
OLD MEXICO, RIGHT, BILLY?
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
HOW OLD'S THIS FELLA?
14 AND--
17.
14 1/2.
OH, WELL,
DON'T FORGET THAT HALF.
THERE'S A LOT OF EXPERIENCE
PACKED INTO THAT HALF.
IT'S DIFFERENT.
WHAT? MY HAIR?
IT'S THE NEW FASHION.
YOU LIKE IT?
YEAH, YOUR HAIR,
BUT EVERYTHING.
THIS WHOLE TOWN,
OUTSIDE, TOO.
THEY GOT A CHURCH.
THIS AIN'T
WHITE OAKS.
YEAH, WELL, THERE'S 2,011
SOULS IN THIS TOWN, KID,
A LOT OF BACK EAST MONEY.
THE TOWN'S DIFFERENT.
IT'S RESPECTABLE.
YOU'RE NOT TELLING US
YOU'VE GONE RESPECTABLE
NOW, JANE, HAVE YOU?
NO. WELL, TO THE EYE
THAT DON'T KNOW NO BETTER,
YEAH, I HAVE.
WELL,
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
MY BOYS HERE WOULD LIKE
SOME BOONDA UPSTAIRS
RIGHT QUICK, DARLING.
DID I HEAR YOU SAY
YOU'D LIKE
AN EXCELLENT MALT
SIX-TIMES SERVED IN A ROOM
WITH A SOUTHERN VIEW?
YOU'RE A LADY
TO THE MANOR BORN, JANE.
TO THE MANOR BORN.
HE'S HURT PRETTY GOOD.
LOOKS LIKE THE MUSKRATS
ARE IN A TRAP.
THEY'RE CHEWING
THEIR OWN LEGS OFF.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE GOING NORTH.
SOUTH, YOU MEAN.
NO, I MEAN NORTH.
BUT, SHERIFF,
LAST TIME I HEARD,
OLD MEXICO'S
STILL SOUTH.
YOU EVER HEAR OF
A COYDOG, POE?
HALF COMMON DOG,
HALF COYOTE.
FEED ONE, HE KEEPS
COMING AROUND.
NO FEAR OF MAN.
KID'S A COYDOG.
HE'S COME 15O MILES
WITHOUT A TOWN.
RIGHT ABOUT NOW,
HE'S LOOKING FOR
SOME ATTENTION.
ASH!
HE AIN'T MY CONCERN.
[SPEAKING APACHE LANGUAGE]
OH!
SHERIFF, I THINK
I NEED TO HAVE A MOVEMENT.
ME, TOO.
UHH! UHH!
''OVER THE MOUNTAINS
OF THE MOON,
''DOWN THE VALLEY
OF THE SHADOW,
''RIDE, BOLDLY, RIDE,
THE SHADE REPLIED--
IF YOU SEEK
FOR ELDORADO!''
MY, THAT WAS HEAVENLY.
WHO WROTE IT?
JOSIAH ''DOC'' SCURLOCK.
WHO THE HELL'S THAT?
NOW, YOU COME BACK NOW.
WHOO!
[BED SHAKING
AND LAUGHTER]
[HOOFBEATS]
OH, NO.
BILLY!
LOOK OUT THE WINDOW,
THEY DON'T TOLERATE SCUM.
HELP ME GATHER
THE BOYS.
GO ON. GET ROLLING
DOWNSTAIRS.
BILLY THE KID!
ALIAS WILLIAM H. BONNEY!
IT'S DEPUTY CARLYLE.
I BEST GO SPEAK TO HIM.
...AND DAVE RUDABAUGH
OF LAS VEGAS!
HE SAID DAVE RUDABAUGH
I'M REAL HAPPY FOR YOU,
DAVE.
...BLACK KNIGHTS
ON THE PREMISES,
TURN YOUR BODIES
OVER TO THE LAW...
OR PERISH IN FLAME.
DEPUTY CARLYLE, WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON DOWN HERE?
BILLY THE KID,
WE HAVE JANE GREATHOUSE
HELD OUT HERE.
I'M COMING IN
TO TALK TO YOU.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS TO ME,
THE CITIZENS HERE
SAY THEY WILL STRING HER UP
AND BURN HER.
DO YOU AGREE TO THOSE TERMS?
DO I AGREE
TO THOSE TERMS?
HA HA HA!
WHO IS THIS GUY?
YES, SIR, WE AGREE
TO THOSE TERMS.
I'M GOING IN.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
PUT YOUR GUNS AWAY
AND LOOK RESPECTABLE.
LADIES, UPSTAIRS.
O'FOLLIARD, DISAPPEAR.
GENTLEMEN.
AHEM! AHEM!
GENTLEMEN, WHICH OF YOU
IS THE LEADER OF YOUR GANG?
THAT WOULD BE ME.
ARKANSAS DAVE.
YOU ARE NOT, DAVE.
I AM SO.
YOU ARE NOT.
I AM SO!
ARE NOT!
AHEM! GENTLEMEN,
I'M A DEPUTIZED MAN,
AND I DO THINGS
THE LAW WAY.
WHICH WAY?
LAW WAY.
LAW WAY. I SEE.
OK, GO AHEAD. GO AHEAD.
NOW, THE PEOPLE OUT THERE,
THEY DO THINGS
THEIR OWN WAY.
THEY GOT THEIR MINDS
SET ON A HANGING.
NOW,
IT'S GOING TO BE HELL
IF I CAN'T CONTROL
THIS SITUATION.
SO, WHAT I PROPOSE
IS THIS:
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE
AN INDIAN IN YOUR GROUP.
YES, SIR.
JOSE CHAVEZ Y CHAVEZ.
HE'S A MEXICAN-INDIAN.
HOW'D THAT BE?
WELL, THAT'LL BE
JUST FINE.
IF I CAN GIVE THIS INDIAN
TO THOSE PEOPLE OUT THERE,
THEY'LL BE
WELL SATISFIED.
THE REST OF YOU
CAN JUST RIDE OUT.
HA HA! YOU HEAR THAT,
CHAVEZ?
SIR, I AGREE
TO THOSE TERMS.
THEY'RE AN ANGRY MOB,
INDEED,
AND WE DO HAPPEN TO HAVE
AN INDIAN
ON THE PREMISES.
GIVE ME YOUR HAT.
NOW, MR. LAW WAY,
MAY I SEE YOUR HAT?
I REALLY DON'T SEE
HOW HATS ARE RELEVANT
IN THIS SITUATION.
I DO.
DAVE.
THE GENTLEMAN'S
JACKET.
THERE.
MR. CARLYLE!
NOW I CAN
TALK TO YOU.
NOW YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
SUCH A POLITICIAN.
CAN I TAKE THE INDIAN
WITH ME OR NOT?
THE INDIAN'S GOING OUT
TO SATISFY THE CROWD,
BUT YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE MEANING
OF THE WORD ''PALS.''
THINK I'D HAND
MY FRIEND OVER TO
A BUCKET OF MULE DUNG
LIKE YOU?
THAT'S AN INSULT.
TURN AROUND, CHIEF.
[GUNS COCK]
COME ON, CARLYLE!
YOU BRINGING HIM OUT OR NOT?
ALL RIGHT,
YOU WHITE CAPS!
WE'RE COMING OUT,
BUT WE'RE COMING OUT
SHOOTING!
GET READY FOR WAR!
[INDIAN WAR WHOOPING CALL]
UH-OH.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S DEPUTY CARLYLE.
THAT'S JAMES CARLYLE.
COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
THEY'RE LEAVING.
THEY'RE ALL SKINNING OUT.
PALS.
OF COURSE,
THEY WERE SKINNING OUT.
THEY HAD JUST MURDERED
THEIR OWN DEPUTY.
THEY PINNED THAT ONE
ON ME, TOO,
BUT I NEVER FIRED
ONE SHOT.
JUST SAYING ''HELLO,'' PAT?
DID YOU ENTERTAIN HIM?
MAYBE.
DID YOU LIKE IT?
REMEMBER THE TIME YOU, ME,
AND HIM LOCKED ALL THE DOORS,
STAYED UP TILL THE SUN,
BREAKING THE PLACE UP
WITH SIX-SHOOTERS?
EVERY BOTTLE IN THE BAR...
NAKED AS JAYBIRDS...
AND THERE WAS NO LAW.
NO LAW...
AND NO BARBED WIRE.
PATRICK,
I'M GOING TO PART
WITH A NASTY SECRET.
YOU USED TO MAKE ME
HOTTER THAN A JUNE BRIDE
SITTING BAREBACK
ON A DEPOT STOVE,
BUT I DON'T SHARE MY BED
WITH THE LAW.
AND I DON'T KEEP
WITH WHORES NO MORE.
SO AIN'T WE BOTH CONTENT?
JANE GREATHOUSE,
THE CITIZENS OF WHITE OAKS
HAVE PROCLAIMED THIS PLACE
THE DEVIL'S DEN.
AS SHERIFF
OF LINCOLN COUNTY,
I HAVE TO HONOR AND PROTECT
THEIR CIVIC VIRTUES.
I'LL SHOW THEM
WHAT MY CIVIC VIRTUES
LOOK LIKE,
ALL THOSE
STALL-FED TENDERFEET
WITH THEIR EASTERN
SHINPLASTER
AND THEIR SUNDAY WIVES
AND THEIR SUNDAY DRESSES
WITH THE PREACHER
AT THE BACK DOOR
BY MORNING
TO SEE IF THEY'VE GOT
THE CONNECTICUT BLUE LAWS
TATTOOED ON THEIR
LILY-WHITE BUTTOCKS!
LET IT BURN!
THE TOWN WILL BE
BETTER OFF--
OH, LORD.
AAAH!
I DON'T BELIEVE
I'M SEEING THIS.
WHOA!
THIS TOWN WILL
NEVER BE THE SAME.
WHITE OAKS,
YOU CAN KISS MY ASS!
SURE.
ANYTIME, HONEY.
HEY, IS THIS ONE
READY TO GO?
IT CAN GO,
DOWN IN THAT
NUMBER TWO LANE.
LET IT GO!
HEY!
YOU GOT ANY WATER?
OLD-TIMER,
WHEN DID THIS PLACE BOOM UP?
LAST WEEK.
COPPER?
NAH! GUANO.
BAT DROPPINGS.
BAT DROPPINGS?
I'VE BEEN
TO GOLD TOWNS,
SILVER TOWNS,
I'VE EVEN BEEN
TO TURQUOISE TOWNS,
BUT I'VE NEVER BEEN
TO A BAT SHIT TOWN.
CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE THE WOMEN.
YAH!
UGH!
YAH! YAH!
GO! GO! HEYAH!
AAH!
YAH!
WHOA!
ASSAY! ASSAY!
ASSAY!
AAAH!
WHOA!
WHEW!
UGH!
LET'S GO! HEYAH!
COME ON!
JESUS CHRIST!
EVEN THEIR HORSES
ARE CRAZY.
AAAH!
HEY!
HAH!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT TIME.
WE'LL GO BACK
THROUGH THE ARROYO.
WELL, THAT'S CONVENIENT,
AIN'T IT?
PARDON ME?
THE KID'LL BE LONG GONE.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT, PAT.
WHAT I WANT
IS FOR YOU TO CORK
YOUR GOD DAMN
GOVERNMENT MOUTH,
AND THE NEXT TIME
YOU ADDRESS ME COMMON,
I WILL PUT YOU ON
YOUR PRISSY LITTLE ASS.
SWEET MARY'S ASS!
HOW THE HELL DID YOU
GET THEM TO DO THAT?
WHAT'S THAT MEAN
ANYWAY? ASSAY, ASSAY?
IT'S AN ANCIENT
NAVAHO WORD.
IT MEANS STOP.
STOP?
YAH! YAH!
WHEN WE GET TO THE TOP
OF THIS BLUFF,
WE'LL HAVE A CLEAR VIEW
OF THE NACHITA RIVER.
WE'LL SELL
THE HORSES OFF,
AND THEN WE'LL TAKE A SKIFF
DOWNRIVER INTO MEXICO.
HEY, TOMMY,
LAST ONE UP THE HILL'S
A THREE-LEGGED DOG!
WHOO!
YAY!
BILLY!
IS THIS OLD MEXICO?
NO.
IT'S GARRETT!
GET DOWN, TOM!
I GOT HIM.
UHH! UHH! UHH!
Oh, my God.
YOU SHOT ME.
YOU REALLY SHOT ME.
TAKE YOUR MEDICINE, SON.
WELL,
IT'S A START.
[SINGING IN NAVAHO LANGUAGE]
I SPENT A LOT OF NIGHTS
IN THIS CABIN
AFTER THE LINCOLN WAR.
TRIED TO PUT
ANOTHER OUTFIT TOGETHER,
BUT IT WAS NEVER THE SAME.
WHEN YOU BOYS CAME BACK,
I FELT LIKE THERE WAS NOTHING
I WOULDN'T DO
TO KEEP THE GANG TOGETHER,
KEEP RIDING.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
CHIVATO?
YOU KNOW WHAT
THE MEXICAN BLACKBIRD IS?
A BROKEN TRAIL THAT
LEADS TO OLD MEXICO.
IT'S A HALF-BLACK,
HALF-MEXICAN WHORE
UP IN PUERTO DE LUNA.
SO YOU MEAN...
YOU NAMED THE TRAIL
AFTER HER, RIGHT?
THERE IS NO TRAIL,
IS THERE, BILLY?
IS THERE?
WHAT ABOUT OLD MEXICO?
YOU PROMISED US.
I'D BE JUST ANOTHER
GRINGO IN OLD MEXICO.
IT'S THE SAME
AS BEING DEAD.
WHAT ABOUT TOMMY?
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU'RE STARTING TO BELIEVE
WHAT THEY'RE WRITING ABOUT YOU,
AREN'T YOU?
LET ME TELL YOU
WHAT YOU REALLY ARE.
YOU RODE A 15-YEAR-OLD BOY
STRAIGHT INTO HIS GRAVE...
AND THE REST OF US
STRAIGHT TO HELL.
YOU, BONNEY...
YOU ARE NOT A GOD.
WHY DON'T YOU PULL
THE TRIGGER AND FIND OUT?
I GOT TO GET BACK HOME.
UGH!
DOC!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
WE'RE NOT IN POSITION YET!
THEY KILLED HIM!
THAT BASTARD KILLED YOU!
GET UP, DOC!
COME ON. GET UP!
YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE!
HE'S A DEAD MAN!
THEY'RE STARTING TO SURROUND US.
WE GOT TO SKIN OUT OF HERE!
PAT!
WE GOT TO
MAKE A BREAK.
DON'T LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK UP.
SO WHO'S GOING TO
BUST OUT FIRST?
HENDRY WILLIAM FRENCH,
YOU NEVER KILLED NOBODY.
THEY AIN'T GONNA
SHOOT AT YOU.
GO TO HELL!
THEY SHOT TOMMY!
SOMEBODY'S
GOTTA DO IT!
THERE MUST BE AT LEAST
1O OF THEM OUT THERE.
GET ME UP.
DAVE...
IT'S YOUR GANG.
WHAT?
YOU LEAD US OUT.
IT AIN'T MY GANG!
IT'S YOUR GANG!
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN
YOUR GANG.
DON'T CROSS ME, DAVE.
BILLY!
LET'S FINISH THE GAME.
AAAAH!
GO! GO!
COME ON, CHAVEZ! GO!
AAAH!
AAH!
WHAT THE HELL DID
YOU DO THAT FOR?
PAT!
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU KILLED A BOY!
AAAH!
AND YOU KILLED DOC!
YOU KNEW HIM!
CHAVEZ IS BACK THERE!
FORGET ABOUT HIM.
HE'S BUZZARD MEAT.
COME ON!
THEY ALL ARE!
IT'S JUST YOU
AND ME, FARM BOY!
WE GOT TO HEAD
FOR THE BORDER.
SHIT.
AAH!
AAAH!
HIYAH!
OH!
AAAH!
[GUNS COCKING]
IT IS THEREFORE CONSIDERED
BY THE COURT HERE
THAT SAID DEFENDANT
WILLIAM H. BONNEY--
ALIAS KID,
ALIAS WILLIAM ANTRIM,
ALIAS HENRY McCARTY--
BE CONFINED IN PRISON
IN SAID LINCOLN COUNTY
BY THE SHERIFF
OF SUCH COUNTY
UNTIL ON THE DAY AFORESAID
HE BE TAKEN FROM SUCH PRISON
TO A SUITABLE AND CONVENIENT
PLACE OF EXECUTION
WITHIN SAID COUNTY,
AND THERE BE HANGED
BY THE NECK
TILL HE BE DEAD, DEAD, DEAD.
NOW, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY, YOUNG MAN?
YES, YOUR HONOR, I DO.
AHEM.
YOU CAN GO TO HELL,
HELL, HELL.
[GAVEL BANGS]
HA HA HA HA!
I GOT 18 DIMES
IN EACH BARREL, BOY.
YOU EVER SEE WHAT $1.8O CAN DO
TO A $4O.OO STEER,
LET ALONE A CHEAP LITTLE CROOK
LIKE YOURSELF?
PLTHTH!
YOU JUST
TAUNT ME AGAIN, BOY.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING.
JUST TAUNT ME AGAIN.
I WANT TO TALK
TO GARRETT.
HE'S IN MESILLA.
GOT A BIG INTERVIEW
AND A TINTYPE
WITH THEINDEPENDENT.
OH, YES. FAMOUS MAN NOW.
HEY, BELL,
DID YOU SEND MY LETTER
TO THE GOVERNOR,
OR DID YOU BURN IT?
IT WAS SENT, KID.
THE SHERIFF HAD ME PUT IT
ON THE MAIL STAGE MYSELF.
THEN WHY
ISN'T HE ANSWERING?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE AIN'T ONE
FOR CORRESPONDENCE.
MY SISTER UP IN COLORADO'S
LIKE THAT.
WELL, I CAN--
WILL YOU JUST
SHUT THE HELL UP, BELL?
CHAVEZ.
CHAVEZ,
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT?
YEAH, YEAH. YOU?
JUST FINE.
OK, BELL,
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE
TO PROVE THAT THE HAND
IS QUICKER THAN YOUR MIND.
ARE YOU READY?
ARE YOU WATCHING?
PSHOO!
HA HA HA!
[FOOTSTEPS]
MA'AM?
HELLO, JANE.
MAY I VISIT
MR. BONNEY?
I'M AN
OLD ACQUAINTANCE.
NO, MA'AM.
THAT AIN'T POSSIBLE.
SHERIFF GARRETT WON'T
ALLOW ANY VISITATIONS.
WELL, MAY I LEAVE A GIFT
FOR HIM THEN?
YOU OPEN UP A NEW
ROOMING ESTABLISHMENT,
GREATHOUSE?
HELL, NO.
I OPENED A GOOD
SAWDUST-ON-THE-FLOOR,
PROPER WHOREHOUSE.
AHEM. MA'AM?
WELL, GOOD-BYE,
WILLIAM H. BONNEY.
THANK YOU.
[FARTING SOUND]
OOPS!
[LAUGHING]
ALL RIGHT, KID.
LET YOUR
SQUIRREL GO.
MUY PRONTO!
I WOULDN'T GO IN THERE
IF I WERE YOU.
KID?
HI.
YOO-HOO, BELL.
I'LL MAKE YOU FAMOUS.
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T DO IT, BELL.
BELL, COME ON,
DON'T DO IT.
I AIN'T KIDDING.
BELL!
THAT WAS STUPID, BELL.
BELL KILL HIM?
DID BELL KILL THE KID?
HELLO, BOB!
SHIT!
IT'S THE KID!
GOOD-BYE, BOB.
BEST $1.8O
I EVER SPENT!
HAH!
QUIT NAPPING
ON THE JOB, BOB!
HA HA HA HA!
HEY, UH,
IS THIS OLD MEXICO HERE?
#ESTA E MEXICO,
HUH, AMIGOS?
WHOA HO HO!
I MADE IT!
WHY, YOUDOKNOW
WHO I AM, DON'T YOU?
ARKANSAS DAVE RUDABAUGH?
YOU KNOW THE NAME?
THEY KNOW THE NAME.
[CHILDREN'S VOICES]
BUENAS TARDES, AMIGOS.
YOU'RE NOT DEAD.
DO I LOOK DEAD?
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE SHORT WORK
I MADE OF BOB OLLINGER.
SPREAD HIM OUT
LIKE TULAROSA.
BWUUSSHH!
WE'RE SKINNING OUT.
THERE'S A HERD OF SLOW ELK
RESTING UP
AT GREZCHELOWSKI'S SHEEP CAMP.
WE'LL CUT THEM,
THEN WE'LL RIDE FOR CANADA.
CHAVEZ,
MAKE SURE THE HORSES
ARE WATERED.
HENDRY--
I'LL BE STAYING HERE.
YOU STAY HERE,
AND GARRETT'LL TAKE YOU.
GARRETT ALREADY TOOK ME.
WHEN?
WHEN HE TOOK DOC.
THAT'S A BAD SHOT,
CHAVEZ.
A MAN GETS SHOT
LIKE THAT, IT'S, UH...
IT'S OVER.
UHHH!
BOY, I GUESS I--
I GUESS I REALLY GOT US
INTO IT THIS TIME, HUH?
IT AIN'T SUPPOSED TO BE YOU
SITTING THERE LIKE THAT.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ME.
CHIVATO.
WHERE YOU GOING?
CHAVEZ?
CHAVEZ.
BUCKSHOT GEORGE.
THAT'S YOUR NAME.
YOU WANTED A NAME.
THAT'S IT.
BUCKSHOT GEORGE.
IT'S A GOOD NAME.
MY NAME'S
HENDRY WILLIAM FRENCH.
THAT'S A GOOD NAME, TOO.
[FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
WHOO! HOO HOO HOO!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
HA HA HA HA!
[APPLAUSE]
[YELLING AND CHEERING]
BILLITO.
IN THE ICEHOUSE--
A FRESH BEEF.
PETE MAXWELL BUTCHER
THIS MORNING.
BRING BACK HERE,
AND I COOK FOR YOU.
YOU ARE HUNGRY, NO?
SI. TENGO HAMBRE.
LET'S FINISH THE GAME.
PETE?
PETE, DID YOU BUTCHER
THIS MORNING?
[CLICK]
#QUIEN ES?
I SHOT EVERYTHING
IN THE WORLD EXCEPT YOU,
BUT YOU STILL
WOULDN'T GO BELOW.
WHY?
THE SAME REASON
YOU COULDN'T STAY HERE
AND RUN A CANTINA.
BUT YOU'D BE ALIVE.
IN OLD MEXICO,
YOU'D BE ALIVE.
I'M STILL ALIVE, PAT,
AND I BELONG HERE.
NOT NO MORE, BILLY.
THE PEOPLE LIKE ME HERE.
THEY WANT ME HERE.
NOT NO MORE, BILLY.
YOU GONNA SHOOT ME, PAT?
I GOT NO CHOICE.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
YOU COULD
LET ME GO, PAT.
I COULD WALK
OUT THAT DOOR
AND HEAD STRAIGHT
FOR OLD MEXICO.
YOU COULD SAY
YOU KILLED ME.
NO ONE
WOULD EVER KNOW.
YOU'D COME BACK...
LIKE A DAMN NIGHTMARE.
SHOW UP IN ARIZONA
STEALING COWS,
AND THEY'D STONE ME.
YOU KILLED THE BOYS,
PATSY!
NO, BILLY...
YOU DID.
IF I WAS WITH YOU,
I'D BE ONE OF THEM.
THIS HURTS, KID,
BUT I'M IN A PLACE
I CAN'T GET OUT OF...
AND I GOTTA DO IT.
YEAH.
YOU GOTTA DO IT, PAT.
DO IT.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS SAID
THAT IF I CARED FOR SOMEONE,
THERE'S NOTHING
I WOULD FAIL TO DO.
SO I'M GOING TO
MAKE IT EASY ON YOU.
YOU REMEMBER SOMETHING,
PAT.
YOU'LL NEVER BE ME.
YOU'LL ONLY BE THE MAN
THAT SHOT BILLY THE KID.
HASTA LA VISTA.
HASTA LA VISTA,
YOU CRAZY SON OF A BITCH.
[SCREAMING]
[PRIEST SPEAKING LATIN]
REMEMBER WILLIAM BONNEY,
''DUST THOU ART,
AND UNTO DUST
THOU SHALT RETURN.''
[LAUGHTER]
YEAH. OH, YEAH...
I NEVER STOLE A HORSE
FROM SOMEONE I DIDN'T LIKE.
DID I LIKE HIM?
HELL, NO.
I LOVED THE SON OF A BITCH.
YOU ASK ME IF I HAVE SCARS.
YES, SIR, I HAVE MY SCARS.
MR. ROBERTS.
BILL, WAIT.
BILLY!
I DON'T THINK SO,
DAVE.
AAAHHH!
[GUNFIRE]
PALS.
ASSAY!
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
Bon Jov:
?? I WAKE UP IN THE MORNING ??
?? AND I RAISE MY WEARY HEAD ??
?? I'VE GOT AN OLD COAT
FOR A PILLOW ??
?? AND THE EARTH
WAS LAST NIGHT'S BED ??
??
?? I DON'T KNOW WHERE I'M GOING
?? ONLY I KNOWS
WHERE I'VE BEEN ??
?? I'M A DEVIL ON THE RUN ??
?? A SIX-GUN LOVER ??
?? A GAMBLE IN THE WIND ??
?? YEAH ??
I'LL MAKE YOU FAMOUS.
HA HA HA HA HA!
?? WHEN YOU'RE BROUGHT
INTO THIS WORLD ??
?? WITH A SEA OF BONE AND SIN ??
?? WELL, AT LEAST
THE GAME IS SOMETHING ??
?? I DIDN'T HAVE TO STEAL
OR HAVE TO WIN ??
?? WELL, THEY TELL ME
THAT I'M WANTED ??
?? YEAH, I'M A WANTED MAN ??
?? I'M A COLT IN YOUR STABLE ??
?? I'M WHAT CAIN WAS TO ABEL ??
?
?? MISTER, CATCH ME IF YOU CAN ?
?? I'M GOING DOWN
IN A BLAZE OF GLORY ??
?? TAKE ME NOW,
BUT KNOW THE TRUTH ??
?? WELL, I'M GOING DOWN
IN A BLAZE OF GLORY ??
?? WELL, LORD,
I NEVER DREW FIRST ??
?? BUT I DREW FIRST BLOOD
I'M THE DEVIL'S SON ??
?? CALL ME YOUNG GUN ??
?? YEAH ??
?? SHOT DOWN
IN A BLAZE OF GLORY ??
?? TAKE ME NOW,
BUT KNOW THE TRUTH ??
?? WELL, I'M GOING OUT
IN A BLAZE OF GLORY ??
??
?? LORD, I NEVER DREW FIRST
?? BUT I DREW FIRST BLOOD,
AND I KNOW WHAT SIDE ??
?? CALL ME YOUNG GUN ??
?? I'M A YOUNG GUN ??
?? YOUNG GUN ??
?? YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ??
?? YOUNG GUN ????
?? I'VE JUST SEEN TROUBLE ??
?? HE'S CALLING OUT
YOUR NAME TONIGHT ??
??
?? YOU BETTER GET YOUR GUNS
?? YOU COULD WALK AWAY ??
?? BUT I KNOW
YOU WERE BORN TO FIGHT ??
??
?? SO, BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS
?? THEBANDOLEROSWERE STRUNG OUT
IN THE PROMENADE ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?? AND THE WIND WHISPERED
SOFTLY ??
?? THAT THE DEVIL'S TO BLAME ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?? THERE'S TROUBLE BLOWING
LIKE A HURRICANE ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?? THERE'S A PRICE ON YOUR HEAD
FOR THE PRICE OF FAME ??
?? AND IT'LL NEVER CHANGE ??
?? THEY CHRISTEN YOU
WITH WHISKEY ??
?
?? AND THERE'S FIRE
RUNNING THROUGH YOUR VEINS ?
?? WELL, YOU'RE AN OUTLAW
JUST THE SAME ??
?? AND EVERY NIGHT,
A BULLET WEARS YOUR NAME ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?? THERE'S TROUBLE BLOWING
LIKE A HURRICANE ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?? THERE'S A PRICE ON YOUR HEAD
FOR THE PRICE OF FAME ??
?? AND IT'LL NEVER CHANGE ??
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ??
?
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS... ?
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS.
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.nccap.org--
?? BILLY, GET YOUR GUNS ????
www.moviesubtitles.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org