Out west there was this fella,
fella I want to tell you about,
fella by the name
of Jeff Lebowski -
at least that's the handle
his parents gave him.
But he never had
much use for it himself.
This Lebowski,
he called himself the Dude.
Now, Dude, that's a name
no one would self-apply
where I come from.
There was a lot about the Dude
that didn't make sense to me,
and a lot about
where he lived, likewise.
But then again,
maybe that's why I found
the place so darn interesting.
They call Los Angeles
the City of Angels.
I didn't find it
to be that exactly.
But there are
some nice folks there.
'Course I can't
say I seen London,
and I never been to France,
and I ain't never seen
no queen in her damned undies.
But I'll tell you what,
after seeing Los Angeles
and this story
I'm about to unfold,
well, I guess I seen somethin'
every bit as stupefyin'
as you'd see
in any other places,
and in English, too.
So I can die
with a smile on my face
without feeling like
the good Lord gypped me.
Now, this story
I'm about to unfold
took place
back in the early 90s,
about the time of our conflict
with Saddam and the Iraqis.
I only mention it 'cause
sometimes there's a man -
I won't say a hero,
'cause what's a hero?
But sometimes there's a man -
and I'm talking
about the Dude here -
sometimes there's a man...
Well, he's the man
for his time and place.
He fits right in there,
and that's the Dude,
in Los Angeles.
And even if he's a lazy man,
and the Dude was
most certainly that,
quite possibly the laziest
in Los Angeles county,
which would place him high
in the running
for laziest worldwide.
But sometimes there's a man,
sometimes...
there's a man...
Wow, lost my train
of thought here.
But... ah, hell.
I done introduced him enough.
'This will not stand.
'This will not stand,
this aggression against Kuwait.'
Where's the money, Lebowski?
I want that money, Lebowski.
Bunny says you're good for it.
Where's the money, Lebowski?
Where's the fucking
money, shithead?
It's down there somewhere.
Let me take another look.
Don't fuck with us!
Your wife owes money
to Jackie Treehorn.
That means you owe
money to Jackie Treehorn.
Ever thus
to deadbeats, Lebowski.
Don't do that...
- Not on the rug, man.
- See?
See what happens, Lebowski?
You see what happens?
Nobody calls me Lebowski.
You got the wrong man.
I'm the Dude, man.
Your name's Lebowski, Lebowski.
Your wife is Bunny.
My... my wife... my wife, Bunny?
Do you see a wedding ring?
Does this place
look like I'm married?
The toilet seat's up, man.
What the fuck is this?
Obviously, you're not a golfer.
- Woo?
- Yeah?
Isn't this guy supposed
to be a millionaire?
Fuck!
- Yeah, what do you think?
- He looks like a fucking loser.
Hey, at least I'm housebroken.
Fucking time wasted.
Thanks a lot, asshole.
I'm throwing rocks tonight.
Mark it, Dude.
This was a valued rug.
This was a...
It really
tied the room together.
So this was a valued...
- What tied the room together?
- My rug.
- Were you listening, Donny?
- What?
Were you listening
to the Dude's story?
I was bowling.
You have no frame of reference,
like a child who wanders in...
Walter, what's the point?
There's no reason -
here's my point, Dude -
- there's no reason...
- Yeah, what's your point?
- Huh?
- Walter, what is the point...
We know who is at fault here.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
No, what the fuck are you...
I'm not...
We're talking about
unchecked aggression here.
- What is he talking about?
- My rug.
Forget it,
you're out of your element.
The Chinaman who peed on my rug,
I can't go give him a bill.
So what the fuck
are you talking about?
The Chinaman
is not the issue here.
I'm talking about
drawing a line in the sand.
Across this line, you do not...
Also, Dude, "Chinaman" is not
the preferred nomenclature.
"Asian-American," please.
This isn't a guy who built
the railroads here...
- What the fuck...
- He peed on my rug.
- He peed on the Dude's rug.
- You're out of your element!
Dude, the Chinaman
is not the issue here.
- So, who... who...
- Jeff Lebowski.
The other Jeffrey Lebowski,
the millionaire.
That's fucking interesting, man.
That's fucking interesting.
Plus, he has the wealth
and the resources...
so there's no reason,
no fucking reason
why his wife
should go out, owe money,
and then they pee
on your fucking rug!
- Am I wrong?
- No.
- But...
OK, then.
That rug really tied
the room together, did it not?
- Fuckin' A!
- And he peed on it.
Donny, please.
I could find this
fucking Lebowski guy.
His name is Lebowski?
That's your name, Dude.
He should compensate me
for the fucking rug.
His wife owes money,
and they pee on my rug?
- They pee on your fucking rug.
- They peed on my fucking rug.
That's right, Dude.
They peed on your fucking rug.
This is the study.
The various commendations...
Jeffrey Lebowski.
- Honorary degrees, etcetera.
- Very impressive.
Oh, please feel free
to inspect them.
- Oh, I'm not really that...
- Oh, please, please.
That is the key
to the city of Pasadena,
which Mr Lebowski received in
recognition of various civic...
Oh, that's the Los Angeles
Chamber of Commerce
Business Achiever Award,
which is... not
necessarily given every year.
Hey, is this, uh,
is this him with Nancy?
Yes, indeed, that is Mr Lebowski
with the First Lady...
That's Lebowski
on the left there?
Of course.
Mr Lebowski on the left...
He's a cripple... you know,
a... handicapped guy?
Mr Lebowski is disabled, yes.
This picture was taken
when Mrs Reagan was
First Lady of the nation.
- Yes, yes. Not of California.
- Pope John.
He met privately
with the president,
but there was no time
for a photo opportunity.
- Nancy's pretty good.
- Wonderful woman!
These are...
Those are Mr Lebowski's
children, so to speak.
Different mothers?
Racially, pretty cool.
They're not literally
his children.
They're the Little
Lebowski Urban Achievers,
inner-city children of promise
but without the means
for a higher education.
Mr Lebowski is committed
to sending them to college.
Excuse me. Thank you, thank you.
Far out. Think he's
got room for one more?
One, uh... Oh!
You never went to college.
Please, don't touch that.
Yeah, I did, but I spent
most of my time...
occupying various
administration buildings,
smoking a lot of Thai stick,
breaking into the R.O.T.C.
And bowling.
To tell you the truth,
I don't remember much.
OK, sir, you're a Lebowski,
I'm a Lebowski,
that's terrific.
But I'm very busy,
as I imagine you are.
What can I do for you, sir?
Well, sir, it's this rug I have,
it really tied
the room together...
You told Brandt, he told me.
Where do I fit in?
Well, they were
looking for you, these guys.
I'll say it again.
You told Brandt
on the phone, he told me.
I know what happened. Yes?
So you know that they were
trying to piss on your rug?
Did I urinate on your rug?
Did you personally
come and pee on my rug?
Hello! Do you speak English?
Parla usted ingles?
I'll ask you again.
Did I urinate on your rug?
No, like I said,
Woo peed on my rug.
I want to understand this, sir.
Every time a rug is
micturated upon in this city,
I have to compensate...
Come on, man, I'm not
trying to scam anybody here.
I... I was just...
You're just looking for
a handout like every other...
Are you employed, Mr Lebowski?
Wait, let me
explain something to you.
I am not Mr Lebowski.
You're Mr Lebowski.
I'm the Dude.
So that's what you call me,
you know, uh, that
or, uh, his Dudeness,
or Duder, or, you
know, uh, el Duderino,
if you're not into
the whole brevity thing.
- Are you employed, sir?
- Employed?
You don't look for a job
dressed like that on a weekday?
Is this a... What day is this?
Well, I do work, sir.
So if you don't mind...
No, I do mind. The Dude minds.
This will not stand, you know.
This aggression
will not stand, man.
- I mean, your wife owes...
- My wife is not the issue!
I hope that my wife will learn
to live on her ample allowance.
If not, that's
her problem, not mine,
just as the rug is your problem,
just as every bum's lot in life
is his own responsibility,
regardless of who
he chooses to blame.
I didn't blame anyone
for the loss of my legs.
Some Chinaman
took them from me in Korea.
But I went out
and achieved anyway.
I cannot solve your problems,
sir, only you can.
- Oh, fuck it.
- "Oh, fuck it."
Yes, that's your answer
to everything.
Tattoo it on your forehead.
Your revolution
is over, Mr Lebowski!
Condolences! The bums lost!
My advice to you
is to do what your parents did!
Get a job, sir!
The bums will always lose!
Do you hear me, Lebowski?
The bums...
How was your meeting,
Mr Lebowski?
OK. The old man told me
to take any rug in the house.
Well, enjoy, and perhaps
we'll see you again, Dude.
Sure, if I'm in
the neighbourhood, you know,
and, um...
I need to use the john.
Blow on them.
Go ahead, blow.
You want me to blow
on your toes?
Uh-huh. I can't blow that far.
Are you sure he won't mind?
He doesn't care about anything.
He's a nihilist.
Oh, that must be exhausting.
You're not blowing.
He has to be getting along,
Mrs Lebowski.
Oh, you're Bunny.
I'll suck your cock for $1,000.
Wonderful woman.
We're very fond of her.
Very free-spirited.
Brandt can't watch,
or he has to pay 100.
That's marvellous.
I'm just gonna
go find a cash machine.
Whoo! Slamming them tonight!
You guys are dead in the water.
All right! Way to go, Donny!
If you will it, it is no dream.
You're 20 minutes late, man.
What the fuck is that?
Theodore Herzel.
The state of Israel. If you
will it, Dude, it is no dream.
The carrier. What's
in the fucking carrier?
Oh, Cynthia's dog.
I think it's a Pomeranian.
I can't leave him,
he eats the furniture.
I'm watching it
while they're in Hawaii.
- You brought it bowling?
- "Brought it bowling"?
I didn't rent it shoes,
I'm not buying it a beer,
he's not taking your turn, Dude.
If my ex-wife asked me
to take care of her dog
while she and her boyfriend
went to Honolulu,
I'd tell her to fuck herself.
Dude, you don't have an ex,
and this is a fucking show dog
with fucking papers.
You can't board it. It gets
upset. Its hair falls out.
Over the line!
Sorry, you were over the line.
That's a foul.
Bullshit. Mark it 8, Dude.
Excuse me, mark it zero.
Next frame.
Bullshit, Walter.
Mark it 8, Dude.
This is not 'Nam, this
is bowling. There are rules.
Hey, Walter, come on,
it's Smokey.
His toe slipped over.
It's just a game.
It determines who enters
the round-robin. Am I wrong?
- Yeah, but...
- Am I wrong?
Yeah, but I wasn't over.
Give me the marker, Dude.
I'm marking an 8.
Smokey, my friend,
you're entering a world of pain.
- Walter...
- You mark that frame an 8,
you're entering a world of pain.
- I'm not...
- A world of pain.
Look, Dude,
this is your partner.
Has the world gone crazy?
Am I the only one
who cares about the rules?
Mark it zero!
- They're calling the cops.
- Mark it zero!
- Put the piece away.
- Walter...
You think I'm fucking around?
Mark it zero!
All right, it's fucking zero.
You happy, you crazy fuck?
It's a league game, Smoke.
You can't do that, man.
These guys are like me.
They're pacifists.
Smokey was
a conscientious objector.
I myself dabbled in pacifism,
not in 'Nam, of course.
You know he's got
emotional problems.
You mean, beyond pacifism?
He's fragile, very fragile.
I did not know that.
Well, it's all
water under the bridge,
and we do enter
the next round-robin.
- Am I wrong?
- No, you're not wrong.
- No, you're just an asshole!
OK. We play Quintana
and O'Brien next week.
They should be pushovers.
Man, will you just...
Just take it easy, man.
That's your answer
for everything, Dude.
Look at our current situation
with that camelfucker in Iraq.
Pacifism is not
something to hide behind.
Just take it easy, man.
I'm perfectly calm, Dude.
- Waving the fucking gun around?
- Calmer than you are.
Just take it easy!
Calmer than you are.
'Dude, this is Smokey.
'I don't want to
be a hard-on about this.
'I know it wasn't your fault,
'but Gilbert and I
will submit this to the league
'and ask them
to set aside the round,
'maybe forfeit it to us.
'So, like I say,
you know, fair warning.
'Tell Walter. I'm sorry.'
'Mr Lebowski,
this is Brandt at, uh,
'well, at Mr Lebowski's office.
'Please, call us
when it's convenient.'
'This is Bill Selliger of
the Southern Cal Bowling League.
'I just got an informal report
'that a member of your team,
a Walter Sobchak,
'drew a firearm during play.
'This contravenes a number
of by-laws and article 27... '
- Dude.
- Hey, Monty.
Dude, I... I finally got...
the venue I wanted.
I'm performing my dance quintet,
you know, my cycle,
at Crane Jackson's Fountain
Street Theatre on Tuesday night.
And, well, I'd love it
if you came and gave me notes.
I'll be there, man.
Tomorrow's already the 10th.
Far out.
Oh. Oh, all right, OK.
Just slip the rent
under my door.
'... serious infraction
'and examine your standing.
Thank you.'
'Mr Lebowski, Brandt again.
'Please, call when you get in,
and I'll send a limo.
'I hope you're not avoiding
this call because of the rug,
'which, I assure you,
is not a problem.
'We need your help, and, uh...
'well, we'd like to see you.
'Thank you. It's Brandt.'
We've had terrible news.
Mr Lebowski's in seclusion.
Mr Lebowski.
Funny...
I can look back
on a life of achievement,
challenges met,
competitors bested,
obstacles overcome.
I've accomplished more
than most men
and without the use of my legs.
What...
What makes a man, Mr Lebowski?
Dude.
I... I don't know, sir.
Is it being prepared
to do the right thing?
Whatever the cost?
Isn't that what makes a man?
Sure, that
and a pair of testicles.
You're joking. But...
Perhaps you're right.
You mind if I do a "J"?
Bunny...
Excuse me?
Bunny Lebowski,
she is the light of my life.
Are you surprised
at my tears, sir?
Fuckin' A.
Strong men also cry.
I received this fax
this morning.
As you can see,
it is a ransom note.
"We have Bunnie."
Sent by men who can't achieve
on a level field of play.
"Gather one million dollars
in unmarked,
non-consecutive twenties."
- Weaklings!
- "Await instructions."
- Bums!
- "No funny stuff."
- Bummer.
- Huh?
This is a bummer, man.
That's, uh, that's a bummer.
Brandt will
fill you in on the details.
Mr Lebowski will make you
a generous offer
to act as courier once we get
instructions for the money.
Why me, man?
He believes the culprits
might be the people
who, uh... soiled your rug,
and you're in a unique position
to confirm or disconfirm this.
He thinks
the carpet-pissers did this?
Well, Dude, we just don't know.
Fucking Quintana.
That creep can roll, man.
Yeah, but he's a pervert, Dude.
Yeah.
No. He's a sex offender
with a record.
He did six months for exposing
himself to an 8-year-old.
When he moved to Hollywood,
he had to go door-to-door
to tell everyone
he was a pederast.
What's a pederast, Walter?
Shut the fuck up, Donny.
- So... How much they give you?
- 20 grand, man.
- And I get to keep the rug.
- Just for making a hand-off?
Yeah. They gave Dude a beeper.
- So whenever they call...
- What if it's during a game?
- If it's during league play...
- What's during league play?
Life doesn't stop and start
at your convenience,
- you piece of shit.
- What's wrong with Walter?
I figure it's easy money.
It's harmless.
- She probably did it herself.
- What do you mean, Dude?
Rug pee-ers didn't do this.
Look at it.
A young trophy wife
marries this guy for his money.
She figures
he isn't giving her enough.
You know, she owes money.
- That fuckin'... bitch.
- It's all goddamn fake, man.
It's like Lenin said.
You look for the person
who will benefit,
- and, uh, you know...
- I am the walrus?
You know, you'll, uh...
- You know what I'm saying.
- I am the walrus.
That fuckin' bitch!
- Shut the fuck up, Donny!
V.I. Lenin.
Vladimir Ilyich Ulyanov!
What the fuck
is he talking about?
Fucking exactly what happened.
That makes me sick.
- What do you care, Walter?
- Those rich fucks.
This whole fuckin' thing.
I didn't watch my buddies die
face-down in the mud
so that this fucking strumpet,
this fucking whore...
I don't see
any connection with Vietnam.
No literal connection.
Face it, there's no
connection. Your roll.
- But my point is...
- Your roll.
Are you ready to be fucked?
I see you roll your way
into the semis.
Dios mio, man.
Liam and me,
we're gonna fuck you up.
Yeah? Well... you know,
that's just like, uh...
your opinion, man.
Let me tell you
something, pendejo,
you pull any crazy shit with us,
you flash a piece out
on the lanes,
I'll take it
and stick it up your ass
and pull the fuckin' trigger
till it goes click.
- Jesus.
- You said it, man.
Nobody fucks with the Jesus.
8-year-olds, Dude.
Ohh, man.
They called 80 minutes ago.
Take the money,
drive north on the 405.
They will call you with
instructions in 40 minutes.
One person only. They were clear
on that, or I'd go with you.
- What happened to your jaw?
- Oh, nothin'.
Here's the money. And the phone.
Please, Dude,
follow their instructions.
All right.
- Her life is in your hands.
- Oh, man, don't say that.
Mr Lebowski asked me
to repeat that.
- Her life is in your hands.
- Shit, man.
Her life is in your hands, Dude.
Report back to us
as soon as it's done.
Where the fuck are you goin'?
Take the ringer. I'll drive.
- What? The what?
- The ringer.
The ringer, Dude.
- What the...
- Have they called?
- What the hell is this?
- My dirty undies, Dude.
Laundry. The whites.
I'm sure there's a reason
you brought your dirty undies.
The weight.
The ringer cannot look empty.
What the fuck are you thinking?
You're right, Dude.
I got to thinking,
why should we settle for
a measly fuckin' 20 grand...
We? You said
you just wanted to come along.
Why should we settle
for 20 grand
when we can keep
the entire million? Am I wrong?
Yes, you're wrong.
This isn't a game, man.
It is a game.
You said so yourself.
- She kidnapped herself.
- I said I thought...
- Dude here.
- 'Who is this?'
Dude the bagman.
Where do you want us to go?
- 'Us? '
- Shit!
Yeah, you know,
me and the driver.
I'm not handling the money,
driving the car...
- 'Shut the fuck up! '
- Are you fucking this up?
Who is that?
That is the driver.
I told you...
- Shit!
- What the fuck's goin' on?
- Walter!
- What the fuck is goin' on?
He hung up! You fucked it up!
You fucked it up!
- Her life was in our hands.
- Easy, Dude.
We're screwed now.
We don't get shit.
They're gonna kill her.
We're fucked, Walter.
Nothing is fucked, Dude.
You're being very unDude.
They'll call back.
She kidnapped...
You see?
Nothing's fucked here, Dude.
They're a bunch
of fuckin' amateurs!
Hey, will you shut the fuck up?
Don't say peep
while I'm doin' business here.
OK, Dude, have it your way.
- But they're amateurs.
- Fuck.
- Dude.
- 'OK, we proceed,
'but only if there's
no funny stuff.'
Yeah, yeah.
'So no funny stuff, OK? '
Just tell me
where the fuck to go.
That was the sign, man.
So all we gotta do
is get her back.
No one can complain,
and we keep the baksheesh.
Terrific, Walter,
but how are we
gonna get her back?
That's the simple part, Dude.
We make the hand-off,
I grab one, beat it out of him.
- Huh?
- Yeah. That's a great plan.
That's fucking ingenious,
if I understand it correctly.
It's a Swiss fuckin' watch.
Yeah, the beauty
of this is its simplicity.
If it gets complex,
everything can go wrong.
If I learned one thing
in 'Nam, it's...
- Dude.
- 'You're coming to a bridge.
'When you cross the bridge,
'you throw the bag from the left
window. You're being watched.'
Fuck!
What'd he say?
Where's the hand-off?
There isn't one, we throw
the money out of the car.
We throw the money
out of the moving car!
We can't do that.
That fucks up our plan.
Call 'em and explain it to them.
You're plan is so simple
I'm sure they'll understand.
I'm throwin' the money, Walter.
We're not fuckin' around.
Bridge is comin' up.
Give me the ringer.
Fuck that. I love ya,
but you have to face the fact
- you're a goddamn moron.
- No time to argue.
- Hey, man.
- The bridge.
Hey, Walter! Hey! Walter!
There goes the ringer!
- What the fuck?
- Here, your wheel.
At 15 mph, I roll out,
grab one and beat it out of him.
- The Uzi.
- Uzi?
- I'm not rolling out naked.
- Walter, please!
15, Dude. This is it.
We have it! We have it!
We have it!
We... have it!
Aw, fuck it, Dude.
Let's go bowling.
Etz chaim he, Dude,
as the ex used to say.
What the fuck does that mean?
What the fuck
are we gonna tell Lebowski?
Huh? Oh, him. Uh...
Well, what exactly
is the problem?
The problem is...
What do you mean, what's the...
There was no...
We... we didn't, uh...
They're gonna kill
that poor woman.
The poor woman...
That poor slut kidnapped
herself. You said so yourself.
I said I thought
she kidnapped herself.
- You're the one who's certain.
- 100% certain.
- They posted the next round.
- Shut the fuck...
- When do we play?
- This Saturday.
Saturday?
They have to reschedule.
What am I gonna tell Lebowski?
I told that fuck
at the league office...
- Who's in charge of scheduling?
- Burkhalter.
I told that kraut
I don't roll on Shabbos.
- He already posted it.
- He can fuckin' unpost it!
Who gives a shit?
They're gonna kill that woman.
What am I gonna tell Lebowski?
She'll get tired
of her game and go back.
- Why not on Saturday?
- I'm Shomer Shabbos.
What's that?
What do I tell Lebowski?
Saturday is Shabbos,
the Jewish day of rest.
I don't work,
I don't drive a car,
I don't handle money,
I don't turn on the oven,
and I sure as shit
don't fucking roll!
Sheesh.
Shomer Shabbos!
- Walter, how am I gonna...
- Shomer fucking Shabbos.
- That's it! I'm outta here.
- Come on, Dude.
Dude! Dude!
Look, you just tell him...
Tell him we made the drop
and everything went...
- How'd it go?
- Went all right.
Walter, we didn't make
the fuckin' hand-off.
They didn't get the fuckin'
money! They're gonna...
They're gonna kill
that poor woman.
If you can't go by car, how
do you get around on Shammos?
Really, Dude, you surprise me.
They're not gonna do shit.
What can they do to her?
They're amateurs, and meanwhile,
who's sittin' on a million
fucking dollars? Am I wrong?
Who's got a million
fuckin' dollars in our car?
Our car, Walter?
What do they got? My dirty
undies. My fuckin' whites.
Say, Dude...
where is your car?
Who's got your undies?
- Where's your car, Dude?
- You don't know?
It was parked in a handicap
zone. Perhaps they towed it.
You fuckin' know
it's been stolen.
Well, certainly,
that's a possibility, Dude.
Oh, fuck it.
- Where you goin', Dude?
- I'm going home, Donny.
- Phone's ringing, Dude.
- Thank you, Donny.
Uh... yeah...
Green... uh, some brown or...
rust colouration.
Was there anything
of value in the car?
Oh. Uh, yeah...
a tape deck,
some Creedence tapes,
and there was a... uh...
My briefcase.
In the briefcase?
Uh, papers.
You know, just papers.
You know, my papers.
Business papers.
And what do you do, sir?
I'm unemployed.
My rug was also stolen.
Your rug was in the car?
No, here.
Separate incidents?
'The Dude is not in... '
Do you find them much,
these stolen cars?
Sometimes.
- No hope for the tape deck.
- Or the Creedence.
Well, what about, uh...
The briefcase?
'Mr Lebowski,
I'd like to see you.
'My name is Maude Lebowski.
I'm the one who took your rug.'
Guess we can close
the file on that one.
Elfranco, ayúdame abajo.
I'll be with you
in a moment, Mr Lebowski.
Does the female form make you
uncomfortable, Mr Lebowski?
Is that what
this is a picture of?
In a sense, yes.
My art is strongly vaginal,
which bothers some men.
The word itself makes some
men uncomfortable. Vagina.
Oh, yeah?
They find it difficult to say,
but without batting an eye,
a man will refer to his dick
or his rod or his... johnson.
- Johnson?
- All right, Mr Lebowski.
Let's get down to cases.
My father agreed
to let you have the rug,
but it was a gift from me
to my late mother,
and not his to give. Now...
Your face.
As for this kidnapping...
I know all about it,
and that you acted as courier.
Let me tell you something.
It stinks to high heaven.
Right, but let me explain
something about the rug.
- Do you like sex, Mr Lebowski?
- Excuse me?
Sex. The physical act of love.
Coitus. Do you like it?
I was talking about my rug.
- You're not interested in sex?
- You mean coitus?
I like it. It's a myth about
feminists that we hate sex.
It can be a natural, zesty
enterprise. But some people -
satyriasis in men,
nymphomania in women -
engage in it compulsively
and without joy.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes, Mr Lebowski.
They cannot love
in the true sense of the word.
Our mutual acquaintance,
Bunny, is one of these.
Listen, Maude,
um, I'm sorry if your
stepmother is a nympho,
but what has that
to do with, uh...
- Do you have any Kahlua?
- Take a look at this, sir.
Oh, I know that guy.
He's a nihilist.
Karl Hungus...
- 'Hi.
- Hello. Meine dispatcher says
'there's something
wrong mit deine kabel.
'Come in. I'm not sure
exactly what's wrong.
'Zat's why they sent me.
I am an expert.
- 'The TV's in here.'
- You recognise her, of course.
'That's my friend. She came
over to use the shower.'
The story is ludicrous.
'Meine name is Karl.
Ich bin expert.'
'You're here to fix the cable.'
You can imagine
where it goes from here.
- He fixes the cable?
- Don't be fatuous, Jeffrey.
Little matter that she pursues
a career in pornography
nor that she's been
"banging" Jackie Treehorn,
to use the parlance
of our times.
But I am one of the two trustees
of the Lebowski Foundation,
the other being my father.
The Foundation
takes youngsters...
Shit, yeah, the achievers.
Little Lebowski
Urban Achievers, yes.
I asked my father about
his withdrawal of $1 million,
and he told me
about this abduction.
It is preposterous.
This compulsive fornicator
is taking my father
for the proverbial ride.
- But my...
- I'm getting to your rug.
My father and I don't get along.
We don't approve
of each other's lifestyles.
But I hardly wish to make his
embezzlement a police matter.
I propose that you try
to recover the money.
Well, I could do that.
If you do so,
I will compensate you
to the tune of 10%
of the recovered sum.
A hundred...
...thousand, yes, bones or clams
or whatever you call them.
Yeah, but...
what about my, uh...
Your rug. With that money
you can buy any rug
that doesn't have
sentimental value for me.
I am sorry about
that crack on the jaw.
Oh, that's fine.
That doesn't even, uh...
Here's the number of a doctor
who will look at it.
You'll receive no bill.
He's a good man.
- That's thoughtful, but...
- Please see him.
He's a good man.
Oh, well... all right.
He says, "My wife's a pain.
"She's always bustin'
my friggin' agates.
"My daughter's married
to a loser bastard,
"and I got a rash
so bad on my ass
"I can't sit down. But you
know me, can't complain."
Fuckin' A, man.
I got a rash, man.
Fuckin' A.
I gotta tell you, man,
earlier in the day,
I was feeling shitty, man.
Down in the dumps.
Lost a little money...
Hey, you know what?
Forget about it.
I can't be worried about
that shit. Life goes on, man.
Home, sweet home, Mr L.
Look. Who's your friend
in the Volkswagen?
Yeah, he followed us here.
When did he start foll...
What the fuck?
In the limo, you son of a bitch.
No arguing.
Careful, man.
There's a beverage here.
Start talking and talk fast,
you lousy bum.
We've been trying
to reach you, Dude.
Where's my goddamn money,
you bum?
W-well, we...
I don't...
They did not receive
the money, you nitwit!
- Her life was in your hands!
- This is our concern, Dude.
No, man, nothing is fucked here.
- Nothing is fucked?
- No, man.
The goddamn plane
has crashed into the mountain!
Come on, who are you gonna
believe, those guys or...
We dropped off the damn money.
We?
I.
The royal we.
You know, the editorial.
I dropped off the money
exactly as per...
I've got certain
information, all right?
Certain things
have come to light, and...
Has it ever occurred to you
that instead of,
you know, running around,
blaming me, given the nature
of all this new shit,
this could be a lot more...
Complex?
I mean, it might not be
such a simple, uh... you know?
What in God's name
are you blathering about?
I'll tell you
what I'm blathering about.
I've got information.
New shit has come to light.
And, shit, man...
She kidnapped herself.
Well, sure, man.
Look at it.
A young trophy wife,
in the parlance of our times.
She owes money all over town,
including to
known pornographers.
And that's cool. That's cool.
I'm saying she needs money, man.
And... and, you know,
of course they're gonna say
they didn't get it,
because she wants more, man.
She's gotta feed the monkey.
I mean...
Hasn't that ever
occurred to you, man? Sir?
No, Mr Lebowski,
it had not occurred to me.
That had not occurred
to us, Dude.
You guys aren't privy
to all the new shit, so...
you know. But...
Hey, that's what you pay me for.
Speaking of which,
do you think that you could...
give me my 20,000 in cash?
My concern is... and I gotta
check with my accountant...
but this might bump me
into a higher tax...
Brandt... Give him the envelope.
Oh, if you've already got the
cheque made out, that's cool00Oh
We received this this morning.
Since you have
failed to achieve,
even in the modest task
which was your charge,
since you have stolen my money,
since you have unrepentantly
betrayed my trust...
I have no choice
but to tell these bums
to do whatever is necessary
to recover their money
from you, Jeffrey Lebowski.
With Brandt as my witness,
I will tell you this:
Any further harm
visited upon Bunny
will be visited tenfold
upon your head.
By God, sir, I will not
abide another toe.
That wasn't her toe, Dude.
- Whose toe was it, Walter?
- How the fuck should I know?
Nothing about it indicates...
- The nail polish, Walter.
- Fine, Dude.
You can get nail polish and
apply it to someone else's toe.
Where the fuck
are they gonna get...
You want a toe?
I can get you a toe.
Believe me,
there are ways, Dude.
You don't wanna know about it.
I can get you a toe
by 3 pm, with nail polish.
These fuckin' amateurs.
They send us a toe,
we're supposed to shit ourselves
with fear. Jesus Christ!
They're gonna kill her
and then me.
Dude... that's...
That's just
the stress talking, man.
We have what appears to me
to be a series
of victimless crimes.
- What about the toe?
- Forget about the fucking toe!
Could you keep your voices down?
This is a family restaurant.
Dear, for your information,
the Supreme Court
has rejected prior restraint!
This is not
a First Amendment thing.
If you don't calm down,
you'll have to leave.
Lady, my buddies died
face-down in the muck
so we could enjoy
this family restaurant!
- I'm outta here.
- Dude, don't go away, man.
This affects all of us.
There are basic freedoms!
I'm stayin'.
I'm finishing my coffee.
Enjoying my coffee.
'The Dude is not in.
'Leave a message after the beep.
Thanks, man.'
'Mr Lebowski, this is duty
officer Rolvaag of the LAPD.
'We've recovered
your automobile.
'It can be claimed at... '
Far out, man. Far fucking out!
Hey! This is
a private residence, man.
Ah, nice marmot.
Vere is the money, Lebowski.
Ve vant the money, Lebowski.
You zink ve are kidding
or making with the funny stuff?
Things you haven't
dreamed of, Lebowski.
Ve believes in nossing,
Lebowski, nossing.
Ve come back
and ve cut off your chonson.
Excuse me?
I said we'll
cut off your johnson!
Just think about that, Lebowski.
Ja, your viggly penis, Lebowski.
Maybe we stomp on it
and sqoosh it, Lebowski.
It was discovered last night
- lodged against an abutment.
- Oh, man, lodged where?
You're lucky she didn't
get chopped, Mr Lebowski.
A joyride situation.
They abandon the vehicle
once they hit the wall.
My fucking briefcase!
Man, it's not here. Shit!
I saw the report. Sorry.
You gotta get in
on the other side.
The side-view was found
on the road by the car.
You're lucky they left the
tape deck, and the Creedence.
Aw, Jesus!
What's that smell, man?
Probably a vagrant
slept in the car
or just used it as a toilet.
Hey, man...
Are you gonna find
these guys, you know...
I mean, you got any
promising, uh, leads or...
Leads? Yeah, sure.
I'll just check with the boys
down at the crime lab.
They got four more detectives
working on the case.
They got us working in shifts.
Leads?
I hope the big Lebowski kills me
before the Germans
can cut my dick off.
That is just ridiculous, Dude.
No one'll cut your dick off.
- Thank you.
- Not if I have anything to say.
- That makes me feel secure.
- Dude.
- It makes me feel warm inside.
- Now, Dude.
This whole fuckin' thing.
I could be sitting here
with just pee stains on my rug.
- But, no, man, I gotta...
- Fucking Germans.
Nothing changes. Fucking Nazis.
They were Nazis, Dude?
Come on, Donny, they
were threatening castration.
- Are we gonna split hairs?
- No.
- Am I wrong?
- Well, he...
They were nihilists, man.
They kept saying
they believed in nothing.
Nihilists.
Fuck me.
Say what you want about the
tenets of national socialism,
at least it's an ethos.
And also,
let's not forget, Dude,
that keeping wildlife,
an amphibious rodent
for, you know, domestic...
within the city...
That ain't legal either.
- Are you a fucking park ranger?
- No, I'm just...
Who gives a shit
about the fucking marmot?
- We are sympathising, Dude.
- Fuck sympathy.
I don't need your fucking
sympathy. I need my johnson.
- What do you need that for?
- You've got to buck up!
You cannot drag this negative
energy into the tournament.
Fuck the tournament.
Fuck you, Walter.
Fuck the tournament?
OK, Dude. I can see you
don't want to be cheered up.
Come on, Donny.
Let's go get us a lane.
- Another Caucasian, Gary.
- Right, Dude.
Friends like these,
huh, Gary?
That's right, Dude.
Do you have a good Sarsaparilla?