A little late.
Ain't it so?
Mornin'.
Giver of all graces,
the author of everlasting light,
send Thy blessing...
upon these, Thy servants...
this man and this woman
whom we bless in Thy name...
that as Isaac and Rebecca
lived faithfully together,
so these persons may surely
perform and keep...
the vow and covenant
between them made.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here...
What's ticklin' you? Do
you smell somethin' funny?
Fool. It's the cologne my ma
slapped on me this mornin'.
...signifying unto us
the mystical union...
What brings you so late
to sister's funeral?
I mean wedding.
My pa had me workin'.
Huh.
Son.
Let him speak now, or else
forever hold his peace.
Do you believe all those men
are necessary, Horton?
We can take
no further chances, Asa.
You and I both know it'll soon be war
between us and the Yankee aggressors.
With that black republican
Abe Lincoln in the White House,
Missouri's no longer safe from the depredations
of Jennison and his Kansas Jayhawkers.
They've yet to strike this
deep into Missouri, Horton.
Lawrence, Kansas, and its
abolitionists are a long way from here.
There are Union men
even here amongst us, Asa.
Schmidt and his Germans formed
a militia at Independence,
and his Lawrence cohorts
have eyes and ears amongst us,
even here.
Good-bye.
Take care, now.
I've been thinking, Jack Bull,
a wedding is a peculiar thing.
It's no more peculiar, Jake,
than slavery. That's certain.
That's why I've often wondered
for what cause those Northerners...
are so anxious to change
our Southern institutions.
When both North and South, men are
every day enslaved at the altar,
regardless
of their state or color.
When there's a type of subjugation,
we should avoid it, Jake.
Happily, my poverty insures
my freedom from such a fate.
Oh, no. Not if my mother
can help it.
I heard her singin' your praises
earlier to the sister of the groom.
Good day, Mrs. Chiles, sir. Father.
Please give our regards to your
father, Jake. You know he's invited.
He's more comfortable
workin', you know.
You must at the least bring
Mr. Roedel some of the cake.
I will, ma'am.
Thank you.
Guten Morgen.
Guten Morgen, Jakob.
Father, Mrs. Chiles sends her
regards, a piece of the cake.
You are to see tomorrow
Mrs. Kreitzer.
The war is sure to come now,
with the secession.
Mrs. Kreitzer's husband
will take you in St. Louis.
Pa, I told you, I'm not gonna huddle
with all the Lincoln-lovin' Germans.
It is safer.
For us, this is no war.
Pa, you may have bore me in
Germany, but I was raised here.
These are my people. And if
it gets hard... Your people?
No, Jakob,
this they are not.
You will always be
a deutschman, a German to them,
no matter with who
you are friends.
Promise me you'll go
to Mrs. Kreitzer.
Where is he?
I got him! I got him!
No!
Let's go, Asa.
My son's gone.
Where's your boy?
Jake, my pa.
He told me to run, Jake.
He told me.
Did you see
who they are?
Jayhawkers, Jake.
Lawrence men.
Father! Come on! Don't you die here too.
Find the boy. Let's go look in the mill.
Check the barn.
Find the boy.
Ted. Riders.
Gentlemen,
Captain Henderson, Company D.
You boys have rid
a bit far from home.
Hell, spent two night trackin'
this bushwhacking bastard...
and his Confederate friends.
What are you boys doin'
this far into Missouri?
Just rootin' out rebels
and conscriptin' chickens.
Been through Cass
and Lafayette Counties.
Killed our share.
Not much action
in Lafayette.
We got four Sunday last.
Stretched their necks.
They're still hanging.
Hey, George, fetch
a busthead out there.
So you men were in
on Lafayette?
Yes, sir.
We were tired of chasin'
these rebs into the bush.
Can't trust none of these
locals. They're all hiding 'em.
I wish we had
a real army to fight,
not these sneakin' bastards.
Battles and armies...
it's all back east.
Down here in Missouri, you just
have the people to fight ya.
Ted.
Ted!
So you were in on Lafayette?
Bushwhackers!
Whoo!
Doin' business with
the Yankee invaders, huh?
No. They forced me.
He's dead.
You killed him.
Shoot me too, please.
We don't hurt women, ma'am.
We took her man.
We should leave her the store.
Come on, Jake.
It's gettin' hot in here.
Enough of this, boys.
Let's load up!
Hyah! Hyah!
"Dear Mrs. Chiles,
by this letter you will know...
"that I and your son
Jack Bull are living yet.
"We long for news of you, but our
horses'backs remain our only residence,
"and it is yet too dangerous
to return home.
"Our news is this:
Jack Bull and I at last...
"met with Captain Warren,
the killer of your husband,
"and he and four of his
accomplices breathe no more.
"I know it must be painful to recall the
night your husband was taken from you,
"but we hope you will find some comfort
in knowing how our work continues.
"Often we don the Union Blue to lull
the Federals into a false serenity,
"and the Yanks pay dearly for
their belief in appearances.
"Under the disguise, we wear our
bushwhacker vestments close to our hearts.
"They may not be regular
army uniforms,
"as there is no Southern army
out here for us to join,
but where we find true Missouri
men, we make our own army. "
Black John!
George Clyde.
Whoa!
"If you should happen
upon my father,
"kindly express to him
my truest regards.
"He will not accept news from me
directly, as he disapproves of our cause.
"Please tell him, though,
that in my disobedience to him,
"I still obey the call to honor
he himself taught me.
"With warmest love
from me and from your son,
Yours Sincerely,
Jakob Roedel. "
Always loved ridin'
with George Clyde.
He makes Yankee killin' as entertainin'
a pastime as greasin' ganders.
Whose guns are those?
You mean Holt over there.
You'll get used to him.
That's Holt.
That's George Clyde's
pet nigger.
Don't call him that
in front of George, though.
George don't like that.
He carries those?
Yeah. He's
a damn fine scout.
When George tosses him a
gun, a good Yankee killer too.
Him and Clyde
growed up together.
When Jim Wayne's boys come for Clyde,
Holt sent three of them to heaven,
so he rides with us now.
'Cause them Yankees
want to kill him real bad.
Yeah, well, a nigger with guns
is still a nervous thing to me.
We're lookin'
for the Dorr's place, ma'am.
It's just up the road.
Who are you?
Why, we are Southern men,
and hungry.
You don't look like
Southern men. How do I know?
Woman, my name is Crawford, one
of the Six Point Creek Crawfords.
Do you know me?
I knew the father.
Well, come on.
Eat as what we have.
Whoo.
You're an interestin'
foreigner, Jake.
Why is that?
I hear your pa's a Dutchman.
That you're loyal to here and
not the North. It's uncommon.
No, Jake may have been
born a Dutchman,
but my ma and pa
practically raised him.
He's as Southern
as they come.
Where's the other one,
you devil?
Speak up now,
and maybe you'll live.
I'm alone.
That's my daddy's horse.
He was shot off it
three days back.
He's lyin'. Let's parole
him to Jesus, and right now.
Jake, get in here!
Get the horses!
Damn!
They took my pinky!
You boys, cover all sides!
Damn! Cover the women!
Go over there!
- Ahhh!
- Turner, cover the women!
Please, ma'am,
get over there!
No!
Ow! Damn!
Don't fret
about that now!
Cease fire!
- Cease fire!
- Hold your fire!
I said, cease fire,
goddamn it!
Control your fire!
Do you kill women?
There's women in here!
No, we don't kill women!
Send 'em out now...
and they'll be safe!
Please, ma'am, you and
your daughter got to go.
We are goin', son. You best believe
it, there ain't no way we're not goin'.
- You'll have to come out!
- Fire!
Riley!
- Trust me.
- We can't hold 'em from here!
Get back, Lewis!
We'll kill them yet!
We'll just have to take
our chances running!
They'll whittle us down! There ain't
so much as a stump out there for cover!
Come on, men!
Let's go do it!
Let's go.
Holt.
Go! Go!
Go, Riley!
- Come on!
- Let's go!
Come on! Get Riley!
Come on!
Hold your fire!
- Hold your fire!
- Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Giddap, boys!
Everyone!
Come on.
Giddap!
Hyah! Hyah!
Let's go!
Come on!
Where's my brother?
Don't know.
Did you see my brother?
Uh-uh.
- Black John. With him alive.
- With Black John? Alive?
Whoo! That was sure
enough! They left us hurt.
This way, boys.
Hyah! Come on.
Turner.
Jake? Well, Jack Bull.
Jake Roedel.
Well, Alf Bowden,
you sure are in a fix.
Seems so.
Surely does seem so.
Do you know this man?
Certainly.
His daddy's place is just
downriver from the Chiles'.
Hemp growers.
Jack Bull.
Goes it at home?
No, no, no.
It all just goes on.
Some may have died,
not most.
What of my mother?
Well, now...
Well, she is watched.
All the secess
are watched.
And my father?
He comes and goes.
He's a Union man.
He ain't bothered by no one.
You must know that.
You must know the whole town talks about
you boys out here black-flaggin' it.
Some friendliness
may be lost for your kin.
Come on, now.
You been fed?
Not so as you notice.
I'll look into it.
Roedel.
Now, take this down. This
is for the Lexington Union News.
So do it fine
the way you do.
Gladly.
"Dear Citizens,
"The stakes are most common
these days in deadly foray.
"The Federals are to hang
William Lloyd and James Curtain,
"two fine sons of Missouri.
"But by a provident
cut of the cards,
"four Federals
have been dealt to me,
"and it is their hope that Lloyd
and Curtain are not hanged,
"as they would provide
the sequel to these murders.
"However,
if our boys are released,
"I will, as a gentlemen,
"release these unfortunates.
"The choice is yours, citizens,
so make it wisely.
"Signed, John Ambrose
and George Clyde,
Commander and First,
Irregulars. "
That's good.
Put a note on it that says,
"What you think we ain't,
we are. Remember it. "
Who will deliver it? There are
Federals all over Lexington.
We could slip a man in
there. We done it before.
Oh, I reckon a citizen could be pressed
into service, if one could be found.
That might be a job, for
citizens are cautious hereabouts.
You got some
better idea, Dutchie?
Maybe you should
volunteer yourself.
Well, there is a way we could
prove more things than one.
If we send a prisoner, it would
prove we have prisoners,
and also, he can attest
to our intentions.
It seems to me he could get
more quickly into town as well.
And time is short. Lloyd and Curtain
will be hanged right quick, I would think.
It's a good idea.
Some fine touches to it.
Yeah, you should
speak up more, Roedel.
You're not near so dumb
as you let on.
Awww.
Now, go put one of them Federals
on a horse with that letter.
Convince them to see
this deal through, Alf.
We're only askin' to be treated
like the soldiers that we are.
We shall do the same
for your companions here.
Do your best.
Huh.
What are you lookin' at?
Jake.
Aw.
Black John says you're
lettered. It's Union mail.
He wants you to look it over, tell
him if there's anything to learn.
All right.
Well, it's just stuff
from up north.
There's no military
intelligence in here.
Well, maybe you could read it
to us just the same.
Read us this letter,
Dutchie.
That's someone else's letter.
Was. I wanna
hear you read it.
I don't think I care to.
Oh, is that so? Well, I think that if
you think a little bit more, Dutchie,
you'll think you do
wanna read at me.
Right now, too.
How do we know there might be
secrets in it? Read it at us.
Yeah, come on, Dutchie.
All right.
This here is from Mrs. Mary
Williams of Bear Lake, Wisconsin.
"Dear Sons,
No word of you in so long,
"right past first frost
of the year last.
"Your father is better, but
his feet are still bloatin'.
He won't walk right
on them. "
That's the blood does that.
The blood bloats the feet.
"Fire hit the old church.
Burned down.
"The new one was just ready, so
no great trouble was had of it.
"Margaret is married since
the frost of this year last.
"You wouldn't know it, for how could
you? Her husband is Walter Maddox.
"He is out of the war, with
one arm busted at New Madrid.
"But it works fine enough.
"The dirt was turned over, and the
smell and deepness gave me heart.
It is just black rich.
You boys know how that is. "
My daddy was up there.
He was up there
way before they hung him.
He said the dirt was so rich
you could've et it like porridge.
Yeah, very good dirt up there.
Short grow season.
Yeah, sounds like
real good dirt to me.
"That girl Dave got sweet for is
in town and still single and about.
"She asks of you, but I have no news
since first frost of the year last.
"Without news,
I cannot answer her.
You are both missed here.
Your mother. "
Sounds like my mother.
What a woman does.
One mother's
very much like another.
Remember one thing: Her boys
will kill you if they can.
What is it, Jake?
I hear you ruminatin'louder
than a cow chewin'in my ear,
and it's keepin' me
from my sleep.
Do you think Alf Bowden's made
it back to Lexington as yet?
There was a minute there
when I saw him ridin' off,
and I thought maybe
you and me could join him.
That we could all
ride home together.
Just ride back home.
What have you left at home
you're so anxious to ride back to?
Nothin'.
Just a passel of memories.
Mostly memories
of you and me.
Of your father,
old Asa Chiles.
We'll stick together, Jack Bull.
We'll get all of it back.
You're a black magician
who can raise the dead, are ya?
No, my father's
under the dirt to stay.
Like that's
goin' to stay too.
My finger?
Mm-hmm.
Well, so it is.
And it makes me notable
by the loss.
You sound pleased, as if that finger
had been pesterin' you for rings.
No, it was a fine finger,
and I'd rather have it still.
But it was took from me, and
it's been et by chickens for sure.
And I say, "What is the
good side to this amputation?
And there is one.
Name it, Jake.
Well, say one day
some Federals...
catch up to me and
kill me in a thicket.
They would riddle me
and hang me,
and no Southern man
would find me for months.
When they did, I'd be bad meat,
pretty well rotted to a glob.
You're scientifically accurate,
I'm afraid. I've seen it.
I'd be a mysterious
gob of rot.
People would say,
"Who was that?"
And surely someone
would look up and say,
"Why, it's nubbin-fingered
Jake Roedel. "
And then you could go and tell
my father I was clearly murdered,
and he wouldn't be tortured
by uncertain wonders.
And that's the good of it?
Yes, sir,
that's the good.
Go to sleep, Jake Roedel.
It is time for our winter
hibernation.
I have gathered the names of loyal
Southerners who shall provide for us.
We'll group in fours.
I'll send word the beginnin' of
spring for where to rendezvous.
We shall
to the Evans farm, boys.
Their place is about half
a mile from the Willards',
where there resides
a certain Miss Juanita,
to whom, if I
do not flatter myself,
my attentions are not
unfavorably regarded.
You mean to say we're to spend
the winter in Lafayette...
solely on account that you're
sweet on Juanita Willard?
That's as good a reason
as any, Dutchie.
Nolan's brought
some news from home.
Hank Patterson is murdered.
Our old neighbor Jansen got him
with his gang of militia.
That's sad. He was a good
Southern man. What of Thomas?
Oh, he is murdered too.
And Sally Burgess
married a Federal from Michigan.
Her whole family
hides their faces.
And...
well, Dutchie,
that Federal,
Alf Bowden,
he rode straight from here
and killed your father.
He shot him in the neck
down by the river,
then booted him
along Main Street till he died.
I spared Alf Bowden.
You all know it.
You taught him nicely,
but he forgot the lesson.
But my father... My father was
a Unionist like all the Germans.
An unconditional Unionist.
Well, yeah, but he was mainly
known as your father, Dutchie.
You got a reputation now.
Come here, boys.
Good day, sir.
Abel Evans.
George Clyde.
Sorry we can't all be of proper
hospitality, but with the Federal patrols...
We're much obliged.
May I ask after Mrs. Evans?
My wife. Well, she's as well
as can be expected.
Our other Mrs. Evans,
Sue Lee...
Well, she was a Mrs. Evans
for but three weeks...
until my son joined
our Confederate forces.
He was killed in the
fightin' at Independence.
We're sorry
to hear of it.
Yes, well,
you boys lay low.
We'll come by from time
to time with provisions...
such as there are.
We're much obliged.
Been a while since we done work.
Somethin' soothin' to it.
Yeah, well, work has never
been my main ambition.
We've done much work. I think
I've spied an easier way to riches.
Spell out this miracle.
You just ride on up
and take it.
Ah, good old rule.
Simple plan.
It's a workable method
that is proven.
George, you got
mud in your eye.
Rider's comin'.
Let's go see our visitor.
Good day. Don't shoot
or some dumb thing like that.
Whoa. Well, how do?
You must be Mrs. Evans.
I brung you some supper.
I'm, uh, pleased to
meet you, Mr... Chiles.
Mr. Jack Bull Chiles.
This is Jake Roedel.
And...
George Clyde, Mrs. Evans.
Mr. Evans wishes me to apologize
for not havin' sent you food sooner.
The Federals
have been on the move.
Don't you call me Mrs. Evans.
My name is Sue Lee Shelley.
It's a good one,
and I am a widow now.
Reckon I'll go back to it
and use it.
Please pardon me.
Won't you come in?
It's not much to gaze upon,
but I reckon we could assay
some hospitality.
George.
After me, ma'am.
Right this way, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Damn.
What are you smilin' at?
I'll see to that mule.
Wait a second.
What did you say?
I say I'll look to him.
You better go on in there,
let that woman see your face.
Damnation, Holt. I think I know best
how to handle my personal affairs.
Now, you see that lady's mule while
I check on what she brung to eat.
Excuse the mud. We'll just...
There you are, ma'am.
My! Aren't you
bushwhackers the gentlemen.
We try to make the effort
when possible, ma'am.
Do you think manners should
be dropped in times like these?
No. But I don't think horse
sense oughta be dropped either.
It's cold.
You're so kind
to think of us, ma'am.
You men think of us more.
You do the good work.
I know it's dirty
and it's dangerous.
Those are good words
to hear, ma'am.
It's not always
we hear them.
Well, I really
should be goin'.
Mrs. Evans will worry
if I don't.
Uh, ma'am?
We're awful sorry about
Evans, Jr. gettin' killed.
Well, we all suffer,
but he suffers no more.
He was a good husband to me.
For three weeks he was a good
husband, but he didn't last.
What's he doin' here,
inside?
Oh, ma'am, this nigger's
with me. His name is Holt.
Well, wouldn't he be more useful
off in a field, plowin'?
Oh, no, I reckon not.
No, ma'am. That's one nigger I
wouldn't try to hitch behind a plow.
No, I wouldn't try that.
Well, now.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mr. Evans asked that you come to the
house tomorrow evenin' after dark.
He's up on latest Federal movements,
and he could post you on 'em.
Why, we'd be honored.
Um, I'm not sure about him.
Mr. Evans...
You ain't got nothin' to worry about on
that score. You needn't worry about Holt.
I'll be takin'Holt with me
to the Willards'tomorrow.
We won't be comin'
to your dinner.
Mr. Clyde, honestly, I didn't
mean to speak ill of your nigger.
He's not my nigger.
He's just a nigger who I trust with my
life every day and night, that's all.
- That's very high praise.
- Yes, ma'am, it is.
I see.
Well, gentlemen,
I really must take my leave.
I hope the food'll please
you. It looks wonderful.
Why, thank you.
Now, good night, all.
- Good night.
- Good night, ma'am.
Holt, the lady said
good night to all.
Touch your hat
and say good night.
- You don't tell him nothin'.
- He's bein' rude.
- Gentlemen, please.
- He don't need no tellin'.
George.
Good night, missy.
Good night, Holt.
I'll see the lady
to her mule.
Holt. It won't be a hardship, George.
Well, let's eat.
This smells good.
Be careful.
Holt, you want my bacon?
I could eat more.
Go on, then.
I appreciate it.
Roedel...
do you want my bacon?
Yes, I could eat it.
Well, I'll shit it out by
the oak tree in the mornin'.
You can just go
and help yourself.
And why, if you do not mind my askin',
did you not join the regular army?
Army? Well,
we thought of it.
I suppose we decided this fight's
got to be made in our own country,
not where some general
tells us it should happen.
It soon will be everywhere.
My family and I, we will be
quittin' this house in the spring.
As soon as the roads are clear,
we're gonna be tryin' for Texas.
About half of Missouri's
went to Texas.
Now, the whole state's
thick with invaders.
We cannot
drive them away.
We have different thoughts.
I still want to fight.
I reckon I'll always
want to fight them.
Always.
Have you ever been
to Lawrence, Kansas, young man?
No, I reckon not, Mr. Evans.
I don't believe I'd be
too welcome in Lawrence.
I didn't think so.
Before this war began,
my business
took me there often.
As I saw those Northerners
build that town,
I witnessed the seeds
of our destruction being sown.
The foundin' of that town was truly
the beginnin' of the Yankee invasion.
I'm not speakin' of numbers,
nor even abolitionist
trouble-makin'.
It was the schoolhouse.
Before they built their church,
even, they built that schoolhouse.
And they let in
every tailor's son...
and every farmer's daughter
in that country.
Spellin' won't help you
hold a plow any firmer.
Or a gun either.
No, it won't, Mr. Chiles.
But my point is merely...
that they rounded every pup
up into that schoolhouse...
because they fancied
that everyone should think...
and talk the same
free-thinkin' way they do...
with no regard
to station, custom,
propriety.
And that is why they will win.
Because they believe everyone
should live and think Just like them.
And we shall lose because we
don't care one way or another...
how they live.
We just worry about ourselves.
Are you sayin', sir,
that we fight for nothin'?
Far from it, Mr. Chiles.
You fight for everything
that we ever had.
As did my son.
It's just that
we don't have it anymore.
Mr. Evans, when you
get back from Texas,
it'll all be here
waitin' for you.
Jack Bull and me,
we'll see to it.
Well... yes.
Thank you, son.
Well, enough of this war talk.
Let's have the ladies join us
and think nobler thoughts.
Lydia!
Fine idea.
Some company
would be splendid.
We should be thinkin'
about gettin'back.
The Federals
could pass by anytime.
Sue Lee! Oh, put a gown
on, Jake. It's too cold.
They'll all be in front of the
fire examinin' their plunder.
I, uh, have it in me to sing
Shall we have a sing-along?
Oh, yes.
I like those the best.
My voice is not
what it should be,
but it was once rumored
that I could carry a tune.
- And you, Mr. Roedel?
- I believe I won't sing. Young ears are present.
- I bet you sing lovely.
- You would lose that bet.
He really does sing very poorly, but
he imitates the turkey first-rate.
- I best do my gobblin'
out of doors.
You go ahead and sing along.
I'll keep my eye on the road.
- Do you really think that...
- Good man, Jake. I'll relieve you soon.
Clyde back?
I believe he's fixin' to pass a
few more hours with Miss Juanita.
Jack Bull?
He's covered
in Miss Sue Lee Evans.
You mean Sue Lee Shelley.
Roedel?
Yeah, Holt?
What's that?
I've been keeping 'em.
Nobody ever learned me letters.
When you were readin'
the mails out loud,
it was somethin' the likes
of which I'd never heard.
Got me thinkin' you might
sometime try it again.
So you packed those
and kept 'em all this time?
It might not be
too amusin'.
It might just be a bunch of borin'
thoughts from one stranger to another.
That one you read from the
mother was fine. You recall it?
Yeah.
She said things
I enjoyed to hear.
All right, here goes.
"Dear Brother, I must
write this right quick...
"'cause I say good-bye to
Massachusetts and our home in one hour.
"Yes, Danny,
I've joined the fight,
"and a difficulter decision
never before was made,
"as I've been just about the only eligible
bachelor to dance with at Parlans' this year.
"Without my favorite brother,
it is not the same,
"although the beer
has been free,
"as I've been drinkin' it with
one of the Parlans' daughters.
"Which one, I will not tell.
Here's to you, Danny, and keep
your head low out there. Bill. "
It could come to where
you could maybe like that man.
Yeah, in other times
he would not be so bad.
I think, though, I like
the one from the mama best.
Holt, where is your mother?
Ahh...
Kansas or Kingdom.
I don't know.
I know she was sold into Texas.
I reckon she in Texas.
How was that?
Was that George that sold her?
No, sir. George and me,
we growed up neighbors.
It was George what bought me
out when Master Henry passed,
but he didn't have no means
for my mama or my sister.
- So Clyde owns you?
- No, sir.
Not in greenbacks
and coppers, no how.
No, he don't own me
that way.
Nope.
He made it out a gift.
It's me.
Hey, Jake.
Hey, Miss Wild,
you splattered poor Holt.
Well, it surely is.
Oh, no. Mm-mm.
Whoa, mule, settle down
there! Mule? A mule?
Just calm down.
Well, do I look
muley to you?
Why, no.
Well, does that look
like a mule to you?
Does that look like the rear end of
an animal that hee-haws in the night?
It looks like
it might could be.
Jack Bull Chiles!
Just 'cause I'm a widow...
don't mean that you can get
that familiar with me.
Pardon me, ma'am, but I believe it was
you that shoved your rump into my face.
That was only
just to make a point.
You made it. I'll always know
your rump from a mule's now.
Several differences. Don't
know how I missed 'em before.
Well, don't be mean.
I can't tolerate
meanness.
Is that too mean?
No. It's really
not too mean at all.
Oh, for cryin' out loud!
We're sittin' right here.
Show us some mercy.
He really is quite right.
I better get back
to the house.
Cover your tracks
in the snow too.
You'll be leadin' curious
Federals right onto us.
Don't be rude.
There's no reason to be rude.
There happens to be
a war goin'on...
everywhere but between
your two ears, you dumb ox.
Dumb ox, am I?
Sorry, Jake. My leg
Just did that on its own.
No thought behind it.
I hear you. I hear you.
But Holt and me ain't dyin'
Just so you could be kissed.
Leave Holt out of this. Holt ain't
even here. Holt ain't nowhere near here.
I don't think anybody's
about to die from my kiss.
In fact, she seems
to be doin' tolerably well.
Well enough
to get goin' too.
Good day.
You reckon George Clyde'll ever
Join up with us again,
or do you think Juanita Willard will be
his only cause and comfort from here on?
Ah, George is efficient
when it comes to comfort.
This thing with Sue Lee and you,
will it go on?
I reckon.
Well, that's good for you.
Yeah, I believe
I'll marry her.
I believe you should.
Sue Lee'll be by
this evening.
Oh, good. It's been near
a week since I've seen her.
Yeah, all this warmth has
the Federals out for jaunts.
It's kept her home. It won't be
long before we join 'em out there.
No, it won't. That's why I want
to ask somethin' of you and Holt.
Name it.
Well, future best man, I'd like
to ask you for some privacy.
Oh, you would, would you?
It's not much to ask.
And what are Holt
and me to do?
Anything you'd like. Throw walnuts
at squirrels. Play mumblety-peg.
I reckon we could come up with a better
use of our time than that, eh, Holt?
It's possible.
Howdy.
Ahem, brung you two
somethin'.
Try this bread, boys.
Why, thank you.
Did you make it?
No. Miss Evans' sister
lives in town.
She's a Federal, but a sister
still. She gave us two loaves.
Well, that's kind of her. You
thank her for us, won't you?
I don't suppose I'll tell her
where it went. That might not do.
Well, this good weather has me and
Holt wantin' to fling walnuts...
at mumblety-peg players or
something along those lines.
All right.
Now have fun.
Jake, one hour, please.
"Dearest Ruth Ann,
"I trust this letter
will reach you before winter.
"Here it is always a sort of
winter, as folks are so cold now.
"Rebels are out of the city
as far as armies go,
"but there are copperheads
around performing misdeeds.
"So much cruelty goes on.
"Prison is full of rebels and they
are left to waste away so pitifully.
"They are traitors
but also human.
"If you looked in on them, you
would not believe that they were...
"for they so resemble
scarecrows now.
"Father believes
the war will go on and on...
"but is ever more committed
to the... struggle.
"He manages to send ever greater
numbers of slaves up north...
"to freedom and away from the
grasping hands of their masters,
"who even in the midst of all
attempt to lay claim to them.
"The Confederates claim that we
strike at their liberty and rights,
"but what kind of liberty is it that
takes away the liberty of others?
The war will end. "
Has it been an hour yet?
No, ain't an hour
passed yet.
Roedel,
you know my name?
It's Holt.
No, my whole name.
My whole name is Daniel Holt.
Daniel, like that lion's
den man. You know his story?
Of course I do.
They throwed Daniel to the
lions, but he weren't never ate.
Daniel.
That's what my mama named me.
Is it an hour now?
An hour and two...
That's the Evans' place.
Jake.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Gunshots in the Evans'.
I heard 'em.
Holt!
Jake. Sue Lee, you stay put.
There's gonna be a fight.
Holt, got 'em guns?
Take it easy.
Bring her in! Bring her in!
Jack Bull, let's go!
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!