I like The Last Samurai.
The integrity and respect is different.
The mother and child
took care of the person...
who murdered the woman's husband.
That's an intense sacrifice.
Respect.
When there's no respect,
you wouldn't be happy...
even if you have lots of money.
It's a curse.
By the way, why do you want to talk to
me all of a sudden?
What are you thinking?
I want to rest.
Good.
You need that.
- We're a bit on the hotspot right now.
- I'm going to rest but not temporarily.
Permanently.
Maybe it's here in the Phlippines where
you can find the best in abilities...
and the best kind of people in the world.
They are all here in Manila.
This is the training ground.
You should be careful
and alert with everything...
and all the time.
Even America's Pentagon
weren't able to survive.
Our best ability to live here
is way different.
And so to fill someone's stomach.
Some stretches their bones...
some just want to sit down and eat.
Others share with someone else's
shelter and food to live.
There are only but a few good leaders
here in our country...
you can count them
in less than 10 fingers.
We despise them...
but the moment they speak on stage...
we applaud them.
Too much corruption.
We want to change them
but we don't want to change ourselves.
There are a lot of jobs here.
Others need to kill just to live.
It's sad to say but that is my job.
I have given a thought just recently...
that our mission in this life time...
is not to change the world.
Our missions here is to change ourselves.
I tried.
But then, maybe I have done
so many bad things...
the world didn't agree.
Boss it's Attorney.
Attorney, I want you to listen carefully.
Yes, sir.
I want a 10 billion out of that deal.
Switch it to the other side.
I can't make it in a short time.
Attorney listen first.
We'll earn bigger than that.
Our 1 billion collectible with Robles...
we need that.
You know what I mean.
Good.
You've improved a lot Ben...
from the day we first trained.
I think your old strength has returned.
You know brother Ben, what you need
now is to regain your memory.
So how's it gonna be Ben, until next week.
Okay.
That's okay.
Ouch!
That h u r"I:s?
Ben I'll go up there
co'z I think he's mad at me.
Don't...
You might hurt yourself more.
Okay.
Thank you.
Your day will come.
Is this the bag?
That's the bag.
You know Ben, I really kept all of that.
I really didn't take that out
'til you come into consciousness.
Good thing I kept it somewhere high...
that's why ﬂood by storm Ondoy
didn't damage it.
Your properties have almost gone out...
while you were unconscious.
I always clean that.
Thanks Caloy.
You're welcome Ben.
You know Ben,
what happened was really a miracle...
because I thought that you're not going
to wake up anymore.
Have you thought how the bullet slipped
your forehead.
How long have I been unconscious?
Almost 7 years.
The doctor said...
- Doctor here's sir's x-ray.
- There's no damage in the brain.
Thank you.
But there's a bit crack because of the
pressure from the bullet that hit it.
When he'll be awake...
we wouldn't know yet.
God knows.
But for now, we'll do all what we can...
the hospital will give it's best...
but still the same thing...
Mr. Morillo is still in the stage of coma.
You can go stroll around.
The place you used to go to
will help you a lot...
It will open the door to bring back
your memory.
But you should go somewhere far Ben...
the enemies might accidentaly bump
with you.
You know Caloy, I believe that all of
these things happen for a reason.
And I will look for that reason.
Hey and here we go.
Nice.
Tilt your head.
Good.
Catch the wind. Catch the wind.
Nice.
Last two for the magic.
Beautiful!
Last two!
Last two.
Look at the camera. Good!
Keep it going-
Nice, good.
One more.
And beautiful!
Beautiful!
Perfect. Okay.
Next set-up.
Coffee break.
You're one of a kind Gina.
You're still the sexiest
in the whole wide world.
Your really deserve
to be on top of RHM hundred sexiest.
That's great Gina.
You never failed to amaze me.
Thanks Xander,
I'll have a coffee break, yes.
Okay, I will still set-up the lights.
1 hour.
Shoot!
Hi, ma'am.
Hi, can I get a caramel macchiato.
135, ma'am.
I receive 200.
Your change ma'am.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Boss, the car is here. I left it.
It's clean. They won't be able to get
finger prints anymore.
Iced caramel macchiato for Ms. Gina.
What the...
Sorry, miss.
Sorry.
No, it's okay, it's okay.
Miss! Can I have tissue, miss.
Sir, one more...
What did she order?
Iced caramel Macchiato, Sir.
Thank you. Thank you.
One more please.
Yes sir.
Make it two.
Okay, sir.
Oh, no, no. I'll order.
No it's okay.
I insist.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean.
- Iced caramel macchiato.
- Thank you.
Are you sure,
maybe you want to eat something?
No, no. It's okay.
Is it okay if I join you.
No it's alright.
By the way I'm Ben.
Gina.
Sorry I really didn't mean that.
You got wet.
It's okay.
So that's how an angel looks like up-close.
I've forgiven you already.
Besides I've a got another coffee.
Oh hold it.
What angel are you talking about?
Angel from heaven?
Or angel of darkness.
You know I seldom meet girls
who has that good sense of humor.
That's one point for you.
What happened?
I don't know.
Policemen were everywhere
while I was passing by earlier.
Fix it.
They're chaotic now.
Okay thank you boss.
What is it again?
That's really you.
Who?
Gina Sevilla.
22 years old, from White Plains.
You're a stalker?
That's our bad side.
We'll let magazines cover our story...
we'll tell them the details of our lives...
then forget about it totally.
2 points.
2 Points!
Hello.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Sorry, it's my photographer.
Our photo shoot's not yet done.
I have no right to stop you
from doing your work.
And besides,
it's my first time to see an angel so sorry.
Sorry the angel is busy.
I have to go back to heaven now.
Nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you.
Sir, the boss is here.
Tomas come here.
Waiter.
Order now.
Come one, they've got delicious food here.
Tomas your've got great bodybuilt
right now.
You've seem to have been practicing a lot.
Your age isn't obvious.
It's just okay brother Mando.
The one that you promised me.
10 milion!
Are you crazy?
I can't give you that amount Tomas.
Thank you.
What was written in the contract...
that's it.
You told me that you'll give me 10 million
so I could start my own business.
And for my early retirement.
The transaction didn't push through.
It did push through, brother...
you just didn't tell me.
You're an idiot Tomas!
I promised to help you.
But I didn't tell you
that I'll give you 10 million.
What I'm as asking is...
not more than your capacity.
I am not stupid.
I'm not a bank
that you can hold-up anytime.
You really forget easily.
All your enemies in business...
gambling, white slavery...
drugs.
All your enemies...
you asked me to kill them.
I killed all of them for you.
You seemed to have won the lottery
when I became one of your men.
You ask me to kill all of them...
including my best hitman.
Even if I don't want to.
Because you've said that he knows a lot.
So I killed him.
I am only asking
for money brother Mando.
I gave you my whole life.
What is it now?
I owe you, is that right?
Tomas all the things I asked you to do.
Could have been done by my other men.
Your lucky I gave you a job...
or until now you will still be extortioning
money from chinese businessmen.
You've changed a lot.
You got rich.
You became boastful.
And now you became greedy.
You're no different
from the criminals I've killed.
So you mean that
if I didn't give what you want...
you'll kill me, too.
I'm so scared Tomas.
I'm so scared .
I don't want to get mad at you Mando.
Get the money ready.
Tomas hold it!
Are you threatening me?
Dad are you okay.
Can you shoot that...
because if I pull my gun...
and face you.
I'll shoot you
and I'll make sure you fall down.
Now...
can you shoot that.
Just as I thought.
Gina where are meeting later?
The usual, I'll be there at 9.
That's early.
You've got a date?
I hope so.
Why aren't you sure?
With your beauty.
you can date anybody.
If that's gonna be someone...
no way.
And beside,
Alex, you just don't pick a date...
you should choose them.
It seem like your hoarding
from the market.
And you know what...
I met this guy at the coffee shop.
He looks so sweet and so nice.
And very sympatico.
Total stranger.
Yes. Why?
Are you going to oppose me again?
That's dangerous.
That makes it more exciting.
Going out with a total stranger.
You're daddy wouldn't like that.
I was just kidding.
I think he's nice and very gentleman.
But you should be careful.
Thank you but he seems different.
Have you agreed?
To what?
To go out with him.
It was just my fantasy.
But I hope to see him later.
Nuts.
You are so weak.
- You could have hit the ball directly.
- Why don't you do it yourself?
What?
- You keep on talking.
- Hey I want to play, too.
You haven't done anything.
And you know how to answer back now.
Stop that or you might get mad
at each other in the end.
Hey, can you be at least good at this.
I've been waiting here.
Nothing.
You are no match.
Let's just drink.
You're turn.
And you'll see.
- Hit it now.
- Let's just fight.
- Relax.
- So we'd know who's better:
So everyone would know.
Boss.
Engineer.
What's the news?
Is project almost done?
Sorry boss.
We'll be a bit delayed...
because of Mr. Alex Co's materials.
We don't want to get from other supplier:
But it's in the ship now?
It's going to come after a week.
Alright.
By the way Sir...
This Engineer Nepumuceno.
One of the best.
We added additional manpower
to supervise our project.
Alex maybe the supply
that's going to come...
maybe you can rush it.
We can.
We'll do our best effort.
Best effort.
You know what...
I don't care about what you want.
Whoever you want to add.
How many people you are going to add.
The date we've agreed with...
that's when I want to finish the project.
Don't give me your best effort crap.
If you don't like it,
I'll give it to someone else.
Please don't boss.
Don't worry, we'll finish it
on the date we've agreed with.
There you go.
I'll see you at the ribbon cutting.
Thank you.
Thank you boss.
I've noticed, you've been playing on me.
- Dude, I've seen it.
- How come you saw it moved?
This is what happened.
- It moved, dude
- It moved, what are you?
You're cheating.
Sorry, dude, sorry.
Nothing will happen there.
Nothing.
Oh no you missed!
You didn't hit on anything thing.
You see.
Who's next?
You're turn.
You're all show off.
I agree.
Mike they're so annoying.
Let them be.
They are customers.
Remember that customers
are always right.
You're turn, dude.
Do your best, dude.
Come here Alvin.
What are you? You keep on coming
through even with narrow space.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
It's narrow here.
Sorry. Sorry-
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Move now.
Are you going to move?
Mike that's enough!
Mike.
Don't move.
Mike that's enough!
- You still want some fight?
- Mike.
Don't move.
Mike that's enough!
Mike.
Alvin hurry.
PO3's here.
You're rude.
Next time, get to know whom you're
playing dumb with.
Si r, sorry.
This won't happen again.
Mike don't.
SPO3 is here.
You take care of him.
Where is Mike?
He's in the CR. Why?
You're uncle wants to talk to you...
He has an important thing to say.
Okay I'll tell him.
Vin would that be okay.
All of that are Mike's.
If you want, you can ask him.
Okay tell him to meet
your Uncle Tom in the bar.
Okay.
Bullshit.
What is he proud of?
This building?
His drugs in the basement?
His white slavery?
His gambling business?
Why?
He won't be able to establish
all of those if not because of me.
He only thinks of nothing but socialization.
Play golf.
What I'm asking from him...
is what he promised me.
I am not asking too much.
Sir we received an information
that you ought to know.
What is it?
Ben Morillo alive.
Hey Robby stop kidding like that...
I've got a lot of problems.
Positive sir.
Our 2 spotters confirmed it.
He was seen in two different places.
Positive they saw Ben.
Do you want us to clean him up?
Sir we can't let him last like that.
Study his moves first.
I'll handle my brother Mando first.
And then he'll be the next one.
Keep your eyes keen.
Because you may just be starting to turn
your head on him...
that you'll realized you already have
a bullet in your head.
One jack please.
Thank you.
Gins my sister.
Alvin.
Gina let's talk.
If this is just about
what daddy wants me to do...
you're just wasting your time.
Let's go, let's talk.
Mike I can live independently
without his money.
My principles are different.
Damn your principles.
Keep it cool Mike.
There are a lot of people here,
it's embarrassing.
My order.
Excuse me.
Your principle should be on daddy's side.
He is your father.
Where is your brain?
In your feet?
Daddy wants you to handle
our family business.
Who do you think he'll leave that?
With his hitman.
There were quite a number of them.
Hi, guys.
You seem to be talking seriously.
Drinks?
Who's this crazy man?
Mike... he's my friend.
Don't you ever play fool with my sister.
Or you better hide.
Ben let's go.
Okay, see YOU GUYS
Did you miss me?
No.
Your face tell it all that you miss me.
Not really.
Major good evening.
Good evening major.
Good evening.
Where is Gina?
She already left.
She's with a guy.
How does he look like?
Handsome, tan...
but I'm better looking Major.
That's guts.
Mike is inside Major.
He's with Alvin.
Is that so.
Call him here.
Go on call him.
I'm asking you to do it.
You can do it. Call him.
Tom why did you come here?
Mike when will you start
to pay respect on me?
Uncle Tom good evening.
Where is Gina?
She's with a friend. Is there a problem?
There is.
Go home Mike.
The situation is hot, let's all cool down.
We're okay.
If you want you can go home now.
Drink beer, stand in front of the aircon...
I'm sure you'll feel cold.
Mike.
What's you're problem?
I don't have a problem.
There's no source of hotness here,
but you.
What do you mean?
I know your fight with daddy...
I am not sleeping in vain...
so don't show off here.
I came here Mike...
to make sure that you
and your siblings are safe.
And the feud between your dad and me...
that's just ours.
You're out of it.
You're dad had wronged a lot
of people Mike.
Don't fool me Tom.
You have the biggest reason
to hurt my daddy.
Uncle let's just talk about this next time.
I'll say it again to you Mike.
The feud between your dad and me
is just ours.
And remember this Tom.
Whoever the enemy of my daddy...
is also my enemy.
I hope that's clear to you.
Alvin.
Cheers.
Seriously I'm an architect.
Imaginative, adaptable...
independent.
Oh I see.
You're an architect?
Why is it instead of spending
your time making plan...
you're here in front of me
wasting your time.
Do you really have to ask that.
You wanna get close.
Closer.
You think I'll allow you.
I'm hoping.
Let's go.
This is my first time Ben.
Okay.
Alvin
Mike.
What's that?
Uncle Tom and I are just talking
about something.
Yes.
Get inside.
But brother.
You know Tom...
I know that I owe you big time.
All the bad things that I've done...
you cover it for me.
But that doesn't mean...
that I will love you more than my dad.
Don't tell me that you're my uncle.
And don't tell that you're a policeman.
I'll fight you.
What did you say Mike?
Can you say it again.
Tom if not for my dad...
you don't have money...
you don't have a house...
you don't have a car.
You're poor.
Yes.
But you know what's in exchange of that.
My principles.
My dignity.-
My whole life.
Son of a sheep.
Let's finish this Tom.
Tom!
Mike.
If you'll continue that...
I'll forget that you're my nephew.
I didn't know that,
that's what you mean.
When you told me that it's your first time.
But don't worry.
That didn't change my feelings for you.
Thank you Ben.
But you know...
I don't know why I did this.
And why with you.
Why then?
Maybe because
I know that you're a good person.
And nothing bad will happen to me...
when I'm with you.
Even if I have tattoos?
And a scar on my forehead...
because I was naughty when I were a kid.
I started to become independent when I
had a fight with my daddy.
I moved out of the house.
But he keeps on calling...
trying to persuade me.
That's why I kept on telling him...
that this is the life that I chose.
You're lucky...
you have a family.
I'm just waiting for daddy to wake up.
And accept my principles.
I just wanted to have a good family.
Hold it, I'll check. Stay here.
Ben.
Put it down.
I told you to put it down.
Ben?
Gina get back inside.
Don't.
Do you know them?
No.
But I know that they're not robbers.
That is what I've thought, too.
Don't you recognize any of those faces.
No, I don't know them.
I'm quite sure that they are the men
of my dad's enemy.
I'm sure they wanted to kill me.
We should leave this place.
Hello, sir.
The men that you sent for Gina missed.
The hitman that we killed but survived...
interfered .
What do you want us to do.
Okay sir.
You know Ben
I have something to tell you.
I know that I can't trust
even my own brothers.
I don't know why I feel so good with you.
I'll tell this only to you.
That I'm keeping a big amount
of daddy's money.
And if my brothers find out...
my life might be at stake.
Gina I'll do everything to protect you.
I also want to let you know something...
but I can't say it now.
The memories that were erased from my
mind haven't returned yet.
But I can promise you one thing.
I wouldn't let anything bad happen to you.
Hello.
Hello, Ben.
Caloy, what?
Positive Ben. Mando plotted your murder.
Mando?
Yes .
Who's Mando?
Tom's brother:
Mando, the brother of Tom.
Ain't he the father of Gina Sevilla?
Yes Ben.
Mando Sevilla.
Okay, come here Caloy.
Go here.
I'll wait for you.
Ben, I'm scared.
I feel like it wouldn't last long.
I'll be involved in my daddy's wickedness.
Maybe they'd take first revenge on me.
What are you thinking?
Mando could have children...
but why you.
You're right.
Somebody's going to make
your father pay.
That's me.
And you'll be involved.
What do you mean?
I once worked with your father.
But he ruined all my dreams.
You're daddy's hitman?
You tricked me?
You made me believe
that you're a good person...
you're an architect.
No one's good for your father.
None.
I planned to change.
Move away.
Leave the evilness that your father leads.
He involved...
he murdered my pregnant wife.
But he made a mistake...
for letting me live.
Ben!
Are you involving me in all of these.
He took away my wife and child.
You and your dad will pay for it.
It seems destiny has made you cross
paths with her.
Ben looks like
I'm going to clean up a lot of mess.
By the way, the brother of that woman...
they call him Mike.
He's dead.
He was shot.
Where did they take him?
Sir, it's confirmed.
Tom killed him.
Mike!
I'll kill you Tom.
I'll kill you Tom!
Dad.
Brother.
- You ungrateful!
- Dad.
- Dad that's enough.
- You're an idiot.
Dad that's enough, I didn't do anything.
You should be the one who's there.
- Idiot!
- Dad believe me.
You're not my son.
I just adopted you.
You're ungrateful.
- Dad that's enough
- You're ungrateful
Stop it Dad.
I didn't do anything bad.
- Dad believe me.
- Idiot!
- You're just my adopted.
- Dad.
Dad it's not my fault.
Give me that!
Dad have mercy on me.
- I'll kill you.
- Dad stop it.
You're ungrateful!
- I'll kill you.
- Believe me, it wasn't my fault.
- You idiot.
Ungrateful!
Ungrateful.
- I'll kill...
- Boss calm down.
Have pity, he's your child.
You're right.
Next time don't pry.
Meddler.
What happened?
We were attacked by person.
Somebody sneaked up here.
- All our guns were stolen.
- What?
Son of sheep!
Sorry boss.
Sorry.
You idiot.
Son of a sheep.
Only one person stole all our guns.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Don 't!
I'll take off that plaster on your mouth...
but in one condition.
Don't scream.
Do you understand?
Ouch. What are you?
You're an awful person to talk with.
You snap ped it.
There.
You are like that.
Instead of thanking me...
you're hurting me.
- Would you just shut up.
- Rich people are like that.
You look down on us poor people.
Where are you going?
You know I am a worthless person.
But Ben took me in.
He treated me like true family.
He treated me like one of his kin.
I was surprised.
When he got married.
I never thought he'd find someone to love.
But you know...
one night, all of Ben's dreams were
disappeared.
Because of what your family did.
That's it?
Choose a card here.
Get one card.
I'll guess what card did you get.
Just one card.
One card.
You are on handcuffs
Let's do it like this.
Remember one card.
Just remember.
That card will disappear.
No more.
Even if you go find it one by one.
It's not here.
No more, right
One card isn't here.
The one that you chose wasn't here
anymore.
Bastard!
This old man literary let me eat the dust.
Don't worry, I'll let you have a snack.
Move!
That's new, I haven't seen that yet.
- Mike!
- Hello.
Mike, hello.
Can you hear me?
- Save me here.
- Where?
Where?
I'm here in Fairview.
Caloy!
Caloy.
Brother Ben.
What happened?
She was taken.
Give this to Benjamin.
I promised to give that to him.
Benjamin?
Who's Benjamin?
Forgive me, I kept a secret from you.
Caloy, what secret?
The night when armed men
attacked your house...
Carol was killed.
But the baby in her womb survived.
My child is alive?
Where is my child?
Caloy.
Gina knows.
Hello?
Where are you hiding now Angel?
Like the old times.
I'm still better than you.
I'll kill you.
I should have killed Mando not you!
You're wrong Angel.
My brother owes me big time.
So it's just right that I kill him.
Bring back Gina to me.
You don't need her.
You're wrong again Angel.
I need Gina more right now.
Because she will tell me
where to find my money.
And besides...
I'll use her...
so we could come face to face.
Just tell me where.
Anytime!
I'll come.
Why are you doing this to us, Uncle?
You could have told daddy.
Your daddy is greedy.
I'm just getting what is mine.
The one that should be mine.
Where is the money?
Tell me first where is my daddy
and brothers.
Don't ask me, ask Ben.
Ben knows.
Before I lose my patience.
Where is the money?
Bring it out!
Here.
Who moved it?
What?
The money is gone.
Where did you put it?
I just placed it here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Damn!
Those animals!
Shit!
Did you tell with someone else?
Ben.
Who?
Tom.
Is this the one you've been looking for?
Tom I didn't know if you recognize.
If I want to shoot you...
I could have killed you yesterday.
But I want to hear from your own mouth.
That your group killed my wife.
And you were the one who shot me.
You're one of a kind Angel alias Ben.
I've shot you on your forehead.
Now you're still breathing in front of me.
What are we going to do now?
We should continue
what we haven't finished.
We will really continue it Tom.
Co'z I won't ever forget
what you did to my wife and child.
You are animals.
I begged to all of you.
But you didn't listen.
Now Tom...
you'll regret that you taught me
everything you knew.
But you should be careful, too.
- Or you might... hit Gina.
- Ben!
Gina has nothing to do with our feud.
And you didn't teach me to hide
from a girl's skirt.
How can this old man run?
I thought he has rheumatism.
His knees are aching.
You're an idiot Angel.
I've killed you already.
You should have died.
You should have been with your family.
But don't worry.
You can catch them up.
They miss you badly.
This grandpa talks a lot.
Are you okay grandpa?
The reason why I came to life...
co'z they're waiting for you there.
You should go first.
And not in heaven, alright in hell.
Co'z you fit there.
Idiot!
Can you still chase me?
Or your knees are aching?
Let's go grandpa.
Son of a bitch,
he's gonna let me chase him again.
I can see you now. Hide at least.
I thought your knees
were the ones aching...
You also have poor eyesight.
Fool!
Why don't you show your head?
So you'd know how poor my eyes are.
Ben?
Ben.
- Gina come here.
- Ben.
Hurry!
Angel.
You could have been really good.
I taught you how to kill.
Become rich.
And I've taught you a lot of things
more than that.
But you made one mistake...
that I didn't ever teach you.
To die for a woman.
Uncle Tom you're an evil.
You don't have a heart!
Why do you think your father has?
Don't meddle on this one Gina.
This is a fight between the teacher...
and his student.
But Tom.
The teacher will be gone later...
the student will remain.
Gina listen to your uncle.
He's right.
What now Tom?
Are you done with your speech.
Let's finish this.
Gina bow down.
Alvin ?
Alvin.
I saved you.
Are just going to stare?
Aren't you gonna thank me?
You and your father...
you really deserve to die.
You don't appreciate
the things around you.
You were like leech.
You know nothing but to suck.
Alvin what are you saying?
Don't talk yet.
Listen first.
You know,
your dad and you are the same.
You just want to be heard.
You don't want to listen.
When did you give me an attention...
real love.
Alvin I loved you like a true brother.
Damn!
Loved?
I am the poorest...
the most stupid...
- the moron.
- You should have been there.
You are not my son! I just adopted you.
The worthless child in our house.
But I told myself.
It wouldn't last long.
Our situation will all turn.
Ecclesiastes chapter 3 verse 2.
When there's a beginning,
there's an end.
Thy kingdom will come in no time.
What do you mean?
You know I need to employ new people.
You should have killed him.
Shit!
That's what we've agreed Tom?
You're wasting my time.
Don't shout at me.
Don't teach me what to do.
I know when to move.
You know?
Why is it until now Mike is still alive?
And then your brother Mando will follow.
This is not just for me, right?
For the two of us.
Uncle Tom.
Whom your dad took advantage of.
And Lucas who's behind you now...
can easily be paid.
Boss the car is here, I left it.
This is clean, they won't be able to get
finger prints.
What happened?
The men that you sent for Gina missed.
Those idiots!
What do you want us to do?
Don't move yet...
wait for my call.
Your kingdom is mine.
What do you mean?
Simple.
Now that I have no one to share it with.
This is the one.
Lying down.
And your protector Ben is gone.
How's that now?
Let's finish your suffering here on earth.
You might be happier in heaven.
Goodbye my dear sister.
Alvin no.
Alvin have mercy on me please.
Ben are you okay?
I thought...
This is the necklace
that Caloy is talking about.
That's the one.
He'll give it.
And I can't give it if you won't help me.
Because you know the place...
where we could find him.
That hurts.
Ben answer me truthfully.
Did you come here for me?
Before I answer that...
I want to know if I'm really alive.
You're still alive.
I'm still alive?
I won't let you go.
Really?
I also don't want to lose you.
I once lost my loved ones.
I won't let that happen again.
What are you waiting for?
That's the cue.
What cue?
Cue.
Don't you watch action films?
No.
You...
When the conversaion reached that level.
What?
That means kiss.
Again.
Yes.
That is necessary.
Help me.
I'm having a hard time here.
That's your kiss?
That kiss is so plain.
Make it better.
You're going to die.
It's the end.
You're getting there.
My chest is aching.
Help me.