Okay, Abrams.
Allende.
Bernstein.
Buckley.
Cohen.
Thanks, Mr. Aaron.
Garcia.
Paul.
Take a seat, Lisa.
I just wanted to talk to you
about your test, for a minute.
Sure.
Now, I know you had a little help.
A lot of people did.
Well, be that as it may...
I mean, I'll take it over again if you
want, but, like, what would be the point?
It's not like I'm ever gonna actually
need to know this stuff in my daily life.
Well, that's just not
necessarily true, Lisa.
Haven't you ever developed
an interest in something
that you didn't initially think you
were gonna develop an interest in?
Um...
No, not really.
Haven't you ever...
Haven't you ever been
put in a new situation
and found that after
overcoming its difficulties,
you had developed a new set of skills
and new experiences along the way?
No, I really haven't.
Anyway, it was open-book.
So, what's the difference
between using a book
and, like, I don't know,
using somebody else's mind
who's, like, really good at math?
I mean, it's not like this person
did the whole test for me.
- Oh, no?
- No, I did some of it.
Well, next time I'd appreciate
it if you did it all.
Okay?
You are so fair.
Hey, Lisa.
What did he say to you?
Nothing.
Mr. Aaron and I have an understanding
about my math problem.
So the president of the United
States, William B. McKinley,
authorizes the use of private
detectives to break the strike
and they went out there
and shot them down!
Just like they did in Virginia,
just like they did in Pennsylvania.
Because they didn't care!
They did not care!
And that's basically it.
That's basically all there is to say.
All right? Go ahead.
- Uh, Becky.
- Well...
Mr. Klein! I mean, was there ever, like,
a good President of the United States?
I don't know, Becky. I think
that's a good question.
What do you think?
You. Lionel. What do you think? Did
we ever have a good president?
Um... I don't know.
I guess most of them have just
been, like, totally corrupt.
Lisa?
Can I just say that I'm not
necessarily, like, a big fan
of all the presidents
of the United States,
especially the current one.
But I still don't think it's
necessarily all that useful
to categorize every president
as universally corrupt,
because that just seems
really general to me.
Especially if you're gonna
judge them by the standard
of whatever they're supposed
to traditionally be like
in some mythical version of America that
probably never existed to begin with.
Lisa has raised a salient point.
Tell him to be polite, tell
him to answer the questions,
and I'll arrange for his
bail in the morning. Yes.
Hey, how'd you do?
Hey, Darren. It was fine.
Thank you so much.
So he didn't give you a
hard time or anything?
Well, he knows I'm not planning to,
like, go into mathematics or anything.
He was totally cool about it.
- He's so cool.
- Oh, yeah, everybody loves Mr. Aaron.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing. The man is very lovable.
What are you doing now?
I was gonna go look for a cowboy hat.
Why would you want
to buy a cowboy hat?
Because my dad is supposed
to take me and my brother
to this ranch in New Mexico
to go horseback riding
and I don't think it would be right
to appear on horseback in New Mexico
without the appropriate
equestrian paraphernalia, Darren.
You wouldn't understand these things.
- That is a definite possibility.
- Anyway, thanks again.
Well, before you venture forth on your
bizarre quest for a cowboy hat...
- Yes, Darren?
- What are you up to later?
- Like tonight.
- I don't know.
You wanna go to a movie?
What, you mean, like on a date?
No, not on a date, just go to a movie.
I don't know if it's a fucking date!
All right. Calm down.
What do you wanna see?
I don't know, I don't
even know what's playing.
I don't know if it's a date.
Let's just forget about it. I
hate the fucking movies anyway.
They're just bullshit.
They're all bullshit!
Okay, take it easy. I'm sorry.
I was just asking!
What if it was a date, anyway?
Would that be so horrendous?
Oh, my God. Are you like...
Are you asking me out?
Are you?
Hello! Earth to Darren.
I don't know.
- I don't know.
- Are you?
Yeah. I mean...
- I feel like we're already really close...
- Oh, my God.
...and I think we'd be
a really good match.
- What?
- Nothing, this is...
Nothing.
So, yeah.
I would. I mean, yes, I am. Yes, I am.
Well, I would definitely
have to think about this.
Absolutely. Give it some thought.
Okay. I will.
Okay.
- Why do you look like that?
- Like what?
- What do you want from me?
- Not a thing!
All right. I'll see you later.
All right.
Hello!
Hi.
- Is Mom home?
- She went to the store.
- Hey!
- What are you doing tonight?
Nothing. Darren wants me to
go to the movies with him.
- Oh, my God.
- You want to come?
What's that about?
I have no idea.
Becky, there is not a cowboy hat to be
found in the entire upper West Side.
And I am very depressed about it.
Dude, the Upper West side is
saving you from yourself,
because no one wants to
see you in that hat.
Hey! Hey!
- Where'd you get...
- How you doing?
Your hat!
What?
Where'd you get your cowboy hat?
What are you, crazy?
Hi.
Where'd you get your cowboy hat?
- My hat?
- Yeah! Your cowboy hat!
You like my cowboy hat? Really?
Yes! Where did you get it?
Somebody call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance.
Everybody just step back!
I'm calling one right now!
- Can you hear me?
- Get an ambulance!
- Someone's calling one!
- Ma'am, can you hear me?
- Can you hear me?
- I don't know! Where am I?
You're on Broadway and
75th street in New York.
Between 75th and 74th street.
- You were in a bad accident.
- Who are you?
- My name is Lisa.
- What do you mean? Am I dead?
No, you're not dead.
You were in a traffic accident,
but you're gonna be okay.
I don't have a direct address.
She's out in the street.
What do you mean? What happened?
- You were run over by a bus.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- A bus?
- Yeah.
- Is there a doctor anywhere?
- So where am I now?
- An ambulance is on its way.
- Is it still happening?
No. The accident's over. I think
you're a little confused.
I'll say I'm confused.
Here. Let me try to see...
- No! Don't let go!
- Ma'am!
- Don't let go of me! Don't let go of me.
- I won't.
I won't. I'm not gonna let go.
Thank you. Thank you, honey.
Don't let go of me.
She needs a tourniquet
or she's going to die.
Okay, let me just...
Christ!
Jesus!
I mean, what's happening to me?
Oh, my God, get your hands off!
I'm sorry. I'm trying to
put a tourniquet on you.
Ma'am, we need to get
a tourniquet on you.
Do you have a belt? You
can use your belt.
I just can't see where to do it.
You're gonna be all right,
so just hang on. Okay?
- Thank you, honey. Just don't let go of me.
- I won't.
I swear to you, I'm not gonna let go.
They just wanna put a
tourniquet on you.
What do you mean? Are they doctors?
- No, they're not doctors.
- Who are they?
They were just passing by.
Well, get them the fuck away from me!
Ma'am! We're only trying to help you!
Never mind that! Just try
putting it around...
Do you wanna do it? You know
how to do it. You wanna do it?
Are you kidding me!
I can't see anything.
Are my eyes open or closed?
They're open.
What do you mean?
You were in a terrible accident.
But you're gonna be fine,
so just hang on, okay?
There's no place to put it.
I can't even find a...
Will somebody call the
fucking ambulance!
Calm down! We already called them!
They're obviously not coming fast enough,
so maybe you should call them again!
Why not call them again?
- You're gonna be okay...
- Could somebody...
Could somebody call my daughter?
Sure! We can call her.
What's her name?
Just tell me her name
and give me her number.
It's Lisa.
No, that's my name.
Is that your daughter's name?
What? What are you talking about?
I'm sorry. I'm not
trying to be confusing.
My name is Lisa. Is that
your daughter's name?
Jesus Christ, just call her!
Would you call her?
I can't call her if you
don't give me the number.
I got it. I got it!
Ma'am?
- You're gonna be okay.
- You're gonna be okay!
What's your daughter's number?
Sweetie,
- I don't think I'm gonna make it.
- Oh, no!
No! Please hang on. The ambulance
is gonna be here any minute!
So just hang on, okay?
- Please!
- It's okay.
- She's gone. She's gone.
- No! No!
Let go of me!
Please, let go! Please, let go of me!
Please, let go of me!
Just hang on. They're gonna
be here any minute, okay?
So just hang on, honey!
Just hang on!
Hang on!
- You were going the speed limit?
- Yeah.
Lisa? Okay, you're Lisa? Lisa?
Lisa, I just want to ask
you a few questions, okay?
Okay, sure.
Tell me everything you saw,
even if you think it might
not be important. All right?
- Could somebody call my mother?
- We already called your mom,
but I'll have them put another call
in to your mother right now, okay?
Some of these questions might seem like
they don't make a lot of sense to you.
They do make sense. Just ask me!
Okay, that's what I'm doing.
All right?
So now I'm gonna ask you,
from where you were standing,
could you see the traffic light?
Could you tell me if it was red?
Yellow? Green?
What color was the light?
I...
- I guess it was green?
- Green?
I think it was just an accident.
- What happened to you?
- Nothing.
Hello?
Good one, Lisa.
I don't know if I'm gonna
be able to get these clean.
- Just throw them out.
- Well, let me see if I can get them clean.
So, does anybody know who she was?
I don't know. I guess
she lived around here,
if she had all these
Fairway grocery bags.
- What did they do with her leg?
- I have no fucking idea.
Hey.
Lisa? Are you sure you
don't want me to call in?
Oh, no, thanks.
I mean, thank you.
That's really sweet,
but I'm supposed to
go see Becky anyway,
and I don't really want to sit
here thinking about it all night.
Go to work. I'll be all right.
- Hey.
- Hey, Darren.
Hey.
- Joan?
- Yeah?
- You got some flowers.
- Can you bring them in?
I just wanna get home.
Yeah. Yeah, she's fine. She'll be fine.
I just...
So, how's your... how are your boys?
Been so long since I've seen them,
they don't even know me anymore.
- Hey, are you coming out?
- Um... I don't know. I'm not sure.
- Come on.
- Maybe I will.
I don't know if I'm going to.
But I might.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Goodnight.
- See you later.
Hi, are you Ramon?
Yes. Hello. You were wonderful again.
Oh, you're so sweet. And thank
you for the beautiful flowers.
- You're very welcome.
- And you've seen the show before?
Yes, two times.
Gosh. That's a lot!
It's a beautiful performance.
I'm sure you will have a big success.
Well, right now, we're just trying
to focus on what we're doing.
I don't know if you are busy, but would
you allow me to buy you a drink?
There is a nice place
right down the street.
If you like to ask your friends...
- I'm sorry. I can't. I'm just on
my way home. - Okay, that's no problem.
Tomorrow I'm going to
London for a few days.
- Perhaps when I come back.
- Um...
- Well...
- If it's not convenient...
No, no. It's okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry. I really have to go.
- Okay. That's no problem.
Anyway, thanks again for
the beautiful flowers!
- It's a privilege to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you, too.
- Goodnight.
Hey.
- I thought you were at the movies.
- Yeah, it wasn't very good.
I was doing a show in Detroit
and this woman came backstage,
and she's like, "wanna come back
to my place and do some cocaine?"
I was like, "I'm not
the kind of person
"you want wired in your apartment
at 4:00 in the morning. "
I'll get us thrown out.
Oh, oh. Do the Shirley Temple! Come
on, do the Shirley Temple for us.
Okay.
On the good ship lollipop
it's a sweet trip to the candy shop
and there you are
happy landing on the chocolate bar
if you eat too much
Oh! Oh! You'll...
Keep going!
That's awesome!
Wait, what's that one?
Do the baby.
No. That's too strange.
No, no, no, you have to do it.
- It's so disturbing.
- I know. It's too weird.
- No, it's not.
- Have another drink.
I think we can tell I've had enough.
Matthew, if you would
read the role of France.
And, Anthony, why don't
you read Burgundy?
Ah, Burgundy.
And I guess I'm gonna hog
the part of Lear again.
Okay, Anthony?
Uh...
"Royal majesty, I crave no more
than what your highness offered,
"nor will you tender less. "
"Right, noble Burgundy,
"when she was dear to
us, we did hold her so,
"but now her price is fall'n. "
But he is a very nice person.
I know him. He's wonderful.
He drives down to meet
her every Saturday.
That's a very long drive.
Do you know that he has three sisters?
...so I invited her along.
I didn't think it was gonna
sully our whole relationship.
They haven't spoken to
each other for 14 years.
Nothing.
She has a dog. It used
to belong to her father.
Such an ugly face.
She loved that dog.
When I saw the dog, I told her,
I said, "I never saw such an ugly dog. "
You know what she said? "Good.
Nobody's gonna steal him. "
Who wants to steal him?
No, I can't.
I've been thinking
about your suggestion.
Mmm-hmm.
I guess, I don't think
it's a very good idea.
Why not?
I guess I don't feel
that way about you.
But those kinds of
feelings can develop.
I definitely feel like
there's a connection there.
I know there is.
I think you're just scared.
I think you've been hurt
by other relationships
you've had in the past,
and I think what it would feel
like to have a real feeling
is really terrifying you.
What's the matter?
Hey, what's the matter?
My family are from Colombia.
My father worked in the
diplomatic service.
Really? Wow.
I grew up five years in Panama
and nine years in Paris.
And what do you do, Ramon?
I have a company. We
design computer software
to help companies in
South American countries
that use an incompatible software, so
the computers can talk to each other.
It's a big problem in South America
where there is not so much coordination
in computer communication.
Right now is a lot of
opportunity for us
because for the big software
companies, we are still the backwoods.
That's changing quite fast.
Can I give you a lift?
Oh, no, thank you, I'm just
gonna grab a cab. But thanks.
May I call you sometime?
Okay. Sure, that would be great.
May I have your telephone number?
Oh, my God. I'm sorry. Of course. Duh.
Hold on a second. Do you have a pen?
What's your number?
212-555-0157.
- Mom?
- Just a minute!
- Can I come in?
- Just a second, please. Hold on.
Come in.
Can I talk to you?
Sure. What's up?
I have not heard a thing.
The odds are probably good.
I mean, same crap happened
last time he was with her.
Last time he was seeing
her, he disappeared...
Larry, I didn't want to ask her
about it in the middle of dinner.
I didn't expect you to. It just galls
me that they put us in this position...
You know what? I really don't
want to shout from room to room.
I'll be ready in five minutes. You can
tell me everything I did wrong last night,
and then maybe I'll give you a little preview
of everything I'm gonna do wrong tonight.
You know what? Fuck it, I'll just...
And I guess I was kind of waving back
because I was trying to get him to stop.
But I'm supposed to go back to the
police to confirm my statement, like,
the day after tomorrow.
So what do you think I should do?
Well,
it doesn't sound like
it was anybody's fault.
But don't you think I should
say something to them now?
Well, I don't know, sweetie.
I mean, that bus driver probably
has a family to support.
He could probably lose his job.
So I think you should really think
about it before you say anything.
Okay.
Think of the implications
of what you're saying.
I'm saying what is the frame of reference
for the average arab on the street?
- Angie.
- Yeah. My mother's family is from Syria,
and they're not exactly in
love with the current regime.
And I definitely don't agree with
a lot of their religious views,
especially when it comes to
the oppression of women.
But I just wanna say that
Americans have no idea
how much people hate them
all over the world. Okay?
We don't?
And all my relatives in Syria
think what we did in Afghanistan
was terrorism, okay?
- Anthony?
- Not to mention Iraq.
- Syria is a theocratic military
dictatorship. - No, it's not. Sorry.
Syria is not a theocratic
military dictatorship?
I think we have a pretty good idea how
much people hate us now, actually, Angie.
No, we don't.
They blew up our city, okay? So, yeah,
I think we have a pretty good idea
- and personally, I don't give a shit.
- You should.
Because the people who blew
up the World Trade Center
were a bunch of sick monsters.
- Oh, they were monsters?
- Yes!
Why, because they're Arabs?
No, because they killed
3,000 people for no reason.
Maybe they think they had a reason!
- Like what?
- One at a time!
- Why did we drop bombs on them?
- What should we have done?
- Why did we invade Iraq?
- They declared war on us.
No, they didn't. Iraq didn't
declare war on anybody!
- They didn't do anything to us!
- Come on, guys, one at a time!
- Anthony.
- They did have a reason.
Thank you.
They wanted to establish a medieval
Islamic caliphate in the Middle East
and destroy Western civilization.
- Where did you read that?
- It's on their website.
- Okay, forget it.
- Angie!
Go ahead with what you were saying!
No! Why should I?
But why are you defending someone
who murdered 3,000 people?
I'm not!
Why are you defending a country that
unilaterally invaded two Muslim countries
and supports the Israeli
occupation of Palestine?
Give me a break!
And drops bombs on women and children
and then calls other people terrorists
for doing the exact same thing?
- Because it's not the same thing!
- Yes, it is!
- Come on, guys.
- Lionel! Go ahead.
Yeah, I just want to ask why is
it okay to drop bombs on men
but it's not okay to drop
bombs on women and children?
I mean, isn't that just
like reverse sexism?
I don't know. I agree
it's a bullshit term.
- This is totally stupid.
- Monica!
I think the whole class should
apologize to Angie, actually,
'cause all she did was express her opinion
about what her relatives in Syria think.
- Thank you!
- And everyone started screaming at her
like she was defending
the Ku Klux Klan!
They are the Ku Klux Klan! They
throw acid in women's faces.
- Who? Afghanistans?
- Why not drop bombs on the Ku Klux Klan!
Because they're white?
Six people had their hands
raised before you, Lisa.
Okay, I'm not even saying
that I disagree with you.
I'm just saying I think it's pathetic the
way people in this class treated Angie
just for saying something they
didn't happen to agree with.
Because that's censorship. Right?
- Right?
- It's not censorship!
- Right on!
- This class is not the government.
- It's censorship.
- Oh, my God, no, it's not!
Ready?
He's been with this other
woman for 12 years.
He has a 4-year-old daughter,
and every year he says he's gonna
tell his wife he's gonna leave her.
He never tells her.
He never tells her anything.
She has no idea what's going on.
Finally, the woman calls up and
says, "I'd like you to know
"that your husband has another wife and
another daughter in Staten Island. "
This is like an ordinary guy.
We work out of highway
one out in the Bronx.
Near the Bronx loo.
- Oh, okay.
- But for a situation...
Hey, how are you doing? But
for something like this,
we usually find a local
precinct or an apartment.
Whatever will expediate the
situation most effectively.
Have a seat wherever you want.
Just pull up a chair.
According to this statement,
the light was green
when the bus passed
through the intersection.
Yes.
So you're saying she
walked against the light?
It's true. Two years of college,
two years at the magazine.
Two years with you.
I'm kind of a two-year gal!
What's funny about that?
What did you think of the play?
It was okay.
Well, thank you, honey.
- Hello?
- Hi, Dad!
Yeah! Hi!
- How are you?
- I'm okay. I'm fine.
I'm just sitting here, looking at the
ocean, trying to do a little work,
listening to some music.
- How are you?
- I'm okay.
Are you practicing
your horseback riding?
Oh, yeah, I've really
been riding a lot.
I'm getting these really
bad saddle sores.
- Are you?
- No, I'm kidding.
Yeah. Do you know
Claremont Stables on 89th,
between Columbus and Amsterdam?
- Yeah.
- Well, it might be really worth your while
to go over there and maybe sign
up for a couple of lessons.
- No...
- I'd be happy to...
I'm sorry, what?
I was just saying I'd be
very happy to spring for it
if you want to take a couple of lessons.
I think it would pay off in the end.
- Thanks. I actually may take you up
on that. - Yeah, just let me know.
- I appreciate that.
- So, how's school?
School's okay. I'm kind of
fucking up in geometry.
But I assume you're not torpedoing your
scholarship or anything like that?
- Nope. The scholarship's on.
- Okay, good. Good.
Well, math was never my
strong suit either, so...
Well, I guess I'm following in
your footsteps in that regard.
Well, I'm proud to hear it.
So, how are you?
Um... I'm okay. Things are okay.
They're a little slow and
a little frustrating.
But there's one or two projects we're
going after that seem to look promising.
And, I don't know, I think it's okay.
Okay.
How's the boyfriend situation?
Oh. The same.
- Nobody...
- They're all kind of the same.
No fascinating young men
knocking at your door?
Yeah, very few fascinating
young men at my school.
Well, I know this is not
going to go anywhere,
but our next workshop is
comprised, for the most part,
of strapping young men of
about 17 years old who,
for some peculiar reason, are
interested in using their brains
to get on with their lives.
Nobody really understands
why or how this happened,
but if you're interested in meeting any
of them when you come out next time...
Yeah, I don't really go for the
California type, but thanks.
Well, I don't either, per se. It
depends on the person, obviously.
Hard to argue with. I think
I'll stop generalizing now.
Well, that's about it
on my end, sweetie.
I'll give you a call in a week or two.
- Give my love to Curtis.
- Okay. I can't wait for our trip.
Yeah. I think it's gonna be really fun.
I really do.
I think you're gonna have
- a really, really good time.
- Okay. Well...
- I love you.
- I love you, too. Bye.
- Okay. Bye, Dad.
- Okay. Take care, bye.
- You do know I have two kids, right?
- Yes. I would like to meet them.
You are really smooth.
I would love to meet your kids. I
have two boys myself. I'm not smooth.
Would you like to have a nightcap?
- Hey, Carol?
- Yeah?
Did you happen to talk
to Jennifer last night?
I just...
I feel like we used to
be really close, like,
up until a few days ago,
and I'm really not getting
that from you anymore.
Becky, give me a break.
I can't believe you
just said that to me.
Now you wanna do the other nostril
because you always want to be symmetrical.
Very important.
You are so funny.
Symmetry.
So, what do we do now?
- Now we make out.
- Paul! What about your girlfriend?
I'm sorry. It just sounded like
you asked me about my girlfriend.
Oh, never mind.
We're not serious.
Oh, okay.
I don't know, man. I
don't wanna get into it.
Hey.
You know I really love you, right?
Not really.
I guess I'm not very consistent.
I don't mind.
I gotta go home.
Okay.
I'm just gonna head out, too.
You need a little help, I take it?
Need some help?
Okay.
Joan, are you all right?
Yes, fine. I'll be out in a sec.
Okay, we're gonna start with
a few simple stretches.
And I want you all to watch me
first, and then you'll follow.
All right, so left arm goes up.
And then all the way over to the side,
you're gonna feel a long, long
stretch along the side of your body.
And then up, under.
Right arm up, and a long
nice stretch the other side.
All right.
- Mr. Aaron?
- Yes, Becky... Lisa?
Are you still mad at
me about the test?
What's going on, Lisa?
Because maybe the bus driver is
completely devastated as it is,
and I'm just gonna be
this little rich girl
who calls up the cops
to ease her conscience.
What does your being rich
have to do with anything?
- You know what I mean.
- No, I don't.
I don't mean literally rich. I mean
rich compared to the bus driver.
Lionel? I'm going to
need five minutes.
I just thought you wanted to know
that there's a lot of people out here
and it's getting kind
of hard to breathe.
You better close that
door now, Lionel.
I'm sorry, I gotta let these guys in.
I don't want to leave you hanging.
Look, if you're hurting,
- we could get a cup of coffee after school.
- I'd do that.
Hey, does this dress make me look fat?
Um... a little.
Well, there's nothing
I can do about it.
- Where are you going?
- The opera.
Why are you going to the opera?
Turns out he's a really big opera fan.
Anyway, don't you think it sounds
kind of fun? We should all go sometime.
No, thanks.
- Why not? I bet you'd like it.
- I don't like that kind of singing.
You like classical music.
Yes, that's true, but I
don't like opera singing.
- When have you ever...
- It's like their entire reason for existing
is to prove how loud they can be.
I don't really find that
all that interesting.
Yeah. I know what you mean, but it's not
all like that. You like The Magic Flute.
Okay. I guess I'm wrong.
I guess I do like opera singing.
I just didn't realize it.
- What is the matter with you?
- Nothing at all.
Why are you pushing this? I
don't want to go to the opera!
Yes, okay. It's called an invitation.
I'm not pushing anything. All
you have say is, "No, thanks. "
I did and then you
were like, "why not?"
So then I told you, and then
you started debating me,
like you assumed that I've never
thought this through for myself,
which I have, many times!
Okay, well that was a really
contemptuous assumption on my part.
I don't actually like the
opera that much myself,
but I'm trying to expand my mind.
Maybe that's wrong.
I'm sorry. I guess I'm a little
nervous about you guys meeting Ramon.
Why? What's the big deal? Why are you
so influenced by what Curtis and me...
...what Curtis and I think?
Hey, why does everything
I say annoy you?
Jesus Christ, I'm just sitting here.
Here, you be me, and say
anything and I'll respond to you
the way you've been responding
to me this whole conversation.
- Go ahead, you say something to me...
- No! I'm not gonna do that.
- Why not?
- Because it's dumb!
I'm horrible. I get your point!
Oh, okay. Whatever.
Was that supposed to
be an imitation of me?
Mmm. Okay, withdrawn.
Are you coming to my opening night?
I will if I have to.
- You're a little cunt, you know that?
- Yes. You're a big cunt.
Okay, let's not start talking
to each other that way.
You just called me a cunt, Mom.
- I'm sorry I said that...
- Why? It's refreshing.
If you're saying you're not aware
you've been really annoyed with me,
or really irritable with me,
and it doesn't matter if I
express it exactly accurately,
- because you know what I'm trying to say.
- Not really.
If you're really saying that
you're completely unaware of that,
then I have to say I don't think
you're being honest about it.
Now, maybe I'm doing something really
horrible to you without being aware of it,
but I have a show opening in two
weeks. I'm really nervous about it,
I'm seeing a new person
and I'm obviously anxious about
you and Curtis liking him,
you were involved in this
horrible, traumatic accident,
you're going on this crazy horseback
riding trip with your father...
- Oh, my God! - ... which sounds
like a recipe for disaster.
And on top of everything else, Lisa,
ever since I told you about Ramon,
you have been treating
me like I'm insane.
- I think you're exaggerating.
- Now, what am I supposed to do?
- What am I supposed to do?
- Just stop whining about everything!
It doesn't matter. None of it matters
at all. You've been in a million plays,
you always get freaked out
because of what some dumb critic
is gonna say about your dumb play.
I don't frankly give a shit about Ramon
or who you're going out with this week.
I never go out with anyone.
- I don't care!
- Don't talk to me like that!
I've barely had a date
for the last two years!
Yeah, but I don't care about any of it.
It doesn't matter.
Your boyfriend doesn't matter. Your
play doesn't matter, except to you.
I don't care about New Mexico,
because to tell you the truth,
I'm probably not even going.
- What do you mean?
- Want to know something else, Mom?
There are more important problems
in the world than our relationship.
There is a whole city out there
full of people who are dying,
so who gives a shit if I
like your fucking boyfriend?
It is so trivial. Why are you bothering
me with all this? It doesn't matter.
Well, should I have him come up now?
Or should I have him
just wait downstairs?
Do whatever you want. I don't care.
Lisa, I don't even know
what we're talking about.
I know you don't. That's the problem.
Oh, give me a break.
Everything is all right?
Oh, yeah. Oh. I'm so excited
to be going to the opera.
I don't think I've really gone
more than one or two times.
I wish it wasn't Norma,
but still it's fun to go.
- It's beautiful.
- Shh.
- Yo.
- Hey, Paul.
- Hey.
- It's Lisa Cohen.
Yeah, how's it going?
Okay. What have you been up to?
Seeing some questionable movies, and
not deciding where to go to college.
Sounds good.
So, I was just thinking...
This is gonna sound really queer,
but, by any chance would
you want to meet somewhere
and, like, take away my virginity?
Um... all right.
Really?
God, I'm so flattered.
To what do I owe this
inconceivable honor?
Actually, it's because of my deep,
passionate feelings for you, Paul.
That's pretty much
what I figured.
- Hello?
- Hey. What are you up to?
Hey. Nothing.
Writing my King Lear paper.
Really? That's impressive.
Not really.
So, what did you do tonight?
Actually, Darren, I don't really
feel like talking right now.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah. I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
- Hey.
- Hey, come in.
I think I just alienated one of your
neighbors by smoking in the elevator.
Really? What did they say?
She basically said there was
no smoking in the elevator.
That's original.
So, this is the living room.
- Very livable.
- We like it.
My mom hasn't read any of
these books, by the way.
Have you?
Some of them. Not all of them.
This book is a very cool book.
Yeah, I think the Third Reich may be a
little bit too much for me right now.
It's pretty hard to put
down once you get started.
Do you want anything to drink?
I'd take a beer.
Okay, that's in the kitchen.
Okay.
- I have no idea where the bottle opener is.
- Let me have them.
Thanks.
Oops, I think I just permanently
damaged your kitchen counter. Sorry.
- No, it's okay. Don't worry about it.
- Won't your mother be upset?
How come everything you say
always sounds so ironic?
You don't even have to do anything,
and it just comes out sounding,
like, totally ironic and funny.
It's just a gift.
- So, do you want to see my room?
- Sure.
This is my room. Ta-da.
Very nice.
And these are my stuffed animals.
Always important to meet
the stuffed animals.
These are some drawings I did.
Not that I should be
showing them to you,
because I know you're like a
really good artist, right?
I would like to be a
really good artist.
At this point, I think it would be more
accurate to say I'm good at drawing.
Yeah, I just do it for fun. But
I've always really liked it.
- So, can I ask you something?
- Yes.
This is probably gonna
sound very immature,
but how can you be so relaxed,
knowing what we're about to do?
Or is it just like no big deal to you?
Okay, that was a really stupid question,
and I'm totally embarrassed right now.
I'm actually more embarrassed
than I've ever been in my life.
If you wanna go home now,
that's totally okay.
Easy there. Don't be embarrassed.
It's basically, like, the
world's greatest activity,
but it's not actually worth
getting nervous about.
Yeah, I don't usually get nervous
because I think it's worth it,
I usually get nervous because
I can't help the way I feel.
There is that philosophy.
You are so funny.
Do you have an ashtray?
You can just chuck it out the window.
How would one just chuck
it out the window?
Oh, you just slide the little door...
Like that?
Yes.
Am I supposed to go really
fast at the end or something?
Yeah, but we're gonna
move on before that.
Here.
Oh, oh. You don't have to do that.
I know. I want to.
But don't do that. Okay?
I'm just embarrassed.
- Let me do it to you.
- All right.
Uh... um...
Any general guidelines?
Just be careful.
Okay.
This is a little tricky.
It's probably gonna hurt a little at
first, but then it's gonna get better.
Just be patient.
There are certain technical difficulties
on my end that have to be addressed,
or it's not gonna happen.
Okay. You sound insane.
Okay, ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay, hang on.
Okay, there we go.
- Does it hurt now?
- Kind of, yeah.
Okay, just try to relax. It'll
get better in a second.
- Did you bring a condom?
- Uh-huh.
- Shouldn't you put it on?
- I will in a second.
- This is really kind of hurting.
- Okay, one second.
- I love you.
- What?
Nothing.
Okay. Hold on.
- Shit.
- What?
Okay, one second. Oh! Sorry.
Sorry.
Oh!
Sorry about that.
Kind of got away from me.
- Did any of it get inside me?
- I don't know.
Yeah. It definitely did.
Honest to God, it's probably okay.
The odds are overwhelmingly
that it's okay.
That's my little brother.
- Hey, Curtis.
- Hi.
Thanks.
I'm actually kind of mad at you.
Why?
Because we didn't use birth control?
I guess so.
It was at the ready.
Well, I don't really want
to get AIDS, you know,
and I really don't want
to have an abortion,
because I know when you
have one at my age,
it can be really hard to
get pregnant later on,
and I definitely want to
have children someday.
Try to listen to me.
You're not gonna get AIDS
because I don't have AIDS.
How do you know? Have you been tested?
No, but I'm pretty sure I don't
have it because of my demographic.
And the odds are you're probably not
gonna have to have an abortion either.
And since this was your first time,
it might as well be a basically happy
memory instead of a shitty one.
I'm sorry.
I'm not completely in
control of my emotions.
Anyway, thank you for deflowering me.
You're welcome.
Did it freak you out
that I said I love you?
Nope, didn't freak me out.
You don't have to say it back
because I know you probably have,
like, no feelings at all for me.
I think I just proved I
have some feelings for you.
You should probably go now.
Pass my sweatshirt?
Yeah.
Which way is the door?
- The front door?
- Yeah.
I'll walk you out.
- You'll have to wait.
- That's fine.
I loved it. It was so exciting.
But how about those people
yelling "bravi" and "brava"?
"Bravi, bravi. " Why can't
they just say "bravo"?
Well, it's the plural.
No, I know it's correct, but don't
you think there's just something
a little pretentious about
some of those people?
- Pretentious?
- I don't mean they didn't really enjoy it,
but you know how you can
really be enjoying something,
but you're also kind of looking around,
out of the corner of your eye,
because you know people are
watching you enjoy it?
Yes, but I wouldn't say
that it was pretentious.
In Italian, you say "bravo"for the
man and "brava"for the woman,
and "bravi" for the whole company.
Uh-huh. Okay, I see what you mean.
You use the masculine
for the male singer
and the feminine for
the female singer.
Anyway, I really enjoyed it.
Thank you.
We'll have to go again.
It was so glamorous.
Cue 36. Go.
- Oh, man...
- Okay, hold on a second.
Okay, we're gonna do that
one more time, please.
Let's back it up, please.
Now I know there's been
a lot of shit going on
between a lot of the
people in this room.
But I want to tell you something.
You've worked too fucking hard
for this show to be derailed now
by the kind of bullshit that I know
has been going on around here.
Now I bet you there's not one
person working on this show
who hasn't got somebody they
want to say something to,
including me, so I'm gonna start.
Matthew.
By "Matthew" I assume you mean me.
Yes, I mean you.
- You want me to sit on that little box?
- Yes.
But it's like I was so jealous of you
that I wasn't even there for you
when the whole thing
happened with that woman.
And I'm really sorry if I hurt you.
I didn't mean to.
Darren.
I know that I'm not who
you want me to be to you,
and I know how much I've hurt you.
But I still can't believe it means
we can't be friends anymore.
So much has been happening
to me this semester,
and it's like I can't even talk to you
about it because I hurt you so bad.
Yes, you can. You can. Of course you can.
You can talk to me about anything.
I don't love anybody more than I love you.
You're practically my best friend.
I love you, too. I really do.
Okay, guys. Great. Very good.
Leslie.
Can I just say, I think this show is,
like, two-and-a-half seconds away
from being fucking amazing.
And if we can all just work together instead
of being at each other all the time,
I think we could all
just be incredible.
- Angie.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna say it.
I feel really fucked over by
some of the people in this room.
And I'm not saying I'm
not gonna do my job,
but for some reason, a lot of the
actors in this show seem to think
that this whole show is about them.
And I think I speak for
a lot of the techies
when I say I feel
really unappreciated,
and basically fucked over.
And I don't know if I can get over it.
I don't.
That's it.
Okay.
Paul.
Yeah. I'm just playing
in the band, you know.
This is high school, you know.
I don't really feel a deep need to all
be on the same team with everybody.
I just wanna show up to
rehearsals, do the show,
go up on the roof, smoke
some pot, like, go on home.
I don't really wanna
cry and hug anybody.
You wanna hug me a
little, don't you, Paul?
Hey, Gary, man, I'll give you a little hug.
I'll give you a hug.
- No kissing though.
- Come on.
Accident Investigation,
Detective Mitchell.
Hi. My name is Lisa Cohen. I was a witness
in a bus accident case a few weeks ago.
Yeah, hi, Lisa. What can I do for you?
Well, this is probably gonna
sound a little weird,
but are you allowed to tell me how to
get in touch with that woman's family?
I really wanted to send
some flowers or something,
or is that like
classified information?
No, the family's been notified.
Let me see what I got.
She mentioned she had a daughter.
Just hold on a second.
How are you doing? Okay?
I'm okay.
All right, let me just...
Okay, I don't have
anything for a daughter.
The only contact I have is
a cousin, Abigail Berwitz.
- I got a phone number in Arizona.
- Okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, fuck me.
- Hello?
- Yes.
I'm trying to reach Abigail Berwitz?
- This is Abigail.
- Hi.
My name is Lisa Cohen.
You don't know me. I...
Yes?
- Hello?
- Sorry. Yeah.
I'm actually calling about
your cousin, Monica Patterson?
Okay?
Um...
I was actually there when she had...
During the accident,
I didn't know her,
but I was sort of holding
her hand at the time.
Yes? What can I do for you?
...Uh, um...
Okay, well...
I saw her obituary in the paper,
but can you hold on one second?
Can you shut up for
five fucking minutes?
What am I supposed to do?
I have to practice.
I don't give a shit!
Sorry. Um...
I didn't see anything about a funeral.
I assume they had one.
As far as I know, they're doing
something or other next week, but...
I'm sorry, I was also wondering...
She said something about her daughter?
- No.
- She wanted someone to get in touch...
No. Her daughter's not alive. She
passed away quite a long time ago.
Oh, my God.
- Was she sick? Or was it...
- She had leukemia.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Mmm-hmm.
And, do you mind if I ask?
Was her name Lisa?
Yes.
Okay, see, that explains it.
I think that she thought...
Could I just interrupt? How
did you get this number?
Oh, the police. I...
Well, they really shouldn't be giving
out my number. This is harassment!
I'm sorry. I'm not
trying to harass you.
I've been getting calls about this for
three weeks, and I gotta tell you people,
I didn't have any kind of
relationship with Monica whatsoever.
Unless you want to count the fact
that she held up my children's
inheritance for 15 years.
I guess we're supposed to
forget about all that now.
I'm sorry...
The person you should be calling is Emily
Morrison, who was Monica's friend.
She's the person who's been dealing
with all of this in New York.
I had no idea.
It has nothing to do with me.
Now, I can give you her number,
but I would very much appreciate
it if the calls would stop.
Yeah...
- Can you hold on while I get a pen?
- Yes. All right.
Okay.
Thank you so much. I am so
sorry for bothering you. Bye.
- Hi, are you Lisa?
- Yes.
I'm Emily.
Well,
thank you all for coming.
Thank you for doing this, Emily.
Thank you.
As most of you know,
Monica was not a religious woman.
Anybody who ever had to sit through
a wedding or a funeral with her
knows how she felt about
formal occasions.
So Harry, Elise, and I,
when we were talking about this,
decided we would just
have everyone over,
and let anyone who wanted to talk
about Monica, just talk about her.
Maybe share some remembrances.
Some of us know each other
and some of us don't.
But we're all here...
We're all here because we loved Monica,
and because we want to pay
tribute to her in a way
that might conceivably not enrage her.
Now, I don't wanna tell anyone
what to think, or how to feel.
And I don't want to kid myself about the
stupid, meaningless way that she died,
because that would really
make her throw up,
but I don't want it to become
the summation of her life,
because it's not.
When her Lisa died...
When her Lisa died, I said to
her, "how can you stand it?"
And she said, "first of all, I can't.
"But I don't want to take away
the 12 years she did have
"and turn them all into leukemia,
because they weren't. "
And so I do think it's
important to remember
that despite the fact
that she got ripped off,
she was the most fully developed
person I, personally, have ever known.
She was also impossible
to get along with,
but that's another story.
So, now I've said my little piece.
And now I want to talk a bit about
the first time we ever met.
She was 21.
It's okay, Emily.
I know.
I was 19.
Even though I realize
it's impossible
for my children to believe
I was ever that young.
Hi. Yes, I'm trying to get some
information on one of your bus drivers.
I'm sorry.
His name's Gerald Maretti. He
drives the 104, I believe. I...
No.
It's kind of a private matter.
I'm sorry.
It's not possible for you to
confirm the phone number?
Okay.
M- a-r-e-t-t-i.
I show nothing for that
name in Manhattan.
What about Brooklyn?
- I show a listing for a Gerald Maretti.
- You do?
Hi, Dad.
Yeah, hi, how're you doing?
Okay, how are you?
Okay. I'm just sitting here
listening to some music,
having a delicious glass of beer.
That sounds pleasant.
Yeah. Yeah. How's everything going?
How's the boyfriend situation?
Well, there's this one guy I sort
of had something going with,
- but he kind of has a girlfriend, so...
- Uh-huh.
I realize I'm incredibly enthralling.
You are. You're very lucky. You're a very
beautiful girl, and you've got brains.
- That makes you a little dangerous.
- Don't forget mature.
Well, I hope you're not too mature.
- No, don't worry.
- Okay. Good. That was a very good answer.
Anyway, I do think it's a pretty
longstanding relationship.
Then you know what?
You just do nothing.
Do absolutely nothing. And I guarantee
you one of two things will happen.
Either you're going to get the guy to start
doing back flips to get your attention,
or you're going send him a crystal-clear
signal that if he doesn't do back flips,
- he's not gonna get your attention. Okay?
- I think he...
...if you just suddenly
give him nothing,
I guarantee you, the guy
is going to go berserk,
unless he's just not interested.
In which case, you just gotta
take your lumps, which is tough.
Okay, thanks, Dad. I'll be sure to try
out the technique next time I see him.
So... well, everything's okay here.
- Things are a little slow, but...
- Actually, Dad?
Yeah?
I actually have something kind of
serious I want to ask you about.
Okay.
I'm, kind of, soliciting people I
respect for their views on this.
Okay, what's up?
So, do you think I should go
back to the police, or what?
Well, first of all, I'm very
glad you told me about this.
Second of all, I want you to let
me call my friend who's a lawyer,
just so we can find out what some
of the ramifications would be.
Maybe the three of us could talk
on the phone and possibly...
- Hey.
- Hey, babe.
Actually, Dad, please
don't call anybody.
- Did you get my message?
- Um... I got a message.
- Hello?
- Sorry.
About the flowers for my mother?
Just one second. Annette just walked in.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Who are you talking to?
I guess I would just like to know later
that I would have done the right thing
by myself, if you see what I mean,
because I don't think I have so far.
Not that I'm trying to make
this woman's horrible death
into my own personal
moral gymnasium...
Right. Well, that's
that Shaw quote, right?
- What?
- The Shaw quote? That great Shaw quote.
"The Englishman sees
the world as expressly
"designed to be his own
personal moral gymnasium. "
I think it's in one of
those wonderful prefaces.
I don't know where I read it.
- Who is that?
- It's Lisa.
Oh, good. Will you please ask her...
- Anyway...
- Hold on. I'm sorry, Lisa.
Can you hold on one second?
Yes?
Please ask if there's
anything we don't know about
that she won't eat, for the trip.
Because I have to call the ranch
because they do all the meals
- ahead of time.
- Okay, I will.
I really will. We're just
in the middle of something.
Karl, I was supposed to call them last week.
You said you were going to call her.
If I hear about this fucking ranch one more
time, I'm going to blow my brains out.
I'm just in the middle of something.
I don't... what do you want me to do?
Fine, but if they put anything
in the baskets she can't eat,
well, she's not going to
have anything to eat.
- I will ask her...
- The last time she came out here,
we went to three different
restaurants and she...
I will ask her. We're just right
in the middle of something, okay?
Okay. Tell her I said, "hi. "
I will. Okay.
Hello?
Yes. Hi.
Mom?
Monica!
There's somebody here to see you.
Hi.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
We never met. I'm Lisa Cohen.
Yeah. What can I do for you?
Well, do you remember me
from the bus accident?
I don't know. What's this about?
Would it be okay if I
talked to you for a minute?
What do you want to talk about?
I don't understand.
I just wanna talk about the
accident for a minute.
I don't want anything, and I'm
not here to do anything bad.
I just wanted to talk to you about it.
I was gonna call first, but...
It would have been better if you had.
We're about to sit down.
I don't know what this is...
Yeah. All right. Let's go outside.
I'm sorry. Could I use your bathroom?
- No, let's just go outside.
- Gerry, let her use the bathroom.
No, I don't want her to use the bathroom.
I don't understand what this is.
Honey, it's right down the hall.
Hey, will you kids settle down, please?
I'm not kidding!
- What's the matter with you?
- Who is she?
Some girl that was at the accident.
Nothing is the matter. I let
her use the fucking bathroom.
Who is she?
- Honey, just do me a favor and wait inside.
- No, I want to hear what this is.
Well, if it's okay, I'd rather
talk to Mr. Maretti in private.
No, it is not okay.
Look, we're just...
Okay. What?
Okay.
I hope this isn't going
to insult you too much.
Insult me?
I was just wondering if you felt
bad at all about what happened.
- About the accident?
- Yeah.
Honey? Are you just upset
about the accident?
Yes! I'm upset about the accident.
I'm very upset about the accident.
And I wanted to talk to you
about it for a minute.
Why is that so strange?
- Gerry, why don't we all go inside?
- Could I please talk to you alone?
Okay, what is going on here?
Nothing's going on here. So
why don't you calm down?
Look, go ahead inside. Let
me find out what this is.
In the meantime, why
don't you make sure
those kids aren't killing
each other, all right?
All right.
No, you know what? Let
them kill each other.
Give us all a rest.
All right, Lisa. What?
I just...
- Well... I just want you to know...
- Yes? What? Speak.
Well, you probably already
know, obviously, that
I told the police, on the police report, that
I thought the whole thing was an accident.
Uh-huh. Right. Because
it was an accident.
Well, I mean... I know you
didn't do it on purpose.
- "On purpose"?
- But it wasn't like...
What? Speak. What?
Well, I mean...
We were looking at each other.
Who was looking at each other?
You and me?
Well, yeah.
I mean, not like
romantically or anything.
- Romantically?
- Scratch that. That's not even relevant.
Look, you're not coming
through very clearly here.
If you could just let me...
From my point of view, I was out
that day trying to buy a cowboy hat,
so I was waving at you,
because you were wearing one,
and you were kind of waving back.
And...
I know I was distracting you,
but I did see the bus go
through the red light,
and that's when it hit that woman.
Okay.
- I'm getting a little confused here.
- Only nobody said that to them,
and I wanted to acknowledge with
you that that's what happened.
First of all, I don't really know
what you mean by "waving at you. "
What, were you, like,
trying to catch the bus?
No. Yes.
Maybe I was waving at you
to say, I don't know, like,
"step away from the bus. "
Because if the bus was in motion,
then I would have been waving
you away for your own safety,
but that's all that would be.
You don't remember looking
at me and waving at me?
Not really. No.
- Your brother's on the phone.
- Tell him I'll call him back.
I'm not trying to get you in trouble.
I know you're not, because you can't,
because I didn't do anything wrong.
All right. There was no criminality found.
That's it. The report is final.
- So you're just gonna leave it? - I'm
gonna leave it because that's all it was.
If something else would have happened,
then I'd take that to whatever that was.
Okay? It's a tragedy. It's tragic.
But there's only a certain speed
that those brakes can react.
That's the physical
limitation of the machine.
I don't know what else to tell you. It's
a shock. It's a shock. But that's it.
You can't bring her back.
You cannot bring her back.
I'm not talking about
bringing her back.
I'm talking about telling the accident
investigators what really happened.
But you already talked to them!
- I know that. But I lied.
- You lied.
Yes, and I can understand if you don't
want to get in any trouble, but...
Why didn't you say
something right then?
Because when they were
asking me what happened
it seemed like you were looking at me
like we were saying to each other,
"let's not say anything
about what happened. "
Now, I really don't know
what you're talking about.
I can't prove that
you were doing that.
- What, did I say something to you?
- Did I threaten you?
No! And I am not blaming
you for any of this!
All I'm saying is that I didn't
really tell the cops what happened,
and I didn't want to go back without
having spoken to you first.
But you told them what you saw! You
told them what you saw. And so did I!
Only I'm the one driving the bus!
I'm the one behind the wheel!
- Gerry, take it easy.
- No. You know what? Leave it alone.
You wanna ruin my life?
You want to start telling
them about looks
and you waved at me and I had
my cowboy hat on. Go ahead.
But you're gonna go back
and do your homework,
and I'm gonna lose my job. And who's
gonna take care of my family?
You?
Are you gonna do it? And for what?
She's dead! Okay? She's dead! And there's
nothing that I can do to bring her back!
I just want to say
what really happened.
You do whatever you
fucking want, lady!
But those cops are gonna laugh in your
fucking face because this was not my fault!
It was both our fault.
- What did you say to me?
- It was both our fault.
Don't ever say that again unless
you got a fucking lawyer.
- What's your phone number?
- Why?
- Give me your number.
- No! Why do you want it?
What, you wanna show up at my
house like some anonymous person
I can't get in touch with? What's your
fucking phone number, Lisa Cohen!
- Gerry, take it easy.
- Fine! It's 212-5...
Hold on! Go on.
555-0157. Why do you need it?
You do whatever you're gonna do.
I hope you get a good lawyer.
Why are you being like this?
This was very traumatic for him!
Yeah, it's almost as bad as
getting your leg cut off!
I don't understand.
I guess I was afraid. I
didn't know what to do.
You didn't know what to do?
- I know it doesn't sound very impressive.
- Impressive!
Okay, I know you're trying
to do the right thing now.
What does your mother say?
My mother hasn't really
been that helpful.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, she's got a lot going on right now
and she just hasn't been
that interested, I guess.
What could she possibly have going on?
- Her show's opening.
- What do you mean, "her show"?
What show?
She's in a play.
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna talk to a friend
of mine who's a lawyer,
and you're gonna go
talk to the police.
- Do you want me to go with you?
- No, thanks.
Do you think maybe you should
ask your mother to go with you?
I think I can handle this part myself.
She's been so suspicious lately.
I don't know how to get her
into the office without...
Now, what do you think?
Hey! Let me tell you something, eliot.
You want to fire me, go ahead and fire me.
Only don't tiptoe around me
like some kind of deranged ballerina every
time I see you in the fucking hall!
Now, do you have anything
to say to me, eliot?
Um...
You're not fired?
Oh.
So... what are you guys talking about?
You happy now?
Hey, what do I care what
they say in the papers?
"But it is the frankly
extraordinary Joan Caplan
"who transforms the savage wit of
David Holmes' acid comedy drama
"into something approaching
sheer luminosity. "
Get out!
"But don't be misled by
her feather-light timing
"and expert comedic
touch, the canny... "
Bravura.
A female suicide bomber attempted
to set off a blast
Wednesday in Jerusalem.
No, Lisa read it to me.
No. No, I never read them unless I know
for sure there's nothing bad in them.
Well, thank you.
I'm ashamed of myself for giving
a shit, but I'm very relieved.
Victor, I wish you wouldn't
talk that way to me.
You know I'm...
"Spring and Fall, to a Young
Child" by Gerard Manley Hopkins.
"Margaret, are you grieving
over Goldengrove unleaving?
"Leaves, like the things of man,
"you with your fresh
thoughts care for, can you?
"Ah! As the heart grows older
"it will come to such sights
colder by and by, nor spare a sigh
"though worlds of
wanwood leafmeal lie,
"and yet you will weep and know why.
"Now no matter, child, the name:
"Sorrow's Springs are the same.
"Nor mouth had, no nor mind, expressed
"what heart heard of, ghost guessed:
"It is the blight man was born for,
"it is Margaret you mourn for. "
Any thoughts?
Lisa?
Could I help you?
Yeah, is Detective Mitchell here?
- No, he's not.
- Oh.
I talked to him on Monday,
and he said he'd be here.
Yeah, he's not back yet.
Could I help you with something?
Um...
Well, do you know when you expect him?
What's this about?
I was involved in an
accident a few weeks ago,
and I filled out a report
with Detective Mitchell
but I wanted to amend the report...
What do you mean, you want to amend it?
How do you want to amend it?
Well, there was something I didn't tell
him, and I wanted to tell him because...
I don't understand.
- You wanna change your statement?
- Yes!
Yes, I want to change my statement.
Yes.
Well, you'd usually have to talk to the
investigating detective on the case.
Yes, I know. That's why I asked
to see Detective Mitchell.
Who said he'd be here
now, but he's not, so...
- Do you remember the case number?
- No, sorry.
It was that woman, Monica Patterson, who
got run over by the bus on Broadway.
- It was in a lot of the newspapers...
- Sure, okay, sit down. Sit down.
- Thank you. I...
- You know the case is closed.
I assumed it was. But part
of the reason it's closed is
because of my statement,
and the statement I...
- Because of your statement?
- Yes.
What do you mean it was closed
because of your statement?
- I mean, I was the...
- The D.A.'s office closes the case.
You don't close the case.
The D.A.'s office closes the case.
I'm sure it does. I obviously didn't mean
I personally closed it, like legally.
I meant what I said was
probably instrumental in
- getting the case closed...
- What's your name, honey?
Lisa Cohen.
- Okay.
- Don't call me "honey," okay?
Okay.
Are you not gonna help me
now that I've said that?
- Look, what's your name?
- Lisa Cohen!
Okay, Lisa, first thing,
you're gonna calm down.
- I'm calm right now.
- Okay. Just checking.
Second thing... oh. Here he is,
your knight in shining armor.
- This guy giving you a hard time?
- No.
So, now you're saying he ran the light.
Yes. He wasn't even
looking at the road.
And I was definitely trying
to get his attention, but...
No, no. I get the picture.
So you're flirting with this guy.
He's waving at you, he runs
a light, hits the decedent.
The both of you lie to me
on both your statements,
and then, somewhere in there,
you turn around and decide
the guy belongs in jail.
Is that right?
Is that about right?
I don't have any control over
if he goes to jail or not.
And what do you think
I should do with you?
Do whatever you want.
I know what I did.
Okay.
Well, before we do anything, Lisa,
anyone will tell you that just
because he ran a red light
- is not a criminal offense.
- Even if he kills someone?
Even if you cause an accidental
death, that's right.
For this to be a criminal offense,
the law says you need two
aggravating circumstances.
Like he ran a red light
and he was speeding.
- Or he ran a red light and...
- So he's not liable to be prosecuted
- for manslaughter or 2nd degree murder?
- No.
He could be charged with reckless driving,
or filling out a false police report,
- which... that's no joke...
- That's unbelievable!
What does he have to do?
Kill her on purpose?
Yes. Because that's the
definition of murder.
Killing someone on purpose.
Now, you're not saying that
he ran her over on purpose.
Are you?
No.
Okay, look...
Why don't we take another statement?
And I'll look into it, okay?
I'll talk it over with my sergeant,
probably pull this guy in again.
Put a little pressure on him.
We'll see what he says.
Yeah.
The Central Park Conservatory,
or whatever it's called,
put up about 500 miles of these cheap,
shitty-looking fences all over the park,
which is totally antithetical to what
the park was originally designed for.
We are so gonna miss the game.
- Oh, my God, it's John!
- Hi, John.
Hi, John.
You want some?
Come on, guys.
Come on, you can't be smoking a J on
your way to a school soccer game!
- Now, come on!
- Sorry!
We're really sorry.
So, how about how he was
like, "smoking a J"?
Like, "you can't be smoking a J."
Like, "everybody, let's go over
to John's house and smoke a J."
- Hi, Mr. Aaron!
- Lisa, how are you?
Pretty damn good. How are you?
I'm all right. I'm all right.
Hey, tell me something.
Whatever happened with that situation?
Oh, I'm working on it. I'll
tell you all about it sometime.
- Hey, what kind of a bike is that?
- It's a trek.
I'm supposed to go on a horseback riding
trip with my father over Christmas break
and I was just wondering, does it bear
any resemblance to riding a bicycle?
As far as I know, no. I don't... no.
But you must have
ridden a lot of horses.
What makes you say that?
Aren't you from Texas or Wyoming
or some place like that?
- Some place like what?
- You know, not New York.
I'm actually from Indiana.
But don't let me overwhelm you
with superfluous details.
God, so what are you doing
at a New York private school
teaching geometry to a bunch of
over-privileged liberal Jews?
Well...
I came... I wanted to be a
teacher, and that's what I did.
I came here, and I'm a teacher.
- Well...
- Before you go,
I'm actually thinking about getting
one of these. Can I try it?
Just for a second?
- All right.
- Thanks.
- Here, I'll adjust the seat for you.
- Thank you.
- Watch my bag?
- Yeah.
You know how to...
Whoa! All right, off.
Can I just ask you,
how is it possible that I'm
totally in love with you
and you have almost no
interest in me whatsoever?
Can I have my bike back, please?
I can tell you like me.
It's not like I'm a virgin or anything,
if that's what you're worried about.
Not even close.
I shouldn't even be having
this conversation with you.
Hey, it's not my fault if
I revere you as a God.
I made you laugh. I am
so happy right now.
I'll see you in class.
Someone named Emily called.
And detective Mitchell called from
the accident investigation squad.
Is that that one we met?
What's going on? Did you
ever go back and see him?
I'd rather not talk about it when
you have one foot out the door.
I'll tell you later, if it's okay.
Of course it is.
- Hello.
- Congratulations on the show.
- Oh, thanks.
That was such a wonderful review.
And I read somewhere it
was going to Broadway?
Yeah, supposedly, in march.
God, it's exciting.
Yeah, it's going very well.
Good.
Lisa, Dave.
Dave, Lisa.
- Hi.
- How are you?
So...
Lisa, Dave is one of my best friends.
He's a terrific lawyer, and if he
doesn't know what to do himself,
he'll certainly know
someone we can talk to.
Okay, great.
When someone is killed, it's what's
called a wrongful death suit,
which is a statutory case, which
just means there's a statute
passed by the legislature which gives
you the right to bring the case.
As opposed to what?
As opposed to common law, which
is law passed by judges,
which is why the damages are limited.
- I don't understand.
- Just skip that part.
We don't care about that.
I thought we were trying to get
the police to arrest this guy.
- No, the police are not gonna...
- Why not? They told me
they were gonna look into it again.
I'm just telling you
that even if they do,
there is no way in this world
the police are gonna recommend
- to the da that they charge this guy.
- So, what can we do?
- I'm getting to that.
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
- That's okay, honey.
I'm just getting to that.
You can't do anything
unless you're a relative...
She didn't have any relatives,
except for those idiots in Arizona.
Hang on a minute. Or unless you're
the executor of her estate...
- I am the executor of her estate.
- Which is Emily. I know.
- So good.
- Yes, this is good.
Because the executor of her estate
can bring a wrongful death suit,
but the beneficiary
has to be a relative.
So let me explain about that.
In a wrongful death suit, you can
sue for pain and suffering,
loss of support or services,
also what's called care,
comfort and society.
It's like advice or counseling
of the parent that the kids
- aren't gonna get anymore.
- I don't understand.
Who are we suing? The bus driver?
Well, no, because the bus
driver wouldn't have any money.
You basically sue everybody
and hope something sticks.
The person who pays will probably
be the MTA's insurance company.
But do you think the
driver would get fired?
No. Not necessarily.
But how much could they be liable for?
- It depends...
- How badly do you think
we could ever hurt them?
If she was alive, and in a lot of
pain for an extended period of time,
they give more money for that.
I'd say she was alive for 10 minutes.
And, I gather, in a lot of pain?
Was she conscious? Was she
awake the whole time?
I'm sorry, Emily.
Yeah, awake.
It's okay.
Well, if she was in a lot
of pain for that long,
I don't know, maybe 300,000,
half a million dollars
to get a sustainable verdict.
A brain damaged baby
would be three million.
But the truth is, Lisa,
when all is said and done,
- it's not a very good case.
- Why not?
Because it's your word against his,
and because you already lied
on your first deposition.
A red light case is a 50-50
proposition already.
And with only one eyewitness,
with two conflicting statements?
I wouldn't take that case.
Nobody really cares about
getting a lot of money here.
I understand that, but...
We just want this prick to suffer,
and we want the bus company to take
responsibility for hiring this guy.
Anyway, can't I explain why
I lied the first time?
It's not like I'm trying to
get any money for myself.
That's true. She has no financial interest,
she can't be impeached for bias.
Impeached for what?
She can't have her credibility
attacked on financial grounds
because the jury knows you're not
gonna get any money if you win.
So that's something, isn't it?
But do you really think
we know what that means?
I'm sorry. That's what it's called.
But who are you talking to?
You know we don't
know what that means.
It's like you're not really concentrating.
You're not concentrating.
I don't know. I am concentrating.
I'm just thinking out loud.
Okay.
All right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Okay. All right.
He wasn't always a
lawyer, you know.
He used to be a very nice, little boy.
- Anyway...
- Anyway, the whole point of this
- is to get...
- To fucking get this guy!
It was to get him out from
behind the wheel of a bus!
Did she know she was dying?
I only ask because the terror of knowing
you're dying raises the damages.
I think she had a pretty good idea.
If she had lived for a couple more
days it would make the case better.
Thank you.
I know that sounds horrible, but
that's what it comes down to.
We know, Dave.
It's okay.
I would just like somebody to take
responsibility for what happened.
I understand that, Emily, but
no matter how you slice it,
the fact that Lisa lied on her first
statement is a disaster for your lawyer.
"As flies to wanton boys
are we to the gods.
"They kill us for their sport. "
"As flies to wanton boys
are we to the gods.
"They kill us for their sport. "
What do you make of that?
Lisa? Lisa?
I don't know.
You know what, Lisa?
That's not good enough.
That's just not good enough.
Shakespeare wrote something.
What's your response?
And don't tell me you don't have
one, 'cause I don't buy it.
I don't really have a lot to say.
It seems pretty self-evident to me.
- Matthew?
- I think it is self-evident.
I think he's saying that human beings
don't mean any more to the gods
than flies do to little boys who
like to torture them for fun.
As far as the gods are concerned,
we're just ants. Nothing.
Darren?
Thank you, Matthew.
Yeah, I agree.
Only it's not Shakespeare
saying it, it's Gloucester.
Maybe another character would
have a different point of view.
Okay. That's a valid point.
Just because Shakespeare
has one of his characters say something,
doesn't mean he personally agrees with it.
Yes, David?
Yeah, maybe Shakespeare isn't saying
the gods don't care about us.
Maybe he's saying there's a higher
consciousness that we can't see.
That the gods' perception of reality
is so much more developed than ours
that, compared to their perception,
our perceptions are like
comparing flies to boys.
Okay, I really don't think that
that's what he's getting at.
What I think he's getting at here
is a very dark view of the arbitrary
nature of human suffering.
But maybe he's not.
Maybe he's comparing human
consciousness to divine consciousness,
and that even though it seems to us
that human suffering is just arbitrary,
that's just because we're
limited by our viewpoint.
Okay, I...
I still don't think
that's what he's saying.
No, like, if you say they
kill us for their sport,
when our perception of
the gods is so meager
that we can't even tell
what they're doing,
then how can we be so
arrogant as to think
that they would even bother
to kill us for their sport?
I don't know.
Uh...
Monica?
I don't think that's
what he's saying at all.
I think he's saying the gods don't
give a shit about human beings
and that they just like to
kill and torture us for fun.
But if the gods' consciousness is
so much more developed than ours
that we seem like flies to them,
then how can we be sure what
they have in mind for us
or why they do anything?
Okay, David, I think
you've made your point.
But that's not what Shakespeare meant.
Scholarly opinion is pretty consistent
that he's trying to say something...
- Scholarly opinion?
- ... About human suffering here.
What are you saying? A thousand
frenchmen can't be wrong?
No, I'm not saying that. But
I would like to move on...
Well, I think he is saying that.
Because he's comparing human
consciousness to flies
and he's saying that we can't
see the truth around us
because our consciousness
is undeveloped.
No, David, you're wrong. That's
not what Shakespeare meant.
He says it somewhere else in the play,
but I don't want to get hung up on this
because that's not what
Shakespeare meant.
I would really like to move on.
"Poor Tom's a-cold. "
I don't know. Maybe two weeks ago that
she had just brought the baby home.
Detective Mitchell.
Oh, hi, it's Lisa Cohen calling.
Hi, Lisa, what can I do for you?
I was just wondering whatever
happened, if anything, with the case.
You said you might
re-interview the bus driver.
Yes, we did. We brought him back in.
You did? What happened?
Well, he basically stuck by
his original representation
and that was pretty much it.
So there's not a lot more
we can do at this point.
Well, I'm not trying to tell
you how to do your job,
but how did you ask the questions?
- Excuse me?
- He's obviously not gonna
change his statement if you just ask
him really politely. Why would he?
- We already know he's a liar.
- Hey, you know, in the old days, Lisa,
we'd just throw him in the
back room with a rubber hose
and get whatever answer
we want out of him.
But, fortunately, we
don't do that anymore.
Yeah, not to white people.
Excuse me?
You don't do it to white people.
Anyway, I'm not saying you...
- Wait. We don't do it to who? Shh!
- Oh, my God!
First of all, I don't understand why
you bring this guy's race into it.
- There's 40,000 cops in this city...
- Yes...
And I hate to disillusion you, but
most of them are pretty good guys
just trying to do their job.
Now, the bottom line is the D.A.
is not gonna take this case.
Now, you could take it up with my
sergeant if you want to, but he's...
- Sure, I would.
- Well, I will patch you through, then.
The original decision was
based on false information.
So what's the point of
even bringing him in if...
So there's no way to appeal?
But how do you know Detective Mitchell
interrogated him aggressively enough
- if you weren't there?
- What's going on?
It's funny. It's the same show, but
now they've all read how great it is,
we get these big standing
ovations every night,
and it's the exact same
show it was before.
But why do you put yourself down?
It's a wonderful show and
a wonderful performance.
No, no, it's not... No, I'm
not putting myself down.
It's just the audience
always reacts differently
once they've been told it's good.
A lot of actors have that experience.
Hmm.
I love this view.
Ramon, this may sound
very stupid to you,
but do you ever worry that we
don't have very much in common?
What do you mean?
Well, I don't mean to sound
dissatisfied or disgruntled,
but it seem like we're always
misunderstanding each other.
Do you ever feel that way at all or
am I just completely off the beam?
I don't think we should
talk about that, Joan.
You don't?
Well, I feel it's kind of important
or I wouldn't have brought it up.
Joan, I like you very much,
but let's not talk about what
you are like or what I am like.
That never makes a good result.
Talk about it with your friends.
My friends?
Yes.
- May I show you some pictures of my boys?
- Sure.
That's a little place we
used to go on holiday,
two hours outside of Cartagena.
My family is all there still,
but Rodrigo is
studying in London,
and Hector is in Geneva.
Uh-huh.
I'm sure they will go
back eventually because
they will like to do
something for their country.
But it's a worry. It's
very bad there now.
Yeah? I haven't really
been following it.
It's a big mess. Last year I
helped to found an organization
to work with children whose
families have been killed
or the parents have been kidnapped.
We try to find them homes,
preferably in Colombia,
because if we lose our
young people, that's it.
That's the future.
We have raised a lot of money, but
it's hard to see the solution.
Yeah. Gosh, I wish I
knew more about it.
I just feel kind of ignorant
about your whole world.
You think it would be better if we
knew about all the same things?
Not really, not exclusively.
It's just unusual. Don't
you think it's unusual?
Not for me.
I guess you travel a lot.
I've only been out of the country
a few times in my whole life.
You should travel more.
Yeah, I know. I've
always wanted to travel.
But it's difficult with
two kids and no husband.
- My ex-husband...
- Karl.
Yes. You remembered. Very good.
Karl is very generous with
the kids when he can be,
but he's struggling, too.
He's a director, he directs commercials,
and now he's trying to produce them, too.
Anyhow, I'm not ignorant
because I like it.
I don't say you're ignorant.
You think Lisa would be
interested in acting?
No. I don't.
I think she has a lot of
contempt for it, actually.
Anyway, maybe it's the age.
She would prefer the world
with no plays? No films?
Oh. Who knows?
Would you like to see a
picture of my mother?
Sure.
These are all my aunts and uncles.
- See? Big family.
- Mmm.
So after I talked to you
guys the other day,
I called this P.I. I know
to see if he could...
You called a what? A what?
Private investigator, to see if he could
find anything out about your bus driver.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Dave! I can't believe you called...
- Wait, let me tell you what he said.
So this guy calls someone he knows who
used to work as a cop at the MTA.
And you know the MTA
have their own police?
The MTA police?
- They have their own uniforms...
- Yeah? Yeah?
- Just a minute!
- Jesus Christ!
What the fuck do we care about the
MTA police and their uniforms?
Okay, so this guy gets a
look at your guy's file.
And it turns out that he's had two previous
accidents less than two years apart.
What?
But that he's never been
disciplined or cited,
just moved around to different shifts.
- Are you kidding me?
- Why does this not shock me?
Because, surprise, surprise,
his brother-in-law
is some very big muckety-muck
in the transit workers union.
And if you read the
papers, you'll know that
they're going through a protracted
labor dispute at the MTA right now.
And according to my P.I.,
management doesn't want to aggravate
the situation by firing this guy.
This is making me sick.
I know, but what it means,
Lisa, is that we have a case.
- We do?
- What it means, in fact,
is that we have a very good case.
Because we can now sue for what's
called "negligent retention. "
Which just means they should have
known this guy was a bad risk,
and they negligently retained him
until, finally, he killed somebody.
- And you can prove that?
- Sure, because
we can just subpoena
their personnel records,
which we already know contain
damaging information.
- But you wouldn't be our lawyer, right?
- No.
Why not?
- I'm not a personal injury litigator.
- It's not his area.
I don't know enough about it.
I would lose.
But you could recommend someone?
Sure.
I know a very good guy.
His name is Russel Deutsch.
He's not a sleazebag.
Very, very experienced.
You gotta get that crazy cousin on
board. She's gonna be your beneficiary.
She's not gonna want
to come to New York.
I can tell you that right now.
If you win, she stands to get
anywhere from $300,000 to $500,000.
She's coming to New York.
You're awesome!
What's with Monica
and her cousin?
Monica's father left some
money to Abigail's kids.
And he made Monica the
executor of the estate
because he didn't want Abigail
and her idiot husband
to get their hands on the money
before the kids were grown up.
For which Abigail rewarded her by
badgering her about it on the phone
for 15 years.
Always trying to borrow
money against the estate,
accusing her of making
lousy investments with it,
nasty phone calls, nasty letters
every month for 15 years,
until Abigail's daughter
turned 21 and got married.
Then Monica goes to the
wedding in fucking Arizona,
and Abigail, literally, won't speak to her.
She's a dream.
So that's who we're
getting the money for?
It's not who we're getting it for,
it's who we're getting it from.
First thing we do is we file
a summons and a complaint
against the MTA. They
get 20 days to respond,
and when they do, we can
make our discovery requests.
Accident reports, personnel
records, etcetera.
Now, you gotta realize, this
is going to take some time.
The law says you have to have
a court date within one year.
Usually it takes
around six, depending.
- Six years?
- Yes, depending.
Now, I mentioned to Dave,
I have a friend who writes for
the Metro section of The Times.
Yes, now this, if it could really happen,
this changes everything in our favor.
If they think there's gonna
be adverse publicity,
especially in The
New York Times,
they're gonna want to
settle right away,
as soon as possible, and
as quietly as possible.
So they'd make it a
condition that we didn't...
It usually works, you get the
money, but you can't talk about it.
Nobody knows the terms.
So what good does that do?
You get the money.
Is that bad?
This is how our society punishes
people for doing bad things.
By getting money from their
employers' insurance companies?
Yes. It's called "punitive damages. "
Could we insist they fire the driver?
As part of the settlement?
- Yes. Sure, why not?
- But is that something people do?
Sure. It's one of your conditions.
- Great.
- And you think we're gonna win?
- They're gonna settle?
- Oh, they're gonna settle.
Oh. Hi.
I want to talk to you.
I take it that's my report card?
It sure is.
Hi, I'm Joan.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Come on in.
- Hi, Emily.
I had a friend who used to
live on this block, at 262?
Oh.
Oh, that's so nice. Thank you. Yeah,
I don't know if you know her.
Cheryl Rowan? She's a physiotherapist?
No, I don't know her.
I think about 1,000 people must...
What?
Nothing.
- Lisa says you're in a play, Joan?
- Oh, yeah.
You should go see it,
it's really good.
Well, the play is great, and
we have this really nice cast.
She's just being modest. She's
gonna win every award in New York.
Oh, all that stuff's a long way off.
I don't go to the theater very much.
No, it's just nice, because you can
work a long time in the theater
and play a lot of really great parts
and not get a lot of recognition.
And even though you don't necessarily
do it for that as your primary motive,
it is nice when people do
notice something you've done.
I was on a television show a few years ago.
I'd been doing theater all my life,
and suddenly all my relatives started
calling me up to congratulate me
because they thought
I'd finally made it.
All it was was this dumb show
that paid the bills for a while.
That show was so stupid.
Well, it wasn't that bad.
Anyway, I realize this is
horribly embarrassing for Lisa,
but I just really wanted
to meet you, Emily,
because you've frankly become
such a big part of Lisa's life,
and I don't want to be intrusive,
but this whole court case seems to
suddenly be dominating everything
and I can't get Lisa to
tell me anything about it.
- That's not true.
- Well, I can't.
And I want you to know, Lisa,
I'm very, very proud of you for
pursuing this the way that you have.
But I can't let you pursue it to the
point where it's taking over your life
or interfering with your schoolwork.
See, it's really come down
to a question of homework.
Lisa's on a half
scholarship at her school.
And I know she feels a real sense of
responsibility about what happened.
Yeah, I do.
I know you do. I know you do. But
you can't not do your homework
and you can't throw away your
scholarship because of it.
I'm not. My grades slipped a little.
They'll get better.
Anyone can do their homework.
You just sit down and do it.
I've been distracted. I'll stop.
- All right.
- We didn't need a big conference about it.
No, it's not a big conference.
I just wanted to know
what was going on.
And I wanted to meet you, Emily.
I know it's a little awkward.
Lisa? Do you think Emily would
like to come see the play?
I thought you could both come, and
then we could maybe go out afterwards.
All right. Let me ask her.
Okay.
Dig in, everybody.
I was thinking about
spending next year with Dad.
Oh?
Yeah.
You're all worried about my grades.
They have really good public
schools in Santa Monica
and if I officially lived with him,
you wouldn't have to worry
about my scholarship.
- Have you talked to him about this?
- We've had some general discussions.
- Do you want to go, too?
- Me?
- Yeah. Do you want to move to LA, too?
- No.
Well, just let me know if you do.
Why are you being like this?
- Why am I being like what?
- Why are you about to start crying?
Because it's your intention
to make me start crying!
No, it's not.
You want to move to LA, move to LA.
Why can't this even be mentioned
without you taking it personally?
I'm just introducing a possibility!
Here's a possibility, that you can
make your own fucking dinner!
do whatever you want to do...
Jesus Christ! What is with you?
I don't care anymore,
you heartless little fucking bitch!
Fine! Keep it up! This really
makes me want to stay here!
You think you're so fucking perfect?
No!
- Nice one.
- Shut up!
How would you describe the
relationship overall?
Did you talk on the phone a lot?
Were there a lot of visits?
I would say we talked on the phone a
couple of times a month, at least.
Sometimes more than that. I would
call her, she would call me.
And what were the nature
of the conversations?
Oh, family stuff, mostly.
Her family, my kids.
She'd give you advice about your family?
That kind of thing?
Oh, I would say so, yes.
Do you have any phone records?
I have all my phone bills,
if that's what you mean.
I didn't record the
actual conversations.
No, no.
You'll see we talked on the
phone quite frequently.
- Okay, terrific. I see you came prepared.
- Well, I wanted to bring everything.
Now, when they take your deposition,
you're gonna say the same
thing you just told me.
Just talk about the relationship.
Uh-huh.
- Kind of advice she used to give.
- Okay.
Now, Emily, where did
you find this lawyer?
He was recommended by my friend.
I'm asking because my husband
knows a real good New York lawyer
and I'm not entirely comfortable
with someone no one's ever heard of.
My friend's heard of him.
He says he's very good.
Well, I'm sure he is.
But I have a responsibility
in this situation
and I would feel a whole lot more
comfortable with someone who didn't just
drop in out of the clear blue sky.
He didn't drop in out
of the clear blue sky.
But, Abigail, even if we switched
lawyers, we would still have to pay him.
But it all comes out of the
settlement, so it's really up to you.
No, if you all think he's good...
I don't know whether he is or not.
- My friend thinks he is.
- All right.
Now, Lisa, what's your
involvement in all this?
What's your angle?
I was just there.
Oh, my God, is that you?
That's me.
And that's you and Monica, obviously.
Mmm-hmm.
Is that her daughter?
God.
So, how old was she when she died?
Twelve.
God, I can't even imagine.
Neither could we.
Do you know Monica asked about
her when she was dying?
No, I didn't.
Yeah, I think she was confused, like,
I think she thought I was
her daughter for a minute.
And then she was asking me to call her,
like, to tell her what happened, you know?
Like she didn't remember she was dead.
But, then it got confusing, because
I said, "sure, what's her name?"
And she said her name was Lisa.
And I said, "no, that's my name. "
Because it took me a minute.
I didn't realize we had the same name.
But then, when I found out
her daughter was dead,
ever since then
I've had this really strange feeling that,
some way, for those last five minutes,
I kind of was her daughter.
You know, like in some weird way,
this obviously amazing woman
got to be with her daughter again for
a few minutes, right before she died.
I see.
And is she still inhabiting your body?
Or did she go right back to the
spirit world after it was over?
I didn't mean she was
literally inhabiting my body.
I don't believe in all
that stuff at all.
I don't give a fuck
what you believe in.
Oh, my God! Why are you so mad at me?
Because this is not an opera!
- What?
- I said this is not an opera!
You think I think this is an opera?
- Yes!
- You think I think this is dramatic?
I think you're very young.
What does that have
to do with anything?
If anything, I think it means I
care more than someone who's older,
because this kind of thing has
never happened to me before!
No, it means you care more easily.
There's a big difference.
Only it's not you that
it's happening to.
Yes, it is! I know I'm not the
one who was run over by a bus...
That's right, you weren't.
And you're not the one
who died of leukemia,
and you're not the one who just
died in an earthquake in Algeria!
But you will be. Do you understand me?
You will be.
And it's not dramatic,
and it's not an opera.
I'm well aware of that!
This first-blush, phony deepness
of yours is worth nothing.
- Oh, wow.
- Do you understand?
It's not worth anything!
Because it'll all be troweled
over in a month or two.
And when you get older
and you don't have a big reaction
every time a dog is run over,
then we'll find out what
kind of a person you are!
I'm sorry, but I didn't start this
conversation and I don't play these games.
- I'm not playing games!
- And don't look so outraged!
You have every right to
falsify your own life,
but you have no right to
falsify anybody else's.
It's what makes people into Nazis!
And I'm sorry, but it's
a little suspicious
you're making such a big fuss about
this when you didn't even know her
and you're having troubles
with your own mother.
Oh, my God!
But this is my life that we're talking
about, much more than it is yours,
because it's my real friend who got
killed, who I'm never going to see again,
really, who I've known since
I was 19 years old myself.
And I don't want that sucked into
some adolescent self-dramatization!
I'm not fucking dramatizing anything!
I was there and you weren't,
and if I happen to express myself
a little hyperbolically, Emily,
that's just the way I talk!
I can't help it if my mother's an actress!
Why are you being so fucking strident?
- "Strident"?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You should leave.
Why? Because I called you strident?
Yeah. Strident. You should leave.
Okay, I will.
- Now!
- Okay, let me get my bag!
Does this mean we're
dropping the whole inquiry?
It means you're leaving. I
don't know what else it means.
All I meant by saying
that you were strident
is that you were being emphatic!
I obviously misused the word.
- Look it up when you get home.
- Jesus Christ. You're amazing.
- Yes. I'm amazing.
- Why are you doing this?
Lisa, I'm not doing anything.
I'm a human being.
Monica was a human being.
So was her daughter and
so is your mother.
We are not supporting characters in
the fascinating story of your life.
I never said or thought you were,
and I really didn't mean to call you
strident. I totally misused the word.
I feel so bad about
what happened,
and I'm trying so hard to
do something about it.
And I don't understand why,
if I say something wrong,
you can't just give me a break.
But I'm not trying to
dramatize anything, Emily.
I really do know about that trend, and I
really don't think I've been doing that.
Thanks for letting me come over.
I know you don't want me here.
No, it's not that.
But I didn't have
anyone else to talk to.
You've always been very
sympathetic to my craziness,
and I may not show it all the time,
but I actually really appreciate it.
It's no problem.
So...
What's been going on?
I just need to talk to somebody
who doesn't completely
misunderstand who I am.
Or not even who I am,
but what's going on inside
me, or all around me.
- Sound confused enough?
- No, no.
Anyway, for whatever reason,
I always felt like we understood
each other on some level.
Even though I'm like this
mass of conflicting impulses,
and you're basically the most
grownup, rational man I know.
I doubt that's actually
true, but thank you.
You seem pretty fucking
rational to me.
Like, that seems to be your
leading feature, I mean.
You obviously have a lot
of pretty deep feelings.
So when you're rational, just...
To finish my thought, it's like
this really interesting way
of governing yourself.
And you don't have to get
all uncomfortable again.
I'm not talking about what
you think I'm talking about
because I know that
subject's off limits.
I'm talking about your soul, I guess.
And how you feel you have to
keep it in check all the time,
by being sensible.
Do you know what I'm saying at all?
Well,
everybody has feelings.
I happen to believe that who you are
comes out in how you deal
with those feelings, so.
Somebody makes you mad, you don't
just pick up a gun and shoot them.
Or if you do, then that says
something about who you are,
how you've been raised.
Well, I don't want to disillusion you,
but we happen to be living in a world
where that is what people
do, more often than not.
No, I don't believe that's true.
I'm sad to think you see it that way.
There are seven billion
people in the world.
You think they don't all want to
kill someone once in a while?
But they don't, most of them.
Or they meet some person.
I think that people do try to
be civilized by some standard,
even if that's a standard
you and I don't agree with.
No, I get it.
That's actually the most helpful thing
anybody's said to me for a long time.
I don't know why I take such a dire
view of things. I really don't.
It's just a little hot.
A little warm.
- Is this all right?
- Yeah.
Do you allow smoking
in your apartment?
You can smoke.
- I like your apartment.
- Thanks.
It's a sublet, actually.
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
This is terrible.
What is?
What's...
I just like you so much.
- Sorry. What a moron.
- Hey, Lisa. Lisa.
I'm your friend.
And that's not gonna change.
It's not gonna change.
Thank you.
Hey, Lisa.
Please, just let me for a second.
I like you so much.
I like you so, so much.
What's it like in Indiana?
It's okay.
Look, okay, look.
Please, just let me.
Don't stop me yet.
I really wasn't expecting
anything like this to happen.
I'm really not sure how
I'm supposed to react.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna tell anybody,
if that's what you're worried about.
I totally initiated the whole thing.
Anyway, it's just sex.
You're acting like a little kid.
I'll see you in school.
You're a fucking idiot!
I think that teenagers should
definitely rule the world because
teenagers aren't corrupted by adult life
yet and they're idealistic and they care.
And I know a lot of people feel
that teenagers are really nave,
which they are, many of them.
But they still haven't had a chance to
get burned out by the disappointments
and harsh realities of
learning how to play the game.
So, yes, I would vote "yes. "
All right. Lisa?
I'm not even gonna comment on the fact
that you just compared a
19-year-old Palestinian
to a member of the Hitler youth!
That's right, because they
both like to kill Jews.
- Lisa! Hey!
- Come on, guys.
It's not because they've
been occupied and humiliated
and bombed out of their homes
for the last 50 years?
Yes, that's partly why they like it.
It's not like killing civilians
is their last resort.
It's their first resort because
it's easy and they like it.
- Raise your hands.
- They like it?
They're just bad people
and they like it?
Yes! There are bad
people in the world.
I think they liked blowing
up the World Trade Center!
They kill their own sisters
when they get raped!
- It's called barbarism!
- Who?
It's, practically, all people
do is kill each other.
If they didn't like it,
they wouldn't do it.
You guys aren't the
only ones in the class!
You're not even Jewish, Lisa!
The next person who opens their
mouth without raising their hand...
I'm fucking half Jewish, and who cares
what I am? I'm anti-murder, not pro-Israel.
Lisa! You can leave!
Fine. Thank you.
I guess I lost my cool a little,
but there is such a thing as...
Who is running these discussions?
But, Lisa, you have to remember,
it's always easy for the dominant side
to be content with the status quo.
How do you mean, Ramon?
I mean the oppressor is always
in favor of law and order
because it is his law and his order.
He uses violence to maintain his
position and calls it the rule of law.
But when the person underfoot uses
violence to change his status,
he's called a criminal
and a terrorist.
- In Colombia...
- I see.
And what would you like them to do?
"They" meaning?
The Jew oppressors. What
would you like them to do?
I didn't use that expression.
- No, you didn't.
- But since you ask...
I just spent the whole
day arguing about this.
I didn't really mean
to bring it up again.
- Don't handle me.
- I'm not handling you.
- What did you think of the play?
- Don't bother, Mom.
And I think it's ironic in the
extreme that the victims of Nazis
- find it essential...
- If Israelis were like Nazis
- there wouldn't be any arabs left.
- ... To use Nazi tactics...
That's what I've been saying!
- That seems excessive, Emily, come on.
- I'm leaving.
That's the response. That's
the Jewish response.
It's the what?
It's the Jewish response.
You don't like what I am
saying or what I do, so you...
- That's my Jewish response.
- Oh, my God!
It's all right. That's all right.
It's a perfect little encapsule.
It's the Jewish response.
Joan, I won't defend myself.
All what I meant was
that was the typical response
you will get from someone
who will take that position
that woman was taking.
If I would have said the word "Israeli"
instead of the word "Jewish,"
I don't think there
would be a problem.
But if you want to break up with me
because I used the wrong adjective,
what I'm going to do?
I'm not going to beg you.
- Hello?
- Yeah, it's Dad.
Hi, Dad, how are you?
I'm really looking forward to
our horseback riding trip.
Yeah. That's why I'm calling. I
don't think it's going to happen.
Really? What's the matter?
Nothing's the matter. Nobody
really seems to want to go.
And I don't really feel
like spending 3,000 bucks
on something nobody seems to have
the slightest interest in. Okay?
So, I think it'll be
just better, obviously,
for everyone if we
just cancel it.
I never said I didn't want to go.
Well, I can't get a straight answer from
anybody about what they want to eat.
Annette says that she's called you four
times and you haven't called her back.
The ranch seems to be putting some
kind of intolerable pressure on her
to choose five lunches for a 5-day trip that
we're not taking for a month-and-a-half.
I talk to Curtis about it and all I get
is monosyllables. So what is the point?
I think he's really
looking forward to it.
I don't think anybody's
Okay?
I don't want to go.
I also think, Lisa, that
it would be a good idea
if we just tabled the notion of
you coming out here next year.
Things look like they're gonna start
picking up for me a little bit in the fall
and that means I'm not gonna be
around the house all that much,
and since you and Annette
detest each other,
I honestly don't think that's what I want
to come home to after a 14-hour day.
We don't detest each other.
Well, it doesn't really strike me as
something you seem all that serious about.
Just forget it. Let's just forget it.
Okay.
So, just tell Curtis that New Mexico's
off and I'll talk to you whenever.
- Okay.
- All right.
What's wrong?
Dr. Berger.
Excuse me, the man is not experiencing
discomfort, he's in pain.
Well, I use the real word.
Uh-huh. His other knee is
87 years old, too. Okay?
So I'm not exactly bowled
over by your diagnosis.
Okay. I'm gonna have to call you back.
Ladies, come in. I'm sorry.
- Russel.
- Hey, Lisa.
Hi.
- Well, they want to settle.
- They do?
- Mr. Deutsch?
- I'm right here.
I had the thought, if they're
willing to settle so quickly,
maybe we're better off
waiting a little bit,
you know, rattling the
saber a little more?
- What you got to realize...
- Abigail, Russel doesn't...
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. Go ahead.
But if they responded so
strongly based on one story...
Maybe we're cutting
our own throats here.
They are responding to
the story in the paper.
That's just common sense.
But what you gotta understand is
they're making the offer to settle now
because they want to get the
story out of the paper.
Besides, the main point is
not to jack up the price.
I'm sorry?
- We didn't hear that last bit.
- Ladies, let me just...
Rob, Abigail, if I could
just finish my thought.
They are jumping at
the bait right now.
But if another six months goes by, we run
a serious risk of losing our momentum.
That's why I wanted all of
us together on the phone,
so we could talk about your other
terms, besides the damages.
I promise you, I am gonna
be very, very aggressive.
What other terms would there be?
What do you mean, like
some kind of a fund?
- A what?
- Some kind of fund for the kids?
I don't understand what
you mean by a fund.
What does he mean,
"besides the damages?"
Mr. Deutsch, do you mean
some kind of trust fund?
A fund that would be set up by
the bus company for our kids?
For tax purposes?
- What fucking fund?
- I have no idea.
Because I have to tell you,
we have just lived through that
nightmare with Monica and our children,
and it was not a pleasant experience.
We just want a clean, straight...
Damages is fine.
We're talking about the driver,
getting the driver fired
as part of the conditions.
Oh, yes, absolutely, if
you think he's at fault.
Just as long as they don't
think they can buy us off
just by getting rid of this guy.
- You see what I mean?
- Absolutely.
Absolutely. If they're so quick to
agree to a settlement on this basis...
You see what I mean?
I mean, what we're most concerned
about here is the amount.
Yes, we're getting that, Rob.
- Lisa, I'm really proud of you!
- Thank you.
- Really, really proud!
So, what happens now?
- They have to figure out the terms.
- Uh-huh.
Hello? Yes?
- What do you mean!
- What's the matter?
Yes?
Yes.
- Ramon's had a heart attack.
- What?
- Is he gonna be okay?
- Quiet!
Yes?
Let me write this down.
Do you know any of these people?
No, I never met any of his friends.
I don't know who they are.
Okay, I'm really not
trying to be funny,
but isn't this a Jewish funeral home?
I guess they do both.
Excuse me.
- Joan?
- Yes.
Oh, you must be Rodrigo.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
- Rodrigo, this...
- I want to tell you, Joan,
my dad talked about you all the time.
- He did?
- Yes.
The night he met you, he called
me in England and woke me
to tell me about it.
He was so excited.
I haven't heard him talk about anyone
like that since my mother died.
Really?
- I don't know if this is appropriate...
- No, it's okay.
But...
He went out a lot.
But the last time I spoke to him,
he told me, from the
moment he met you,
he knew he wanted to marry you.
Because, for the first time
since he lost my mother,
he finally met a woman he
could really connect with.
Well,
he was... he was a very sweet man,
and I know he loved you and
your brother very much.
Yeah, I know he did.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Thanks for coming with me today.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, you're welcome.
I don't want to be macabre, but...
Ramon and I were supposed to go to hear
The Tales of Hoffman the week after next,
and I still have the tickets.
Would you be interested in going?
Or should I give them away?
- I'll go.
- Okay.
- It's Monday night. We can dress up.
What did you make of that?
People don't relate
to each other, Mom.
They're totally disconnected.
That's what I make of it.
Well,
I think that's kind of
unfortunate that you think that,
because I feel like you and I used
to relate to each other really well.
I'm not trying to hurt your feelings.
It's just a general observation.
Okay.
Hey, can I get a hug?
Sure.
I just feel totally at sea.
Okay. What do you want to do?
What do you mean? Aren't you
gonna tell me what to do?
- It's your body. It's your baby...
- Baby?
Yes.
Now, who's the father?
It could be a lot of people.
Honey...
Who?
I'm never going to tell you, Mom.
It's against my principles.
No, no. But you want to send
that bus driver to jail
for running a red light, and you
won't tell me about these boys?
Mrs. Cohen.
She's right here.
Hi.
Hi, honey.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Let's talk about it later.
Hi, Emily. Hi, Lisa.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
I am very pleased to be
able to inform you all
that I had a long meeting with
the lawyer from the bus company
and they have agreed to settle,
out of court, for $350,000.
- What? Fantastic!
- That is just great!
I assume this is agreeable
with everybody.
Yes! It's just fantastic!
But, of course, I gotta bring the
offer to you, and get your approval.
- Uh, Mr. Deutsch?
- Now,
I know there was a concern
after our last call
that we were jumping
the gun a little bit.
- That's okay.
- We're only...
Abigail. Rob.
Could we just listen to
what Russel has to say
and then talk about it once
he's told us the whole story
and given us his recommendation?
Yeah. Yes. Sorry. Fire away.
I was gonna say,
I know there was a concern
after our last call
that we were jumping
the gun a little bit.
Well, that's okay.
- Would you let him talk, please!
- It's okay.
- We're sorry.
- Sorry.
I want to tell you that I
think it's a very good offer.
I think they're very
anxious to settle.
But I also do think
that at this moment,
they are under the maximum amount of
pressure that we can really bring to bear,
and I don't believe they're
gonna come up any higher.
Hey, $350,000, that's
nothing to sneeze at.
Let me just... I just want
to introduce the thought...
- Can you all hear me?
- Yes!
Was that everybody? Okay.
Emily? What do you think?
I think it sounds
like we should do it.
- But I'd like to be...
- Okay. If that's the vote.
Unless you think there's something to
be gained from holding out for more.
I think that would be a big mistake.
Robbie, what do you think?
- Sold!
Okay.
Now, the only downside
to this as it stands,
and the reason I asked
Lisa and Emily to be here
is because I know this may be a
serious wrinkle for all of you,
is that the bus company will absolutely
not discuss the removal of the driver.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- The driver?
- Then tell them to forget it.
What do you mean? They won't
discuss the removal of the driver?
- Ladies. Let me finish what I was saying.
- It's just a blast in our ears.
- Let him finish.
- Finish what? Forget it!
Thank you. Lisa, I want you to understand,
I pressed them very, very hard on this.
They will not discuss
disciplining a company employee
as part of the settlement
because it could be seen as an admission
of guilt on the part of the MTA.
What does giving us $300,000 mean?
Settling out of court does not
imply an admission of guilt.
It simply does not
carry the same stigma.
On top of that, you
may not know, Lisa,
that they're currently involved in a
very tricky labor dispute right now.
Yeah, we know all about that!
Just tell them to forget it.
- I know that's your reaction...
- It's the only reason we're here.
- Can I jump in here? Russel?
- It's really not your decision.
- It's Emily's decision.
- Hello?
- No.
- It's not?
- Are you still with us?
- It's Abigail's decision,
- because she's the next of kin.
- They're not listening, Robbie.
- But she didn't even know about it!
- That doesn't matter.
Could we get back in this
conversation, please?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Obviously there's some strong
emotions going either way here.
Listen, Emily? I don't
know what you're thinking,
but Rob and I are thinking we should take
Russel's recommendation while we can.
Because if they won't fire the
guy, they're not gonna fire him.
- And six months or a year from now...
- Exactly.
...we're gonna be in a situation
where we're begging them
for half this much...
The entire point of the lawsuit
was to get the guy fired so he
doesn't kill somebody else.
It was not to get you $350,000
you didn't know you were entitled to
for somebody you didn't even like!
And the only reason you're
getting the money at all
is because I started this whole
fucking thing in motion!
I'm sorry for swearing,
but you should be willing
to trade in all the money
- for getting this guy off the street!
- For getting him, Abigail!
Well, I'm sorry, but I
have a responsibility
to Monica, and I take that
responsibility very seriously.
And rather than being abused
over the telephone and cursed at
for having the courtesy to involve
you in these discussions, Lisa,
I would hope you would be
guided by our judgment.
- Unless I'm wrong about that.
- None of that matters.
Unless I'm wrong about that! Just
what is your interest in this?
Because I'm the one who killed her!
I'm the one who killed her,
but at least I know I did it.
And that guy has no idea!
And he is wandering around
blaming everybody else.
And all I want is for somebody to let
him know that what he did was wrong.
And if they don't fire him, and
all you want is the money,
and the police won't do anything,
then how is he gonna know he's wrong?
You can't take the deal, Abigail!
It wasn't to get you any money, it was
because we wanted to get him fired!
Well, it may not matter to you,
but where I come from, $350,000
is an awful lot of money,
and to my mind is a positive result of
all this tragedy, and not just negative.
Not just getting someone fired for one
mistake, no matter how bad it was.
Shove it up your ass!
Lisa!
You sleazy fucking lawyer!
And you're a moralistic cunt!
At this point, I literally have
a zero-tolerance Roger policy.
Hey!
Lisa. What's up?
Hey, did you guys know I
had an abortion last week?
No. I didn't know that.
Yeah, it cost $400.
Do you want to tell us about it?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Well...
Do your parents know about this, Lisa?
Yes.
And have you told the father, honey?
No. There's a couple
of people it could be.
Well, I think you better
tell them, whoever they are.
No.
No. Never mind, I mean, I'm sure
he's sorry, whichever one he is.
I don't see how that makes any
difference, at all, if he's sorry.
That doesn't matter.
It's okay. I...
I gotta go.
It doesn't matter about the father
because the whole thing was my fault.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
really embarrassed. Sorry.
What was that?
- Mom's looking for you.
- What for?
She thinks you're going
out with her tonight.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
...Don't get run over.
- Wait.
- What?
I want to see if that's him.
It's him, Mom. That's the one.
Come on, sweetheart.
Hey.
Well, so far it's not the
greatest opera I ever heard.
What do you mean? It's okay.