Take off your clothes.
What?
I said, take off
your clothes.
But you saw everything
last night.
Mm, but I need
to check something.
Shh.
Only for three seconds.
The bastard.
How does he
do it?
I've got to go.
Don't you ever spend the night
at the woman's place?
Never.
What about when a woman's
at your place?
I tell her
I get insomnia...
anything.
Besides, I have
a very narrow bed.
Are you afraid
of women, Doctor?
Of course.
I really like you,
Tomas.
You are the complete
opposite of kitsch.
In the kingdom
of kitsch,
you would be...
a monster.
No, wait.
Sabina, I've got to go.
Ah!
Ha ha ha!
Oh...
Oh... oh...
No, wait. Wait.
Ha ha!
Now. What am I?
Ha ha ha ha!
Grrr... a monster.
Ha ha ha!
Room 6.
Here we go.
Oh! Oh...
Ah...
Oh...
Oh!
Oh, cognac.
Can you charge it
to my room?
Yes, of course.
Oh, that's funny.
You're in Room 6.
So?
And my shift
finishes at 6:00.
And at 6:00,
I have to be
back in Prague.
Well...
around 6:00.
Oh, I'll be back.
Wait.
Lo lo lo
Lo lo lo lo lo...
You know,
this is my bench.
Your bench?
Yes, I come here
every day to read,
to this same bench.
Isn't that funny?
Yes.
What are you
reading?
Anna Karenina,
by Tolstoy.
Oh, yes,
that Anna Karenina.
Yeah.
I would have come
earlier,
but... my mother...
You live
with your mother?
Well, I've checked out
of my room.
Are you leaving?
Yes, it's getting late.
I just came
for an operation.
A colleague of mine
was supposed to come,
but he injured
himself, so...
Well...
maybe I'll
come back sometime.
Why would you
come back here?
It's so boring.
Nobody here reads.
Nobody here
discusses anything.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Well.
Nice to meet you.
Good-bye.
Tomas.
Are you only
searching for pleasure?
Or is every woman
a new land
whose secrets
you want to discover?
You want to know what
she's going to say
when she makes love?
Or how she will smile?
How she will whisper?
Groan... scream?
Maybe the very smallest...
unimaginable details...
Tiny things
that make one woman
totally unlike
any other.
What's my detail,
Doctor?
Your hat, Sabina.
The hat...
comes from
my grandfather's...
grandfather.
He lived
a long, long time ago.
A long time ago.
Tomas.
What are you
looking at?
Your eyes.
Hello.
So...
you are in Prague.
I just arrived.
I have friends to see.
I'm here
on some business.
Mm-hmm.
I'm looking
for another job.
Ha...
Why don't you come in?
Are you alone?
Yeah.
Take off your clothes.
Achoo!
Excuse me.
I must have caught a cold
on the train.
Perhaps I better
take a look at you.
Come here.
My hands cold?
I'm very ticklish.
Does it hurt there?
Look up.
Down.
Left.
Right.
Ha ha...
Don't worry.
I'm a doctor.
A bit higher.
That's it.
Breathe.
Again.
Cough.
That's fine.
Up we go.
Everything looks fine.
Fine.
Open your mouth.
Tongue.
Ah! Mmm...
Ooh!
Mmm! Mm!
Ah!
Aah!
Hi.
Tomas?
They called
from Geneva.
They are still
offering you that job.
Why should I go
to Geneva?
Everything's
fine here.
Well... I hope so.
You think the Russians
won't interfere?
Think about what
happened in Hungary.
They couldn't.
The world wouldn't allow it.
Besides, we have socialism
with a human face.
Who could be
against it?
Ah, my patient is here.
Which one?
Pigs are not allowed.
I told him to wait
in the truck.
But we will make
an exception.
Hello, Doctor.
You are not angry with me
because I brought
Mephisto?
Look, Doctor,
a gift for you.
Wonderful.
Oh, thank you!
Hmm.
So... Pavel.
Ha ha!
We operated
a month ago.
Yeah.
Any pains?
No.
Dizziness? Headaches?
Good. You can get
back to your farm.
We just need
a small procedure
to replace
the bone flap.
What time shall I expect
your visit tonight?
Ah...
I'm sorry,
I can't make it tonight.
Too bad.
Um... how about
tomorrow afternoon?
Tomorrow night.
So what I heard
was right.
Somebody has moved
into your place.
No.
I have my spies.
Good-bye, Doctor.
Ah...
Ah!
It's not here.
You must have come
without your sock.
How could I have
come without it?
I wouldn't wear
only one sock.
You've been absent-minded lately,
always in a hurry.
Always looking
at your watch.
I'll lend you one
of my stockings.
You want me
to put this on?
It's cold out,
Doctor.
Mm-hmm.
You think I'm doing
something silly.
Maybe.
How can I know?
What are we
talking about?
Tereza.
If I had two lives...
with one, I'd have her
stay at my place.
With the other,
I'd kick her out.
Then I'd compare
and see which was best.
But we only live once.
Life's so light...
like an outline
we can't ever...
fill in...
or correct...
make any better.
It's frightening.
She's looking for something
to do here in Prague, and I...
Now...
you want me
to help her?
She is not
qualified for anything,
but she takes
beautiful pictures.
I was wondering
if you might...
You mean...
you want me
to help you.
Come on in, Tereza.
Let's have some tea.
Yes. Why don't
you fix it?
Yeah, sure.
Hee hee!
It's very messy
around here.
I always try not to get
too attached to a place,
to objects.
Or to people.
Hmm.
Tereza, come over here.
I want to show you
some pictures.
You know Man Ray?
No.
I like...
I like this one very much.
Mmm.
This is Lee Miller.
She's so...
She's so beautiful.
Tomas says
you're a photographer.
Well, I like to
take pictures, but...
Take pictures of what's
going on in the streets.
I'll help get
them published.
Thanks, Sabina.
I love
those pictures.
They were trying
something different.
Searching for
a new beauty.
Yes.
Something higher.
Here's the tea I made.
Aaah. Aaah.
What is it?
Tereza?
Oh, I had a dream.
I was at her place.
Sabina's.
In her studio...
and you were
making love to her.
In that
big bed of hers.
You made me
stand by a wall
and not move at all.
You made me watch.
And I had such pain
from seeing you
that I started to pierce needles
under my fingernails
to stop the pain
in my heart.
It hurt so much.
Why did you
do it to me?
It was just a dream.
Try to sleep.
I can't sleep.
Yes, you can. Come here.
I can't fall asleep.
You can sleep.
Sleep in my arms.
Like a baby bird.
Like a broom...
among brooms...
in a broom closet.
Like a tiny parrot.
Like a whistle.
Like a little song.
A song sung by a forest...
within a forest...
a thousand years ago.
Oh!
Look! They are here!
Tereza's pictures!
Two full pages!
Thanks, Sabina!
Congratulations!
They're really great!
Tereza, this is
my colleague Jiri,
and this is the chief.
- I'm pleased.
- Hello.
Wonderful! You've really
captured a new spirit here.
You can see how
everything is changing.
Not everything.
Look over there.
Our comrades
with the Russians.
Some people
never change.
Some people are
always scoundrels.
How can you tell?
Does it show
in a man's face?
Can we judge
by a man's face
if he is
a scoundrel or not?
Let's look
at them and see.
Scoundrel.
- Scoundrel.
- Definitely.
- No doubt.
We know you.
Scoundrels.
What would you say
about Tomas?
Hmmm.
He's definitely
scoundrel.
Why?
Is it the mouth?
The sly eyes?
No, it's carefully hidden...
in the brain.
Such things are hidden
in all of our brains.
So what makes
the difference?
Maybe only
one millionth part.
Maybe there is
no difference.
These men don't even know
if they're scoundrels or not.
Are you serious?
More than 100,000 people
were imprisoned, tortured,
executed in their regime.
And now,
these men cry out
that they didn't
know anything...
that they were
misled or manipulated.
That they were... innocent.
Not innocent,
but, um...
unaware, perhaps.
They had to know
what they were doing.
Otherwise,
it's unthinkable.
It doesn't matter
whether they knew or not.
- Boo! -
Boo! - Boo!
I've been thinking
about Oedipus.
Good King Oedipus.
Is sleeping with your mother
the same sort of crime?
When Oedipus realized that
he had killed his father-
unknowingly...
unknowingly killed his father...
and was sleeping
with his mother...
and that because of his crimes
plagues were
ravaging his city,
he couldn't bear
the sight of what he'd done.
He plucked out
his own eyes and left.
He did not feel innocent.
He felt he had to
punish himself.
But...
our leaders, unlike Oedipus,
they felt
they were innocent.
And when the atrocities
of the Stalinist period became known,
they cried,
"We didn't know!
We weren't aware
of what was going on.
Our conscience is clear. "
But the important
difference is...
they stayed in power.
And they should have
plucked their eyes out.
All I'm saying is that
morality has changed
since Oedipus.
Come on.
Yes!
Why don't you
write it down?
I'm not a writer.
It will be published.
Our politics are in it.
I don't really care
about politics.
What do you
care about?
Is something
bothering you?
No, why?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
No...
When I watched you
dancing with another man...
I thought to myself,
"He could be her lover. "
You are jealous.
No, I'm not jealous.
You are.
I'm not.
I'm not jealous, Tereza.
He's jealous.
No, he isn't.
Who's he?
He's jealous
I'm not jealous.
He's jealous,
he's jealous
Whatever you say, Tereza.
You're jealous.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
You're jealous.
I'm not jealous.
Doo be doo
be doo be doo
No!
You are!
I'm not.
Let go!
I won't let go!
You're jealous!
You are!
I'm not!
No! No! No!
Ha ha ha ha!
Will you marry me?
What? No!
Yes!
No!
- Yes.
- No.
Yes? Ha!
Be my witness?
Of course!
I'll have to buy
Mephisto a black tie.
Did you hear, Mephisto?
A black tie.
My dear fiances,
I am welcoming you
from the deep bottom
of my heart
on this very special day
when you freely decided
to be legally man and wife.
I suppose that
both of you know your duties
in supporting each other,
and I am sure
both of you know
your own medical records?
I have to
tell you this.
Don't think a life is
a walk on a sunny meadow.
Life isn't a walk
on a sunny meadow,
and life isn't a walk
on a rose garden.
Our socialist country
has done much for you.
Now it's up to you.
Shh.
Shh!
I make you laugh?
No... no.
Shh!
You are laughing at me?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I refuse to go on.
In this country,
is nothing sacred anymore?
If you can't be serious,
you don't deserve
to be married!
Mmm!
Let's take one, Tomas.
It will make us happy.
Choose one.
This one.
Hey!
My nephew from
the country's here!
Uncle!
Hey!
Let's call him Tolstoy.
When I first met you,
you were
reading Tolstoy.
It can't be Tolstoy.
It's a girl.
It's a girl!
How about Anna Karenina?
It doesn't look at all
like Anna Karenina.
Look.
It's a man's face.
It looks more
like Anna's husband.
Let's call her Karenin.
Karenin.
Come on, Karenin.
Let's go home.
Heh heh heh...
I like it very much.
King Oedipus.
It's a very good idea.
And with those changes,
we can publish next week.
Eva, will you
type this, please?
Now we can publish
a piece like this.
It's fantastic.
Think about it.
Complete rehabilitation of
the people who were prosecuted.
Complete freedom of speech,
of the press,
emancipation
from the Russians.
That's all we wanted.
And you think the Russians
will let us emancipate?
What can they do?
Nothing, Doctor.
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
Keep on writing.
Thanks, but surgery's easier.
Take me to them.
Oh, you're awake.
To whom?
To the other women.
Take me to them
when you make love to them.
I'll undress them for you.
I'd like to.
Really.
I'll give them a bath
and bring them to you.
I'll do anything you like.
Other women's bodies
will be our playthings.
Tereza, what are
you talking about?
I know you see
other women.
I know it!
You can't hide it from me.
Every day,
I try to tell myself,
"Well, it's nothing.
It's not important.
He's just playing around.
He can't resist it.
But he loves me.
I'm sure about that.
He loves me. "
"He loves me!"
But I can't stand it.
I tried hard.
I just can't.
Take me to them.
Don't leave me alone!
Tereza, calm down.
Stop talking.
Try to sleep.
You need
some sleep now.
I don't
want to sleep.
You're tired of me.
I know that.
I can see it
in your eyes.
Arf! Arf! Arf!
Hello.
Yes.
What?
Tereza!
Here they come!