This is a diary of...
hate.
And perhaps I wouldn't
be writing it...
if some devil hadn't made me stop
him that night in the rain.
You want to drown, Henry?
I wanted a bit of air.
How nice to see you, Bendrix.
How long has it been? A year?
June 1944.
As long as that?
How's Sarah?
She's out and about somewhere.
She at the cinema?
No, she never goes.
Good night, Henry.
You should go home before
you catch your death.
Is something wrong?
Let me take you home, Henry.
Or perhaps I wouldn't
be writing this...
if I had known then who I hated.
Was it Henry?
Was it his wife, Sarah?
Or was it some other, who was
yet to be revealed to me?
Sarah?
See, she's out still.
Come upstairs.
Come in. Let me get you a drink.
Whiskey, thank you.
So what's troubling you, Henry?
Sarah.
She's out for a walk now, Bendrix.
A walk.
Well, she always was a great walker.
Jealousy's a terrible thing.
Well, you know you can
trust me, Henry.
You know, I went so far...
as to get the name
of a private detective.
Do you think she's seeing someone?
- Of course. You think me a fool?
- No.
I don't think you're a fool.
- You mean you think it's possible?
- Of course.
Sarah's human.
I can't sleep.
I keep picking up this wretched card.
Burn it.
- I wish I could.
- Then go see... Who? Savage?
And sit where all the other
jealous husbands sit?
Do you think they have
a waiting room...
where we see each other's
faces as we pass?
Why not let me go, Henry?
- You?
- Yes.
I could pretend to be a jealous lover.
Jealous lovers are less ridiculous
than jealous husbands.
They're supported by
the weight of literature.
Tragic, never comic.
Think of Trollus.
I shan't lose my amour-propre
when I interview Mr. Savage.
It's ridiculous. One's friend
can't spy on one's wife...
...and pretend to be her lover.
- What else are friends for?
You're a good chap, Bendrix. All I
needed was to talk, clear my head.
The name was Savage,
and the address was 3 Vigo Passage.
Forget what I said. Doesn't
make sense. I'll see a doctor.
That was the door.
Sarah's home.
It's the maid.
She's been to the pictures.
No, it was Sarah's step.
Sarah, darling.
You. Is that you?
Been out for a walk?
- Yes.
- It's a filthy night.
You're wet through, Sarah.
You'll catch your death of cold.
Good night.
Their marriage was conventional,
like their well-appointed house.
And I liked them both
the first night we met...
drinking bad South African sherry
because of the war in Spain.
Good evening.
May I take your hat?
Thank you.
Mr. Mlles is upstairs.
Sherry, sir?
Thank you.
She seemed restless.
In the summer of 1939, the whole
of London was restless...
in the face of the coming storm.
Sarah, this is our neighbour,
the novelist chap.
What's a novelist doing here?
- Research.
- On what?
On your husband.
I'm writing a character who
works for the ministry.
I need to know his habits.
What he drinks at bedtime...
- Cocoa.
- And when.
Eleven o'clock.
Unless we're entertaining.
Would you excuse your character?
- The ministry needs him.
- Unfortunately, it does.
- So tell me.
- What?
His secrets.
Henry's a good man.
He has no secrets.
I was afraid you'd say that. Goodness
has so little fictional value.
What does have fictional value?
- A minister of home security.
- My husband's fictional?
I'm saying he could be.
In the right hands.
Can we head away from
the service for a moment?
Change the subject?
- I meant fresh air actually.
- Of course.
- How long have you been married?
- Is your character married?
Yes, he's been married
apply for 10 years.
Henry's a perfect model then.
We've been married 10 years.
You know that happiness is even harder
to write than goodness.
Henry prefers habit to happiness.
We were discussing the house, darling.
Let me fill that for you.
- It's a lovely house.
- My wife found it.
Your wife is charming.
- She's a great help to me.
- Yes, I'm sure.
Haven't they made a picture
of one of your books?
Yes, it's playing at the Rialto.
I'll take you both.
I'm far too busy for pictures,
I'm afraid.
Should I note that?
Make sure your character's
never home before 10.
- Come out, Henry. For once?
- I can't, darling.
But you go. Take her, Bendrix.
With Sarah, one has to insist.
- It's not what I wrote, you know.
- You can't keep saying that.
It's true.
I know.
There was one scene you did write.
Describe it.
Where he offered her onions
with her meal.
She refused because her husband didn't
like the smell. And he got angry.
And why did he get angry?
He didn't want to think of her
going home to him.
Does Henry like onions?
No.
I'm in love, you know.
Me too.
Susan?
Come upstairs.
Sarah?
One minute, dear.
What if he heard?
He wouldn't recognize the sound.
- Sarah, been eating onions?
- Sorry, darling.
Bendrix, how was the picture?
Up to scratch?
And, of course,
as she began to love me...
she learnt to deceive Henry.
So why was I upset to find
that two years later...
she was deceiving him again?
Mr. Bendrix, I assume we're
discussing Mrs. Bendrix.
Not exactly.
She's the wife of a friend of mine.
Perhaps you and the lady are intimate?
I've only seen her once since 1944.
I don't understand.
You said this was a watching case.
Can't one love or hate
as long as that?
There's nothing discreditable
about jealousy.
I always salute it as a mark
of true love.
I've come on behalf of the husband.
He thinks she's deceiving him.
She has secrets.
Secrets.
There may be
nothing in it, of course.
In my experience, Mr. Bendrix,
there almost invariably is.
Shall we report to you
or the husband?
To me. He must know nothing about it.
A most interesting case.
All my men use great discretion.
I will put one on it immediately...
and he will do his damnedest
to put your mind at rest.
Or should I say, the husband's?
Good.
Yes, it was good to see you.
Yes, how long has it been?
Two years. As long as that?
You were always better
at anniversaries than me.
You want to meet?
Well, whatever for?
Not tomorrow, no.
I've got this article.
Wednesday? Let me check.
Would Thursday do?
Good. The Park Lane Hotel at 1?
It was odd to think
that during the war...
we could be so totally at peace.
There were nights when I wished
those sirens would never end.
Tell me again.
I love you.
And I always will.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I came by tube, but it was crowded.
Well, taxi's quicker.
I know. Didn't want to be quick.
I booked a table at Palmer's.
Can't we stay here?
Well, it's where we always used to go.
But, you see, I've never
been back there.
It was never
your restaurant, was it?
So you still go there?
Yeah, two or three times a week.
It's convenient.
Let's go.
- Sorry about that.
- It's all right.
A pleasure to see you, sir. It's been
so long, I thought you'd forgotten us.
I was afraid you'd say that.
And you, ma'am.
It's been a long time too.
Two years, Alfred.
- There.
- Thank you.
Why did you lie?
- About my coming here?
- Yes.
Why did you want to meet?
I wanted to ask you about Henry.
I'm worried about him.
How did you find him the other night?
Was he strange at all?
I didn't notice anything wrong.
I wanted to ask you,
but I know you're very busy...
whether you could look him up
occasionally. I think he's lonely.
With you?
You know he's never really noticed me.
Not for years.
Maybe you've given him reason.
What reason could I give?
What reason did you give me?
None.
- Are you on a new book?
- Of course.
It's not about us?
The one you threatened to write?
A book takes a year to write.
It's too hard work for revenge.
If you knew how little
you had to revenge.
No, I'm joking.
We had a good time together.
We're adults, and we knew
it had to end sometime.
And now we can lunch
and talk about Henry.
Sorry.
This was stupid.
I really shouldn't have called.
That cough needs attending to.
It's only a cough.
Goodbye, Maurice.
Your menu, sir.
I'm sorry. You have to realize...
I'm jealous of everything that moves.
I'm jealous of the rain.
How can you be jealous of the rain?
Where did you get it?
Spain. That was my war, I'm afraid.
It finished me off for this one.
You were shot. How romantic.
Not really.
They put a pin inside me.
I wondered about the limp.
Could I grow to love it?
And have you?
I have never, ever loved anyone
as much as you.
Yes?
Mr. Parkis to see you, sir.
Show him in.
This way, please.
I'll be with you in a minute, Mr...?
The name's Parkis.
Mr. Savage's man.
Sit down. Take a cigarette.
No, not on duty, sir.
Unless for purposes of concealment.
But you're not on duty now.
Well, in a manner of speaking,
yes, sir.
I've been relieved for half
an hour while I make my report.
So there's something to report?
It's not quite a blank sheet, sir.
Have we met somewhere before?
I don't think so.
Like I say, sir,
it's not quite a blank sheet.
But then it never is.
Me and my boy, we followed...
Your boy?
My son, sir.
I'm teaching him the business.
I mean, a boy can be useful
in all sorts of ways.
On the day in question, the party
went by tube to Piccadilly...
and proceeded to the
Park Lane Hotel.
She seemed quite agitated.
She met a gentleman with whom
she was obviously quite close...
since they greeted each other with
an affectionate lack of ceremony.
And at one point...
although I cannot be certain,
held hands along the bar.
They held hands?
Yes, sir. The gentleman pushed
the lady's glass towards her...
and the hand sort of stayed there
for some time, sir...
which indicates
a squeeze of that nature.
And after a short conversation, they
proceeded to a restaurant called...
Palmer's, which was difficult to gain
access to, with the boy and all.
I observed them through the window.
And after a while, the lady left...
laboring, it seemed to me,
under great emotion.
Great emotion.
You're sure of that?
Without doubt, sir.
Then I followed her down
Charing Cross Road to Maiden Lane...
where she turned into a church
for what I presume was a good cry.
- She's not a Roman, is she, sir?
- No.
Thought not.
She didn't kneel, sir, but sat.
And from the angle of her face,
I could tell tears were an issue.
Forgive the personal touch.
Of course.
You see, I like the lady,
the party in question.
As did I, but you were wrong
about the hands.
The hands, sir?
We never so much as touched hands.
Oh, dear.
I've made a fool of myself.
Well, Sarah has that effect.
Mr. Savage should've introduced us.
Oh, no, sir.
It was up to me.
Well, it's not serious.
If you look at it from the outside,
it's quite funny.
But I'm on the inside, sir.
It's not Mr. Savage I'm worried about
so much. It's my boy, sir.
When I tell him
you're the husband...
But you're wrong.
I'm acting on the husband's behalf.
So you've requested
an investigation of yourself?
It's an interesting paradox.
Who's the wronged party then?
Pardon me, sir.
I am slow in such matters.
You've both been supplanted
in that lady's affections by...
Another?
Try to think of it
the way I do, Mr. Parkis.
Jealousy can only exist with desire.
You are on a hunt for desire.
Just regard yourself as its servant.
Of course, sir. That's my job.
Thank you.
The vicarious lover, Parkis.
- Good night, sir.
- Good night.
I wondered how much of her
he could reclaim for me.
For a moment, I wished I was him...
shining his searchlight
around her world.
I am a jealous man.
- I'm jealous of this stocking.
- Why?
Because it does what I can't.
Kisses your whole leg.
And I'm jealous of this button.
Poor, innocent button.
It's not innocent at all.
It's with you all day. I'm not.
I suppose you're jealous of my shoes.
Why?
Because they'll take you away from me.
I measured love by
the extent of my jealousy.
And as my jealousy was infinite...
Anyone who loves is jealous.
My love should be infinite too.
I hate you being unhappy.
- I don't mind what makes you happy.
- If I slept with someone else?
That's neither here nor there.
I want you to be happy.
Maybe you'd want to do the same.
- I never would.
- But you do.
- Do what?
- Sleep with someone else.
You mean Henry?
How can anyone be jealous of Henry?
He has you. I don't.
We inhabit the same house,
that's all. You know that.
I'm the shadow he walks around.
And I love you.
I'd rather see you dead
than with another man.
I will never, ever be
with another man!
You may see me dead, but I will
never be with another man.
We should go to the shelter.
If a bomb hit, think of what
wouldn't happen.
You wouldn't walk back to Henry.
I'd never imagine another lover.
- My jealousy would end.
- Would that make you happy?
Do you believe me now?
But, sadly, I didn't believe her.
There was a devil in my mind
that would never let me.
And now I had Parkis' boy
playing the devil's game.
My boy managed to gain access, sir.
Remarkably useful, he can be.
I call that Exhibit A.
They say a promise is forever, but
I don't know if I can keep this one.
He killed me with jealousy.
You're killing me with love.
So he's got the scent too, Parkis.
- What scent?
- The scent of love.
Stalking it like a retriever.
Well, he's remarkably persistent, sir.
He observed the party in question
in a state of partial undress...
with an unidentified male.
- Where?
- In the bedroom, sir.
The male party closed the door,
and my boy made his exit.
The implication, and I think you would
agree, is that intimacy was...
imminent.
Indeed. Who is he?
Here is where our progress was made.
My boy glanced at the appointment
book in the front hallway.
The party in question had a dental
appointment at 3:30 the following day.
And in fact, she visited, at 3:30,
a premises on 65 Cedar Road...
where no dentist's sign
was in evidence.
A Mr. Smythe owns the premises, sir.
Smythe. With a "Y"?
Yes, sir. S-M-Y-T-H-E.
Though we have no evidence
of intimacy...
the implication is clearly there.
Well, how is it there?
The fictitious dental appointment.
Exhibit B.
My boy took that.
And the party in question
emerged two hours later.
Passage of time being amply sufficient
for intimacy to have taken place.
The courts generally demand
at least an hour, sir.
My boy would have photographed
her re-emergence...
but for the unfortunate occurrence
of him falling asleep.
Luckily, sir, the party in question
mistook him for an abandoned urchin...
and led him
to the tube station.
So the time of re-emergence
is definitely established...
as was an acquaintance, which
may have its uses in the future.
Should I confront him
like an injured husband?
I'm against it, sir.
It complicates things in the courts.
This will never reach court.
- An amicable settlement.
- There's lack of interest.
One can hardly make a fuss
about a man called Smythe.
I'd just like to see him, that's all.
Perhaps Lance can oblige us
next time with a frontal.
- Lance?
- My boy.
Called after Lancelot.
The Round Table.
He found the Holy Grail.
That was Galahad. Lancelot was found
in bed with Guinevere.
I hadn't heard.
I have to say, sir,
I would advise against it.
I'd just like to see what a man
called Smythe looks like.
Will you lend me your boy?
If you'll assure me there'll be
nothing unpleasant.
Well, Sarah isn't there. This scene
will have a universal certificate.
Come with me, young Lancelot.
Go on, Lance.
No need to worry.
You're feeling ill, remember?
How ill, sir?
Ill enough to faint.
Can you act that?
If I hold my breath, I can go pale.
Good.
Excuse me, but does
a Dr. Wilson live here?
I'm afraid he doesn't.
I was given this address,
and my boy's quite ill.
- You all right?
- Come in.
Would you mind? I'm sorry.
He needs to sit down, perhaps.
Thank you.
Can I fetch him a glass of water?
That's very kind.
Or some orange squash?
Water will be fine.
Orange squash, please.
Say thank you, Arthur.
Is his name Arthur?
Yes, Arthur James. His mother
was fond of Tennyson.
Is she...?
Yes, yes. Four years now.
He must be a great comfort to you.
And anxiety.
I ought to introduce myself.
- Bridges.
- My name is Smythe.
With a "Y"?
This is my brother, Richard.
This is Mr. Bridges.
His boy isn't feeling well.
I was given this address
for a Dr. Wilson.
There's no such doctor here.
I've seen your boy before.
Maybe on the common.
What was the real purpose
of your visit?
I told you, a doctor.
No, you're not ill, are you, boy?
People sometimes come to me
and can't explain why.
But if there is a reason...
- My brother often deals with...
- Hush, Susan.
They must ask themselves.
I recognize your boy.
But you...
Who recommended you?
We have a friend in common.
Sarah Mlles.
And your name is?
Bendrix.
I know all about you.
I'm sure you do.
But you must enlighten me.
Aren't you bound by vows of chastity?
Oh, my dear.
Go, please.
Would you just go?
Come along, Lancelot.
Poor Sarah. She had committed
nothing but love...
and here were Parkis and his boy
watching her every move.
I would've called the spies off...
had the devil not tugged
at my elbow once more.
Still in the rain?
Walking, Bendrix.
Doctor recommends it.
Well, walk with me.
I recommend a drink.
How's Sarah?
Pretty well.
Did you ever consult
that private detective?
I hoped you'd forgotten that.
I was overworked.
I had Royal Commission brewing.
Don't worry, Henry.
I did it for you.
You had no right.
- I'm paying all the charges.
- It's infernal cheek.
Here's the report, Henry.
His name is Smythe with a "Y."
You've been properly
led up the garden path.
Let me pass.
You don't want them? Photographs,
names, love letters?
Now will you let me go?
I can always get you a carbon copy.
Strange how much dignity
there can be in a hat.
Without it, he seemed one of
the anonymous. The dispossessed.
I had pitied myself
for so long, it was...
odd to pity him.
I'm sorry, Henry.
Sit down.
Were you two lovers, Bendrix?
It's the only explanation.
The only excuse too.
Can't you see that what
you've done is monstrous?
You must think me a fool
not to have guessed.
Why didn't she leave me?
Because you're a habit she's formed.
You're her security.
Why did she leave you?
I became a bore like you.
But I wasn't born one.
You created me.
She wouldn't leave you,
so I bored her with my jealousy.
You can't be jealous of me.
Well, you won, in a way.
We had come to the end of love.
She'd only make love with me...
but she could shop and cook
and fall asleep with you.
She's still very fond of you.
One isn't satisfied with fondness.
- I was.
- Yes, and that made you her pimp.
A husband who knows where his slippers
are but never notices his wife.
But you weren't the only pimp.
The war was the greatest pimp of all.
And the V-1 s never affected us...
until the act of love was over.
So what will you do when it ends?
It won't end, I told you.
I meant the war.
It's the only certain thing.
What do you mean?
That allows me to see you.
You think love ends
when you don't see me?
To be is to be perceived.
Do I exist when you're with Henry?
Yes.
Isn't that why you stay with Henry?
Because you know this will end?
No.
- Let's go to the basement.
- My landlady's there.
- Does it matter?
- To her.
- It's close, Maurice.
- I'll check.
- Let me go with you.
- I'll be one second.
Nobody's there.
It's clear.
I never heard the bang.
I awoke after five minutes
or five seconds...
to a changed world.
For a moment, I was free of feeling...
love, hate, jealousy.
And it all felt like happiness.
Oh, my God.
You're alive?
You sound disappointed.
You're hurt.
I just cut myself, that's all.
What were you doing on the floor?
Praying.
To what?
To anything that might exist.
It'd have been more practical
to have come downstairs.
I did.
Well, why didn't you wake me?
I tried.
You didn't move.
I don't understand.
I knew for certain you were dead.
There wasn't much to pray for
then, was there?
A miracle.
And we don't believe in those.
No.
And that siren means you go.
Yes.
Please don't.
I have to. Henry will...
Forget Henry.
You don't understand.
You were gone.
Now I'm back.
I'm sorry to disappoint you, Sarah.
Love doesn't end...
just because we don't
see each other.
Doesn't it?
People go on loving God, don't they?
All their lives, without seeing Him.
That's not my kind of love.
Maybe there's no other kind.
So I was a disappointment in the end.
I lived. And that was
the end of the affair...
until I met you with that
detective's card in your hand.
I wondered why we hadn't seen you.
You should go home, Henry.
You'll catch your death.
I'm sorry.
It was quite easy, sir.
There was such a crush.
Mrs. Miles thought
I was from the ministry.
Mr. Miles thought
I was one of her friends.
I knew the way to her room
from my boy.
Anybody would've stopped me, I
would've been looking for the toilet.
Of course, nobody did.
Did you think it was
a good cocktail party?
Highly successful, I would say, sir.
But Mrs. Miles looked
a bit out of sorts.
I refer to this...
as Exhibit D.
Did you look at it?
I ascertained its nature, sir.
I judged she wasn't the cautious type.
So happy. M returns today.
My experience of diaries is, they
always give things away, sir.
People invent their little codes.
You see through them.
I woke up and the sun was shining.
This covers several years.
I hope you're satisfied, sir.
Life was going to be happy again,
but last night I dreamt...
I think this may well close
our account, Parkis.
I had a feeling it might, sir.
I have enjoyed our association, sir...
if one can talk of enjoying
under the sad circumstances.
As have I.
So I hope you wouldn't
resent a memento, sir.
There's quite a history with that.
Do you remember the Bolton case?
I can't say I do.
It caused quite a stir
at the time, sir.
Lady Bolton, her maid and the man,
all discovered together.
That ashtray stood
beside the bed, sir.
On the lady's side.
I shall treasure it, Parkis.
If ashtrays could speak, sir.
Indeed.
I'll call later to make sure
there were no loose ends.
Thank you, Parkis.
- Good night, sir.
- Good night.
Sometimes I get tired of trying
to convince him that I love him...
and shall love him forever.
He pounces on my words
like a barrister and twists them.
So what will you do when it ends?
You think love ends
when you don't see me?
To be is to be perceived.
Do I exist when you're with Henry?
Yes.
Isn't that why you stay with Henry?
Because you know this will end?
No.
- Let's go to the basement.
- My landlady's there.
- Does it matter?
- To her.
- It's close, Maurice.
- I'll check.
- Let me go with you.
- I'll be one second.
Nobody's there.
It's clear.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, don't take him.
But you had.
Whatever was him was gone.
You'd taken it.
I'd never believed in prayer.
Oh, God, please bring him back.
Let him live.
I don't believe in you,
but please let him live.
Dear God, please.
Dear God, please, let him live.
Please bring him back.
Please don't take him.
I'll give him up forever.
Only, please let him be alive.
Let him live...
and I promise I'll never
see him again.
Oh, my God.
You're alive?
You sound disappointed.
But if he was alive...
now I was dead.
What were you doing on the floor?
Praying.
To what?
To anything that might exist.
How could I explain to him
what made no sense to me?
You didn't move.
I knew for certain you were dead.
There wasn't much to pray for then?
A miracle.
And we don't believe in that.
No.
And that siren means you go.
Yes.
And I knew that nothing in this world
would make sense to me again.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Love doesn't end...
just because we don't
see each other.
Doesn't it?
People go on loving God, don't they?
All their lives, without seeing Him.
That's not my kind of love.
Maybe there's no other kind.
I can't be held to that promise.
But something told me I would be.
I had tempted fate,
and fate had accepted.
So I was in the desert now,
the desert without him.
I started a tour with Henry.
Civil defence in southern England.
Henry and I sleeping side by side
like figures on tombs.
In the new reinforced shelter
at Bigwell-on-Sea...
the chief warden kissed me.
I allowed him to but felt nothing.
I'm beginning to believe in you, God.
And maybe that's how you work.
You empty me of love,
then fill that emptiness.
They're recommending me for an OBE.
- What's that?
- A step below a CBE.
When I retire,
I'll probably be a KBE.
It's confusing. Couldn't they
stick to the same letters?
Wouldn't you like to be Lady Mlles?
This was the British people's
finest day:
V- E Day, the end of the German war.
A man we have seen before looked down
from a balcony in Whitehall.
The whole of London seemed happy
because there was peace...
and there were no more bombs.
But I'm not sure I liked the peace.
I walked his walks...
tried to think where he'd be.
Then I gave up.
I thought that now
the world is at peace...
maybe I should have some.
I told him it all.
And whoever heard my promise
must have heard it too...
and must have known it already...
since God knows everything.
How cruel that knowledge seemed.
It knew what I would say
before I made that promise.
Knew it would keep me to it.
Knew me the way his hands knew me.
Sarah, darling.
You.
Knew I would meet him
on the stairs.
It's a filthy night.
You're wet through, Sarah. One day
you'll catch your death of cold.
Good night.
Knew he would hate me.
- Wednesday.
- Wednesday. Let me check.
- Would Thursday do?
- Thursday then.
The Park Lane Hotel at 1?
I took my time.
I didn't want to be early.
Why did you want to meet?
I wanted to tell you I'd been dead
for the last two years.
I can't be without you any longer.
But, of course, I didn't.
He's never really noticed me.
Not for years.
Maybe you've given him reason.
What reason could I give?
What reason did you give me?
None.
- Are you on a new book?
- Of course.
It's not about us?
The one you threatened to write?
A book takes a year to write.
It's too hard work for revenge.
If you knew how little
you had to revenge.
No, I'm joking.
We had a good time together.
We're adults, and we knew
it had to end sometime.
And now we can lunch
and talk about Henry.
In the old days,
he would have followed.
We would have made up...
or made love.
I said to God, as I might have
said to my father:
"Dear God, I'm tired.
I'm tired of being without him.
And it's all because of you."
Dr. Gilbert's appointment.
I'd almost forgotten.
He asked me how I felt.
I said I felt nothing.
There was a stone where
my heart should be.
I need help, father.
God granted us free will.
Good. So it's settled.
I'm leaving my husband.
You can't.
Why can't I?
I'm a whore and a liar.
I'm asking Henry for a divorce.
You can't, because you're good.
Better than any person I know.
You're wrong, father.
And you don't know me.
I found a small boy
sleeping on the steps...
with a birthmark
covering his face...
and wondered what kind of God
would give a child that.
Are you lost?
It's all right. It's all right.
Where do you live then?
- You'll be all right now?
- Yes, ma'am.
I kissed his cheek and wished
I could wash it away.
And suddenly, I felt happy again.
I could free myself of this.
I...
am leaving you.
For the last...
five years...
I have been in love...
with Maurice.
I love you.
Know that.
Why now, Henry?
Why do you say that now?
I had a drink with Bendrix.
A horrible drink.
I can't do without you.
"Oh, yes, you can," I thought.
"You changed your newspaper once,
and you soon got used to it."
What's wrong, Henry?
Did Bendrix upset you in some way?
I know I haven't been much
of a husband to you.
We are good friends.
You can do without a friend.
Don't leave me, Sarah.
Stick it out a few more years.
I'll try.
I promise.
Is this coincidence, I wondered?
Or the way life happens?
And if this is life,
am I stuck with it?
But whatever it is,
I can't fight it anymore.
It has won and we have lost.
She's not here.
I know your voice, Sarah.
Talk to me.
Stop here.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much, guv.
One, please.
How did you get it?
You had a drinks party last week.
- Yes. That small man.
- Yes.
He is my snoop.
Oh, Maurice...
how ridiculous.
It's no more ridiculous than you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I tried. Each time I tried,
something would happen.
That's mumbo-jumbo, Sarah.
No. It doesn't work like that.
Accidents.
Little things.
God is in the details, Maurice.
You can't believe that.
Do you believe in things
you can't see?
- You mean Him?
- I mean you.
You see, I never stopped loving you.
Even though I couldn't see you.
My mother baptized me a Catholic.
My father was Jewish,
so we never practiced.
But she always said
she hoped it would "take".
Like a vaccination.
I've only made two promises
in my life.
One was to marry Henry,
the other to stop seeing you.
And I'm too weak to keep either.
I know you don't believe in Him...
but try to.
Talk to Him.
I can't.
Tell Him I'm sorry.
I'm too human. Too weak.
Tell Him I can't keep my promises.
I'm tired of being without you.
- Let's get you home.
- I don't want to go home.
I know.
So have we broken the spell?
The world didn't end, did it?
It did, in a way.
But then, it always did.
Can I sleep now, Maurice?
Please let me sleep.
- It's Henry.
- Don't answer it.
Why not? We'll have to
tell him sometime.
- Come away with me.
- Where?
Anywhere. Brighton.
I want a few days peace before
the arguments begin.
Well, Henry never argues.
I wasn't talking about Henry.
Pain is easy to write.
In pain, we're all drably individual.
But what can one write
about happiness?
It doesn't suit you. And it's mine.
You want it? There's a price.
How much?
Can I pay again?
I want children, you know.
How many?
We'll start with one.
Only one?
You want to start with two?
Is that a promise?
Yes.
Let's get you back to the hotel.
- It's a bit of a mess, isn't it?
- You're right.
Business going well?
Still on the job, Parkis?
Don't worry. Come with me.
Come.
So where's your boy this time?
I left him at home, sir.
Hardly a wise move. He has
the sense not to get noticed.
You think so? Perhaps I wasn't
cut out for this job.
Tell your employer
the circumstances are unique.
What was your phrase?
The party in question is a writer.
They notice everything.
They certainly seem to, sir.
- So who's hired you this time?
- I'm not at liberty to say, sir.
Let me guess. The jealous husband.
I never expected to be recalled
to this case.
Yours is a secure profession.
As long as fools like us love,
your employment never ends.
You could put it like that.
And love never ends, does it?
It seems not, sir.
So what do you need? Photographs
of us in flagrante delicto?
Copies of hotel bills?
Evidence of soiled sheets?
We'd be happy to oblige.
No. My brief is to follow you.
Inform him as to your whereabouts.
Which, of course, you'll do.
I'm obliged to under the terms
of my employment, posthaste.
Won't you need supplementary evidence?
The divorce courts will demand it.
They generally do, sir,
if it come to that.
Exhibit A.
Receipt for two sandwiches bought
on the train to Brighton.
Mutual sandwiches are evidence
of intimacy, aren't they?
They could be so construed.
Exhibit B.
Two tickets for a Big Dipper.
You seem to be doing my job.
Yes, but we haven't quite gotten there.
What would clinch it for us, Parkis?
What would make divorce a certainty?
Generally, sir, some kind
of photographic evidence of...
Of intimacy.
Would be most useful, sir,
if it came to such a pass.
It will, Parkis.
It certainly will.
Here, here, drink this.
I dreamt we had a child.
We will.
We were on the bed together.
The room filled up with water.
There was a child between us.
Why water?
The sea had come in the window.
So you'll marry me?
That's a promise.
The prince regent began building it
for his mistress, Mrs. Fitzherbert.
Beautiful but flawed.
How was she flawed?
She was Catholic.
Impossible, of course.
So he loved her.
Yes, but he married Princess Caroline
of Brunswick, who was Protestant...
but huge.
And he built this huge
folly to impossibility.
- Not now, Henry.
- Forgive me, Sarah. I had to.
- Oh, God, please. Henry, not now.
- You had to what, Henry?
Talk.
Go back home.
You can't hold on to her forever.
I know that.
It hardly suits you, Henry,
the role of jealous husband.
I don't mean to make a scene.
Henry, go home.
I'm not jealous, Bendrix.
What was it you said?
Lovers are jealous.
Husbands are ridiculous.
I was never her lover.
Not much of a husband either,
I'm afraid.
But you hired our detective.
I had to find out where she was.
So you know.
She wants a divorce.
That won't be possible, old man.
You'll contest it?
No. But it would take
at least three months.
What's three months, Henry,
out of a lifetime?
Half.
Half of what?
Of a lifetime, I'm afraid.
Sarah's dying, Bendrix.
Her doctor called the night
she didn't come back...
...with the result of some tests.
I knocked on your door.
I imagined you were both there.
How oddly we behave at such moments.
You shouldn't get wet, darling.
- Don't you like the rain?
- Yes, dear, but...
You've heard news, Henry.
Is it good?
No, dear.
You see, Maurice, never make
a promise. You may have to keep it.
You should never have been
jealous of me, Bendrix.
I did Sarah a great disservice when
I married her. I realize that now.
I'm not the sort that makes a lover.
She wanted someone like you.
I'm not sure it's as simple as that.
If you don't mind me asking...
I'd like you there
when the time comes.
It may not come, Henry.
You, of all people, don't believe
in miracles, Bendrix.
No, but Sarah does.
You see, I'd always believed that
I'd be the one to die first...
and that Sarah would
know what to do.
Are you at a loss, Henry?
I am quite.
And it would save you a bit
if you moved in with us.
Sarah always said your books weren't
as successful as they should have been.
You could be there...
working in the daytime
while I'm at the ministry.
And at night...
we could both...
And so I moved to the north side
of the common...
and, oddly enough,
I felt instantly at home.
Can I help you, father?
- I've come about Mrs. Mlles.
- She's indisposed.
You mean she's ill.
Don't you?
Yes, I suppose I do.
She's been to see me several times, and
I know she'd like to see me before...
She's left word with me,
she's not to be disturbed.
Is her husband here?
No.
She told me about you.
I know she did.
I'm the lover, father.
Who was that?
The postman.
What did he bring?
He had the wrong address.
How odd for a postman.
You know what happened that day?
You thought I was dead and I wasn't.
No, darling.
Something happened in that room.
There were the same walls around me...
the same sunlight coming in
through the window.
But nothing would ever
be the same again.
You can't believe this, Sarah.
But it's true.
I never loved anyone as I loved you.
Then when you came through that door
with blood on your face...
another kind of love came with you.
And I caught belief like a disease.
I fell into belief like I'd...
fallen in love.
And I tried to fight it...
but I haven't any fight left.
It wasn't the postman, was it?
No, it wasn't.
Dear Maurice, you can't
go on fighting.
It's only love, after all.
So you're taking her.
But you haven't got me yet.
I don't want your peace
and your love.
I wanted Sarah for a lifetime...
and you're taking her from me.
So I hate you, God.
I hate you as though you existed.
You have to help me, Bendrix.
I can't.
I will.
I can't live in a world,
where she's gone.
I'll help you.
I would have taken care of all
the arrangements if I'd known.
Surely you disapprove of cremation?
I would've arranged a Catholic burial.
She wasn't a Catholic,
was she, Henry?
We recognize the baptism of desire.
She said things that seemed
like prayers.
We've made the arrangements.
We can't alter things now.
You don't want talk.
The notice in the Times.
No. Oh, no.
If you'd come a little sooner,
father. Please don't think...
I think nothing bad of you.
Perhaps me?
Don't worry, Mr. Bendrix. Nothing
you can do will affect her now.
She was a good woman.
She wasn't. She could put
the blinkers on any man.
She deceived you, her husband and me.
She was a consummate liar.
- You've no right.
- Let him rave.
Don't give me your pity!
Keep it for your confessional!
You can find me when you want me.
I don't want you.
I'm no Sarah.
- Sorry, father.
- No need to be.
You see, I know when a man is in pain.
I'm not in pain, father.
I'm in hate.
I hate Sarah because she was a tart
to your mumbo-jumbo.
I hate Henry because she stuck to him.
And I hate you
and your imaginary God...
...because you took her away
from all of us.
You are a good hater.
To hell with all of you!
I'm sorry, Henry.
The thing is, Bendrix...
I always knew.
I knew she was with someone.
But I never thought you.
But the odd thing is...
I'm glad it was.
It's a sad pleasure to see you here.
Bygones are always bygones.
Do you always follow your people
as far as this?
She was a very fine lady, sir.
At the cocktail party, she handed
me a glass of sherry.
Was it South African sherry?
I wouldn't know, sir.
There weren't many like her.
My boy, now, he's always
speaking of her.
How is your boy, Parkis?
He's exceptionally well, sir,
though he's a bit upset today.
He imagined she'd be buried
a Catholic.
And why would he think that?
Young boys, sir, they get these ideas.
Though I have to admit, even
I can't explain it.
Explain what?
On the day of her assignation,
she walked him to a tube.
She thought he was lost, gave him
a coin and kissed him on his cheek...
on his afflicted cheek, sir.
And over the weeks that followed,
his affliction gradually went away.
I tried to keep him rational,
but he swears it was because of her.
Say hello to Mr. Bendrix, Lance.
Hello, sir.
I wrote at the start that this
was a diary of hate.
I hated you as though you existed.
Now I am tired of hating.
But you're still there.
So your cunning is infinite.
You used my hate to win
my acknowledgment.
And I've only one prayer left.
Dear God, forget about me.
Look after her and Henry.