I think she cried at my funeral.
I don't mean to brag about it or anything,
but I'm pretty sure she did.
Sometimes I can picture her talking about me
to some guy she feels really close to.
You're never going
to see him again, you know?
How they lowered me
into the grave
all pathetic and shriveled up,
like a melted chocolate bar
or something.
About how we never
actually got a chance.
Then the guy fucks her real nice...
a fuck that's all about
making her feel better.
Soon after I killed myself,
I found a job here at Kamikaze Pizza.
It's not a great job, but it'll do for a while.
The manager was cool enough
to hook me up with a place to live, too,
with this Austrian guy named Erik.
You did it again, Zia.
Did what?
Don't play dumb. You promised.
If you're going to live in this apartment,
you have to sit while you piss.
That. I'm sorry. I forgot.
How in the world you forget
something like that?
Sit, sit, sit.
Who could think
of a better punishment, really?
Everything's the same here.
It's just a little worse.
I've thought about suicide again,
but I haven't tried it.
I didn't want to end up
in a bigger shit hole than this one.
Yeah, I was missing Desiree.
I even had a feeling
that this whole suicide thing
just made me miss her
and love her more.
But... who knows?
Maybe you just need a drink.
Hi.
Listen, my friend Rachel and I,
we play this game
where we try to figure out
how people off themselves.
We were just guessing about you.
How'd you do it?
Three points for me!
That's an extremely rude question to ask.
Precisely.
That's what the game's all about.
I see. What about you?
Me?
No, no, no, no, no.
Look at him.
He can't stop burping.
It's definitely drowning.
No, I'm telling you,
look at the bluish face.
It's got to be gas.
Go over and ask him.
No. I don't know about this one.
- He seems ill-humored.
- No, no, you got to...
Why don't you try it with me?
Do you know this guy?
I'll bet you girls a beer you won't guess.
Tania, look who's here.
We'll be right back.
Right back.
I will tell you something.
Whenever a chick says
"I'll be right back,"
write them off, man.
They always end up leaving
with some retarded big-Joe guy.
So what was it?
What was what?
How did you, uh,
you know, off yourself?
Oh, that.
Let me go, lovely
Let me go
You guys suck!
Suck big time!
Get off the stage!
Fuck it all!
Jesus! Go home, man!
Boo!
You offed with the guitar?
Sure, I did.
On stage, man.
It was wild.
Iggy Pop almost came to see that gig.
No way.
It's true.
I live with my parents
and my kid brother Kostya.
You're fucking with me.
I'm not fucking with you.
I've never heard of
a whole family here before.
Mom...
offed because she was
missing Russia a lot.
And my father, he just didn't feel
like going on without her.
But what really did it for him
was my little brother turning out to be gay.
And your kid brother?
- Kostya?
- Kostya.
I guess he had it in his genes, man.
That's the craziest thing
I've ever heard, man.
When, uh, Kostya came here,
my father...
a man who wouldn't cry...
if you dropped 10-pound
sledgehammer on his foot.
Hugged kid, though,
and cried like baby. No shit.
Wow.
We have to kill those germs.
- For borscht...
- We have a saying in Russia.
How much you eat,
that's how old you are.
My grandpa, before
he'd hire anybody,
he'd feed them a free meal.
- Those who ate the most...
- Whoa.
...that's the ones
he hired, 'cause...
Those were the best workers.
Are you trying
to hire me or something?
How about
doing the dishes after dinner?
Kostya, no.
You know, Zia, dishwashing was Eugene's
first job in America.
No way.
I did a lot of shit.
Last job I had before I offed
was waiting tables.
I thought it was the band thing.
I had to eat, too.
You know, I wish
we were there for Eugene.
You see, Zia, all of us,
we were always together.
First in Russia,
then in America, now here.
When lvan and I came here and left our boys
alone, they just couldn't make...
Mom, that's all over now.
Yeah.
Where are you from, Zia?
Uh, New Jersey.
Oh. What about your parents?
Uh, it's... it's a long story.
It's not... Basically, at the end,
- I hadn't talk to them in a while.
- Zia, it's okay.
They hadn't talked to each other.
It is, yeah.
Nyet.
Not every family is lucky like we are.
That's true.
But all of us being together...
You know,
I'd be here a long time ago
if it weren't for Eugene.
Yeah? How come?
I was 10.
We had these soccer finals.
I was the goalie for my school.
Eugene!
Don't you hear I'm jamming?
How is it possible
for the better team to lose?
We didn't deserve to!
The ball just wouldn't get in!
And they won it in the finals!
So what's the point of living
when life is so unfair
and everything?
I'm just telling you this because you're
the smartest person I know.
If you don't give me one
good reason to keep living
and tell me what's the meaning of life,
I'm gonna do this.
Step down from the table.
No. First tell me.
Step down from the table,
and I'll tell you.
He just smacked you?
Yeah.
I don't exactly know what he was trying
to tell me when he did it,
but it worked fine
up until a couple months ago.
You know, when I see
you guys like this,
it kind of makes me
miss my parents,
even though most of the time
they just kind of freaked me out.
You know...
why didn't we move in together earlier?
'Cause we didn't know
it'd be this fun.
Yeah.
Oh, God, I love those things.
These what? These?
Who? Ophelia?
Desiree.
Whatever. An ex-girlfriend from an ex-life.
Listen, tonight when we go out,
man, you got to promise...
No, no, no. Eugene, I'm not going out
tonight or any other night.
- What?
- It just makes me depressed.
So what are you going to do?
Kill yourself?
I don't know. Maybe.
As if anything would make you happy.
I love you.
- I love you.
- You do?
Did you finish my cottage cheese?
Zia, did you finish my cottage cheese?
Calm down, Erik. I'll buy you
some more cottage cheese.
No. That's not the point.
I was planning on having some right now.
Don't you have a plan B
or something?
Zia, you do it all the time!
All right! All right!
I'll go get some more
cottage cheese.
Zia?
I was hoping we'd run into
each other sooner or later.
Brian, what are you doing here?
Same as everyone else.
Only it's got a little something to do with you.
Oh, yeah?
Did you come all the way here
to get the 200 bucks I owe you?
Ha ha. You were always a million laughs.
But, no, that's not it.
You know how people say that
suicides happen in threes?
Well, there's something to that.
Hey, is this cheese any good?
Uh, my roommate likes it.
You know, when people start
offing themselves around you,
you start asking yourself,
what makes me so different?
You know?
What's keeping me alive?
Then it hit me like a mallet.
I don't have the answers.
Too much sodium.
But I think it was Desiree's suicide
that really hit me.
- D-Desiree's what?
- Yeah, Desiree's.
She offed herself about a month after you.
I figured you'd know that.
- No.
- Hey!
What about the 200 you owe me?
I still want that.
So I'm saying I got a pretty good idea
she's not in the city.
Call it, you know, intuition or whatever.
Listen, man, worst-case scenario,
we just take a ride, right?
Who, we?
All right.
Let me put it this way.
Since you got here,
how many times did you get laid, man?
- Why?
- Just a question.
Actually laid?
Yes.
- None, I think.
- You think?
None. But what's that got
to do with any of this?
Plenty. 'Cause your sperm count is so high,
you think you're having
an out-of-body experience
like nobody in the whole
fucking universe, man.
Eugene.
Sperm count too high?
That's a crock.
Listen, man, just let me borrow the car.
You don't have to do anything else.
Don't... Don't get so touchy
on me all of a sudden.
All I said is not good enough reason
for me to go.
Listen, you know what?
Forget Desiree.
I got another reason for you to go.
Give it a shot.
You got anything better to do?
I mean, what's the big deal?
It's just the headlights, right?
You wouldn't
believe how many times
I've tried to have it fixed.
You're telling me this now?
I mean, this means we can't
drive at night. At all.
We'll stop somewhere
before it gets dark.
We'll just get them fixed.
It's on me. I'll pay for it.
If you insist.
But I'll bet you a beer it can't be fixed.
Let's get some music, man.
What is this? These work, right?
- Oh, shit.
- What?
Anything that goes underneath that seat,
forget about it.
Is there a hole or something?
Yeah.
No. It's, uh...
Kind of.
It's more like... I guess you'd say black hole
or a... a... a Bermuda Triangle.
You know, things just
disappear on you.
That's not very good.
What is it?
- It's my old band.
- Really?
I had it in my pocket when I offed.
Take that for a sec.
Oh, man, that's worse
than I remember.
What are you talking about? I like it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's not bad at all.
Mike's Car Shop.
Perfect timing, huh?
I'll bet you a beer they can't fix it.
You're on, man.
Uh, okay.
Um, uh, it's broken.
And so I don't... I don't...
I'm not sure what it is that's wrong.
But Mike is my... is my boss,
and he's an absolute genius.
We're gonna get it fixed.
You guys just wait right here.
Okay? Okay?
Hey, see that car?
It's been cruising back and forth
since we got here.
I saw it five times already.
It's a taxicab, Eugene.
Think, man.
Who the fuck would need taxi here?
I don't... I don't know.
What are you trying to say?
Look at the driver.
- Why?
- He's Arab.
You've never seen
an Arab taxi driver before?
Oh, sure, I did.
But not since I offed.
Connect the dots.
Arabs, suicides.
Doesn't that freak you out
even a little bit?
No, man. You sound
like a fucking, uh,
Homeland Security agent.
I mean, you forget where we are.
He's dead already.
We're dead.
Everybody here is dead.
He's not gonna try anything.
Nobody gives a shit here.
We're all immigrants now, man.
Then why is he looking
at me like that?
'Cause you're staring at him
like you need a fucking taxicab.
Quit looking at him. He'll go away.
Oh, shoot.
It looks like we're staying here tonight.
Hey, boy, how you doin'? You're pretty.
Hey, Jimmy, why don't you
go start this thing up?
Let's hear this beauty moan.
Well... Moan?
No, no. We just want to...
The headlights.
Oh, you need a...
You need an exhaust system,
valves got to be adjusted.
Oh, what a bitch
of a fuel pump you got in there.
No, no, no, no. No, no.
We just want to fix the headlights.
Honey, are you home?
Honey?
He hasn't slept a wink
since we got here.
We'll fix your headlights by tomorrow.
- Get them fixed by tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
Yeah. Tomorrow.
Fucking shift stick.
This is the last time I sleep in the car.
Yeah.
Where are my shades?
I dr... I dropped them.
Man, I told you to be
careful about that, man.
- I know, I know.
- God damn it.
I was, Eugene. It's... It's so bright.
I didn't mean to drop them
under there.
I gotta... I gotta piss, man.
Aah! God damn!
What the hell?
Morning, boys.
Nothing like a good
night's sleep, huh?
These headlights
are giving me a headache.
But you give me a day or two,
I'll have it fixed up
once and for all and forever.
That's how Mike does it.
Once and all and for... forever.
Wait. Look at this,
look at this, look at this.
Looks like you owe me
first beer of the day.
I told you, man. No one can fix
the headlights in this car.
You asleep?
Yeah, man, I'm asleep.
You're missing a lot of beautiful shit.
Can't believe you lost my shades.
Holy shit.
Oh, geez!
What the... Wait. What... Oh...
Eugene, what?
What?
Afternoon, lady.
Where you guys going?
East-ish.
East-ish?
You guys don't have any clue
where you're going, do you?
Well, you haven't been here very long, right?
Why's that?
'Cause if anybody here had a clue,
we wouldn't be here in the first place.
True.
I am pretty new.
Actually, I've been hitchhiking
ever since I got here.
How come?
Because I'm looking
for the people in charge.
- People in charge?
- Yeah.
Just where do you think you are?
Some kind of country club
where you can just walk
into the main office?
Tell me, please,
when you were still living,
did you ever try to go looking for God?
No. But I really didn't have
any reason to back then.
And what reason do you have now?
I mean, you know,
are you just sorry you offed?
You, uh, changed your mind?
Because, you know, if that's the case,
and you're just waiting
for visa back home...
- Eugene, Eugene, Eugene.
- What? What?
What's your name?
Mikal.
- What's your name?
- Zia.
- Eugene.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thanks.
So you're trying to leave?
You don't like it here?
Are you joking?
Do you guys like it here?
Who the hell likes being stuck in a place
where you can't even smile?
It's hot as balls. Everybody's an asshole.
I just want to go home.
- I don't know.
- I like it.
Yeah, better than sleeping
in the car, man.
All right.
I'll go get the cashier.
I like that it has a window right here.
It's nice.
You want to try it out?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
I think I'm gonna go
see how Zia's doing.
I wonder if people who die normally
end up with no stars.
I really miss the stars.
You get used to it.
I don't want to get used to it.
I want to go home.
This guy who gave me
a ride the other day,
he said that he actually heard rumors
about the people in charge.
Um, apparently they wear
white outfits or something.
That's a crock of shit... white outfits.
He was just trying to get into your pants.
No, he wasn't.
He said he thought I had a really good case.
Oh, and what makes
your case so special,
if you don't mind me asking?
That I got here by mistake.
Well, we all got here by some mistake
one way or another.
And believe me,
you have as much chance
at finding your folks in white
as Zia has to find his dead princess.
You don't know that.
No, you don't. I bet he'll find her.
Yeah. Besides, I got a hunch
she's not that far away.
Wherever she is,
I bet she found someone by now.
Probably some black guy
who hanged himself by his dick.
It wouldn't matter, Eugene.
You know, I was thinking.
Yeah?
If you were to ever cheat on me...
make sure you do it
with somebody who's really pretty.
What are you...
What are you talking about?
I'm not gonna cheat on you.
Why do you say that?
I know, baby.
Hey, Eugene, do you mind if I drive?
I'll get us there in half the time.
Get us where?
Over there.
Oh, there.
All right, then.
I'm not sitting in the back.
Why not?
'Cause everybody knows
guy in the back seat doesn't have a cock.
- What?
- That's a fact.
If the guy in the back seat
had a cock,
he wouldn't be back there
in the first place.
Well, l... I mean, I got a cock, man.
So how can... I'm not...
Mik, do you have a cock?
Yeah, I have a cock.
A big fat one.
I'm looking for the people in charge
because I'm here by mistake.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I've been looking for a while.
I'm looking for a girl named Desiree.
Short blonde hair,
about this tall.
I'm not sure what you're
trying to accomplish is completely legal.
- Well, that's very...
- Can I see some I. D?
We're looking for the people in charge
of this place
because I've only been
here a couple weeks
and I got here by mistake.
Did I show you...
Thanks, "Ociffer," but we...
The people in charge.
- Nyet, Mom.
- P. I.C.
About this tall.
Her name's Desiree. She's really pretty.
When there's a trap
Set up for you
In every corner of your room
And so
The only way to go
Is
Through the roof
Underground
And as we crossing border after border
We realize the differences now
It's underdogs who
And if you want it, too
You'll always have to make your own fun
Hey, man, you need
to wipe these off for me.
# The local cultures
are dying and dying #
# The product growers
are buying and buying #
Man, are you doing that
intentionally to hurt me?
No. No. It's... It's not my fault.
I just wanted you to clean those off.
- I know. I was cleaning.
- That's a hole. I told you.
You want to see if my hat
drops down the hole?
No, I'm not gonna
drop your hat in the hole!
Guys, guys, guys, guys!
Here's my tobacco.
See if that goes down.
Guys, guys, please stop bickering.
Please?
Eugene, there's a diner right there.
Will you stop?
Good. Perf... Perfect timing.
And you, don't touch my stuff no more.
- You handed me the shades, man.
- Don't touch my stuff no more.
Yes, Mama.
Didn't he already talk
to his mom this morning?
Yeah, but, supposedly,
that's, uh, normal in Russia.
I don't think that's normal anywhere.
Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna go get some smokes.
Do you want anything?
Next time you grab my ass,
I'm going to tell your mom, asshole, okay?
Okay?
All I'm saying is neither of us
have scored with her, you know?
I don't know about that.
The other night, uh, she said
she thought you were cute.
Cute?
That's what they say about a puppy.
The only thing worse
is "good friend" or "nice person."
In plain English it means
"I'll leech off you as long as I can,
but don't even think
about getting into my pants."
Yeah, well, you might be right about that.
Of course I'm right.
I say we get rid of her while we still can.
I mean, look.
Look at what we're losing out on
because of her.
Yeah, I don't know.
The whole "people in charge" thing
is a little weird.
See? That's what I'm talking about.
Shoot.
Look, fuck her, man.
Okay? That's what I'm talking about.
She's eavesdropping
on her friends now.
Where'd you get those shades?
What shades?
Mikal bought us shades, man.
Sweet of her.
But it is good to be on our own, you know?
Eugene, you know, I love you, man,
but you can be an asshole.
What do you care?
We're looking for Irene, right?
Yeah, we're looking for Irene.
All right. Then let's look for Irene.
Okay, just calm down.
If you just comply,
everything's gonna be just fine.
On what charges?
Breaking that sign is
a clear case of vandalism.
That's absolutely retarded.
- You're handcuffing me, too?
- Yes.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm placing you under arrest.
Hands behind your back.
I was just trying to make this place
a little bit less depressing.
What's the big deal with that?
This is so dramatic.
You don't even need to be doing this.
- No. Wait, Officer.
- What the hell is your problem?
That's my sister. What's going on?
Your sister?
Yeah, yeah. What's going on?
I'm afraid your sister's been arrested.
Arrested?
Wait. Can I talk to you for a minute?
What have you got to say?
l... I mean, she's only
been here a few mo...
- You know, how long you been here?
- Some time.
First of all, she just got here.
Well, you remember what it's like
those first couple months, right?
I mean, the no-smiling thing's
really getting to her.
Nobody's got any good humor
or anything like that.
Well, I can turn
my head away this once.
Yeah?
Ma'am, you better watch your behavior.
You bet, Officer.
You didn't have to do that.
Thank you.
What are you... You gonna...
Can we still give you a ride?
No, thanks. I think I'm headed
the other way.
Listen, l...
I'm sorry about all that back there.
It's...
We didn't mean that.
It's just Eugene's venting.
That's okay.
Doesn't matter.
I just want to...
We don't...
We don't mean that.
You know what?
It's probably gonna be hard
for me to get a ride
with you standing there, so...
Yeah. Probably right.
I hope you find what you're looking for.
Thank you.
I really do.
- Where were you, man?
- Guess who I just saw.
Who?
Mikal. She's right back there.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, man. You didn't
take out the nozzle?
You deal with this guy. I'm not into it.
What?
I'm sorry again.
Oh, it happens all the time.
At least twice a week.
- Really?
- It happens. See?
All these are already filled out.
Right here.
What's this here about, uh,
"What were you thinking
when the incident occurred?"
Exactly that.
Here I am again, buried in debt.
If pulling the trigger
didn't solve my problems,
what the hell will?
I was wondering if I
was too drunk to drive.
But the problem with you
is that you don't think it's fucked up
- to talk shit about me when I'm not there.
- I was kidding.
You were kidding?
You didn't know I was listening.
No, I didn't.
That's eavesdropping.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Whatever.
- Look, I found...
- Calm down, man.
- Look at this.
- Calm down. Relax.
It's her phone number. It's Desiree.
It's her phone number, her address,
everything. Look at that.
I spaced out because the man at pump 3
looked just like my ex-boyfriend.
Where is he?
He feels so close.
I knew she was close, man.
I told you, man. I felt it.
All right. What do you want to do?
You want to call her?
No, let's go over there.
That guy said it's
not very far from here.
Let's go, man. Let's go!
I told you, man.
You should buy her
some flowers at least.
Flowers would be nice, but l... l...
did you see the flowers in there?
Yeah.