MEDITERRANEAN SEA
60 MILES SOUTH OF MARSEILLES
SAILORS:
What a mess.
You've never seen a dead man before?
Put a blanket on him. Cover him.
I'm coming.
Be careful.
One minute. I'll be right there. Cover him.
BOURNE: What the hell
are you doing to me?
BOURNE: What are you doing?
Goddamn it! Where am I?
GIANCARLO: A boat! A fishing boat.
You were in the water.
We pulled you out.
BOURNE: What water?
GIANCARLO: You were shot. See?
There are the bullets.
GIANCARLO: Look, there is a number
for a bank. Why was it in your hip?
BOURNE: My hip?
- Why was it in your hip?
- My hip.
Yeah, in your hip under the skin.
BOURNE: Oh, God.
BOURNE: What are you doing with me?
GIANCARLO: You need to rest.
Please. Lie down.
I'm a friend. I'm your friend.
My name is Giancarlo.
Who are you?
GIANCARLO: What's your name?
What's your name?
BOURNE: I don't know.
BOURNE: Oh, God.
GIANCARLO: Lie down.
CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
LANGLEY, VIRGINIA
It's been confirmed, sir. Mission failed.
BOURNE:
Do you know who I am?
I do not know who I am.
BOURNE:
Tell me who I am.
If you know who I am...
Please stop messing around...
...and tell me.
GIANCARLO: If you want to eat, get in there.
BOURNE: Based on these charts,
I think I may have been closer to the coast.
What is this? You tie these knots?
GIANCARLO: So, it starts to come back?
BOURNE: No, it doesn't.
The knot's like everything else.
I found the rope and I did it.
Same way I can read.
I can write. I can add, subtract.
I can make coffee.
BOURNE: I can shuffle cards, play chess.
GIANCARLO: Yes, it will come back.
No, it's not coming back, goddamn it!
That's the point!
I'm down here looking through this,
all this shit!
For two weeks I'm down here.
It's not working.
I don't even know what to look for.
You need to rest. It will come back.
BOURNE: What if it doesn't come back?
We get in there tomorrow,
I don't even have a name.
It's not much,
but it should get you to Switzerland.
Thank you.
ZURICH COPS:
Can't you read the signs?
On your feet... let's go... right now.
The park is closed.
There's no sleeping in the park.
BOURNE: All right.
Let's see some identification.
BOURNE: No, I don't...
Come on... your papers.
I don't have any papers. I lost my...
I've lost them... my papers... they are lost.
Ok... let's go... put your hands up.
...I just need to sleep...
These people have threatened my family.
My babies.
So I'm telling you,
when the evidence is clear...
...I will have a nice story
for you to read about.
And all my friends out there,
you will read about yourselves.
If you want to play this game...
...after I have been reasonable,
I will show you.
That's Nykwana Wombosi speaking in Paris
the day before yesterday.
He was an irritation before he took power,
a problem...
...when he was in power,
and he's been a disaster for us in exile.
He's writing a book
about the Agency's history in Africa.
He's going to name names.
It's basically a shakedown.
He's demanding the Agency's help.
He wants us to put him back in power
in six months, or else.
This interview, and I'll make the tape
available to whoever wants it...
...he goes on to claim that he's just survived
an assassination attempt.
He says it's us. He says he's got proof.
The Director wants to know
if there's any truth...
...in this accusation.
I've already assured him there's nobody
that reckless on my senior staff.
ABBOTT: I was recalling a conversation
we had some time ago.
Talking about Treadstone.
I seem to remember Wombosi's name
might have come up.
I'm not sure what we're talking about.
Someone tried to take him out.
Tried and failed.
Was this Treadstone?
You're asking me a direct question?
Yes.
I thought you were never gonna do that.
What happened?
Well, we lost the communication
with our man.
This was almost two weeks ago.
CONKLIN: We've worked around the clock.
We've been sleeping down there.
We're doing everything we can.
ABBOTT: And you don't let me know this?
CONKLIN: You never wanted to before.
You never made a mistake before.
GEMEINSCHAFT BANK
ZURICH SWITZERLAND
What can I do for you?
Yes, I'm here about a numbered account.
If you just enter your account number here,
I'll direct you to an appropriate officer.
My name is Jason Bourne.
I live in Paris.
I'm trying to think...
How long's it been since I was here last?
I'm not sure.
It must be three weeks.
BOURNE: Yes, in Paris.
Do you have the number
for a Jason Bourne?
OPERATOR:
Yes. Would you like me to connect you?
BOURNE: Yes, please.
BOURNE:
This is 46990384.
Leave a message at the beep.
BOURNE: I'm an American.
Okay.
GUARD: Hold it.
MARINE 1: You've no jurisdiction here.
MARINE 1: Hold it there. Okay?
MARIE: No.
Excuse me. No.
This is not my current address, okay?
This was my address until two days ago,
when I started standing in line.
Now I lose my apartment, okay?
That means no address, no phone,
no money, no time.
- And I still have no visa!
- Miss Kreutz, please.
CLERK: I must ask you
to keep your voice down.
MARIE: Excuse me. But where's the guy
that I talked to last week?
Every week it's a new person.
How am I supposed to...
I don't know who you saw last week.
MARIE: Let me help you. I'm sure I have it.
Hang on.
CLERK:
Could I have your attention for a moment?
MARIE: I have it right here. Just look at it.
CLERK: You staged an effort to circumvent
the immigration laws of the United States.
MARIE: This is a student visa now.
It's not about a green card anymore.
It's very different.
CLERK: It's not a menu. You don't just...
MARIE: I brought all this proof.
DISPATCHER: Potential suspect...
Help in assault incident.
You! Red bag! The red bag!
SECURITY CHIEF:
Stop right there! Put your hands up!
MAN: I'm on it.
SECURITY CHIEF: Move it! Now!
Now! Move!
Alpha Unit, take the back stairs
and work your way up. Bravo...
SECURITY CHIEF: Move in! Move in!
MARINE 1: Okay, clear!
SECURITY CHIEF: Suspect is...
BRAVO LEADER: Moving up staircase.
Proceeding to second floor.
SECURITY CHIEF: Alpha Unit, you're clear.
MARINE 2: Move! Move!
SECURITY CHIEF:
All Units, target may have a radio.
Go to Code 77. Over.
Code 77, copy.
MARINE 3: The floor! Down!
MARINE 4: Clear!
MARINE 2: Go. Move up.
CONKLIN: He's in Zurich now? Right now?
ZORN: Yes. It just came in.
- They're sure it's him?
- Yes. He went to the bank.
Our source at the bank, that's who called.
CONKLIN: Come on.
But he's got to assume
we're watching the bank, right?
CONKLIN: I don't know. Come on.
I mean, he cleaned out the box.
He left a gun. What does that mean?
I said I don't know!
I liked it better when I thought he was dead.
What are you looking at?
I heard you inside.
MARIE: What?
The consulate. I heard you talking.
I thought maybe we could help each other.
How's that?
BOURNE:
You need money. I need a ride out of here.
I'm not running a car service. Thank you.
I'll give you $10,000 to drive me to Paris.
What, do you think I'm a fool?
You'd be a fool not to take it.
MARIE: Is this a joke? Some kind of scam?
BOURNE: No, it's no scam.
BOURNE: I'll give you another $10,000
when we arrive.
MARIE: Jesus.
- Is that for you?
- Look. You drive, I pay. It's that simple.
I got enough trouble, okay?
BOURNE: Okay.
Can I have my money back?
CONKLIN: All right, go. Keep going.
CONKLIN: Go.
- There! Wait!
- No, it's got to be near the end.
Come on, folks! We caught a break here!
Let's go!
COMM TECH 1: Okay, I'm up.
COMM TECH 1: We're getting grids.
Airline, train, hotels, hospitals.
- Who's getting the address? The street?
- Gemensheidt.
RESEARCH TECH 1: Here we go.
I think I got it.
ZORN: Is it him?
RESEARCH TECH 2: Unreal.
RESEARCH TECH 1: This is 38 minutes ago.
ZORN: Zurich police are looking
for an American carrying a red bank bag.
ZORN: He just tore up the embassy and
put two cops in the hospital last night.
Get everybody up. Do it now.
I want them all activated.
Wait. All of them? At the same time?
You heard me.
I want Bourne in a body bag by sundown.
CONKLIN: All right, let's get a map up here!
Come on, folks! Let's work it!
COMM TECH 1:
The grids are getting updated.
MARIE: Which was fine with me
because I was ready.
After six months in Amsterdam,
you're not sure...
...if you've been there 20 minutes or years,
you know.
So I went. I took all the money I had.
I went in with friends...
...we took over this really cool surf shop
outside Biarritz, right by the water.
It was amazing.
It was just amazing for about three months,
until it turned out that this...
...jerk who had fronted us the lease
was actually shining everyone on and...
And what?
What do you mean "what"? Listen to me.
I've been speed-talking
for about 60 kilometres now.
I talk when I'm nervous.
I mean, I talk like this when I'm nervous.
- I'm gonna shut up now.
- No, don't do that.
I haven't talked to anybody in a while.
Yeah, but we're not talking. I'm talking.
You've said,
like, 10 words since we left Zurich.
Well, listening to you, it's relaxing.
I haven't slept in a while and...
And I've had this headache.
It's like a constant thing in my head...
...and it's just starting
to move to the background...
...so keep going.
Really, if you want, please keep talking.
Okay.
What kind of music do you like?
What do you like? Come on.
- You know what? Never mind.
- No, it's fine. Tell me.
What do you want to listen to?
I don't know.
Come on, it's not that hard.
What do you like? Tell me.
I don't know.
Who pays $20,000 for a ride to Paris?
Fuck it.
I can't remember anything
that happened before two weeks ago.
- Lucky you.
- No, I'm serious.
I don't know who I am.
I don't know where I'm going.
None of it.
MARIE: What? Like amnesia?
BOURNE: Yes.
MARIE: Amnesia.
Right.
- And that's the best angle of the courtyard?
- That's the only angle.
What do they have of the streets?
Or, you know, the area?
They must have something.
Hang on.
What is he doing?
Is it a game? Is he warning us?
Is it a threat?
RESEARCH TECH 1: Sir? Look at this.
- What's that?
- It's an angle of the street, a sort of alley.
Just enhance it.
Now, who the hell is that?
RESEARCH TECH 2: Marie Helena Kreutz.
She's 26, born outside Hanover.
Her father was a welder.
He died in '87.
We still don't have the mother.
The grandmother, she's still in Hanover.
It looks like she's the anchor
for this little domestic disaster.
And there's a stepbrother.
It's tough. The girl's a gypsy.
I mean, she pops up on the grid
here and there, but it's chaotic at best.
She paid some electric bills in Spain, '95.
Had a phone in her name
for three months in Belgium, '96.
No taxes, no credit.
I don't like her. I want to go deep.
Get a phone log for Granny
and the half-brother.
Anybody we can cross-file.
I want to know every place she's slept
in the past six years.
Have Paris get these out in the field.
TREADSTONE SAFE HOUSE
PARIS, FRANCE
BOURNE: I'm not making this up.
These are real.
Okay.
Who has a safety deposit box full of...
...money and six passports and a gun?
BOURNE: Who has a bank account number
in their hip?
I come in here, and the first thing I'm doing
is I'm catching the sightlines...
...and looking for an exit.
I see the exit sign, too. I'm not worried.
MARIE: I mean, you were shot.
People do all kinds of weird
and amazing stuff when they are scared.
I can tell you the license plate numbers
of all six cars outside.
I know that our waitress is left-handed...
...and the guy sitting at the counter weighs
215 pounds and can handle himself.
I know the best place to look for a gun
is the cab of the grey truck outside.
At this altitude, I can run flat out for
a half-mile before my hands start shaking.
Now why would I know that?
How can I know that
and not know who I am?
Hey.
BOURNE: I slept.
- I can't believe it.
- Yeah, well, you were tired.
I haven't slept.
Oh, here. For $20,000,
I like to throw in breakfast.
Did you stop for gas?
You were pretty out of it.
So, do you think there's,
like, a family waiting for you?
I don't know.
I've thought about it.
MARIE: Is that it?
104.
Yeah, that's the address.
No, keep going. Keep going.
- Okay. Where?
- Just take a left. Pull in over here.
MARIE: Okay.
MARIE: So, this is it, right?
Yeah, I guess.
God, I don't recognise any of this.
Okay. I should go.
Jason?
Oh, God. The money. Right.
Yeah.
BOURNE: Here.
Thank you. Okay.
Thanks for the ride.
Anytime.
Well, you could come up.
I mean, or you can wait here.
- I can go check it out. But you could wait.
- Oh, no, no.
BOURNE: You could wait.
With you, you would probably
just forget about me if I stayed here.
How could I forget about you?
You're the only person I know.
Yeah. That's true.
I guess you're not home.
Monsieur Bourne, there you are.
CONCIERGE:
Monsieur Bourne, I was wondering...
I haven't seen you.
Uh, here I am.
BOURNE:
I think I forgot my key.
Hello?
MARIE: Are you sure this is all yours?
BOURNE: I guess.
BOURNE: This is my kitchen.
MARIE: Any clues?
BOURNE:
I think I'm in the shipping business.
So it's all coming back?
Do you mind if I use the bathroom?
Sure.
Okay.
Yeah. Hello? Hello?
OPERATOR: Yes, sir, Hotel Regina, Paris.
How may I direct your call?
BOURNE: Yeah, you're in Paris?
OPERATOR: Yes, sir.
I'm looking for a guest there.
A Jason Bourne.
OPERATOR: One moment, please.
BOURNE: Thank you.
OPERATOR: I'm afraid I have no one
by that name registered.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait! No, no. Are you there? Hello?
OPERATOR: Sir?
BOURNE: Can you check
another name for me, please?
Here, bear with me one second.
BOURNE: John Kane. Kane with a "K."
OPERATOR: One moment, sir.
Thank you.
MANAGER: You call about Monsieur Kane?
John Michael Kane?
BOURNE: Yeah, that's right.
MANAGER: You are a friend of his?
BOURNE: Yeah.
MANAGER:
I have some very bad news for you, sir.
I'm sorry to tell you this, but Monsieur Kane
has passed away almost two weeks ago.
There was an accident. On the motorway.
Apparently, he was killed instantly.
Really, I'm terribly sorry
to be the one to tell you this.
When they came for his things,
it was made known for us, you see?
BOURNE: Who came?
MANAGER: His brother.
Did his brother leave a number
or a way to get in touch with him?
MANAGER: I think not.
No, I'm sorry.
MARIE: Jason? There's no hot water.
It's freezing.
I'll go try the water in the kitchen.
Why don't you just stay in the bathroom?
I'll see if I can get it hot.
Yeah, it's really cold in here, too.
MARIE: The water is still cold.
Yeah, it's cold in the kitchen, too.
I got it running, though.
So...
What?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
MARIE: What is it?
Something wrong?
MARIE: Jason!
BOURNE: Open that. Tell me what's inside.
Who are you?
MARIE: Oh, my God.
God.
BOURNE: Answer me! Who are you?
- He's got my picture!
- All right. Hang on.
MARIE: This is Zurich, yesterday!
BOURNE: Don't...
I don't know. Where did you get this?
BOURNE: Stay there.
MARIE: How did you get my picture?
MARIE: Where did you get this from?
How did you get my... My God!
I'll do this! You stay there. Stay there!
- Where are your shoes? Get your shoes.
- Sure. Yeah, sure.
He went out the window.
Why would someone do that?
BOURNE: We can't stay here. It's not safe.
I can get us out of here, but we got to go.
We got to go right now.
Okay, look, you can wait.
You can wait for the cops. It's okay.
You just wait for them to get here.
But I can't. I got to go.
Marie?
BOURNE: Marie?
BOURNE: Quiet. Be quiet.
Don't look.
OPERATIVE: Code in.
NICKY: Alpha 37509.
ZORN: Yeah.
Hang on.
Bourne went to Paris, to the apartment.
CONKLIN: We got him? Tell me.
NICKY: He killed our man.
CONKLIN: What? In the apartment?
NICKY: Yeah.
CONKLIN: Well, you got to clean that up.
NICKY: No, I can't clean it up.
NICKY: There's a body in the street.
CONKLIN: So?
There's police. This is Paris.
CONKLIN: Put up the scanners.
Get as much radio information as you can.
Okay, you stay here.
I'm gonna go find a place for this money.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
BOURNE: Hey, I told you to stay in the car.
Jesus Christ. I told you to stay in the car.
I needed a drink.
I didn't think you would come back.
Look, you got to go to the cops.
Right now.
You got to go before this gets any worse.
MARIE: By myself?
BOURNE: It's gonna be okay.
You're gonna take my passport, okay?
You show this to them.
You have that picture, you have the $20,000.
You tell them everything that happened.
They'll believe you.
They have to believe you.
Marie, you can't just sit here.
It's not safe here.
MARIE: Safe?
This is from inside the embassy.
- Who can do this? This is from yesterday.
- I don't know.
MARIE: How can they know we're together?
BOURNE: I'm trying to do the right thing.
BOURNE: That's all.
MARIE: Right?
How'll you make this right
by sending me there alone?
You think I want you to go to the cops?
That's good?
- You want to go, fine.
- If you go, I run!
- You tell them what happened!
- I don't know what happened!
I don't know who this guy was
or about that picture!
I don't know who I am!
Look, I'm...
You think I'm trying to burn you.
I'm trying to do the right thing.
Nobody does the right thing.
Look, I can't run with you. I can't.
We run, I got to live like this. I got to...
I don't even know who I'm hiding from.
These people know who I am.
Yeah, I got to stay here.
I got to figure this out.
So figure it out.
You take care of this car?
What do you mean?
The tires felt a little splashy
on the way over here.
MARIE: It pulls a little to the right.
Last chance, Marie.
BOURNE: So...
MARIE: What?
BOURNE: We got a bump coming up.
Turn your head away. Turn your head away.
We can never come back to this car.
You understand?
Okay, we're gonna clean it out,
and I'll wipe it down, and we walk away.
- That's it.
- Okay.
Okay. And I'll find a place for us to rest.
And I got to think.
Do you have a hat or a scarf or something?
- For my hair?
- Yeah. Just until we can change it.
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Okay.
HOFFENMEIN MORGUE - PARIS, FRANCE
It's not him.
This man was not shot.
CONKLIN: What do you have?
NICKY: Wombosi went to the morgue.
He saw the body. He didn't buy it.
Where is he now?
NICKY: I told you, I'm not staffed for this.
CONKLIN: Where is he? Right now!
Where's Wombosi?
NICKY: They were leaving the morgue.
They just left.
ZORN: Sir, what do you want to do?
I need to get the bottle.
BOURNE: Hey.
You already cleaned the room?
I wiped the whole place down
for fingerprints.
Can I walk around
or is it gonna leave any footprints?
You can walk around. It's no problem.
But we'll just keep track
of everything we touch.
I think it's best if we leave a room,
that we don't leave a trail.
Why? Where are we going?
BOURNE: I need to go to the hotel
where John Michael Kane stayed.
The Hotel Regina.
If I was him,
then they're gonna have some records.
We need that hotel bill.
MARIE: Okay.
It gets slightly complicated, though.
Because you're dead.
BOURNE: Right.
BODYGUARD: Please.
WOMBOSl: They want war, we'll make war.
If they want to kill me,
they better kill me the first time.
They better kill me dead.
They better kill me when I'm in my sleep.
BODYGUARD: Listen to me.
We need these people.
It's hard enough getting people
that we know to help us.
BODYGUARD: We must be careful.
We?
No, you.
You need to bring me back
that bastard kid's head...
...put it in front of this house,
and show them the war we're fighting.
But that is precisely...
BODYGUARD: Nykwana!
BOURNE: We'll give the watch
a reference check before we go.
MARIE: Okay.
What's the pay phone number?
MARIE: 616-2468.
Exits?
There's three.
Service at the back,
side goes to the street past the shops...
...front is the best.
If I think I'm being followed, I walk out
with the bag over my right shoulder.
And if there's no taxi?
I keep on walking,
don't look back until you make contact.
MARIE: What?
We need this, right?
Okay.
BOURNE: I need distances.
You walk in, you pick a spot.
Some midpoint in the lobby.
Count your steps to that spot,
and then remember that number.
Because after I call you,
I can get you moving.
You understand?
I also need a head count.
How many people from when you walk in
until you get to the desk.
How many hotel employees are there?
And obviously security.
And it might not be that easy
to see who they are.
So I'll call you, you give me the layout,
and we'll take it from there.
OPERATOR: Regina.
Yes, the house phone in the lobby.
BOURNE: What happened?
MARIE: L...
BOURNE: Did something go wrong?
MARIE: I've got the records.
He, this guy at the front desk
was smiling at me.
So I thought, you know, all this trouble,
maybe it's easier to just ask for them.
BOURNE: You have the bill?
MARIE: He made me a photocopy.
You just asked for it?
I said I was Mr. Kane's personal assistant.
BOURNE: Okay. That's good thinking.
ZORN: Sir, can l...
ABBOTT: No.
ABBOTT: Wombosi was assassinated
in his house in the middle of Paris.
Yeah, we just heard.
It's him. It's Bourne. We're almost positive.
He had an assignment. He failed.
He obviously felt compelled
to finish the task.
ABBOTT: Jesus.
CONKLIN: We think he'll come back in now.
I mean, it's routine.
It's like behavioural software.
He's following a protocol.
Now that he's completed the mission,
we think he'll come back in.
They always do.
When?
ABBOTT: How long till he checks in?
ZORN: 24 hours.
ABBOTT: 24?
Yeah, it's usually something like that.
ABBOTT: Then what?
I told you we'd clean this up.
It will be clean.
BOURNE: I understand you're a dive shop,
but where are you located?
BOURNE: Marseilles?
BOURNE: What specifically does
your company supply?
DIVE SHOP EMPLOYEE: I am sorry.
What is your name, monsieur?
COP:
You've been here for three hours
and you still can't find a print?
CONKLIN: What?
ZORN: Paris police found the vehicle.
RAWLINS: You've reached Simon Rawlins
at Alliance Security, Maritime Division.
Paris office hours are
from 8.00 a. M. To 5.00 p. M.
BOURNE: I got a lead in Paris.
The rest were Marseilles,
and two out in Southampton.
- Paris? It's what?
- Alliance Security. Simon Rawlins.
I got a machine.
SECRETARY: Mr. Kane?
Mr. Kane!
SECRETARY: How are you?
BOURNE: I'm good. How are you?
Mr. Kane. Come right in.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
RAWLINS:
So, this is the PalmerJohnson tri-deck.
I'm assuming you're still in the market.
It's still the same vessel?
Yes.
So I'm Kane.
MARIE: They...
BOURNE: I had a meeting as Kane.
- They said...
- No. I'm definitely Kane.
I just had a meeting as Kane
and he knew me as Kane.
So I'm definitely Bourne.
I'm also just definitely Kane.
It's all just boats.
I got blueprints and cameras
and security systems.
I just found John Michael Kane's body.
In a morgue here in Paris.
But if you are John Michael Kane,
whose body do they have?
ATTENDANT: What was the name again?
BOURNE: Kane.
Kane.
BOURNE: John Michael Kane.
John Michael Kane.
Kane. It's number 121.
I want to see the body.
Our boss could come back.
We are not supposed to do that.
Come on.
Is this it? I mean, where is he?
ATTENDANT: I don't know.
What's going on?
This guy has come to see the American.
But the body has disappeared.
They came yesterday evening... his brother.
He's not in the register.
Who are you? What's going on?
- Where's the body that goes in here?
- I said someone came last night.
I know. Where'd they take the body?
Look, this is not a carnival, okay?
People call, they make an appointment,
follow the rules.
Everyone signs in and out.
This is a serious place. Serious work.
- It's not just to come in whenever you like!
- You're right. We didn't sign in.
BOSS: Get the hell out of here.
BOURNE: Fine. I'm just gonna go sign in.
BOSS: Okay, go.
BOURNE: Is this it?
BOSS: You can't take the book.
BOURNE: This is it?
It's okay. There's a pencil in here.
That's fine.
Honey, why don't you go wait outside?
Here it is.
BOSS: We can't have...
BOURNE: Okay.
MARIE: Jason, what just happened in there?
What are you looking for?
BOURNE: Nykwana Wombosi.
Wombosi went to the morgue to visit Kane.
See?
MARIE: So?
BOURNE: He's in the Alliance brochure.
BOURNE: Same guy.
This guy knows.
My French sucks. I can't...
It says something about a boat or...
I don't understand. What does it say?
You read it. Tell me. What?
It says that 3 weeks before he was killed,
Mr. Wombosi told police...
...that a man came onto his yacht,
five miles off the coast of Marseilles...
...and tried to kill him.
It says that he chased the man off the boat
and shot him twice in the back.
It says I'm an assassin.
Stop the car.
But no... you said Rue de I...
we're almost there.
Just right here, this is good.
I said stop.
MARIE: What's going on?
Well... what's going on?
MARIE: What the hell are you doing?
BOURNE: Go. Go.
MARIE: What are...
You gave me too much.
BOURNE: We're blown. Come on.
MARIE: Blown? What is "blown"?
Monsieur... your change, your change.
Sir, please... You can't stay here...
You have to leave.
BOURNE: Keep walking.
What do you think they're doing there?
They're on to the hotel.
- No. You don't know that.
- Trust me. Just keep walking.
Are you crazy? What are you doing now?
MARIE: Jason!
BOURNE: This is blown.
BOURNE: Marie?
MARIE: Get away.
BOURNE: Stop right there.
MARIE: Get away from me.
What are you gonna do? Kill me?
BOURNE: Marie.
MARIE: Is that next?
Listen, stay calm. Stay calm.
Whatever we do, we have to do it together.
- We have to be...
- We?
The only thing we had in common
was that neither of us knew who you were.
MARIE: We've passed that now.
BOURNE: Listen!
The police'll find us. The people who took
the picture in the embassy...
...who killed Wombosi,
they're gonna come here and kill us.
The people who you work for.
I will take you wherever you need to go.
I'll take you there. I'll leave you there.
You can do what you want.
You never have to see me again.
BOURNE: But not here.
If we stay here, we die.
Boy, great police work! Really brilliant!
Why don't they just hang out a banner
that says, "Don't come back!"
Jesus Christ!
What is the French word for "stakeout"?
CONKLIN: Okay, this was 16 minutes ago.
This is our starting point.
CONKLIN: Can't fly, trains are risky. Nicky?
NICKY: Here.
I need to know everything
Paris's finest is doing on this.
NICKY: I'm on it.
ABBOTT:
You said 24 hours, and he's not back.
CONKLIN:
No. But we got a good idea where he is.
ABBOTT: You've got a black ops agent
who's off the reservation.
He trashed an American consulate.
He's on the run in Europe.
You don't know why. I got to stand
before an oversight committee.
What will I say about Treadstone?
You're worried about a budget meeting?
We don't take care of this,
we don't make it to the men's room.
Now, is that clear enough for you?
We will burn for this.
We will both of us burn.
CONKLIN: All right, I want two teams.
Daryl, Ray, stay on the grids.
Brian, Harris, Steve...
...I want to work on this girl.
CONKLIN: And this residency pattern?
COMM TECH 1: We started it.
Get it out.
COMM TECH 1: We cross-referenced
numbers from her relatives.
When we found convergence,
we took the numbers...
...back-checked them, ran a search merge
with other data we had, which wasn't much.
Pins. These pins.
These are all the places we think she's lived
in the last six years.
CONKLIN: One, two, three, four, five.
That's our pool.
MARIE: No answer.
How many times you let it ring?
- Look, if you don't want to go, I'll hitch.
- I said I'd take you.
CONKLIN: Those are the targets.
Beg, borrow, hack, tap, bypass!
I don't care what you do!
I want to know everything you can tell me
about what's going on at those locations.
BOURNE: How do you know
he still owns this?
MARIE: Eamon always had money.
He would never sell this.
Marie?
MARIE: What?
We got to go.
What?
I thought it would...
MARIE: Shit, that's Eamon. I'll talk to him.
BOURNE: We're leaving.
Eamon. Surprise.
It's me, Marie. Wow, God...
...there's a really good reason for this.
EAMON: There bloody well better be.
CLAUDIA: Daddy!
EAMON: Hang on. Hang on.
I had no idea you would be here.
Well, why would I be here?
It's only my bloody house, right?
MARIE: Yeah.
Did she get you into this?
It was just gonna be for a day.
Daddy, Alain has to go pee!
All right, all right, come on. Here.
Get out of the car.
Okay, in you go.
EAMON: Come on, Alain.
MARIE: I'm sorry. I...
I thought it would be okay.
But I guess I was wrong.
- Let's find Mummy.
- Mummy?
Mummy is away for two days, thank God.
BOURNE:
You've got yourself all tied up here.
BOURNE: Okay.
What's he do for a living?
He used to be in shipping.
Is he good for you?
Are you happy?
You know me. I try too hard.
Here you go.
Sleep well.
Good night.
BOURNE: I'll sleep on the floor.
CONKLIN: This was when?
RESEARCH TECH 2: 11:45 a. M.
Which is definitely within
the driving range of Paris.
RESEARCH TECH 1:
The call came from a rest stop.
CONKLIN: Yeah. What's this yellow pin?
She spent two months there in 1997.
Closest town is Riom.
We took her family's phone records
and collated the international calls.
They were in Paris at 2.00 a. M.
They can't fly. The train's too dangerous.
He knows better than to go anywhere
we might track him.
So this is our best guess.
- What are you doing?
- The kids. I was worried. I couldn't sleep.
MARIE: You'll wake them up. We got to go.
BOURNE:
I don't want to know who I am anymore.
I don't care. I don't want to know.
MARIE: Come on. We'll talk about...
BOURNE: I want to forget everything.
It's okay.
BOURNE: I don't care who I am
or what I did.
It's okay.
BOURNE: We have this money.
We can hide.
Can we do that?
Is there any chance you can do that?
MARIE: I don't know.
MARIE: Come on.
CLAUDIA: Here, boy! Here, boy!
'Morning.
EAMON: Christ. You were up early.
Bless you for making coffee.
One night. You weren't kidding.
For a change.
He's not there either.
EAMON: And you looked by the car?
CLAUDIA: He's not anywhere.
All right, let me get dressed.
BOURNE: Who?
EAMON: Bloody dog's gone missing.
Does that happen a lot?
What? That mutt?
Miss his breakfast? Not a chance.
It's always something, right?
Get in the basement.
What?
- Get everyone in the basement.
- What are you talking about?
You're in danger. Your family's in danger.
I don't have time to explain.
EAMON: Wait a minute. What...
MARIE: Eamon.
You should go.
EAMON: What have you done?
BOURNE: It's not her. It's me.
You need to get out of sight
and in the basement as quick as you can.
CLAUDIA: Daddy.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
MARIE: The phone is dead.
BOURNE: Yeah.
Jason, who's out there? Who is it?
MARIE: What are you doing?
Oh, no.
We should never have come here.
I... These children...
That's not gonna happen.
BOURNE: Where is it? Where's the weapon?
Who else is out here?
Who else? How many you got with you?
BOURNE: I'm not gonna ask you again.
I work alone. Like you.
We always work alone.
BOURNE: What do you mean?
PROFESSOR: Who are you? Rome?
Paris?
Treadstone, both of us.
BOURNE: Treadstone?
PROFESSOR: Which one?
Paris. I live in Paris.
PROFESSOR: You get the headaches?
Yeah.
I get such bad headaches.
You know at night
when you're driving a car?
Maybe it's the headlights.
What is Treadstone?
Treadstone said pills.
They said go to Paris.
Is Treadstone in Paris?
Look at this.
Look at what they make you give.
EAMON: All right, all right.
All right, Claudia,
get in the front and put your belt on.
EAMON:
All right, we're gonna put you in the back.
All right, get in the front, Claudia.
EAMON: I'm not waiting, Marie.
- One minute, Eamon.
- I'm not waiting!
MARIE: Please!
Take it.
BOURNE: I took out $30,000.
The rest is yours.
MARIE: That's it?
BOURNE: That's all I got.
No, that's not what I meant.
This is not gonna stop, Marie.
You got to get out now. Away from me.
BOURNE: You got to get out.
You got to start running.
You get low, you stay low.
No more friends. Nothing familiar.
There's enough in there for you
to make a life. Any life.
EAMON: I'm out of here, Marie!
BOURNE: Hey!
Get in the car. You got to go.
What are you gonna do?
I'll end it.
Go ahead.
BOURNE: Please.
Code in, please.
ZORN: Code in.
Code in.
BOURNE: Who is this?
Who the hell are you?
The man you sent is dead.
So whoever this is, you better start talking.
CONKLIN: Hello, Jason.
So, what are we into now?
It only goes two ways. Either you come in
and let us make this right...
...or we'll keep going until we're satisfied.
You mean until you kill me.
I can't fix this
if I don't know what the problem is.
Tell me what we're into,
and I'll do the best I can.
Why don't you talk to Marie, Jason?
CONKLIN: Let's ask Marie what she wants.
BOURNE: I don't think she gives a shit.
She's dead.
I'm sorry to hear that.
How did that happen?
BOURNE: She was slowing me down.
CONKLIN: All we've been doing right from...
BOURNE: Enough.
Enough.
5:30 p. M. Paris.
Today. Pont Neuf.
Come alone,
you walk to the middle of that bridge.
You take off your jacket. Face east.
BOURNE: I'll redial this number.
CONKLIN: Wait!
First flight out. Tell Nicky I'll call
from the car. Tell her to find Picot. Go.
ABBOTT: So...
What are we gonna do?
I told you I'd clean this up.
That's what I'm doing.
Can you really bring him in?
I think we're past that, don't you?
Do you have a better idea?
You've given me nothing
but a trail of collateral damage...
...from Zurich to Paris.
I couldn't do much worse.
Why don't you go upstairs
and book a conference room?
Maybe you can talk him to death.
COP 1: The bus, the tour bus, second level.
COP 2: Negative on the target.
COP 4: Position one?
COP 2: Negative.
COP 4: Position two?
COP 3: Negative.
COP 1: Position three, motorcycle.
COP 5: Negative.
Jason?
I told you to come alone.
I guess that was too complicated.
BOURNE: So try this: I'm gone.
Fuck.
CONKLIN: Get Nicky on the phone.
NICKY: Yeah?
CONKLIN: How long to wipe down the room
and move it?
NICKY: Get rid of everything?
CONKLIN: Yeah.
NICKY: Two to three hours.
CONKLIN: All right, get started.
Listen, no breaks.
Two men outside, one in the lobby.
And keep your eyes open.
COP 1: Keep the truck?
CONKLIN: Keep the truck.
I'm gonna close this unit down.
We'll move the gear in the truck.
NICKY:
They were covering Spain, Malta, Morocco.
Yes, all local police radio traffic.
No, for northern Europe
we need an authorised directive. Yeah.
Okay, they're on it. We'll have
a satellite download in 30 minutes.
CONKLIN: Where's your field box?
- Where's your field box?
- It's right there.
NICKY: The whole system's gone haywire.
That's this window right here.
Dining room window?
I don't get it.
Dead. The phones are dead.
It's Bourne, isn't it?
Just quiet.
You move, you die.
CONKLIN: Bourne.
Gun down.
In there.
Okay, so what do you want...
BOURNE: Treadstone.
You better take a look around.
There's not much left.
- Are you Treadstone?
- Am I Treadstone? Me?
What the hell are you talking about?
He's lost it.
You better start filling in the blanks here!
'Cause I thought we were on the same side.
Whose side is that?
You don't know what you're doing, do you?
You don't have a goddamn clue!
Who am I?
You're U. S. Government property!
You're a malfunctioning $30 million weapon!
You're a total goddamn catastrophe!
And, by God, if it kills me,
you'll tell me how this happened.
- Why are you trying to kill me?
- What happened in Marseilles?
You sent me to kill Wombosi.
Kill Wombosi?
Yeah, we can do that any time we want.
I can send Nicky to do that,
for Christ's sake.
Mr. Wombosi was supposed to be dead
three weeks ago.
He was supposed to have died in a way
that the only possible explanation was...
...that he'd been murdered
by a member of his own entourage.
I don't send you to kill.
I send you to be invisible.
I send you because you don't exist.
I want to know what happened in Marseilles.
I don't remember what happened
in Marseilles.
Bullshit! This is unacceptable, soldier.
You hear me? You failed!
- Unacceptable?
- You failed!
- You failed and you're gonna tell me why!
- I can't tell you! I don't remember!
You brought Kane to life.
You put together a meeting with Wombosi.
You found the security company.
You broke into the office!
For Christ's sake, you picked the yacht
as the goddamn strike point!
CONKLIN: You picked the boat.
You picked the day. You tracked the crew.
The food, the fuel!
You told us where. You told us when.
You hid out on that boat five days.
You were in, Jason. You were in!
It was over!
CONKLIN: No, you do remember.
Don't you?
I don't want to do this anymore.
I don't think that's a decision you can make.
Jason Bourne is dead. Do you hear me?
BOURNE: He drowned two weeks ago.
You're gonna go tell them Bourne is dead.
Understand?
CONKLIN: Where are you gonna go?
I swear, if I even feel somebody behind me,
there is no measure to how fast...
...and how hard I will bring this fight
to your doorstep.
I'm on my own side now.
It's done.
Shut it down.
ABBOTT: The Treadstone project
has already been terminated.
It was designed primarily
as a sort of advanced game program.
We'd hoped it might build
into a good training platform.
But quite honestly,
for a strictly theoretical exercise...
...the cost-benefit ratio was just too high.
It's all but decommissioned at this point.
MARSHALL: All right, what's next?
ABBOTT: Okay, this is...
...Blackbriar.
Blackbriar is a joint DOD
communications program...
...that we really feel has good traction to it.
It's got legs. It'll run and run.
It combines elements of proactive
and reactive fields of security...
BOURNE: This your store?
MARIE: Yeah.
It's nice. It's a little hard to find, but...
Think I could rent a scooter?
You have ID?
Not really.
Subtitles by SOFTITLER