[The Flaming Lips'
Do You Realize? plays]
[upbeat quirky music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Do you realize ♪
♪ That you have ♪
♪ The most beautiful face ♪
♪ Do you realize ♪
♪ We're floating in space ♪
♪ That happiness
makes you cry ♪
♪ Do you realize ♪
♪ That everyone ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Will die ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And instead of saying
all of your good-byes ♪
- ...On the way out,
but we'll still be dealing with...
...some scattered snow flurries
and sleet.
Expect it to be over
by early afternoon...
...with highs today
in the mid-30s.
Freezing temperatures
will be back this evening...
...with lows in the mid-20s
in Manhattan...
...and high teens
in the outlying suburbs.
So wrap up.
Right now we have
a weather-related delay...
...in the Lincoln Tunnel...
...where a semi apparently
hit some ice...
[footsteps clattering]
[door slams]
[kids chattering]
[baby screaming]
[people chattering]
[chattering stops]
- It's a good school,
isn't it?
You never know.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's good.
- I'm Jamie Brennan.
- Hi.
- My daughter's
in the fourth grade.
We just moved here from L.A.
- Hi, I'm Emilia.
- Hi.
- I'm with William Woolf.
He's in third.
He's my stepson.
- Ugh, they don't mind staring,
do they?
- Yeah, well, you're new,
and you're talking
to the only second wife here.
I terrify them,
like there's such a thing
as a home-wrecker.
- There is in California.
- [chuckles]
Now you're nervous.
- Oh, no, of course not.
- Miss Emilia?
- Sonia, isn't this
your day off?
- Yes.
- It's Wednesday, right?
- Yes, yes.
Dr. Soule asked me
to give to you this...
...for the ears of William.
I go to her office to pick up.
- She made you work
on your day off?
- So three times a day,
he takes this with food.
And keep cold,
but not in fridge.
Oh, and Dr. Soule also says
when Mr. Woolf
drop off William this time,
his clothes are clean
and fold,
not just shoving
in backpack.
- They were not shoved.
They were folded,
I mean, casually.
And they were clean.
Worn once, washed once:
clean.
- This is not me.
This is Dr. Soule.
And do not yell at me.
It is very embarrassing
to be yelling at me in public.
- I'm not yelling at you, Sonia.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I will remember.
Cold, not fridge.
Clean, not shoved.
[kids chattering]
- Sonia!
- Ooh, William.
I just say hello and good-bye.
I bring medicine
from your mommy.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hello, Emilia.
- Hey, William.
You ready?
- Okay, William,
I go to my day off now.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Good-bye, Miss Emilia.
- Sorry, pal.
It's just me today,
Wednesday.
- So it is.
- My gloves weren't in my cubby.
- Here, take mine.
- They're too big.
- William, come on.
Let's go.
Nice talking to you.
Have a nice life.
Oh, great.
It's gonna rain.
- Why didn't you call
the car service?
Everyone calls the car service
when it rains.
- Everyone?
You know, not everyone
can afford a car service.
- My dad can.
- Well, look, what are
all those mothers doing?
Just waving at traffic?
No.
So clearly not everyone
who can afford it
thinks it's necessary to arrange
for a car service, okay?
- Sonia always calls
the car service when it rains.
She checks the weather
the night before.
- I don't want to hear
an eight-year-old say
"car service" again, okay?
- [whispers]
Car service.
- There's one.
- I wonder what temperature
poop freezes at.
- Yeah, me too.
Constantly.
Come on.
- You know that
since poop comes out hot,
it freezes quicker
than a popsicle?
- Mind-blowing.
Get in.
- It's because of evaporation.
Hot water evaporates quicker.
So poop, which has hot water-
- William-
- Oh, oh!
Oh, dear.
- God damn it, William.
Oh, get in.
- Ow!
That hurt!
- Tell your mother.
West 7th and 81st, please.
God, William, keep your foot
away from the heater.
Today's a good day for a video.
- I can't.
I already watched one
Sunday night.
I have to wait till Saturday
to start a new week.
So I'll just play
with my Mega Science Lab.
- Take off your wet coat
before we go in the kitchen.
- I'll probably gather
the bacteria from the sink
and look at it
with my microscope.
- That sounds fun.
- It says on the box
it's for ages ten and up.
- You mean you're not
supposed to be a nerd
for two whole years?
- It's not nerdy to be smart.
- Wait, this is the age
of the nerd.
That was a compliment.
- What's for snack?
- Check your shelf.
There's some stuff there.
- Yay, Tofutti Cuties.
- What kid doesn't love tofu?
- Oh, wait.
I don't like
the strawberry ones.
I'll have a soy pudding.
Chocolate.
- Mmm, fat-free, sugar-free,
fruit juice-sweetened.
Enjoy that.
- Hey, can I have a bowl
for this?
People touch this at the store.
- Yeah, just think
of all the little boys
that die eating their pudding
directly from the container.
The body count is crazy.
- Emilia, do you know
what eBay is?
- Yes, I do.
- My friend Bailey's dad
sells things on eBay.
He takes all their old stuff
they don't need anymore,
like Bailey's old bike,
and sells it.
- That's nice.
- Maybe you should go on eBay.
- I figure if I need
an old bike,
Bailey's dad
will sell it to me.
- Not to buy.
To sell.
To make money.
Don't you have any old stuff?
- I have strawberry
Tofutti Cuties, like new,
in original box.
- I mean the baby's stuff.
We should sell
the baby's stuff on eBay.
We can sell the crib.
The crib cost exactly $1,31 1.
Dad told me.
So I bet we can get $2,000
for the crib.
Maybe even $10,000.
- No, we wouldn't.
- That's how eBay works.
Take all the old stuff
you don't need anymore,
and people give you
money for it.
- We wouldn't get $10,000
for the crib on eBay,
okay, William?
- We can sell the stroller too.
I bet we can get $5,000
for the stroller.
- That's not how it works.
You're not going to get all
that money for something used
when you could get it new
for a lot less.
That doesn't even make sense.
- It's not used, though.
We never used it.
Bailey's dad says-
- William, I really
don't want to talk
about selling
the baby's things, okay?
- But that's what it's for.
- William, shut up!
Just shut up about eBay, okay?
Leave me alone, please.
Just go watch TV or something.
Leave me.
- I'm home.
- In here.
- Thai.
Great.
Can I give you a hand?
- I got it under control.
[dishes clatter]
- Yeah?
[chuckling]
Hello.
So what'd you guys do today?
- Oh, built
a cold fusion reactor
out of swizzle sticks
and rubber bands.
- [laughs]
- We had a little thing,
actually.
- Dad, Dad!
- Hey.
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you too, Will.
- Who wants to help
set the table?
- Emilia told me
to shut up today.
And she yelled at me.
- Really?
What's going on?
- William suggested that we sell
the baby's things on eBay.
The crib and the stroller.
- Okay.
- Well, we don't have
to sell those things.
Anything that we're not using
is okay.
Like, we can sell
my old MEGA Bloks,
'cause I don't use
those anymore.
- Yeah, but you didn't say
your old MEGA Bloks.
You said the baby's things.
- Just a minute, Em.
- Will, did you really want
to sell the baby's things?
- What?
I just told you.
- A minute, Em, please.
Will?
- Well, I wanted to do eBay,
and I was trying to think
of things we aren't using.
So I figured,
the baby's dead.
She's not gonna be using
her stuff anymore.
I didn't mean to make
Emilia so mad.
- See, Emilia is so sad
about the baby
that it's hard for her to think
about selling the baby's things.
And you're right.
We don't need them anymore,
but she's right too.
We're not gonna sell
the baby's things.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
- I know you didn't mean
to hurt anyone's feelings.
[chuckles]
I know it.
And Emilia knows it.
And she's sorry too.
Right, Emilia?
- I know I have to clear
her room out.
I just can't pack up
all her stuff yet.
- It's okay.
- I'm not building a shrine
or anything.
- I know.
It's okay.
- I'm sorry I said "shut up."
I'm gonna read, okay?
- Okay.
Good night.
- Good night.
- I'm so happy to be here.
- Oh, we're delighted
to have you, Miss Greenleaf.
This is a great opportunity
for you to start your career.
- I'm so excited.
I've been hearing
about Friedman Taft
from my father since as long
as I can remember.
- Is your father a lawyer?
- A judge in Westchester.
President of the New York
Bar Association, formerly.
- Oh, right, yes.
That's in here.
Oh, oh!
Oh.
- Oh, are you okay?
- Marilyn.
- My ankle!
Jack, yes.
Just need a minute.
- Does it hurt when I squeeze?
- Ouch!
Yes.
- Oh, could you just
grab that door?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Okay, slowly, Marilyn.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
- I feel so stupid, Jack.
- Okay.
There you go.
- [groans]
- All right.
All right.
- I'm the new associate,
by the way, Emilia Greenleaf.
- Jack Woolf.
- Nice to meet you.
- Same.
- Miss Greenleaf,
you're in room 1818.
Thank you.
- I'll get some ice, okay?
- Ice, yes, please.
- Of course he's married.
He's a senior partner.
They're always married.
What'd you expect?
- I just-I thought
I'd get over this months ago.
But I'm still, like, weak
when I'm around him,
and he doesn't even know
I'm alive.
- "He doesn't know I'm alive"?
What, are you in
the cliché Olympics?
- Ha-ha. Don't you
street lawyers have paralegals?
- No, friends are cheaper.
- I'm sorry I'm late, you guys.
- Hi.
- I couldn't find a cab.
- God, I wish someone
here in New York
would invent something kind
of like a train, you know,
that would go underground
and take you places.
No, that's crazy talk.
- Harris doesn't want me
taking the subway anymore.
Oh, seriously?
Press packets?
You really think this slumlord
cares about bad press?
- If she bails, I get her beer.
- Oh, no.
I'm not drinking.
I can't.
Or smoke.
Or eat tuna.
- Oh, my God.
Mindy, are you pregnant?
- Eight weeks.
- Oh, that's great.
And you were worried.
- Yay, Mindy, that's wonderful.
Yay to the bump.
- Hmm.
Oh, my God.
Did I tell you?
I almost met your guy's wife.
- What?
- Yeah.
Well, since I'm pregnant,
I moved from fertility
to OB/GYN.
And Dr. O'Neal recommends
Carolyn Soule.
And I remember that you said
that Jack is married to her.
So I check her out
on urbanbaby.com.
And I mean, she's like-
people rave about her.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She's, like, top three
in Manhattan,
I mean,
at least on that website.
- Urbanbaby.com?
- Are you a little ashamed
you didn't think of it yourself?
- No, I'm gonna meet her
next week anyway.
Holiday office party
at their apartment.
- Well, I hope you meet
their kid.
That should knock this
out of you.
[people chattering]
- Happy holidays.
- Thanks.
You too.
- Hmm.
- Nice party.
- So far.
I'm keeping my eye on
the paralegals and the open bar.
- [laughs]
- Oh, Marilyn, there you are.
- Carolyn, happy holidays.
- Oh, I have something for you
in the den.
It's marked.
You'll see it.
So before you go.
- Thank you, Carolyn.
- Hello, I'm Carolyn Soule,
Jack Woolf's wife.
- This is Emilia Greenleaf.
She's new.
- Well, September.
Thanks so much
for inviting me here.
- Oh, well, of course.
- Marilyn and Carolyn.
[chuckles]
- That's very good.
Well, enjoy yourself.
- My friend wanted you
to be her doctor,
but you were all booked.
She says you're the best.
- Oh, isn't that sweet?
I wish it were true.
- [chuckles]
- Oh.
- Well, according
to the internet.
- Well, don't let us keep you,
Carolyn.
- Yes, don't forget-
before you leave.
- Thank you, Carolyn.
- We put in an appearance.
I'm heading downtown.
You want to share a cab?
- It's only 10:00.
- Well, you know,
usually the new people
and the support staff
leave these things early.
Adult swim, so to speak.
- Well, I'm an associate,
so I guess I'm gonna dive in.
[both chuckling]
- Your tickets and itinerary.
- What?
- Check your email.
You're flying
to Oakland tomorrow.
Discovery production
on the Jasper case.
- But that's not my case.
- It's Jack's.
You don't want to go?
Talk to him.
He's business.
You're coach.
Policy.
- Wait, a partner's doing
document production?
- Exactly.
For the plane.
- So beautiful
downtown Oakland, huh?
- [chuckles]
- Because of my dad, probably.
He didn't make me,
but as a judge's daughter,
I guess you get to either be
a lawyer or a criminal.
- [laughs]
- Pia, my half-sister,
is a lawyer too.
Common cause.
- Your father was
married before?
- Yeah, then my mother,
his secretary.
- They're divorced now too.
But they're friendly enough.
I mean, you know, with
the grandkids and everything.
- Was that hard for you?
- I was 22, so, you know...
but they're
much better off apart.
Better for my mother anyway.
She gave up everything for him.
The good wife.
- Wives were a great thing.
Everyone needs one.
My wife more than me, maybe.
- I don't need a wife.
I don't even want
to get married.
I'm practically a guy.
- It doesn't show.
- This is me.
Where are you?
- I'm on the spa level.
- But that's-
we passed that on the way up.
- I know.
I don't think I can do
anything else right now.
Is that okay?
- As long as you don't say
that you're married,
and you've never
done this before,
and you're afraid
of hurting your wife.
- I'm married.
And I've never done this before.
And I am afraid
of hurting my wife.
- Who doesn't understand you.
- Good night, Emilia.
- Good night.
[Belle & Sebastian's
Waiting for the Moon to Rise]
[upbeat romantic music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ All the way back home ♪
♪ I'm telling you,
I caught the sun ♪
♪ Creeping up
behind my shoulder ♪
♪ Another day's begun ♪
♪ I was following a trail ♪
♪ I'd never been along before ♪
♪ Chasing darkened skies
above me ♪
♪ Looking like the spring ♪
♪ Like the winter
and the morning ♪
♪ ♪
♪ If there's a place
I want to go ♪
♪ Then I'll be there with you ♪
♪ 'Cause in my dreams
the things I'm wishing for ♪
♪ Keep coming true ♪
♪ Till darkness fills
the eastern sky ♪
♪ And streetlights stretch
for miles ♪
♪ Through the spring
and the winter and the morning ♪
♪ ♪
- It's crazy.
- Oh, Will is so sweet.
He sounds really smart.
- He is.
You know, there's something
I've been thinking about.
- I think we
should move in together.
- Emilia-
- Just hear me out.
I love you,
and I know you love me too.
- I love you.
I do.
But I have a family.
- You have a son, Jack.
You don't have a marriage.
You've said that a lot.
- Okay, fine, I have a son.
That's more than a marriage.
And he's not the happiest kid.
He's not unhappy.
He just-
he's lonely.
It's bad when your kid
is lonely.
I mean, I used to think
we should have had more
for Will, mainly.
But Carolyn-
anyway, we-
I'm glad we didn't.
Screwing up one child
is enough for a lifetime.
I'm done.
- [whimpering]
- What?
- [sobs]
- Emilia.
- I'm on the pill.
I don't understand.
Look, don't-
don't worry about it, okay?
It's early.
It's, like, eight weeks
or something,
so it won't be a problem.
- No.
[laughter]
- To Emilia and Jack.
May their marriage be long
and fruitful.
- Well, fruitful we can do.
[laughter]
I'm so glad you came.
Thank you.
It's so soon.
- No, it's good for me
to get out of the house.
And I'm so happy
that you're expecting.
Don't think I'm envious,
honestly.
- This is gonna be you
before you know it.
- Hmm.
I know.
We're already trying, so-
- Wow, that's so quick.
That's great.
- How long have your father
and Jack known each other?
- Oh, we all had dinner together
last month
just before the divorce
came through.
But they got along right away.
They have private jokes already.
- Hmm, well, they're a day away
from wearing each other's
clothes just for fun.
- Well, we all end up marrying
our fathers, don't we?
- Yes, I only fuck men in shorts
and black socks
who make me join Little League.
It's weird.
- Jack and my dad
couldn't be more different.
Jack's so principled.
- Have you met the kid yet?
- Saturday.
But from Jack's stories,
I get the feeling
he's a little high-maintenance.
- Whatever.
That's the one you want
to please
if you want this to work out.
- Roy G. Biv.
Roy G. Biv.
- Jack.
- Red, orange, yellow, green.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
Will, this is Emilia.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Pleased to meet you too.
This is for you.
I got it at the Museum
of Natural History next door.
That's why I was late.
Your dad told me
it's your favorite place.
- There's no evidence
that theropods were orange.
Plus, I'm eight.
- Well, I guess
it's not very realistic, huh?
But there's also a book
in there about Central Park,
which is my favorite place
since I was about your age.
- Anyway, thank you.
- You know, there's a show
at 1 0:30.
We should go.
- You may kiss the bride.
[applause]
- Oh, good.
William is upstairs.
- Okay.
- No, no, no.
Dr. Soule says to wait here.
- I guess I'm a security risk.
- You're late.
- No, I am not late.
Your father's late.
- He disappoints,
because he was hoping
to see his father.
- Me too.
I disappoint too.
- Okay, William.
See you Monday.
Good-bye, Miss Emilia.
- When is my father coming home?
- By 8:00.
That's, like, three hours, okay?
- That sucks.
- Don't say "sucks."
Your mom's gonna think
you heard it from me.
- I did hear it from you.
- William, why do we
have to fight all the time?
I just-
let's have a nice time, okay?
How about we get
ice cream sundaes for supper,
hot fudge?
I want to eat one
the size of your head.
- I'm lactose-intolerant.
I could get very ill
from eating ice cream.
- Okay.
We'll just see whatever
is in the fridge.
Chinese, Thai,
old and cold, but whatever.
- Rainbow sherbet-
that's no dairy-
or sorbet: lemon, lime,
coconut, and peach.
Everything else has dairy.
- Oh, I guess I'll have sorbet.
Lemon.
- No, he'll have
a hot chocolate
and a banana split.
You want strawberry sauce
or chocolate?
- I can't have that.
I'm lactose-intolerant.
- No, you have that powder here,
right, don't you,
that takes care
of lactose-intolerance?
- Yeah?
- Yeah, William,
they have this powder here,
and you sprinkle it
all over your ice cream.
And you don't even taste it,
but you can have whatever
you want that way.
- My mother isn't convinced
that kind of lactase works.
- William, please,
it's science.
He'll have
the strawberry sauce, please.
- No, chocolate.
And my ice cream flavors
are chocolate, chocolate chip,
and cookie dough.
It's melting.
You better hurry.
- You want it?
- I think I'll have this
next time,
'cause my banana was
a little brown at the end.
You want it?
- Oh, I'm good.
Thank you.
Emilia, how old is that baby?
- Excuse me, is your baby
two, three months?
- Oh, seven weeks.
December 26th.
- Seven weeks,
- Did you know that Isabel
was never really a person?
- What?
- She was never really a person.
In Jewish law,
it says that a baby
is not a person
until it's at least
eight days old.
And Isabel was only
three days old when she died.
So that means she was never
really a person.
- Where did you hear that?
- My mother.
- I told her I was
a little sad about Isabel,
but not as sad as if I've
known her for a long time,
like she had time to be
my real little sister.
So then my mom told me how,
in the Jewish law,
she was never really a person.
So now I don't have to feel
so bad about not feeling so sad.
- Well, Isabel was
a real person.
She was every bit as much
of a person as you are.
- My mom said she was surprised
they even let us have a funeral.
- We're going.
Come on.
Let's go.
- Hey, you forgot to pay!
- That was fun,
wasn't it?
- Yeah.
- It's good to share things
together,
like, you know,
secrets and stuff.
It's fun.
- I'm not supposed to have
secrets from my mom.
- It's not a secret.
It's just private.
There's a difference.
We can have
private things together.
Everyone does.
Like tomorrow.
Tomorrow don't go having
ice cream
in front of your dad, okay?
Not that my sister
will have any.
She probably only
has the soy stuff.
- I don't want to go
to that stupid party.
- It's your cousin's birthday.
- No, she's your niece,
not my cousin.
- Nono will be there.
You like Nono.
You call him your grandpa,
and he isn't, so...
- But sometimes
when it's just you and me,
we can still get ice cream,
right?
- Only if it's just
between the two of us.
Deal?
- Deal.
After the party,
can Emilia and I go to the park?
Maybe go where we went
yesterday, Emilia?
- Well, um, okay, William.
Maybe.
But be cool, fool.
- Uh, totally, dude.
- What's with you two?
- Private joke.
- Uh-huh.
- Private, not secret.
There's a difference.
- Is there?
- Ugh!
- Sweet old grandpa routine?
I just don't believe it.
- Yeah, well, the kids do.
And they usually sniff out
bullshit pretty well.
Oh, hey, your mom called.
She's running late.
[horn honking]
- Dad, Jack's already waiting.
Go.
- Where are they going?
- Oh, we ran out of Rice Dream.
Hey, kiddo.
You hungry?
- No, I had lots already.
I love hummus.
We made it in school
on Middle Eastern day.
Both Arabs and Israelis eat it.
- Yes, it's the hope
of the world, hummus.
- Honey, can you take this
up to the rec room to the kids?
Put it on the table
with the cookies.
The non-dairy has a cow
with the line through it, okay?
- Do I have to?
I don't know anyone.
- Well, you know Josh and Emma.
Okay, look.
If you have no fun,
in ten minutes,
you can come back down.
That's 1 1:28.
There's a digital clock
up there, okay?
- I prefer analog.
- Okay, now you have to wait
till 1 1:29.
Scoot.
- You look good,
better.
- Better than what?
We brought this for Emma.
I can't believe
she's five already.
- Oh, my God.
Developmental K next year,
Greenpoint.
They've got this incredible
bilingual program.
I can't believe you're taking
William out of his school.
It's so great.
- Yeah, but it's public,
and it's what Jack wants.
So now I got to please her.
I bet she'll choose
whatever private school
is most expensive.
- Well, I hope
you choose wisely.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean, William is a sweet kid,
but he could use
a little rough-and-tumble.
You know what I mean?
- I don't know.
It's the East Side,
but it is public.
I mean, there's black
and Asian kids in his class.
Diversity is
one of their things.
- Experiencing rich people
of all colors is not diversity.
- We're not rich, Pia.
We're comfortable.
- Honey, your doorman
is comfortable.
- Hmm.
- Mommy!
Come quick.
It's William.
- What?
What's the matter?
Is he okay?
William?
- He won't move.
- William, did you have
an accident?
- Gross.
- I think it's diarrhea.
- Oh, no.
- Just go away.
I don't want you.
I want my dad.
Is he here?
- He went to the store.
- Then Nono.
- No, they went
to get Rice Dream.
Oh, no.
William, I think this-
- Please, I don't want you.
Leave me alone.
- Honey, why don't you
give me a shot, okay?
You want to go downstairs?
I'll take you downstairs.
I'm gonna pop him
in the bath, okay?
- Here, let me help you.
- Great, get the cake ready.
The candles are in the drawer
by the stove.
[whispering]
Don't worry.
Good job, pal.
He's upstairs
watching a movie.
Fine, just embarrassed.
Some of the kids
made fun of him,
which didn't help.
- It's my fault
that he had diarrhea.
He's lactose-intolerant,
and I gave him ice cream.
- What?
Why?
- Because I didn't
really believe
that he was lactose-intolerant.
I thought Carolyn
was just being controlling.
I know.
I'm a terrible person.
- You're not a terrible person.
You're just not used to kids.
It takes time.
- No, you know what it takes?
A kid.
- Em, I didn't mean-
- Is that okay?
I'm gonna go to the car.
- I told her Mom said
that powder doesn't work for me.
- It doesn't matter, Will.
You just won't be
having ice cream again.
So it doesn't matter.
- Hey, hey.
I'll take a rain check.
I'm kind of beat.
- Okay.
- Sorry I'm late.
Wow, you look nice.
Is that new?
- No.
Thank you, honey.
I just had my hair done.
Take your time, sweetie.
I'm sorry I missed you
yesterday at Pia's.
I heard about Will.
Poor baby.
- He's better today,
but I'm expecting a hysterical
phone call from Carolyn
as soon as he tells her.
She's gonna love this.
Emilia screws up again.
- Well, you couldn't know.
Pia feels terrible.
Six kids, not including Will.
That's seven.
I'm not surprised they got sick.
I'm just surprised
seven kids tried hummus.
I mean, she scares them into it.
- That's what it was?
- She said she told you.
Em, you've got to check
your machine, honestly.
- We have to tell him.
- Well, what did you
think it was?
[knocking at door]
- Hi, I need to speak
to William Woolf, please.
- I'm sorry, how did you-
- I'm Emilia Greenleaf.
I'm his stepmother.
It's important.
- I know who you are,
Miss Greenleaf,
but unless it's
a medical emergency,
we don't allow visits.
It's distracting.
I can give him a message
at recess.
- Okay, tell him six other kids
got sick yesterday,
so it wasn't the ice cream.
It was the hummus.
- All right.
Not the ice cream.
The hummus.
- It's important.
- Have a nice day.
- It went okay?
- Yeah, I think.
We'll know if we get
one of her calls.
- Don't let me forget to pick up
something for your father today.
His birthday is in a month.
- Mom, you should forget
his birthday.
It's been seven years.
- It doesn't kill me
to buy him a card.
- Hallmark has that covered?
"Happy birthday.
Thanks for cheating on me."
- Emilia.
- I'm worried about you.
Simon is too.
- I'm fine.
- Look, I know
what you're going through.
My miscarriage was just like
a child dying.
- Really?
Then isn't abortion
the same thing too?
I mean, I think
there's a difference
between a fetus and a baby.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Mindy.
I just-
I'm all right, really.
Time heals, and I just need
the days to pass for a while.
- No, no, you need to take
an active role
in your own grief.
That's what saved me.
I want you to come with us
on the remembrance walk.
- What, that thing you did
in November?
- Yes, we're doing a small one
next month.
- I don't think that walking
in Central Park
with a bunch of people
with candles
who lost their babies
is really gonna help.
- You don't know that.
Okay?
it saved my life.
- I'm glad.
- Look, here.
Just take the pamphlet, okay?
If you're not interested,
I'll drop it.
But I really think
it would help.
And you need help, seriously.
- [sighs]
- Is she expecting you home
at any particular time?
Will dinner be waiting?
- I'm gonna pick up William
early on Friday,
at 3:00 here instead of 5:00
at your place.
I got tickets to
The Lion King for Friday night,
and I thought we'd make
a day of it.
- He's already seen
The Lion King.
- He can see it twice.
- We hear from the schools
on Friday.
- Great.
Call me,
let me know where he's going.
- I'd like to tell him myself.
William and I went through
the whole process together.
I went on all
the interviews with him.
I really think I should be
the one who tells him.
- Fine.
You can tell him.
- William and I chose
Collegiate together,
and when he gets in,
we will celebrate together.
He knows the letters
are coming on Friday.
He'll be waiting to find out.
- Then meet us here.
Or wait till Monday.
Either way,
I'm picking him up early.
- You realize the message
you're sending.
- And what would that be,
Carolyn?
- Mr. Woolf, Dr. Soule.
- Miss Johnson,
thank you so much
for rescheduling
this appointment.
- It really would be much easier
if we didn't both have
to be here at the same time.
- Well, it's our policy,
when possible.
Now, before I walk you through
William's evaluation-
- What are those?
- Oh, aren't they lovely?
We're doing a unit
on family structure.
The children all drew pictures
of their families.
We're so lucky to have such-
- Where's William's?
- William,
in particular, um,
found this
to be very helpful with...
It's how kids process things.
- Carolyn-
- Dr. Soule, please.
- This is not his family.
- What are you doing?
- This is my classroom.
I will not allow you to destroy
things in my classroom.
- May I?
- That is not his family, Jack.
- It is now.
I'm sorry.
We should just move on
with the evaluation.
I'll tell my wife.
My ex-wife.
- I hate that one.
It's the last one we took.
- I didn't realize
you'd seen these.
I'm...
- This is my favorite.
I framed it.
- I look terrible.
I'm all blotchy.
- You look like a woman
who just had a baby.
- You aren't mad at me?
- What for?
- For stealing the pictures
and getting them printed
and not telling you
and hiding them here?
- You think I'd forget
we'd taken them?
I just ordered another set
and had them delivered
to the office.
This one's on my desk.
Of course I'm not mad.
- You should be.
- I'm not.
Not my favorite.
She's got that Popeye thing
going on.
One eye open, one eye closed.
- You look nice.
You look happy.
- I was.
The day Isabel was born
and the day William was born
were the happiest days
of my life.
Can you meet me tomorrow
at Will's school?
I want to show you something.
- Okay.
- A surprise.
- Yeah.
- [sighs]
[kids chattering]
- Hello.
- Yes.
- Carolyn, I don't know
if you remember me.
- I know who you are.
Is Jack inside?
- Yeah, he'll be down
in a minute.
- All right.
This is all your fault.
Will has been so distracted
and tense and emotional.
I'm sure they sensed that
in the interviews.
- What?
- You just won't be happy
until you've ruined everything.
I don't know what the hell
happened to you
to make you so destructive.
Jack.
He didn't get in.
- He didn't get in?
- No, uh-uh.
Not Collegiate,
not even wait-listed.
- All right, just calm down,
Carolyn.
- Oh, I'm calm.
Would you like me to not care?
Should I be more like you?
- Well, he can always stay here.
I mean, it's not the end
of the world.
- No, it's certainly
not the end of your world.
You don't give a shit.
But it's a disaster for Will.
He didn't get in anywhere.
Not Collegiate, not Dalton,
not Trinity.
- You know what?
This is not the time.
- Not the U.N.
international school.
Do you know where he got in?
Do you know who took him?
West Side Prep.
- That's a great school.
Will, that's great, really.
- It's his safety school, Jack.
Do you know
what a safety school is?
- Yeah, I do.
- Jack, I'm gonna
take William home.
We'll meet you there.
Should I go to the theater?
- No.
- Home.
I'll meet you at home.
Don't worry, Will, okay?
- You don't care.
You don't fucking-
- Of course I care.
- Don't touch me.
- Okay, just calm down,
all right?
- You're really too old
for The Lion King, anyway.
I mean,
it's pretty unscientific.
Talking lions?
Talking lion puppets,
actually.
You dodged a bullet,
my friend.
You want something to drink?
Hey, easy.
We're walking through the park.
Your mom hates
the bathrooms there.
- I can pee on a tree.
I have a penis.
You're the one
who should be worried.
You don't have one.
- Thank you
for clearing that up.
I can stop looking now.
- Come on, hurry up!
- Hey, um,
do you skate?
- It's just wrong.
We should rent helmets.
Rollerbladers need helmets,
and ice is just as hard
as asphalt.
Harder.
- Ice is not as hard
as asphalt.
- Yes, it is.
Much harder.
Actually,
asphalt is quite soft.
That's why my mom runs
in the street
and not the sidewalk.
She knows that kind of thing.
She's a doctor.
- Does she run with a helmet?
You should mention that to her.
- My pediatrician's office
has a safety wall in it.
It has a picture of children
on their rollerblades.
My picture is there too.
I'm on my tricycle
wearing my blue helmet.
I also have a red helmet.
If we really want to do this,
we can go home
and get one of my helmets.
- Oy, with the helmets.
- It looks bigger
than 33,000 square feet.
- How do you know
how big Wollman Rink is?
- It's in that book you gave me,
you know,
the Central Park book?
- Oh.
I didn't know you read it.
Pretty cool, huh?
Come on.
Hat.
- Watch out!
- See?
- At the speed he's going,
he needs one.
- This is very scary.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
You can't say
what's scary to me.
Only I can.
You're not scared,
because you know how to skate.
And that boy's not scared,
because his mother
brought his helmet.
- Which probably means
he's scared of her.
Here, give me your hand.
Good.
This isn't so awful, is it?
- I just want to go back
to the wall.
That was much better.
- You just need
to get used to it.
- No, you just go skate.
I do better
if no one is watching.
- Okay, I'm gonna
go around once,
and you try and balance, okay?
- Go on.
- Okay.
- Whoa, whoa!
- William!
William, just stay right there.
I'll help you get up, okay?
- I'm good.
- Whoa!
Shit.
If you say "helmet,"
I'm gonna leave you here.
- Wrist pad.
- Come on.
Okay, let's go.
- Whoa!
- Are you kidding me?
- It's just,
Collegiate was the best school.
- No, it isn't.
It's snooty.
Plus, Collegiate is all boys.
Who wants to go
to an all-boys school?
- Well, if you go to Collegiate,
you can go to Harvard.
- A: not guaranteed.
B: West Side Prep sends
tons of boys to Harvard.
And C: you're eight.
You don't have to think
about Harvard.
Harvard sucks.
- You went to Harvard.
- Exactly.
- Well, that's true.
But still,
I thought I'd get in.
- Dude, it doesn't matter.
It really doesn't matter.
- My mom is mad at me.
- She's mad,
but not at you.
She's mad at me and at your dad
and everything,
but it only feels like
she's mad at you.
- You don't understand.
You don't understand
about Collegiate or anything.
You're from New Rochelle.
You not sophisticated
like me and my mom are.
- You're feeling better, huh?
You know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna stop at Fairway
on the way home,
and I'm going to make you
a homemade stir-fry
and Tofutti sundaes,
and we're gonna watch a movie
that will shrivel
your young brain.
How's that sound?
- Only if I can let go
of the wall down there.
- You don't have to.
- Only if I can let go
of the wall.
- Right on.
One more try.
- This is done?
What next?
- You can peel the ginger.
We only need this part
like that.
- Okay, just that?
That's it?
- Just the skin off.
Not too much.
We don't need that much.
- Okay, but like this?
- Uh-uh, just the corner,
though.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Dad, hey.
I'm sorry about The Lion King.
- It's okay.
- I'm so proud of you.
You got into a great school.
- What does Mom say?
- She says you're gonna
love it there.
And she's very happy.
- Right.
- Hey, Will, show your dad
the flyer.
- Oh, there's a movie
in the park.
It's Lyle, Lyle, Crocodile.
That was my favorite book
when I was a kid.
Remember?
- Uh, yeah, a long time ago.
But yeah, I kind of remember.
- Yeah, they're shooting
a scene at the zoo,
and they need kid extras.
- Both Emilia and I
can be in it.
I can be a kid,
and Emilia can be a mom.
- And it was my favorite book
too when I was your age,
which is pretty weird.
- Meant to be.
So what's all this?
- Well, Will wanted
a real stir-fry, not takeout.
- Mm-hmm.
- Jump in.
- Sure.
- You got to wash
your hands first.
And you have to sing
Happy Birthday twice
while you're doing it.
Otherwise you don't kill
all the bacteria.
- Got it.
- Hey, Will, why don't you show
your dad the DVDs we got today?
- Oh, they're in my room.
I already previewed them.
I want to start
with Jurassic Park.
- Jurassic Park?
[sighs]
Not the day I planned.
- Carolyn's insane.
She needs a Valium drip
or patch...or four.
- I guess it's the hormones
or something.
I mean,
first there were the shots,
and now that she's...
Oh.
Carolyn's pregnant.
- Carolyn's-
oh, shit!
- You okay?
- Carolyn's pregnant?
How can she be pregnant?
She's 43.
- Well, she's 42, but she's been
seeing someone since summer.
- No, she hasn't.
Will would have told us.
- Well, he told me, and he
doesn't know about the baby.
She wanted to wait
until she passed
the three-month mark
to tell him.
- How pregnant is she?
- I don't know,
seven, eight weeks.
Something like that.
She told me
when we lost Isabel.
It made her realize
that she wanted another child.
She got pregnant right away.
- She got pregnant
because of Isabel?
Your ex-wife got pregnant
because my baby died?
- Not because she died.
Because she saw
how much we loved her.
Emilia, this is a good thing,
like something good
came out of Isabel's death.
She didn't die in vain.
- That is not why she died,
so that Carolyn
could have another baby.
- No, you don't understand.
- Oh, fuck you!
That is not why she died.
That's not a good enough reason.
- Will.
[doors slam]
Oh, fuck.
- Oh, a good movie
always makes me feel better.
- What's with you?
- What do you mean?
- You seem happy.
- Do I?
I'm not.
I mean, I'm the same.
I liked that movie, though.
Didn't you?
- No.
I hate it when the heroine
is beautiful,
but she can't get a date.
Why does everything
have to be so stupid?
- Oh, sweetie, I know.
But you'll feel better.
It'll take time,
but it will happen
at home with Jack.
I really think I'm gonna
have to kick you out tomorrow.
24 hours is enough time
to punish a man
for his ex-wife
getting pregnant.
- Why did you like that movie?
It's a romance.
You should have been
angry at it.
The guy's a creep,
and then he says "sorry."
And then everyone forgives him,
but people aren't like that.
- Some people are.
Sometimes good things happen.
- Did you meet someone?
Is that what this
little black dress is about?
- No.
I have not met anyone.
No one new, anyway.
- Oh, my God.
Mr. Benvenuti.
When we drove out today,
he was chopping wood
all show-offy.
Mama, his wife just died.
- It's not Mr. Benvenuti.
Emilia, you're not
gonna believe this,
but I spent some time
with your father Thursday night.
- What?
- Well, we've been talking more
since your wedding,
and I guess you could say
we had a first date.
- Mom, why do you think
he's changed?
He has not changed.
- I don't think he's changed.
I think there's just as much
and as little to him
as there always was.
- You're just gonna pretend
like nothing happened?
- No, I'm gonna stop pretending
that was the only thing
about him.
- You're on your own,
both of you.
Enjoy yourself.
- Emilia.
[sighs]
- Sonia, I thought
this was my day.
- Dr. Soule said
she was going to call you.
- No, no, Sonia.
No, don't talk to her.
No, can you move away, please?
William, wait in the car.
- Carolyn, this is my day.
- Oh, no, you don't have
any more days, Emilia.
I've just spoken
to the principal.
If Jack wants to pick him up,
that's fine.
Otherwise, it's Sonia.
- Well, I don't know
what William told you, but-
- My pregnancy is my business,
not yours.
- Well, then maybe
you shouldn't have told Jack.
- I'm only six weeks along.
Anything could happen.
He'd be crushed.
Not that it would make
any difference to you.
It's very clear
you don't care about him.
- That's not true.
I like William very much.
- Not enough to make sure
he's wearing a helmet
when he's skating.
Not enough to take
his food allergy seriously.
Yes, that's right.
I heard about that, Emilia.
Maybe it's subconscious,
but it's obvious
you wish he weren't here.
- Now you're just
being paranoid.
- Oh, am I?
Am I?
Because I've never had anything
to fear from you, right?
You're so innocent,
so well-intentioned,
such a safe young woman
to invite into my home.
You have no right
to see Will alone.
I'm going to take care
of that legally.
Your relationship is
with his father, not him.
- But I'm his stepmother.
- That's nothing,
less than nothing.
And if you ever hurt him again,
so help me God,
I will have you arrested
for child abuse.
- Dr. Soule, please.
- Children aren't safe
around you, Emilia.
I think we've proven that.
Stay away from mine.
Let's go.
Come on.
- No, Carolyn, Carolyn.
Are you serious?
No, absolutely not.
She does not.
Okay, you know what?
I'm done.
That's it.
You don't have to like it.
That's the agreement.
Well, luckily,
it's not up to you.
Yeah, okay, great.
Good luck with that.
Yeah, bye.
- Guess you've heard.
- Yeah, I heard.
- She's gonna go to court.
- No, she's not gonna
go to court.
You're gonna pick him up
every Wednesday,
same as before,
and take a cab here.
- Okay.
- And he's coming Saturday
to the remembrance walk
with us,
the three of us.
- How do you know about that?
- Your mother told me.
Mindy called her.
I would like us all to go.
- Look, I don't even know
if I want to go.
So he certainly doesn't have to.
- Yes, he does.
She was his sister.
We're all going.
This is a family.
If Carolyn has to buy it,
so do you.
- Jack, I didn't tell him
on purpose.
He overheard both of us.
This isn't my fault.
- Oh, I know.
Nothing is your fault, right?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Everything just happens, right?
Everything just fucking happens.
[Holly Conlan's
You Are Good-bye]
[melancholy piano music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I remember here ♪
♪ I remember you and me ♪
♪ I remember wild
and wild and free ♪
♪ I remember stay ♪
♪ I remember, please,
don't ever leave ♪
♪ I remember
you made me believe ♪
♪ That tomorrow and today
the sun would hold our hands ♪
♪ But the night came in to stay
while you made other plans ♪
♪ You are the sun gone down ♪
- Emilia?
Ready?
- ♪ You are the moon
rushed round ♪
♪ You are good-bye ♪
- Emilia Woolf
and Jack and William.
I registered online.
- Hi, I'm Janet.
Here we are.
And what is your angel's name?
- Isabel.
Isabel GreenleafWoolf.
December 27th
to the 30th or-
do you want the day
that she was born or-
- 12/27?
- That's my stepson's name.
- I love that name.
We called him Billy.
He died of SIDS.
- I'm sorry.
- I know Billy's here
whenever I think of him.
Don't you feel that
about Isabel?
- She's gone.
I know the difference
between here and gone.
- The candles and the cones
are for down by the pond.
We'll tell you
when to light them.
We light them together.
There are blue and pink balloons
and white.
Take this.
You'll float this
in the pond at the end.
It'll just melt away
after a minute or so.
- I'm sorry I said that.
- No, it's fine.
Really.
- Emilia.
I found your mom and dad.
- My dad's here?
- Mm-hmm, over there with Will.
- I'm so sorry we're late.
Traffic and then parking.
You know your father.
He'll never just put the car
in the lot.
- You told him about the walk?
- No, I did
when he called last week.
- He invited me.
I found out your mother
was going.
I thought we'd come together.
Are Ben and Pia here?
- I didn't invite them.
- Aren't you gonna
put your heart thing on?
- I only have three.
- You can have mine.
I can go get some more
with Nono.
- Thank you.
- You okay?
- Welcome, everyone,
to this special walk
for remembrance and hope.
If you happen to lose your group
for any reason,
you'll be able to find us
at our destination.
We try to observe silence
during the walk until the end.
- Hey.
Hey, Jack.
- Hi.
- I'm proud of you.
I know this is hard,
but it'll be worth it.
I promise.
- "Death is nothing at all.
"I have only slipped away
into the next room.
"I am I,
and you are you.
"Put no difference in your tone.
"Wear no forced air
of solemnity and sorrow.
Play, smile..."
- Where are they?
- Who?
- My father and-
there.
- Emilia.
- [humming and laughing]
- What are you doing?
- We're practicing
our dance steps for the movie.
I'm gonna be Lyle.
- Remember how you and I
used to dance like Lyle
and Signor Valenti
when you were little?
- They're gonna start soon.
I think we should go.
- Right, right.
I think I might be
in this Lyle movie too, huh?
If they need
an old grandpa type.
- You're not a grandpa type.
Not his, anyway.
- Okay.
I think they're starting, huh?
- What are you doing here?
- We just didn't want
to interrupt,
you know, with our nonsense.
- No, why did you bother
coming here at all?
- You know why I came here.
I came for you,
for Jack, to support you.
- Mom's here to support me.
- Will, you want to walk over
with me?
- She was my granddaughter.
I'm here for Isabel.
- Don't you dare say her name.
- Emilia.
- Will, let's go.
Do you want to do this,
or do you want to go home?
- I will not allow you
to speak to me-
- You won't allow me?
- What are you doing?
- You know why my parents
got divorced, Jack?
I didn't tell you.
I didn't tell anyone.
You don't even know I know.
- Emilia, shut up.
- My father was spending
$1,000 a month
on a Russian stripper.
Sheldon Greenleaf:
judge/sex addict.
- Come on, Sheldon.
Let's go.
Come on, just walk.
- You don't have
to chase me away.
I'll just go, if you want.
- Okay.
Thanks, Simon.
- Um, I'm still gonna put
my hearts in the water, so...
- I'll call you later.
- For more than seven years,
he's traveIed the gIobe,
chasing tornadoes
on the rampage.
[knocking at door]
- Hey.
What you watching?
- Some storm chasers thing.
- Is it any good?
Will, I'm really sorry about
what happened today in the park.
I guess I just lost it.
- I'm kind of watching this.
- Okay.
Sleep well.
I'm sorry, Jack.
- I can't do this anymore.
- The whole thing just
freaked me out with the hearts
and the candles and
ectopic pregnancies with names.
- It's not a "Get Out
of Jail Free" card, Emilia.
- I know.
I know.
- Isabel's death doesn't make it
okay for you to hurt people.
- I know that.
- No, I don't think you do.
I'm gonna ask you a question.
- Jack, please.
- I want you to answer it.
Do you know why you
fell in love with me?
- When I first saw you,
it was...
it was like I recognized you.
- Yeah.
Recognized me.
That's probably right.
Your father, Emilia.
That's who you recognized.
- You are nothing like
my father.
- Are you kidding me?
I'm just like him.
- Jack.
- I'm a lawyer.
I'm a cheater.
I left my family
just like he did.
- Jack, I don't want to fuck
my father, okay?
I fell in love with you.
And you fell in love
with me too.
We couldn't help it.
- And that makes it okay?
It's not the two of us
fucking things up?
- That's the last thing
I'd want to do.
That's what he did.
My father betrayed me.
- No, he didn't betray you.
He betrayed your mother.
- That's the same thing.
- It's not the same thing.
Children are not
their mothers, Emilia.
William is not Carolyn.
You don't get to hate him.
- I don't hate William.
- You should see your face
when you look at him.
You're cold, Emilia.
Cold.
He's a child.
He needs to be protected.
And maybe we both
fucked that up.
Maybe I did more than you.
- Yeah, by letting him
near me, right?
- Oh, come on.
- Just say
what you really mean, Jack.
This is about Isabel.
- This is not about Isabel!
Not everything in the fucking
world is about Isabel.
She was my daughter too.
Losing her broke my heart too!
- Losing her?
We didn't lose her, Jack.
I killed her.
- What are you talking about?
- Remember?
You told me to put her
in the bassinet?
And I said I would
when she finished.
[baby squeaking]
And then you fell asleep,
and I was so tired.
But she had finally
started feeding,
so she was fine.
I fell asleep again.
[phone buzzing]
Then something woke me up.
And she was gone.
Isabel.
Isabel!
Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack!
She's not-
she's not breathing!
She's not breathing!
- Isabel.
- What do we do?
- Call 91 1.
I told you
and I told the police
that I found her
in the bassinet, but...
I lied.
She fell asleep in my arms.
I had her head in my hands
and her face pressed against me.
I-I fell asleep.
[sobs]
- No.
You did not smother her.
- I did, Jack.
You know I did.
You knew she wasn't
in the bassinet, didn't you?
- No, the autopsy report said
that she died of natural causes.
It said that she died of SIDS.
- No, the medical examiner
said she stopped breathing.
And the reason
she stopped breathing
was 'cause she couldn't.
- No, you-
you didn't-
she wasn't crushed.
The autopsy report
said specifically
that she wasn't crushed.
- I didn't crush her, Jack.
I smothered her.
- [sobbing]
- You're a lawyer, Jack.
Argue me out of it.
- [quietly sobbing]
- It's not just you.
I can't do this anymore either.
- [sobbing]
- I got it.
Are you okay?
[birds chirping]
- Taxi!
- You looked like you saw
a ghost back there.
- It's just,
you're never up here.
That's all.
- Oh, I was waiting for Will.
We made plans to be in that
movie together in the park.
- How is he?
- He didn't show.
I guess his mother said no.
Jack told me you left home.
You plan on going back?
- I don't think I'm really
very good for that family.
- Look, I was not
a very good husband.
But I am not a bad person.
I didn't think that
at the time.
I thought,
"I'm not fit to be here."
So I didn't fight
when your mother told me to go.
I didn't fight for her.
I didn't fight for you.
Don't make
the same mistake I made.
- My mistakes have happened,
and I've been punished.
- Isabel's not dead
because you needed
to be punished.
- Then why is she dead?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
She stopped living.
That's all.
Is that what you want?
You want to stop living?
- I want her back.
- That's not one
of your choices, honey.
I'm sorry.
That would be my choice too.
- I'm sorry for what I said,
what I said about you.
I don't know why.
- It's okay, honey.
It's all okay, hmm?
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
Oh.
Yeah?
This afternoon?
Okay.
Yeah, I know where
the office is.
Okay.
- Miss Greenleaf?
- Jack told me you moved out.
- You talked to him?
- Yes, I did.
William was very upset to see
you leave with your suitcase.
You never understood that
children have eyes, have you?
I called Jack to talk about it,
and he told me what happened
the night Isabel died.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
He asked if it was possible
that you could have smothered
her with your breast-
my medical opinion.
- What did you tell him?
- I told him,
yes, it was possible.
Yes, you could have
accidentally killed Isabel.
You probably had.
Any woman who's so casual
with William's safety
could just as easily
have fallen asleep
and smothered her own child.
William was very mad at me.
He said I should be
ashamed of myself.
He's very loyal, William.
- He knows?
- Yes, well, he overheard
the conversation.
I'm sorry.
My apartment's quite small.
- Your apartment's huge.
You must have been shouting.
- He said
that you loved Isabel
and that you
couldn't have killed her.
And I told him I hadn't said
that you'd killed the baby.
I told him that you might have
accidentally smothered her.
- Carolyn, why am I here?
I'd really like to leave.
- William asked me to help you.
He said because I'm a doctor,
I could find out what
really happened to Isabel.
- I didn't realize he cared,
since she wasn't a person,
you know,
according to the Jewish law.
- Your pediatrician got a copy
of the autopsy report.
- I know.
- Well, I had his office
fax it to me yesterday,
and I reviewed it
with a classmate of mine
from Stanford.
She's a pathologist who
specializes in neonatal cases.
She testifies
in criminal trials.
And she confirms
the coroner's conclusion.
- I know the official verdict:
SIDS.
- I asked for
more specific conclusions,
and she said
there's absolutely no evidence
to suggest
that Isabel was smothered.
Smothering always
leaves traces:
a torn upper lip frenulum,
signs of positional asphyxia,
dots of blood in the lungs,
and in Isabel's case,
there was no evidence
that she'd been smothered.
So you can't have smothered her.
You didn't kill your baby.
She died of SIDS.
You just had the misfortune
of holding her when she died.
- Your friend's a pathologist?
- A perinatal specialist.
Yeah, she's 100% secure
in her conclusions
that Isabel died from SIDS.
Based on the facts,
it's scientifically impossible
that she died from smothering.
Are you listening?
She also said
she'd speak with you
if you'd rather hear it
from her directly
or if you have
any other questions.
I need to know that you
understand what I'm saying,
so I'm going to repeat this
until you say
that you understand.
You didn't kill your child,
Emilia.
You didn't kill your baby.
Your baby died
because babies do sometimes.
They just slip away
for no reason.
It's no one's fault.
It's not your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
- [sobbing quietly]
- Do you understand?
- [sobbing]
I understand.
- Good.
I'm gonna leave you alone
for a while.
- Hi.
- I've-I just came
from Carolyn's office.
And she told me
I couldn't have killed Isabel.
She had her pathologist
look at the medical report.
- Sit down.
- I really think
you should call her
and hear what she has to say,
because I didn't do it.
- I never thought you did.
- But your face,
your face when I told you
and your face
the night that she died-
- How should I look, Emilia,
when my daughter dies,
when my wife says
she killed her?
People have their own feelings.
- I talked to my father,
and I apologized to him.
And you were right.
You were right.
I've been working through things
in our relationship
that are really about him
and my family and things-
- Emilia, don't.
None of this matters.
- We are not a mistake.
You're my family,
and I want to be with you.
- William's my family.
- And me,
William and me.
I love William.
- Em, please.
- He loves me.
He made his mother find out.
He loves me.
- I know.
It's the people who love you
you're the hardest on.
I'm sorry.
I just can't.
That's how it is.
- Okay.
No, no, no, Marilyn.
I don't need to talk to him.
You can just let him know
that I'll stop by
the apartment
tomorrow around noon, okay?
And I'll leave the keys
with the super.
And to answer his email,
no, I don't want
any of the baby stuff.
He can sell it.
eBay, whatever.
I don't know.
Yeah, seriously.
Thank you.
- ♪ I've been walking
in the same way ♪
♪ As I did ♪
♪ Is there anything
I can do for you, dear? ♪
♪ Is there anyone
I could call? ♪
♪ No and thank you,
please, madame ♪
♪ I ain't lost,
just wandering ♪
♪ Round my hometown ♪
♪ Memories are fresh ♪
♪ Ooh, the people I've met ♪
♪ Are the wonders of my world ♪
♪ Are the wonders
of my world ♪
♪ I like it in the city ♪
♪ When two worlds collide ♪
♪ You get the people
and the government ♪
♪ Everybody
taking different sides ♪
♪ Shows that we ain't
gonna stand shit ♪
♪ Shows that we are united ♪
[phone ringing]
♪ Round my hometown ♪
- Jack?
Hi.
He does?
Uh, where are you?
♪ ♪
♪ Are the wonders
of this world ♪
of my world ♪
♪ Of my world ♪
- Hey, Will.
What's up?
- Well, his mother's
getting married today.
And he wouldn't leave
the house without me,
and now he won't go inside
without you.
- Let me guess.
When I moved out
three weeks ago,
did you think your dad was gonna
move back in with your mom?
- Sort of.
Since you were done
being married,
they could be done
being divorced.
- But it's not working out
that way, is it?
She's marrying somebody else.
- Yeah.
- That's hard.
Not everything works out
the way you hope.
What can you do?
Will, help me out here, bud.
Why'd you ask to see me?
I would have thought I'd be
the last person
you'd want to see.
- Well, Sonia's in New Jersey.
But she's not family.
And I figured,
you're my sister's mom.
And that's family.
Right?
- I will always be
your sister's mom.
- Then how come
you don't live with us anymore?
- Well, because...
I don't belong with you guys.
It's like Lyle the Crocodile.
Lyle doesn't belong
in an apartment.
He belongs with
all the other crocodiles
at the Central Park Zoo.
- There are no crocodiles there,
only caimans.
- It's a metaphor, William.
You know metaphors.
What I'm trying to say is,
I'm sort of like Lyle.
You know, I don't belong
with you and your dad,
'cause, you know,
my teeth are too sharp
and my tail is too long.
- But Lyle does so belong
with his family.
They love him,
even though he's a crocodile,
even when he's not always
the nicest
or not so good with children.
- Lyle was always nice
to children.
- It's a metaphor, Emilia.
- Thanks, Will.
It's a really good one.
- [laughing]
So what do you say, Will?
You ready to do this?
- Let's not ruin her day, okay?
Not bad.
I mean, you look miserable,
but not bad.
That's what I shoot for.
- Come on.
- She'll hold our time,
won't she?
- I'm sure.
- Oh, thank God.
What happened?
Why is Emilia here?
Never mind.
Let's go.
We're late.
We were due in Judge Jody's
chambers ten minutes ago.
We have to run.
- Thank you.
- Anytime.
- What are you doing now?
- Getting fired, probably.
I've been working
at Simon's legal aid thing.
It's day six,
and I've been AWOL twice.
- I meant-
I thought maybe
we could have dinner
or take a walk or something.
- Are we allowed?
- Yeah.
We are.
- So I said, "Really?
Because the Big Bang
is older than the Bible and..."
Come on.
I'm telling a story.
- What are you carrying?
Nothing.
Plus, I'm 100.
Wait.
- Anyway, I said
that the Big Bang
was older than the Bible.
Then Michelle, Burton,
and Kimberly
said that I was gonna
go to hell.
Is there a hell?
- There are several.
Your classroom is one of them.
Let's sit down for a minute.
My feet are killing me.
These shoes.
- My mom says you always have
very comfortable-looking
shoes on.
She says everyone
in New Rochelle does.
- Here, this is for you.
Open it.
- It's the one
from Isabel's room.
- Nono gave it to me
when I was ten.
And now I'm giving it to you.
- It's better than a new one.
- Let's go see
if it still works.
- Most people don't know it,
but the real name
for the boat pond
is the Conservatory Water.
- Hmm, interesting.
It's a birthday present.
- But my birthday's
not until next month.
It's 32 days away.
- It's a birthday present
for you,
but it's not for your birthday.
It's for somebody else's
birthday.
Think.
- Blair?
- Yeah.
- He was born
while I was at school?
- Seven pounds, three ounces.
Your dad and I will take you
to see him tonight.
- Blair Soule-Tolliver I.
And I'm William Soule-Woolf I.
We're both first,
and we have
the same middle name.
- I know.
You've told me about 600 times.
- I'll have to make a new family
portrait with Blair in it.
You never saw the one I did.
- No, I did.
It was beautiful.
- I made Isabel an angel.
Even though I don't
really believe in angels,
I thought it would make you
feel better.
- It did.
Thank you.
- What do you think happened
to Isabel when she died?
- I don't know.
I guess I think
she just stopped being.
I think that whatever made her
different from everybody else
just disappeared when she did.
- No.
We're doing religions in school,
and Buddhists believe
in reincarnation.
That means when someone dies,
they come back as someone else.
And you might see
that dead person someday...
...and think to yourself,
"Hey, I really like
that person."
But you don't know why.
- I don't really
believe in that.
- I do.
I'm gonna be a Buddhist.
And I'm probably gonna be alive
for a long time.
So I'll probably run into her.
So I'll always keep
my eyes open.
When I find her,
do you want me to tell you?
- I'd really like that.
You do that.
- I love my boat, Emilia.
Thanks for the birthday present.
- Happy Blair's birthday,
William.
I love you.
- I know.
Me too.