- Shorter here.
- Shorter?
- Shorter.
- That is short enough.
OK, superstar?
- Wow!
- What's with the shirt?
That is the most frightenin' thing
I've ever seen. Looks like a deformity.
I'll fix that.
- Oh, God... yeah...
- That's better.
Now, if you was a guy,
I might even wanna fuck you.
You mean if you was a guy
you might even wanna fuck me.
So you're a boy. Now what?
Come on.
No fuckin' way.
Yes fuckin' way.
- A joke is a joke.
- Come on, don't be a pussy.
I'm no pussy. Let's go home.
- Someone's inside.
- You've got a date?
I gotta go.
Come here!
Can I talk to you just for a minute?
You look like a fuckin' idiot in that hat.
I'll be back. I'll be back.
Teena...
I don't want you comin' here
And wastin' all my time
I don't mind you hangin' out
And talkin' in your sleep
Yeah... athletic's nice.
But the thing is he's sweet.
And good hair. That's important.
I'm Billy. Are... are you Nicole?
... and talkin' in your sleep
I guess you're just what I needed
Just what I needed
I needed someone to feed...
You don't seem like you're from around here.
Where do I seem like I'm from?
Someplace beautiful.
I'll stand right here until
you're safe inside, OK?
OK.
You're just what I needed
You're not goin' anywhere!
Fucker!
Get back here, you fucker!
- You fuckin' dyke!
- You freak!
- You fucked my sister!
- Open the fuckin' door, you fuckin' faggot!
- Open the fuckin' door!
- Open this goddamn door!
- You fuckin' asshole!
- Brothers!
- I'll kick your fuckin' ass!
- Alicia.
- Who is Alicia?
- You fuckin' dyke!
- Damn, there's a lot of 'em!
- What have you done?!
Your fuckin' faggot cousin, too!
- Fuck!
- What is the matter with you?
I don't know! I don't know what went wrong!
You are not a boy! That is what
went wrong! You are not a boy!
They say I'm the best
boyfriend they ever had.
Do you want your mother to lock you up
again? Is that what you want?
No.
Then why don't you just admit
that you're a dyke?
Because I'm not a dyke.
Fucker!
- What are you doin'? Get outta my pants.
- The money you owe me. I want it back.
Jesus!
Careful with that.
You didn't have to do that. Jeez!
You're not crashin' here any more, Teena.
Get your stuff and go.
Bad night?
The worst.
- So what's your name?
- Candace.
I hate it, though. I'm thinkin' of changin' it.
Sometimes that helps.
I'm Brandon.
I'll pay if you get 'em.
- Sure.
- Marlboros.
I'll be right back.
Check this out.
My friend's sittin' there.
So?
I said get off.
Excuse me. Why don't you leave the lady
alone? I don't want any trouble here.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
I didn't ask you what you wanted,
you little fag.
You fucker! You motherfucker!
- I'll kick your white hick ass!
- Hold on, cowboy.
Can't I leave you alone for five minutes?
You fuck! I'm gonna get your ass!
Come on, stud. You got us into this.
Fucker!
Oh, shit. Cops, man.
They suck.
I would've had those guys
if you wouldn't have stopped me.
Oh, my God! John, look.
You're gonna have a shiner in the mornin'.
- I am?
- Yeah.
Oh, shit!
- You got a light, man?
- Oh, yeah, here.
You have got the tiniest hands.
No. They're big.
- Joe Louis had tiny hands.
- He didn't throw punches without defence.
If you're gonna get into fights
over girls, learn a few moves.
Come on.
- Hey, pussy.
- Fuck you, man!
- Tom, this is Brandon.
- Hey.
John. We'll give you a ride home,
as soon as we find the goddamn car!
Sorry! It's up here somewhere!
We're goin' to a party. You wanna come?
Candace, it's 70 miles away.
I don't care. I mean, the night
is young and... and I am a mess, so...
Good.
Are we there yet?
It's just up ahead... unless you wanna stop
at a roadhouse and get in another fight.
I don't know where the fuck I am.
Falls City?
What are you doin' down there?
That's not even on the map.
Oh, fuck!
Lonny, my life is a fuckin' nightmare.
I got this big court date next week
and I don't got anywhere to stay.
If I don't make it, I'm fucked.
Can I just stay at your house?
- What about those doctors?
- I went.
It's insane. You gotta see shrinks,
shoot hormones up your butt,
and it costs a fuckin' fortune. I'll be
an old man before I get that kinda money.
You gotta do somethin'.
You can't just keep runnin',
because you'll end up in jail.
For ever.
You really think I can do it?
You're the butch.
Now come straight to my house.
No stoppin' in bars, no stealin'...
- And no more girls.
- No more girls.
- Hey, handsome.
- Sleep all right?
- Yeah.
Candace.
I remember.
- This is Cody.
- Cody.
Wow! Beautiful.
You still broodin' over your fiancée?
What?
Oh. It's a real long story.
God, you're really good with kids.
Yeah... I got one of my own.
Hey, Brandon! Good news.
- I got you a ride.
- All right!
- He's goin' to Lincoln later tonight.
- Oh, wow!
Cool.
You suck!
- Hey, champ!
- Hey!
Tom only dates girls
with a little butt and a long crack,
right up to the small of the back.
That's how he picks 'em.
Tom likes 'em coyote ugly.
You know coyote ugly?
I'm all over some booty!
Thank you.
- Looks like you're ridin' with Ted Bundy.
- Shut up, John. He looks fine, right?
Yeah, just like family.
- Speakin' of.
- Hey, where's Lana?
We were gonna go on, but she wandered off.
You got time to stick around, right?
These girls get their shit together,
they're gonna do some karaoke.
Lana! Where you been?
Come on, Lana. Let's go on already.
Lana, it was your idea!
Who are you?
The lonesome Texas sun
Was settin' slow
And in the rear-view mirror
I watched it go
Shut the fuck up!
In her golden hair
I close my eyes for a moment
I'm still there
The bluest eyes in Texas
Are hauntin' me tonight
Another town
Another hotel room
Another dream that ended way too soon
Left me lonely
Prayin' for the dawn
Searchin' for the strength to carry on
The bluest eyes in Texas
Are hauntin' me tonight
Like the stars that fill...
What the fuck...?
You were gonna be five minutes!
- We got stuck in time warp!
- Jesus, get in the car already.
- Brandon, come with us.
- He's a psycho killer, anyways.
- Crash with me again.
- One more night, Tyson!
Come on, buddy.
Like I was sayin'...
I get to the house, you know?
My sister was totally naked
and totally on fire. Right, John?
- Tom was like "Where's my camera?"
- You saved everyone?
Oh, yeah. Tom's a big hero.
He rescued everybody. Right, dickwad?
So when they brought me in, they said "This
is the biggest fire we've seen in 50 years!"
"You're a hero, man!" And I was like "Yeah?"
And they were like "Yeah".
That's why they put me in
all them Lincoln newspapers.
- Probably seen me.
- That's cool.
- What the hell is that?
- Bumper-skiing, man.
Thank you.
Flippin' burgers. That's for squares, man.
Give me real work,
like in the oilfields or somethin'.
I wanna be a smoke jumper
out in Mount St Helens.
You know, fightin' fires,
makin' lots of money,
and then travellin' all around:
Memphis, Graceland, Tennessee...
You dick. Graceland is in Memphis
and Memphis is in Tennessee.
I know.
- Maybe you've had enough.
- I ain't had any.
No shit, man. People like you, you don't need
drugs. You just hallucinate 24 hours a day.
All right, Tom, you're up.
Not me, man. I'm drinkin'.
Brandon, that means you.
- Yeah, stud! Let's go, cowboy!
- Come on, you can do it.
Brandon is a mean prizefighter from Lincoln.
Be careful what you say to him.
Tough. Very tough.
Don't let 'em scare ya. You can do it.
Freak!
Come on!
You can do better than that!
One more time.
John, come on. Stop it, John.
Oh, OK, OK.
- Take it easy.
- I'm fine.
Yeah, you're fine. You're fucked up,
you know? You are one crazy little fucker.
- What are we goin' to do with you?
- Man, it's nothin'.
Wait, where are we goin'?
Wait, I'll drive!
There's a diamond
In her eye
It's a-shinin'
Up above
And the moon
In the sky
Say you want it
Tell her why
Where gamblers
Tell you lies
She'll take a tumble
And never lose
And in the mornin'
She'll wear a smile
She's made of stars
Oh, hi.
You sell, uh...
- Ruffles?
- Ruffles. Right over there.
Thank you.
Dream on, Lana.
- I can't be sellin' you no beer tonight.
- Fine. I'll browse.
The beer's in the back if you want it.
Hey.
Space cowboy!
I'm so wasted. I don't know
if I'm ever gonna come down.
- That's OK.
- I need beer.
Come here.
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK. Here.
- It's for me.
- Can I see some ID?
Sure.
How beautiful!
Jesus Christ, I feel like I'm on acid.
It's like an album cover.
Would you, uh... care to join me?
- Come on.
- Fuck off!
Don't you talk to me like that,
you skanky little snake.
Kwik Stop.
Hey! Lana!
Lana, wait. I'll drive you. I got Candace's car.
I'm walkin'.
Well, here.
What are you still hangin' around here for?
Well, I thought someone oughta
walk you home before you get an MIP.
I don't need anybody to walk me anywhere.
- Jeez, watch it.
- I don't need you to stop me from trippin'.
Lana, you are one cranky girl.
You'd be cranky, too, Mr I'm-Going-
To-Memphis-Graceland-Tennessee,
if you were stuck where there's nothin'
to do but go bumper-skiing and chase bats.
Hey, I've been bored my whole life.
Is that why you let John tie you to the back
of a truck and drag you around like a dog?
No. I just thought that's
what guys do around here.
Wait a minute. What's your name again?
Brandon.
The discs... took off from here.
That's all there is. Let's go back.
Lana? Lana?
Look, just go on home, OK?
God, I hate my life.
Lana?
I hate your life, too.
- Don't look at my stupid house.
- I'm not lookin' at your stupid house.
I'm lookin' at you.
What was I thinkin'?
Mom... come on.
Come on!
Did you eat?
It's all right.
Don't. It's OK.
Hi. Here, drink this.
You'll feel better in the mornin'.
Come on.
It's good for ya.
Yeah, I got a thing for cow.
I know a song about cows.
- My dad taught it to me.
- You're not gonna sing it for me, are ya?
No. I can't sing to save my life.
- Me neither.
- What?
Sure you can. You sing great.
That wasn't me. It was the karaoke.
So?
You were still great.
I couldn't do it.
A lot of people I know couldn't.
You don't know any songs about cows?
Sure I do.
Comin' to you this beautiful Friday,
October 27 th, this is Corn Report.
It is 8am. It is 45 degrees.
You'd better watch out. That winter is comin'.
Hey.
Is it always this nice in the mornin'?
I made you a little breakfast.
Wow!
Thank you.
My hand sucks.
How come Aunt Lana's asleep?
Well, your Aunt Lana is a nice girl, but
she is as lazy as the day is long, sweetheart.
Don't you be like that, OK? Huh?
- Answer if somebody asks a question.
- How are things with her mother?
She gave me April for a couple of days.
I love this song! Yes! Yes!
- Who's that lady?
Who's that lady?
A real, real, real fine lady
Beautiful lady
I wish somebody would introduce her to me
Oh, get up. Dance with me.
Come on. Get up.
I didn't get a chance
I asked her to dance
Asked her to dance
It was love at first sight...
April... come here.
Jesus, turn down the goddamn music!
- Come on, honey. Loosen up.
- No, let me go, let me go.
You motherfuckers!
Why did they let you fuckheads outta jail?
Belly is cravin', I got a shakin' in my head
I feel like I'm dyin' and I wish I was dead
If I live till tomorrow, that'd be a long time.
I'll reel and I'll fall, but I'll rise on cod'ine.
You'll forget you're a woman
You'll forget about men
Try it just once and you'll try it again
You'll forget about life
You'll forget about time
And live all your days a slave to cod'ine
And it's real, oh, it's real
One more time
And some of them fall
And rise on cod'ine
I'm an asshole.
What?
Blowout.
- What happened?
- Aw, I'm in the doghouse again.
- I've been there my whole life.
- Women, right?
Yeah.
- You gonna do a little damage control?
- And then you'll fuck it up again.
Come on. Oh, my goodness!
Hey... who are you? What's your name, huh?
- April.
- April?
- How'd you get such a pretty name?
- My daddy.
Yeah, that's true. I named her.
- Where are you goin'?
- See Lana.
All right. Go on.
Got an extra cig, man?
Thanks, man.
Is, uh... is she Lana's?
Lana's? No.
No, I had April with a different girl. Mallory.
This here's my real family,
even if it isn't my real home, you know?
I mean...
Lana...
I don't know. It's kinda hard to explain.
Well, I got 12 more like this at home.
I keep it in a secret place.
She wrote to me when I was in lockup.
- Lana did?
- Yup. She wrote to me.
Even my own mom didn't
write to me. But she did.
Lana and her mom. They took me in.
Fuck. Fucker.
- Brandon, honey, where are your folks from?
- I'm from Lincoln.
But my dad's out in Memphis right now,
and my mom's in Hollywood.
- Hollywood?
- Yeah.
- Oh, wow!
- Yeah. My sister's a model.
- That's glamorous!
- Hey, Brandon,
- Why don't you clean these ashtrays for us?
- Fuck you!
I'm just playin' with you, bud.
Brandon, honey, come here.
Over here. Closer, where I can see you.
Let me look at you in the light. Come on.
Come on.
Come here. Let me.
I can believe you got a model for a sister.
You're like a little movie star yourself.
Hey, April. Want a beer?
Hey! What the fuck are you doin'?
Here you go, hon. Here you go.
Have some of Daddy's.
Come on. Come on. Little bit.
Four years ago, you wouldn't have thought
he could take care of himself, let alone a kid.
Shit, four years ago you wouldn't
have been able to talk to him.
Prison?
And her mother! Jesus Christ!
And this one...
- This one kept that boy's spirit alive.
- Mom, just forget about that.
The little bastard pissed on me!
She hasn't had the proper trainin'!
- Your mother's an asshole, you know that?
- John, she had an accident.
It's OK, sweetie. It's not your fault.
Havin' fun?
Yeah.
- What do you think of my mom? Weird, huh?
- No, I like her.
I think she's funny.
- Are you for real?
- Excuse me. Am I interruptin' somethin'?
Take a picture of me and my daughter.
Lana's dad gave us that.
- I don't feel like havin' my picture taken.
- Come on, honey. Just one.
Come on, son.
Well... refill time.
Bring it in when you're ready, OK?
Here, look. It's not bad, huh?
What?
- No.
- Why not? You're beautiful.
Come over here.
I had a dream about you last night.
You did? What happened?
Come on, tell me the dream.
Someone walked me home
last night. I think it was you.
No fair!
Lana! It's time to go to work!
John, you're too fucked up.
Why don't you let Brandon drive?
Hey. Here you go, little buddy.
You all right?
Tom!
Nice car.
Why don't you turn down your radio?
Yeah, totally.
- What the fuck are you lookin' at?
- Wall people.
- What the fuck did you say?
Let me outta this fuckin' car!
Bite me, you fuckin' fudgepacker!
- Eat me.
- Fuck you!
- Go after 'em!
- Step on it!
Go! Come on, go!
Come on, pussy. Go faster, you cocksucker.
Come on, Brandon! Go!
Go, Brandon!
Oh, no, it's the man!
Fuck! It's the piggers!
Come on, these cops are onto us.
What the fuck...?
Don't stop, don't stop. Go faster.
- Brandon...
- Go faster.
Brandon, stop.
That's it, that's it.
They ain't got no fuckin' balls.
When you hit the gravel, drop to 40.
I can't see.
That's OK. Neither can he. You're flyin'.
Take it out.
Get off me, dick. I wasn't doin' anythin'.
Goin' awful fast back there, Mr Brayman.
- Tell me what you're doin' in Falls City.
- Just visitin', sir.
Yeah? Where are you stayin'?
He's stayin' with me.
I can't run a check on this.
Our computers are down.
But I could run you all in right now.
You could let these guys go.
They ain't got anythin' to do with it.
I got a little carried away back there.
- We don't got anythin' like this in Lincoln.
- A dustless highway?
Only one in Nebraska.
That's a hundred-foot drop.
- I won't lock you up, but you get a ticket.
- OK.
Those are residential streets
back there, so you slow down.
- Do you read me, Mr Brayman?
- Absolutely, sir.
Did you see this ID?
That's pretty slick: Charles Brayman.
I let you down. I'm sorry.
Man, don't worry. We'll take you
to the tunnel, chase some bats.
Yeah... it's like the tunnel of love.
God, Candace, would you get a grip?
- Is that your real birthday?
- No. November 10th, '72.
Hey, that's next week. Let's have a party.
21! You're gonna be a man!
Shit.
Don't you never pull that shit again.
- What?
- You heard. Don't never pull that shit again.
You got me stopped by the fuckin' cops.
Why... But you're the one
who told me to race after 'em.
I had you in the clear and you fucked up.
John, it's over. Don't get upset.
I'm not upset.
You almost got us killed.
- I almost got us killed?
- Whoo! Brandon...
- You led us 90mph into a cloud of dust.
- Brandon...
- We were about to go off a 400-foot ravine.
- Shit! Fuck!
- Get outta my goddamn car.
- All right...
Get outta my motherfuckin' car!
- Get outta my goddamn motherfuckin' car!
- Shit! Get off me, you sick fuck!
Get outta my goddamn motherfuckin'
shit-eatin' cocksuckin' car!
Get out!
- Not you.
- Fuck you!
Welcome to the psycho ward.
Come on, Kate. He's takin' us to work.
You know, Tom set that fire hisself.
That's my car!
Doctors say he ain't got no impulse control.
I'm the only one who can control that fucker.
Come on. We'll walk you home, Candace.
You ever try this?
Tom, did you set your own
family's house on fire?
What about this?
You ever do this?
What the fuck, Tom?
Some people punch holes in walls.
This... helps snap me back into reality.
Gets a control of this thing inside of me,
so I don't... lash out at someone.
Me and John used to do it
to ourselves all the time in lockup.
I could always go deeper than him.
He was such a wuss.
Try it.
I guess I am a pussy, compared to you.
I'm just jokin' with you, man.
Fuck!
Brandon... hey.
- Lana.
- I'm so sorry. I just had to see someone nice.
I just got off work.
I'm havin' a nervous breakdown.
Just a minute. I have to pee, OK?
God, I was scared to death that
Candace was gonna catch me.
She's obsessed with findin' a husband.
You're her favourite candidate.
I can't believe you worked last night.
You must be exhausted.
Me neither. I do it all the time, though.
You don't have to be sober to weigh spinach.
Thanks for the coffee.
I'm crashin' really hard, though.
l, um... have to go back to Lincoln
to take care of some stuff.
- You really leavin'?
- Yeah.
Are you gonna see your sister? The model?
Yeah.
Nicole?
She's pretty. Is she gonna be there?
Yeah. Now that she's married,
we're gonna be takin' off any second.
So... where are you goin'
on your big trip outta here?
I don't know.
I guess it's not all worked out yet.
That's OK.
Thanks for givin' your address to the cops.
It was nothin'.
I might hitchhike.
Really? I've never done that.
Me neither.
Well...
This might sound really stupid, but, um,
do you think there's anywhere
I could make money doin' karaoke?
Why not? People make money
doin' all sorts of things.
Did you really write letters to him in prison?
Gimme a break. I was 13 years old.
Who told you that? My mom?
He did.
You better go.
That rusty nail over our front door
Is where I hung our tears in a ring
I threw that horseshoe into the wheat
To see what love can bring
Cos you're in your bed and I'm in mine
On either side of town
I think I might take a ride...
Please... Please don't get mad.
One night. One night and I'm gone.
They're not gonna lock me up, are they?
Teena, how the fuck do I know what they're
gonna do? I'm sick of watchin' you fuck up.
But... but I'm not fuckin' up.
It is so good down there, Lonny.
In Falls City? They hang faggots
down there. Did you know that?
You've never even been there. Look.
Look. See, isn't she beautiful?
If you like white trash.
I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
Before or after your sex-change operation?
Before or after you tell her you're a girl?
Shut up!
It's... it's different. It's workin'.
I'm not gonna fuck it up this time.
I hope they do lock you up tomorrow.
Keith Pierce, for spray-paintin' and
smashin' 50 new cars, you are sentenced
to six months at the
juvenile detention centre.
Teena Brandon.
Teena Brandon, docket 72391.
Teena Brandon, docket 7 2391,
grand theft auto.
Psst! Lana! Down here!
Brandon! Where'd you get that?
Nice hat.
I gotta go. My break's almost over.
It all looks so different from the outside.
Oh, you're so pretty.
I feel like I'm in a trance.
Am I goin' too fast?
I cannot wear these. They make me look fat.
Quit changin' the subject.
I saved your ass at work.
Now tell us what's goin' on.
Yeah, I bet Brandon doesn't think you're fat.
- Nobody looks fat when they're layin' down.
- I knew it! I fuckin' knew it!
- We just drove around, takin' pictures.
- Yeah, right.
Oh, I cannot talk about it!
It's too intense.
Come on, Lana! I can't take it!
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I mean, uh... I don't know.
You're so handsome.
And then we took off our clothes
and went swimmin'.
Don't be scared, Brandon.
But did you do it?
What do you think?
- What did you wish for?
- I know what he wished for. Yeah, baby!
Oh, Mom, don't talk so gross!
- Happy birthday.
- You shouldn't have, really.
Keepin' me strong, Mom?
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Sorry, I forgot mine.
- That's OK.
- I haven't wrapped mine yet.
- Hey, grease monkey.
- How ya doin'?
We were doin' a job in Omaha.
We could've used a lookout.
John Lotter, I know your mother, and
I know she taught you how to knock.
We could've been lyin' around
here naked, for all you know.
- Where's Lana?
- In her room.
Come on, get a beer, John.
It's Brandon's birthday. Sit with us.
Hey, gorgeous.
Walk right in, why don't you?
- I'm busy fixin' my hair.
- Your hair's beautiful. I love your hair.
- I got this for you up in Omaha.
- Cool.
Tom and I went up to Lincoln
for a couple of days.
Stealin' cars?
I came by the factory before we left
and you weren't there.
So?
Nice.
- Don't get upset. I just wanna talk.
- About what?
About you and Brandon.
I'm just lookin' out for ya.
What are you talkin' about?
He's your friend, too.
I miss you.
- I do.
- Stop it, John. You give me the creeps.
- You're like a stalker.
- Fuck you!
- No. No. Fuck you.
- John, I'm sorry.
I just need some privacy right now.
Yeah.
You know I just wanna protect you.
I know.
No one's ever protected me like you.
What do you see in him?
I know he's nice and everythin',
but he's kind of a wuss.
I know he's no big he-man, like you.
There's just somethin' about him.
Oh, yeah.
"There's just somethin' about him"!
Stop makin' fun of me!
- Lana, honey, are you fuckin' him?
- Goddamn it, John!
- It's none of your fuckin' business!
- You are!
Excuse me. Did I interrupt somethin'?
Lana, are you OK?
Don't even think about it, John.
- John, let's hit the road, man.
- No. It's Brandon's birthday.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Oh, man. I've known her
since she was like this high.
I could tell you stories about her.
You know what kind of stories?
She told me about you guys.
And I can't think of a better guy to give
Lana to than you, so happy birthday!
Thanks, John.
You know, just one thing you gotta
remember, little man, is this is my house.
Come on, turn up the music!
Turn up the music!
I quit.
- Quit what?
- My evil job.
I've just been thinkin' and thinkin',
what am I doin' here?
And then it came to me...
I'll go to Memphis with you.
- Memphis?
- I got it all figured out.
You're right.
I'll make money singin' karaoke...
- Lana...
- You'll manage me,
and, if I'm no good, you'll sing
and I'll manage you. Perfect.
Nothin' can go wrong if we're together.
Lana, um... it's a little more complicated
than that, you know? Memphis is far.
It's 1,327 miles.
Yeah,
but, you know, I been thinkin'.
We could just start our own trailer park
right here in Falls City.
- You don't wanna go with me?
- No! Of course I do!
That's the point. I'll marry you right now.
Oh, Lana... you're in trouble again.
Actually, that ain't Lana's, it's mine.
I'll take care of it.
I just got my first paycheck.
Come on, now. You go sit down.
- OK.
- I'll bring your breakfast.
The thing about the trailer park
is we'll have picnic tables
and people playin' music,
and barbecues every night.
We'll invite our friends:
Candace, Kate, your mom.
Heck, even John,
if you two don't kill each other first.
And best of all, we'll have our own Airstream.
If that's a hassle, you could
mail the receipt to my house.
That's all right. I'll just be
a moment. I'll be right back.
Just one second.
It's slow.
Miss Brandon?
Miss Brandon, we put your Charles Brayman
ID number through the computer yesterday,
and this is what the Lincoln
authorities faxed us over.
You tell me.
Wow.
This Teena chick seems pretty messed up.
What the hell is this?
- Who wrote this?
- That guy who stayed with you. Brandon.
Dear Lonny, I bet you can't guess where I am.
That's right, back in jail, in Falls City.
I'm so tired of fuckin' up.
I'm tryin' to stay strong, but I don't know
if I can face all the mistakes I've made.
I'm stayin' tough.
No!
Candace... why do you look so funny?
Lana! Lana, what are you doin' here?
What are you doin' here?
The girls' cell?
This place is crazy.
It's, like, put you wherever they want.
It's fine with me, I guess, but...
Julie, give us a break, man. Watch
the rest of the show. Tell us how it ends.
We only got three channels. I hate it.
Brandon, what's goin' on?
You want the truth, don't ya?
It sounds a lot more complicated than it is.
Do you have any water?
Cos I'm really... My voice is... dry.
I'm a hermaphrodite.
What?
Come here.
It's a person who has both...
girl and boy parts.
Brandon's real name is Teena Brandon.
Well, see, Brandon's not quite a he.
- Brandon's more like a sh...
- Shut up. It's your business.
Look, I don't care if you're half monkey
or half ape. I'm gettin' you outta here.
I would say I'm sorry
If I thought that it would change your mind
But I know that this time...
Candace,
I spoke to Lana's mom.
She's missin'.
- You know where she is?
- I don't know. I swear.
Candace, if you know anythin',
you better tell me now.
You know what?
I already opened my big mouth,
and now no one's talkin' to me.
Candace, I'm talkin' to ya.
Either I'm fucked up,
or something's totally weird.
Come on, Kandi. You can tell me.
I won't tell anybody.
- I need more to drink.
- There you go.
I try to laugh about it
Hidin' the tears in my eyes, cos
Boys don't cry
I would tell you that I loved you
If I thought that you would stay
But I know that it's no use
You already gone away
Missed out your limits
Pushed you too far
Took you for granted...
Goddamn it! I wanna touch you
the way you touch me.
No. Wait.
Fuck you, Brandon!
Fuck you!
I want you to feel what I feel.
Lana, wait. Wait.
Soon. I promise.
- Is she back yet?
- No, and I'm worried.
- Come on, let's just go find Lana.
- He'll show up.
Kate, I want you to tell me what's goin' on.
Mom, you read the paper today?
- No.
- Candace, show Mom the paper.
- John, you promised.
- Come on. Is Lana your friend or not?
Just gimme that, honey.
"Teena Brandon, 19,
picked up on a speeding violation."
So? Brandon got a ticket.
The name, Mom. The name.
He's brainwashed her. That's what they do.
Get out! There's nothin' in Lana's room.
John, leave her stuff alone.
I'm not touchin' her stuff! If you were any
kind of mother, this wouldn't have happened.
- I told you you couldn't trust him.
- You never told me anythin'.
Come on, Kate, you got to stop this.
Like you wouldn't jump in if it wasn't
totally obvious you're in love with Brandon!
Holy fuckin' mother of fuck!
Tom, check this out.
"Cross-Dressers and Transsexuals:
The Uninvited Dilemma."
"Sexual identity crisis."
Jesus fuckin' Christ, Tom,
check this out... OK, look at this.
"The grafted skin will mimic
the skin of the natural penis."
Get this sick shit away from me!
Just give it a minute, OK?
She's gotta think I was at work.
OK.
But I'll miss you.
- Whoa!
- Thank God you're home.
Did you party all night without me?
Come on in, have a beer.
Look, I gotta take a shower. I don't mean
to be antisocial, but I'm really tired, guys.
- How was work, Lana?
- Oh, you know, whatever, Mom. The usual.
Mom, what the hell's goin' on?
God, what did you tell them?
We called work. We know you weren't there.
Why is he talkin' to me?
What are you? My dad?
Why are you all starin' at me?
Get away! You're gross! You're
horrible people! Get outta my room!
We're worried. We're just tryin' to save you.
You got a sick way of showin' it.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey... Oh, my God!
Brandon, turn around and go, now.
This is a nuthouse.
- I'm just worried about you.
- Stop with that!
- We just need to talk.
- What do you need to talk about?
There are some things I don't understand.
You took a leak with me and... pardon my
French, Mom, but... you shook off your dick.
And what was that bullshit
about payin' child support for a kid?
- You been lyin' since you came into town.
- No...
When you rode in on your
pussy-whipped faggot horse.
The fact is, little dude,
you're nothin' but a goddamn liar.
You know what we do to liars?
There was never any Memphis, was there?
We're totally fuckin' with you! Seriously!
Go get Brandon a beer.
We were wonderin' about this paper
that you are in, Teena.
It's our ticket. They're hungry for news here.
Yeah, but what I'm
wonderin' about is the name.
Huh, Brandon? I mean, huh, Teena?
I really fucked up.
I borrowed one of Candace's cheques
and I got that ticket and this fake ID.
I guess I just need to learn to stay home.
Brandon, I invite you into my home and
you expose my daughter to your sickness.
- Did you ever think about Lana?
- That's all I've been thinkin' about.
You know, Lana, if you are a lesbian,
you just need to tell me.
- John, I'm not. Mom, it's not...
- Stop it. It's not Lana. It's me.
Lana, I'm so sorry. Mom, wait, I can explain.
We can work this out. I have this thing...
You fuckin' pervert.
Are you a girl or are you not?
There's a real easy way to solve this.
- Fuck you! Get the fuck off of me.
- You want a fight?
- Get out of here with your sick psycho brain!
- I could kill you for lyin' to Lana.
John, there's not gonna be
any killin' goin' on, OK?
Do you trust me enough to let
Brandon show me?  Then I'll tell you.
Do you trust me enough?
OK, John?
Yeah.
OK.
Thank you, guys.
Fuck me!
Holy fuck!
Get over here. I'm so sorry, Brandon.
Lana... I gotta explain.
Oh, no, no, no. Button up your pants.
Don't show me anythin'.
Think about it.
I know you're a guy.
OK, but you gotta listen. I was born
with this weirdness, like a birth defect.
It's actually not that rare,
but these doctors are tryin' to fix it.
But I have really weird stuff, too.
Don't be scared.
Look how beautiful it is out there.
- Oh, Lana...
- That's us. We can beam ourselves out there.
So what are you gonna tell 'em?
I'm gonna tell 'em what they wanna hear.
I'm gonna tell 'em what we know is true.
Mom,
I seen him in the full flesh.
I seen it.
I know he's a man.
Problem done. Now let's go to bed.
Son of a bitch!
What have you done to my baby?
What the fuck are you, you motherfucker?!
Huh?
Tell me!
You little liar.
Kate, get her outta here.
Come on.
All I need is the truth, little buddy. Come on.
All right... I'm sorry to put you
through this. Wait...
- Unstrap his belt.
- I'll do it!
Tom, just turn the light off. I'll do it! Please!
Fuck! John, let me the fuck go!
What's goin' on in there? Open the door!
Open the fuckin' door!
- John, please! Please!
- What do you see?
If it's down here, it's the tiniest I ever saw!
- Touch it.
- Oh, goddamn it, I can't! God, I can't do it!
What the fuck are you?!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Let me go! John, let me go!
Open the door!
Don't look like no sexual identity crisis to me.
- Open the door!
- Get in here.
Look at your little boyfriend.
Come on, I'm holdin' you until you look.
Look!
Leave him alone!
- Leave him alone!
- Him?
Him?!
- Get outta my house!
- John, we called the cops.
- Go on. Get out.
- You are just too fucked up!
Leave us alone!
- Leave me alone. Please, just leave me alone!
- You promised... You promised...
I guess that's everythin'.
You know, I told Brandon...
that nobody has a right to do that to you.
Come on, we've done everythin' we can.
Let's get outta here.
- Let's go.
- I'm waitin' for Brandon.
Your mom's right.
Until this is straightened out,
it'd be better for everyone
if Brandon stays someplace else.
What are you talkin' about?
lt'd be better to lock up Tom and John.
Lana, everythin' Teena told us was lies.
Everythin'. Everythin'.
We need to go.
Now.
Come on!
Come on. Get up!
I'm askin' you this
because if this goes to court
that question's gonna come up
and I'm gonna want an answer.
Uh, I don't know why I have to...
All right, let's back up.
After they pulled your pants down
and seen you was a girl,
what did he do? Did he fondle you any?
No.
Didn't that kinda get
your attention somehow?
That he wouldn't put his hand in your pants
and just play with you a little bit?
I don't know what he did.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go, buddy.
Come on, let's go for a ride. Move!
I can't believe that he pulled your pants
down, and if you are a female,
that he didn't stick
his hand in ya or his finger in ya.
Well, he didn't.
Get outta the car.
Get outta the car. Come on.
- John...
- Shut up. Move!
- Wait, John.
- Shut up.
- John, it's me. Brandon. You know me.
- Don't hurt me.
- Take off your shirt.
You know you brought this on yourself,
Teena. Tom, get out the car!
- I'm...
- Take off your shirt. Take off your shirt.
You can make this easy, or you can
get the shit knocked outta you.
All right...
Please, John, wait. Please...
We can work this out. Please.
Get off me. Get off!
Wait, John. Please. Please don't hurt me.
After you had your pants off,
how were you positioned in the back seat?
On my back.
You was on your back?
You say you're 21 and you've
never had sex before. Correct?
That's right.
When they had a spread of ya,
when they poked ya,
where'd they try to pop it in first?
I said move your fuckin' hands!
My vagina.
Where?
Go ahead, man. Take it.
Come on. Come on.
Get up there. Get up!
Take this fuckin' thing off.
No!
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Just... just take me home, OK?
If you keep our little secret,
we'll stay friends. Right, little buddy?
Cos if you don't...
we'll have to silence you permanently.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
I mean, this is all my fault. I know.
You OK in there, little dude?
Yeah!
I'm fine!
I'm gettin' a beer. You want one?
No.
Make sure you get yourself
cleaned up in there.
Will you need any help?
No! I'm good!
You almost ready in there, little dude?
Gimme a break, man!
Gimme two fuckin' seconds!
Tom! Tom!
Oh, my God! Brandon!
What are you doin' here?
Mom, stop it! He's hurt!
Lana...
I don't want it in the house.
Mom, stop it. He's hurt!
I'm sorry.
Call an ambulance! Now!
OK, almost.
So they assaulted you?
If you don't mind, it's just necessary...
I need for you to take your pants off, OK?
Please.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
How do you know they raped me?
Why do you run around with guys,
bein' you're a girl yourself?
- Why do you go around kissin' girls?
- I don't know what this has to do with...
I'm tryin' to get some answers,
so I can know exactly what's goin' on.
Are you gonna answer
my question for me or not?
I have a sexual identity crisis.
You what?
A sexual identity crisis.
Brandon...
I just wanted to say I'm really... sorry.
Oh, my God!
What did they do to you?
Oh, my God. Come in here. Come in.
Go inside.
That is a bunch of bull.
If I wanted to rape somebody, I got Mallory.
Listen, John.
I'm just here to tell you
that it's been reported.
Listen to me. So if you did anythin',
or anythin' happened in that room,
you get it cleaned up.
We went out, um... muddin' last night,
and we got stuck in a ditch.
- Seriously.
- Why is she fuckin' makin' lies like that?
Seriously!
You want a beer?
- No, no, no.
- Oh, come on.
You take care, John.
I'll come back later. We'll play cards.
Why don't you just give it
a few days, all right?
OK.
God, you're such a stupid fuckin' pussy!
What, man? You're paranoid.
She came here to warn us.
She ain't gonna say nothin'.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
No, sir.
Yes, sir. Tomorrow mornin'.
Yeah, we'll come by.
We have to go by the station
tomorrow mornin'.
Can I come sit by you?
Do you hate me?
Do you need anythin'?
God!
You're so pretty!
You're just sayin' that cos you like me.
No!
What were you like
before all this?
Were you like me? Like a girl girl?
Yeah.
Like a long time ago.
And then I guess I was just like a boy girl.
And then I was just a jerk.
It's weird.
Finally everythin' felt right.
Boy, that's pretty weird, huh?
Yep.
That dream I had? The first night?
We were on the highway together.
We can still do it.
Lana... l, um...
Look, I never been on the highway
or the Grand Canyon, or any place like that.
Until I came here,
I never even been outta Lincoln.
I never even met my dad.
He died before I was born,
and my sister ain't no model in Hollywood.
I don't know if I'm gonna know how to do it.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Um, I was wonderin'
if you wanna come home
to Lincoln with me.
My mom, she'll love you.
And then you gotta meet my cousin Lonny.
He's a pain, but he's great.
When are we goin'?
We have to leave tonight.
Candace says she'll drive us.
All right.
I better get my stuff, then.
OK.
I'll be right back.
Lana...
Sorry.
We could leave right now. It's better.
OK.
Don't pack too much. We'll send for it later.
Tomorrow mornin'
you and I will be eatin' breakfast in Lincoln.
Did you do somethin' to your hair?
I don't know.
You like it?
I don't know. I guess.
I'll try and put it back.
All right... we should go.
It's OK, Lana.
You don't have to come
with me now. There'll be time.
Just make sure you get out.
OK?
- John, what are you doin' here?
- Where are they? Are they here?
Just wait, OK?
I'll be right back.
Brandon ain't here.
- Where is he?
- I don't know, but he ain't here.
Where's Lana?
Brandon's at Candace's.
- What?
- He's at Candace's place.
- You found him?
- Yeah.
- What are you guys doin'?
- Oh, shit.
Listen, you wanna go out for a drink?
- No.
- Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Where are we goin'?
- Told you not to bring her.
Stay off the main road.
Think they'd recognise her
if we chopped off her head and her hands?
John...
We're just takin' care of a couple of dykes.
Are you one of 'em?
Where'd you get that?
You still plannin' on goin' to Memphis?
Memphis...
Why are we here?
Any others in there, you take care of 'em.
What are you gonna do to Candace?
No! John, no!
Wait! She's got a baby, John!
John, look at me. Look at me. No!
Get the fuck off of me!
Candace!
Get the light, get the light.
Where the fuck is it?!
Where the fuck is she?
John...
- Don't hurt my baby!
- Stop...
Shut the fuck up!
- Don't hurt Candace.
- Don't listen to her!
She has nothin' to do with this!
John, you were right about me.
I just keep gettin' back up.
I said shut up. Shut up!
Candace!
- Don't listen to her!
- He said shut up.
John...
Teena...
Please don't hurt my baby, Tom! Please!
Why didn't you leave?
We can still do it.
No!
Tom, don't! Please don't hurt my baby,
Tom! Please, God, please!
No!
Come on.
Come on, Lana.
Dear Lana, by the time you read this,
I'll be back home in Lincoln.
I'm scared of what's ahead, but when
I think of you... I know I'll be able to go on.
You were right. Memphis isn't far at all.
I'll be makin' a trip out on
the highway before too long.
I'll be waitin' for ya.
Love always and for ever. Brandon.