- Your ticket, please.
- Oh, yes.
- Welcome aboard, Miss Debenham.
- Thank you.
Bosporus Ferry will shortly depart
from Istanbul Sirkeci Station,
connecting with the Orient Express.
Here's your ticket,
Monsieur Poirot.
I'm afraid you've still got another hour.
Well, then, please do not wait.
Not wait? After all you've
done for us, Monsieur Poirot?
My general's orders were to
ensure your safe departure.
He also wished me
to thank you again
for saving the honor of the British
garrison in Jordan.
The brigadier's confession
was opportune.
I say, how did you do it?
Was it the old thumbscrew,
you know, the rack?
Yes. Well, you'll be able to rest
as soon as you get to Stamboul.
The...
The church of Santa Sofia
is absolutely magnificent.
You have seen it?
No.
Come on.
Move. Come on.
Get up. Come on.
Chop-chop.
I hope we did the right thing booking
you into a hotel on the European side
rather than the Asian side.
I have no prejudice against
either continent.
The... The crossing
should be pleasant.
The Bosporus is always calm.
You have crossed by the ferry?
No.
Welcome, Colonel Arbu...
Arbu... Arbut...
Arbuthnott.
The Bosporus Ferry will shortly
depart for Istanbul Sirkeci Station,
connecting with the Orient Express.
Not now.
Not now. When it's all over.
When it's behind us. Then.
What a funny little man.
Obviously a frog.
It can be important.
...between East and West, where you
can eat the finest Oriental food.
Good evening, sir.
This way, please.
Ecco finalmente un amico.
Monsieur Poirot.
Bianchi.
How are you, my friend?
- Good to see you.
- You have saved me from apoplexy.
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
You have not dined well.
The skewers are of better quality
than the kebab.
The bottle is more
distinguished than its wine.
And the coffee.
Fortunately, I have been called
to London. I leave tonight.
- On the Orient Express?
- How else?
Evviva! I have a traveling companion.
Eccellente.
Well, where shall we dine?
I am desolate, Monsieur Poirot.
There is not one single first-class
sleeping berth on the entire train.
- What? In December?
- In December, signor.
Has Bulgaria declared war on Turkey?
Are the aristocracy fleeing
the country?
I am a director of the line,
Monsieur Hercule Poirot
is not only a detective
of international fame and distinction,
but he is also my personal friend.
Signor Bianchi, Monsieur Poirot...
Courage, my friend,
we'll arrange something.
Andiamo!
We must go. Come on.
The Orient Express will depart
from platform one at 9 p. M.
For Uzonköprü, Sofia, Belgrade,
Zagreb, Brod, Trieste, Venice,
Milan, Lausanne,
Bazel, Paris, Calais,
with connections for London.
Bonsoir, Pierre.
Madame la Princesse,
mes hommages!
Numéro quatorze.
- Fräulein Schmidt, Willkommen!
- Guten Tag.
Bett. Nummer sechs.
- Danke schön.
- Bitte schön.
Orient Express departs from
platform one at 9 p. M.
Az Andrenyi Grófot es Gröfnét
mindig szívesen látom.
A 12-tes.
Mrs. Hubbard.
It's always an honor to greet you.
You have your favorite number, 11.
Ecco, Signor Bianchi.
Benvenuto!
Numero nove. Come sempre.
Grazie, Pierre. I understand
that you are full up.
It's unbelievable, signor.
All the world elects to travel tonight.
Nonetheless, you must find room
for Monsieur Poirot here.
Monsieur Hercule Poirot?
- The famous...
- Precisely.
And he is also a personal
friend of mine.
Please be so good as to direct...
Fröken Ohlsson, god afton!
Plats nummer sju.
Sju...
Something is lost?
My little medal of St. Christopher,
to bring me luck and deliver...
Deliver me from evil.
Madame. Madame, lucky tooth
from St. Augustine of Hippo.
- Lucky Buddha, madame?
- Madame, lucky Buddha.
Thank God, my St. Christopher.
St. Christopher.
You see, my friend has been
urgently called to London
on a matter of
international importance,
and I have given him my
personal assurance
that you will secure an accommodation
for him on the coach to Calais.
- But, Signor Bianchi, I have already...
- Hector...
Excuse me, excuse me, gentlemen,
but Mr. Ratchett has reservations,
and we'd be grateful if we could
board immediately.
Mr. Ratchett.
Welcome to the number ten.
Mr. Beddoes, the lower berth
in number one.
Mr. McQueen, the lower berth
in number four.
- The upper berth is...
- As arranged.
Now, Pierre, it is cold.
Now we can place Monsieur
Poirot in the number 16,
which is always kept vacant.
It is taken, signor, by a Mr. Hardman.
Then as a director of the line,
I command you to place
Monsieur Poirot
in what we know to be the empty berth
above Mr. McQueen's number four.
Monsieur.
At least you can get two tips.
- Pardon, monsieur.
- Sorry.
- Pardon.
- Excuse me, signor.
Well, my second husband,
Mr. Hubbard, would have raised hell.
No place for my makeup bag,
no ice in my drinking water,
and the hot water burps as it
comes out of the faucet.
Pardon.
Have courage, my friend.
It is the last compartment but one.
Pardon.
No.
I think there's a mistake.
Je crois que vous avez
fait une erreur.
Mr. McQueen, there is no
other berth on the train.
Monsieur Poirot has to come in here.
Voilà, monsieur, all is arranged.
Yours is the upper berth,
the number four.
We start in one minute.
I apologize if I have
incommoded you here.
However, it is for one
night only at Belgrade Station.
Oh, I see. At Belgrade,
you're... You're getting off.
Better than the hotel?
I shall probably keep
the menu as a souvenir.
Hector, I ordered three Islamic
13th-century, perforated pottery bowls
and six beakers.
They delivered only five beakers,
and one of the bowls arrived chipped,
which it was not when I paid for it.
Through the nose.
- Send a telegram from Belgrade.
- Yes. Yes, Mr. Ratchett.
What's the matter? You look tired.
- I slept badly.
- Yeah, why?
The Belgian in the upper berth snored.
Really? Any other
unanswered letters on file?
Only the anonymous ones.
We can't answer those, can we?
You'd better go catch up
on your sleep...
...before the Belgian gentleman
gets back to your compartment.
Go on.
Hi. My name's Hardman.
Call me Dick.
- Foscarelli. Call me Gino.
- How are you?
Beddoes.
Mr. Beddoes.
For the pen of a Balzac.
For three days, all these people,
these total strangers,
meet in a single train whose
engine controls their destiny.
Yes, I know. We are both
envious of the husband.
Is...?
Is the husband as British
as his tweeds?
Oh, heaven forbid.
He's a hot-blooded Hungarian.
If you but look at his wife,
he will cease to be a diplomat.
Thank God we are not young.
My second husband said
always to ask for change in dollars
or at worst, sterling.
So for Pete's sake,
what's a drachma?
It is... What do you call it...?
The currency...
My second husband also said,
"Take a book of food tickets, Mama,
"and you'll have no problem,
no problem at all."
That just isn't so.
First there's this ten-percent tip. Five
would've done the steward more...
I think Miss Ohlsson has a headache.
Would you forgive us if we went back
to the compartment, Mrs. Hubbard?
Gladly, if you must.
If you need aspirin,
I always carry it on my person.
I mistrust foreign drugs.
You must excuse me,
Mrs. Hubbard is upon us.
What's the matter with him?
Train-sick or something?
Some of us, in the words of the divine
Greta Garbo, "want to be alone".
And for dinner this evening?
You will have the goodness
to serve me the poached sole
with one new potato
and a small green salad
with no dressing. Hildegarde.
Who was that majestic lady?
- The Princess Dragomiroff.
- I have heard.
Pardon me, sir.
I wonder if you could
oblige me with a light.
Certainly.
Thank you.
My name is Ratchett.
Do I have the pleasure of speaking
to Mr. Hercule Poirot?
The pleasure possibly, Mr. Ratchett,
the intention certainly.
You asked me for a light.
I offered you one,
and you have not used it.
One can deduce that without
acute mental exhaustion.
That's wonderful. Sit down, sir.
- For a moment.
- Just for a moment.
Thank you very much.
Well, Mr. Poirot.
- Poirot.
- How's that?
- Oh, Poirot. Right.
I just wanted to say that in my country
we also come quickly to the point.
I want you to take a job on for me.
It means big money.
Very big money.
What is the case, or, as you put it, the
job which you wish me to undertake?
Mr. Poirot, I'm a rich man.
Naturally, men in my
position have enemies.
Only one.
Now, what the hell
do you mean by that?
Merely that when a man is in a position
to have, as you say, enemies,
it does not usually resolve
itself into one enemy only.
Oh. Oh, sure. Sure. I appreciate that.
What is your profession?
I'm retired.
- From what?
- Business.
What sort of business?
Baby food.
But what does that matter?
What matters is my safety.
You are in danger?
My life has been threatened,
Mr. Poirot.
My secretary can show
you two letters on file.
And I... can show you this.
I sleep on it.
Mr. Poirot...
...5,000 dollars.
No?
Ten thousand?
Fifteen thousand.
Mr. Ratchett, I have
made enough money
to satisfy both my needs
and my caprices.
I take only such cases now
as interest me,
and to be frank, my interest
in your case is... dwindling.
Belgrade Station.
The Orient Express will
depart in five minutes.
Monsieur Poirot.
I am transferring Signor Bianchi's
luggage to the Pullman.
He's giving you
his own compartment.
But you cannot sit up all night.
My dear friend,
do not concern yourself.
Since you are going to England,
it is better for you
to stay on the through coach
to Calais.
Now, Pierre has made me
very comfortable.
There is no one in the Pullman
but one Greek doctor. Ecco.
- Such generosity deserves my thanks.
- Buon riposa.
- Monsieur Poirot.
- Pierre,
- could I have some clean towels and...
- Yes, monsieur.
Who are my new neighbors?
To the left, monsieur,
the Swedish lady, Miss Ohlsson,
shares seven and eight with
the English lady, Miss Debenham.
And to the right, in number ten,
is Mr. Ratchett.
And where is the loquacious
Mrs. Hubbard?
I should like to get some
sleep tonight.
Beyond Mr. Ratchett,
in the number 11.
She is still too near.
Good night, Mr. Beddoes.
Pardon.
Who is it?
It's me, sir, Beddoes,
with your sedative.
Come in.
Thank you, Pierre. Good night.
Good night, monsieur,
and pleasant dreams in number nine.
- How many drops?
- Of the valerian?
- Two, sir, as you said.
- OK.
No, no. Put it on the table.
And tell Mr. McQueen I want
to see the text of the telegram
he sent from Belgrade.
Very well, sir.
He wants you.
Come in.
La belle Comtesse.
Ce n'est rien.
C'était un cauchemar.
Bien, Mr. Ratchett.
May you now have pleasant dreams.
C'est le silence de mort.
Snowdrift. Mon Dieu. Quelle nuit.
So now there's a man in my room.
I woke up in the dark
three minutes ago,
and there was a man hiding
in this compartment. I sensed it.
What's more, I know who he was
because I absent-mindedly
nearly walked through
his open door earlier this evening.
"Madame," said this Mr. Ratchett,
"If you'd done this 20 years ago,
I'd have said come in."
Twenty years ago?
Why, I'd only have been 15.
If there should be a reoccurrence,
do not hesitate to ring, madame.
Enfin c'est le comble.
Evidemment, j'ai une crise de nerfs.
It's me, sir, Beddoes,
with your pick-me-up.
Your amber moon, Mr. Ratchett.
Your passkey.
The chain.
Pierre, touch nothing.
Where are Signor Bianchi
and the Greek doctor?
In the dining car, monsieur.
Fetch them at once.
Well, can't you tap
the telephone wires?
- Or fire a rocket, or something?
- This is not a ship, madame.
- Where exactly are we?
- We are between Vinkovci and Brod.
- But in what country?
- In Yugoslavia.
The Balkans.
What else can you expect?
Snow is God's will.
And all is for the best.
Yeah, but how long do you think before
we can start getting out of here?
As soon as the stationmaster
at Brod sees
that we do not arrive on time,
he will send...
Dr. Constantine,
Monsieur Poirot wants to see you.
And you too, Signor Bianchi.
Forgive me, ladies and gentlemen.
Only God's forgiveness is important.
Ich mochte meine Prinzessin
benachrichtigen.
Signor Bianchi
and Dr. Constantine.
Mind the broken glass, gentlemen.
Pupils still slightly dilated.
Could've been drugged.
- Was drugged.
- With what?
There's a smell of valerian,
which is harmless,
but something must've been added.
- May I close his eyes now?
- I wish you would.
Why did he lose so much blood?
- Can I pull back the bedclothes?
- By all means.
Mr. Ratchett has been
frontally stabbed
ten, 11, 12 times.
- Oh, Dio.
- Mon pauvre.
If you must go whoop-whoop,
please go whoop-whoop
not to windward, but to leeward.
Help him, Pierre.
There is something in the pocket.
Permit me.
- His watch.
- The time of death.
I can definitely say
that death occurred
between midnight
and 2 in the morning.
That would fit.
I myself heard him cry out and ring for
the conductor at 20 minutes to 1.
When Pierre arrived, he apologized
and said he had been
having a cauchemar.
A nightmare.
Then I heard him
use his washbasin.
And that is the last thing known.
I beg of you, monsieur.
You cannot refuse.
But it is the duty
of the Yugoslavian police.
Oh, what, monsieur, to question
my passengers on my line? Never.
Now you must solve the mystery.
When we get to Brod, if we ever do,
we present the police with
a fait accompli.
We say that a murder has occurred.
There is the criminal.
I should like
the Pullman coach reserved
for the investigation's headquarters.
It will be at your disposal.
And a plan of the Calais coach
with the names and locations
- of all the people in it.
- Yes, it will be there.
And the passports of all
the passengers concerned.
Yes, you can even have mine.
I go to make a special
announcement now. Grazie.
Bring all the passports
to Monsieur Poirot.
Are there any other
passengers on the train?
In the Pullman coach,
nobody but myself and Mr. Bianchi.
Alors.
Then we must concentrate
on the Calais coach.
Where, in my amateur opinion,
the murderer is with us now.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Please, please, patience.
You must have patience.
Now, you will all get the chance
to state your views to Monsieur Poirot
at his own good time.
- Now, please...
- It is not good time. It is bad time.
God's laws have been bust,
thou shalt not kill.
And why was I not notified at once,
Signor... Mr. Bianchi?
- I was his nearest associate.
- And I was nearest to his murderer.
You mean you saw the man?
You can identify the murderer?
I mean nothing of the kind.
I mean there was a man
in my compartment last night.
It was pitch-dark, of course,
and my eyes were closed in terror.
Then how did you know it was a man?
Because I've enjoyed very warm
relationships with both my husbands.
- With your eyes closed?
- That helped.
- Excuse me.
- Anyway, the man smelt of tobacco.
Mr. McQueen,
Monsieur Poirot would be grateful
for a few minutes of your time.
- Excuse me.
- Don't you agree the man
must've entered my compartment
to gain access to Mr. Ratchett?
I can think of no other reason,
madame.
Pierre, your passkey.
Voilà, monsieur.
And will you discreetly procure
me a lady's hatbox,
one of the big, old-fashioned kind,
perhaps from the
Princess Dragomiroff's maid?
Give me five minutes, doctor.
Mr. McQueen, I regret
to have kept you waiting,
but there has been much to establish.
Please be seated. Now,
Mr. McQueen, I should be grateful
for anything you can usefully tell me.
What, for example, is...?
Let's get just a couple
of things straight first, Mr. Poirot.
Who, for example, are you,
and what is your status here?
Excuse me.
Monsieur Poirot is a detective,
officially delegated to investigate
this case by me.
Let us proceed with the matter in
hand. Your relationship with Ratchett?
I'm his... I was his secretary.
- For how long?
- A year, give or take.
- Where did you meet?
- In Persia.
He was collecting Gorgan pottery
with considerable success.
And I was trying to collect oil
concessions, you know,
with so little success
that I went bankrupt,
and he offered me the job. I took it.
- And since then?
- Well, we've traveled around.
He was hampered
by not knowing any languages.
I acted more as his courier
than as his secretary.
It was a pleasant enough job.
What part of America
did Ratchett come from?
I don't know.
The fact is, he never talked
about his background.
- Why, do you think?
- Well, I used to...
Well, I began to believe
that he had left America
to escape something, you know.
Or someone. And until a couple
of weeks ago, I think he succeeded.
And then?
Well, he began to get these
anonymous letters,
threatening letters, like these.
"I kill killers."
"Prepare to die."
- How brief.
- But in a sense, how complicated.
Last night, I noticed you dispatching
a telegram from Belgrade Station.
That's right.
Let's see, he sent for me
to see the text
right after we left Belgrade.
And then he went...
Yeah, it was the last I ever saw of him.
Were there any other
threatening letters?
Yeah, but none that
I was allowed to read.
He used to... He used to burn them.
That explains...
What?
My interest in hatboxes.
Precisely what I needed.
Doctor, first the wounds.
- You counted a dozen?
- Yes.
Five are deep,
of which three are lethal.
The rest are shallow.
And two...
...are so slight as to be
mere scratches.
What does that suggest?
That there were two murderers,
a strong man and a weak man?
Or a weak woman.
Or a strong man stabbing
the victim both strongly
and weakly in order to confuse us.
At least we know that
by the time of the murder,
Ratchett was too drugged to cry out
or defend himself with this.
But how did you guess...?
I didn't. He showed it to me
when he offered me $15,000
to be his bodyguard and I refused.
Ought I to have accepted?
Now, let us consider the ashtray.
Two different matches.
A smoked cigar.
- A pipe cleaner...
- And this.
- The initial H.
- That should not be hard to identify.
I wonder, Christian name or surname?
We must wait until
we examine the passports.
Bianchi, doctor,
has it occurred to you that there
are too many clues in this room?
Let us proceed by examining what
I hope will prove to be the last of them.
The burnt paper.
I use it for the mustaches.
What has that to do
with mustaches?
To melt the wax.
Observe, memorize,
you are my only witnesses.
- A-l-S-Y A-R-M-S.
- What does that mean?
It means we know
the true identity of Mr. Ratchett.
And why he had to leave America.
Do you remember
the Armstrong case?
Of course, the kidnapping of that
little American girl, and the killing.
Who does not?
Do you remember the name
of the child?
Certamente. It was Daisy.
D.
D-A
l-S-Y.
Space, A-R-M-S.
Daisy Armstrong.
- And Ratchett was her murderer?
- Well, no, the actual murderer
was tried, sentenced
and electrocuted.
But he was only the number two.
The subordinate of a boss whom,
at first, he was too terrified to identify.
Only on the eve of his electrocution
did he give the name of the boss,
who by then had disappeared
with the ransom money.
I remember feeling ashamed
that he had an Italian name.
Cassetti.
Che mostro. He had
a child's blood on his hands.
He had worse than that.
After the shock
of the body's discovery,
Mrs. Armstrong gave premature birth
to a stillborn child,
and herself died in the process.
Her husband, Colonel Armstrong,
once a brave officer in
the Scots Guard, shot himself,
and Mrs. Armstrong's personal maid,
who came wrongly
under suspicion of complicity,
threw herself from her
bedroom window and she died,
so five deaths, five.
Then I thank heaven that Giuseppe,
who spilt so much blood in his lifetime,
should have his own blood
spilt now.
Excellent, Pierre. And could you
summon the passengers to me here?
One by one in this order except
for the Princess Dragomiroff,
who is not only of royal blood, but also
much older than she tries not to look.
And, Pierre, since you are here
already, we can conveniently start
by questioning you.
Your full name is Pierre Paul Michel.
- Correct, monsieur.
- Two male saints' names.
You must be greatly blessed.
I've had my share
of good fortune, monsieur.
So... And of bad.
I note the cancellation
of your wife's photograph
nearly five years ago.
- She is deceased.
- She died, monsieur.
Of grief at the death
of our only daughter.
From scarlet fever.
I am truly sorry.
Let us talk of less
distressing matters.
On the night of the murder,
after we left Belgrade,
who were the last passengers
to retire to their compartment?
Show me on the diagram.
About 1:30, I remember seeing
the English colonel say good night
to Mr. McQueen outside
number three and four.
I saw him walk back into his
compartment, number 15,
which he did not leave.
And after that,
did no one reemerge?
No, but there was one lady
who opened a door,
I don't know which, and walked
in the direction of the toilet
at the far end of the corridor,
next to the dining car.
- Did you see her return?
- No, monsieur.
It is possible
I was answering a bell.
That reminds me of a final point.
Much earlier, soon after 12:30,
you and I both heard Mr. Ratchett
ring his bell several times and then
apologize for having had a nightmare.
Ce n'est rien.
C'était un cauchemar.
Who rang the second bell while
you were answering Mr. Ratchett's?
The Princess Dragomiroff, monsieur.
She asked me to summon her maid.
Thank you, Pierre.
That is all for the moment.
He had the means to do it.
The passkey to Ratchett's room.
- And a knife borrowed from the chef.
- With whom he was in league.
Which he plunged repeatedly
and without motive into the body
of his suitably astonished victim.
Anyway, we know the door
was not only locked, but chained.
Mr. McQueen.
Since our last conversation,
I have learned the true identity
of your late employer.
You don't say.
Ratchett was, as you yourself
suspected, merely an alias.
He was, in fact, Cassetti.
The gangster who masterminded
the kidnapping and killing
of little Daisy Armstrong.
You had no idea of this?
Oh, no, sir.
If I had, I'd have cut off my right hand
so I couldn't type his lousy letters.
And I'd have killed him with my left.
You feel you could've done
the good deed yourself?
It seems like I'm kind of
incriminating myself.
I should be more inclined
to suspect you, Mr. McQueen,
if you displayed an inordinate sorrow
at your employer's decease.
Sorrow?
My dad, my father,
was the district attorney, yeah,
who handled the Armstrong case.
Mrs. Armstrong and her husband
came to our house twice
for advice about the ransom money.
She was gentle and frightened.
But not too frightened to take
an interest in a young man
who wanted to go on the stage.
She even said she'd write to...
She died before
she got around to that.
She was as helpful
to me as a...
Well, a mother.
Forgive a Freudian question.
- Do you love your mother?
- I did.
She died when I was 8.
An impressionable age.
- Why do you ask?
- We shared a compartment
on the first night of our journey.
You cried out to your mother
twice in your sleep.
Did I?
I still dream about her.
Go on. Tell me.
I'm emotionally retarded.
Tell me that's why
I never married.
I am not here to tell you anything,
Mr. McQueen. You are here to tell me.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah, there's just one thing.
How did you...
...figure out Ratchett's identity?
By a message found
in his compartment.
He'd have burnt that, though,
as I told you.
He did.
Yeah, he did.
- Then how did you decipher...?
- With the help of a hatbox.
Thank you, Mr. McQueen.
He did it.
He murdered Cassetti.
He practically confessed as much.
No, the psychology is wrong.
A sensitive, motherless boy
conceives a passion for a lady
whom he admires above all
for her gentleness.
Now, could McQueen,
admiring the gentleness,
commit so foul a murder
without betraying the gentleness
of what we might call
his fairy godmother?
Godmother.
Now you have accidentally
said something valuable.
Come.
Mr. Beddoes, this is not
an inquisition, only an inquiry.
When you took Mr. Ratchett
his valerian drops
about 9:40 yesterday evening,
was he already in bed?
That is so, sir. Mr. Ratchett
always retired early on trains.
What were your duties before
leaving him for the night?
To place the valerian drops
within reach, sir.
- Beddoes.
- Sir?
Did you put this on my table
during dinner?
- No, sir.
- Then who the hell did?
I have no idea, sir.
May I ask what it is?
What it is, is none
of your damn business.
I wanna know how it got here.
- Will there be anything more, sir?
- There will.
Tell Mr. McQueen
I wanna see him, now.
Very well, sir.
At what time would you like
to be called in the morning, sir?
Not before 10.
Very good, sir.
- Was that usual?
- Oh, quite, sir, yes.
His breakfast was his amber moon.
He never rose
until it had had its full effect.
So you instructed Mr. McQueen
and then returned
to your own compartment,
the number one and two,
whose upper berth was occupied
by Signor Foscarelli.
Oh, yes, sir, the Italian person.
- Does he speak English?
- A kind of English, sir.
I think he learned it
in a place called Chicago.
Did you talk together much?
Oh, no, sir. I prefer to read.
Hey, what are you reading,
Mr. Beddoes?
Love's Captive,
by Mrs. Arabella Richardson.
Is it about sex?
No, it's about 10:30, Mr. Foscarelli.
I like that.
"It's about 10:30."
- And after that you went to sleep.
- Oh, no, sir.
Not until 4 in the morning.
Unfortunately, I had the toothache.
- And your companion?
- He snored incessantly.
One final point. How did you come
to be employed by Mr. Ratchett?
Through Maibaums, sir,
the big agency in New York.