Transcribed by:mermaid52
My father once told me to be careful
of the things...
...you love most in the world.
Because if you're not careful...
...that very thing can also destroy you.
The bank called. They're gonna
take your boat.
I had a job offer.
A lot of money.
- What can I do for you?
- I'm going to offer you 100K Euros...
...and took me in the water
with the great white shark.
Outside the cage!
I've spent ten years. It's taking me that long
to be able to get outside of the cage.
You're gonna show us how is done.
- Take his offer.
- Like it's that easy.
- Why are you freaking now?
- 'Coz you told him...
...he get this onto that.
I wasn't even sure I can do.
Swim with the sharks...for me.
That is the ultimate.
That's putting the courage on the line,
right?
Let's do it.
From the Director of "BLUE CRUSH"
and "INTO THE BLUE"
- Where are we going?
- Shark Alley.
There is big ones down there, right?
- Twenty footers.
- Is safe out there?
- Are you sure about this?
- Let's give him his money's worth.
Let's do it!
Academy winner
HALLE BERRY
OLIVIER MARTINEZ
It's gonna be fine.
HOLD
YOUR
BREATH
- Come on Al. What's going on?
- It's stuck!
DARK TIDE
Transcribed by:mermaid52