When a man loves a woman
Can't keep his mind
on nothin' else
He'll trade the world for
the good thing he's found
If she is bad he can't see it
She can do no wrong
Turn his back
on his best friend
If he put her down
When a man loves a woman
Spend his very last dime
Tryin' to hold on
to what he needs
He'll give up all his comforts
And sleep out in the rain
- If she said that's the way it ought to be
- Hey, that looks good.
That sandwich. Looks good.
You on your lunch hour?
When a man loves a woman
- Any news in the paper?
- Would you like to read a section of this?
No, thanks. I, uh,
actually read for a living.
- So, the last thing I want to be doing
on my lunch hour- - Oh, excuse me. - Hey!
- Sorry. Excuse me, miss.
- Yeah.
Baby, please don't treat me bad
- Okay?
- Yeah.
When a man loves a woman
- What?
- Where you going after this?
- Why would you be asking that?
- Ah, I am a pilot.
And I'm gonna barely make
my flight to Seattle-Tacoma...
and I haven't had a chance
to pick up my laundry.
- And?
- I thought you could pick it up for me.
Oh, I'd give you the money
and everything.
Here's the receipt and $30.
That should cover it.
What do you propose that I do with
your laundry after I pick it up?
Good question.
Here's the keys to my place.
The address is on the,
uh, little thing.
And I will be there
at about 12:30 and...
- you can bring it by then.
- After midnight?
- Uh, excuse me., Actually, sir, I was- - No,
no, hold on one second, one second, one second.
- If I could impose one further question.
- Okay.
Why wouldn't I drop off your
laundry at my convenience...
since I have your key?
Because then I wouldn't be able
to thank you properly.
Oh, I see.
And how would you do that?
I would give you something...
that you can take away with you.
- And what might that be?
- Oh, you want to know up front?
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me.
I bake.
You bake?
You bake!
You like... chocolate.
I'm allergic... to chocolate.
Do you like carrot cake?
Very much.
Well, then?
Cream cheese frosting?
My specialty.
- Check it out.
- Look.
She's so lucky.
- Jesus!
- Whoa.
Cable guy come this morning?
No? That's three weeks those kids
are without adult movies.
What a fuckin' world.
Hey, that looks good.
Is that Chablis?
Does anyone have, like,
a towel or something?
Now, this is you, inside.
Not inside the dress,
inside the body.
- How did I get in there?
- That's a whole other set of videos.
And they won't
let you watch those.
- Give me this.
- There you are.
Why wasn't your
real daddy there?
- You say the dumbest things.
- I'm four years old.
- Guys!
- Mom, can you tell her?
Oh! I married your daddy...
because he made me a cake
with cream cheese frosting.
That's how much he wanted me.
How come Daddy wanted you?
God, woman, just look at her.
Oop, late!
Second team, take over.
Porsche. Jesus, one more time.
Amy?
Jess has to do her homework tonight so
she doesn't leave it for the weekend.
Let's go. Amy, did you get that?
Which part were you
afraid I missed?
- Amy?
- Sorry.
Happy anniversary.
It's a press-on tattoo!
It says, "If found naked,
please return to Alice Green. "
It's to wear on trips so that the
stewardesses know you're spoken for.
- Flight attendants.
- Flight attendants, whatever.
Very thoughtful.
- I went over the 20 bucks.
- Oh, hey, I didn't go over the 20 bucks.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You rat.
That's incredible.
Now I'm gonna have to do
that thing to you tonight.
I think she wants you, baby.
- Hello, how're you doing?
- Fine.
- Mm, you're a good dancer.
- Thank you.
Ooh! Thanks.
- How was he?
- He was great!
Happy anniversary.
- Oh!
- What?
- Porsche again.
- Oh, honey.
Come here. No, no, no. Alice?
- Honey.
- Goddamn it.
Hey, it's 1:00 in the morning.
People are trying to have sex up here!
Alice, there's nobody down there.
You're talking to a car.
Goddamn it!
Alice.
- Alice.
- What a piece of shit. Damn it.
- Goddamn it. Shut up!
- Alice! Alice!
- Goddamn it!
- Alice, am I gonna like this?
- Here.
Shut up!
Shit!
Fucking foreign car!
Okay, batter up!
Right here! Hey, batter, batter,
batter, batter, batter, batter!
Right here. Come on,
baby. Let's go.
I'll start your shower.
You're not suggesting
I go to work?
Yes.
Okay. You promise
no one will be loud?
Six hundred kids? Sure.
Go on.
Get dressed, sugar.
We're runnin' late.
See, I'm not sure that
Matthew Wasserman's...
glance at your breasts rises to
the level of sexual harassment.
Well, what if he said,
"You know you want it. "
- Did he?
- No.
- But what if he did?
- Well, that would be closer.
I think if we can get him to lift up
your dress, we can put him away.
So, uh...
what is the deal with cutting
language lab- Shit!
Another self-mutilation day.
I'm checking on availability
for end-of-the-day wind-down.
Oh, come on. My problem's gotta
be more sordid than Shannon's.
Okay, a quick one.
Michael's got a trip.
Yes.
- Hi. - Hey. -
Where's Alice?
That's right, where's Alice?
Bye.
Amy! Amy! Amy, Amy, Amy, Amy,
Amy, Amy.
Listen, I, uh, got a trip.
I'm late, and Wayne's supposed to
meet me. I've got no way to call him.
He's waiting at my Lamaze class.
I just can't not show up. I-
Amy, Amy, uh, this is important.
I got a trip.
You're not saying my life
is less important?
Of course not.
I didn't think so. Bye.
She didn't come home.
I did notice that.
- I have a trip.
- What if she doesn't get back?
Well, I'll just go down to the corner
and offer the first person I see...
- five bucks to stay with you.
- Michael.
Okay, ten bucks.
You're so pretty.
Twenty minutes, lights out.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You're okay.
I've called everyone we know.
Hospitals, the school.
- You're up.
- I'm supposed to be up.
I'm just supposed to be
doing it in Chicago.
Hey! Stop that.
You got a trip.
Really?
I better get a move on.
I forgot that. I'm sorry.
I owe you a trip.
What happened?
- We went for a drink.
- Pam? - Yeah, Pam.
My friend. She needed me.
She needed to talk.
She needed me 'cause
Joe is an asshole.
I'm glad she needed you 'cause
she's the one who got you.
- Nobody else got a fucking phone call.
- We were just talking.
She was crying and, and, uh-
Ah, when I looked at the time,
I just figured you were asleep.
So, uh-
I- I-I don't know how
I forgot the trip.
I don't know either.
Christ, Michael.
You don't know what I go through.
You don't have a fucking clue.
- What do you go through?
- My job, for one.
The girls and,
and running this place...
and I know a lot of women
go through the same thing...
but their husbands
aren't gone half the time.
I miss you...
when you go.
You got pressures,
you come to me.
Why do that to you? What are you
supposed to do with all that?
You let me worry about that.
I'm gonna trade Ed Buckley for a trip to
Mexico for a week and we're gonna disappear.
Would you like that?
Would you like to disappear?
Go get some candy from Grandpa.
And Mama Andretti.
Hello, Casey, Casey!
How are you?
Look what I got for you. See?
- I'm not staying with her.
- Hey, it's gonna be okay, honey.
Yeah, but she doesn't
care about us.
Listen, she's crazy about you,
and she's gonna spoil you rotten.
- Hi, Mom. How are you? Thanks for coming.
- Hello, Michael, dear.
- She still puts you down, and I don't like it.
- Hey.
You're gonna have to cut Grandma a little
bit of slack. She hasn't had the easiest life.
Jessica.
- How's my sweet angel?
- Oh, just fine, Mom.
- How are you?
- Have you lost weight?
- No. No.
- I guess you're just tired.
- Hello, Jessie.
- I wish I had time to be tired.
- Give me a smile. Come on. Give me a big smile!
- Walter!
- Don't let Michael carry all those bags in by himself!
- I'm sorry.
It's all right, Ma.
It's only two bags.
Give him the small one.
He likes to feel useful.
I got it, I got it.
Mom, can I get you anything before we
fly off and leave you with the kids?
The best thing you can do for me is just
have the grandest time in the world...
and come home rested, please?
- Hello. - Hey,
Dad! - You know what?
When Mama comes home, we're gonna
have a big surprise for her.
We're gonna have
the whole house clean.
Won't that be nice, huh?
- Thanks, I gotta go. Bye. Bye, girl.
- Bye.
- Thanks. Bye. Thanks.
- Bye. Have fun.
Safe trip.
- Bye, Mom. I love you! -
Bye, bye. - Love you! Bye!
- Okay, let's go.
- Don't clean too hard.
It's a press-on tattoo.
Just in case. You never know
what might happen in Mexico.
Found a guy at the beach
who'll watch us have sex.
Ooh.
- A local?
- Mm-hmm.
- Come on, honey.
- Ooh. Okay.
Come on.
Baby, gotta tell you something.
Listen.
I think we should do this
more often.
I do... because...
they paid you to fly here,
I got a pass...
the hotel
is a remarkable discount.
There are meals, as you've
said before, Johnny.
You gotta eat anyway,
so we can afford this.
- Not unless they comp the drinks.
- Ah.
What's that supposed
to mean, hmm?
- Hey. - You lookin' for a
fight, buster? - No, I'm not.
- Buster, buster. Wait, wait, wait. I got a bruise here.
- Sit down, Alice. Alice, please.
- Hey! Alice!
- If you wanna fight, I can give you...
- all the trouble you can handle.
- Sit down. Okay, great. I know you can.
Alice, sit down. Sit!
- Sit.
- Woof.
Alice! Alice!
I'm waiting for my spanking.
I know we have pressures.
And we need to have fun.
But wringing you out at the end of an
evening is less fun than it used to be.
And thinking back, it's been going on
for quite a while, Alice.
What's wrong, baby?
Can you talk about it?
You scared me last night.
Didn't you scare you?
Huh? What's gonna happen?
I'm gonna stop drinking
so much.
Last night was the best thing that
could've happened to straighten my ass out.
I promise you.
I promise me.
- Hey!
- Jessie! Ow!
- Pinatas!
- They're here!
- Oh, honey, don't get dirty.
- Casey!
- Hi- Hey!
- Someone's getting married.
Hi, pretty girl.
- Hi, Casey, honey.
- You look wonderful.
- Hey.
- Oh, my God, I hope those pinatas aren't full of candy.
- Let me take this for you, darling.
- Hi. Hi, Daddy.
- Hi. Wow, man. - Good to see
ya. - Hey, Pops, how are you?
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, honey.
- I smell Murphy's Oil.
- Yes, I used it a lot.
Shit!
Well, everything's fine
on the curb.
Garbage compulsion.
I feel much better now.
Come on, baby, it's late.
Casey.
You're not going to Dana's.
Case, I think we're gonna have to fill out
one of these homicide reports for Felicia.
- She's soaking off her make-up.
- Oh.
- Did I miss something?
- She didn't do her book report, so she can't go to Dana's.
- It's not due till Monday.
- I told you last night not to save it for the weekend...
- to make sure that you did it on-
- Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning,
the first words out of our mouths.
I think we have all we can handle right
now with our coffee and our little spoon.
So, you go to Dana's, and the report
gets done first thing Saturday...
- and not last thing Sunday, okay?
- What's the difference?
The difference between me
helping you do it...
and me pulling your lungs out
through your belly button.
- Sorry I'm late.
- That's okay.
Um, Casey's taking a nap...
and Jess is teaching Samantha
how to use a computer.
- You all right?
- I- Whoa.
I had lunch at this Thai place,
and, uh...
something in the oil,
maybe, but-
I'll be fine. See you tomorrow.
Uh, Alice, um, I can call my mom. I'm
sure I can stay and make some supper.
I said, see you tomorrow.
- Alice, I think you should-
- Ah, ah, Amy.
Go home.
Okay?
Please!
Go home.
You get some rest.
And I'll call you
a little later.
Mom, look. Samantha drew
a Buick on the computer.
- It's green.
- Do your homework.
Mom?
- Mom, are you sick?
- I said...
do your homework!
Mom, are you sick?
I did my homework!
That's all I wanted to tell you!
Good girl.
Jess!
Mom?
Is there a Michael Green?
Michael Green?
- Switchboard tracking you down, I guess.
- Thank you.
Hello.
Jess, what's the matter, honey?
- Mommy died.
- What?
She just fell through
the shower door and...
all the glass is all shattered
and on the floor...
and she's laying
in the middle of it.
Jess, listen to me. I'm gonna have
somebody over there right away.
- You understand?
- Okay.
- Okay? And I'm gonna call you right back.
I need an outside line.
- I need an outside line!
- Sir.
Hi.
You're all right.
Doctor says.
How's Jess?
She's really happy you're okay.
I hit her hard, Michael.
- I hit her so hard.
- It's all right.
She's fine.
We're gonna get you better
so it doesn't happen again.
All right?
- God, just don't hate me.
- Mmm.
Because I'll die if you do.
That thought would
never enter my mind.
I start at 4:00 in the morning,
and it goes all day.
I drink in the john, I drink...
in the closet, and I drink in
the kids' room when they're not there.
You know how when we...
go out to the car...
- and I have to go back
inside for a second? - Mm-hmm.
I have to be high
to do anything.
And I'm scared all the time.
- I drank for Casey's goddam birthday party.
- So did I.
I drink a quart a day.
It's vodka, so you
couldn't smell it.
How come I didn't see this?
Because I hid it.
You were scared.
- What am I gonna do?
- We'll figure it out.
I don't want you
to worry about it.
I'm gonna find you
the best treatment...
the best in the fucking world.
You're not alone, honey. Never.
Never.
- Okay, girls, I'll see you later.
- Bye.
- Mommy. - Amy. - Oh, I'll
just wait in the kitchen.
Okay.
So...
we'll talk on the phone
and you'll come see me.
- And then I'll be home.
- And we'll go to the beach?
- Are you gonna take care of your sister?
- I'm gonna take care of Daddy.
Sorry, baby.
It will never happen again.
Mommy loves you.
- That's us.
- Hi.
Uh, we're Alice Green.
Hi. Welcome.
Alice, before we check you in,
I need to look through your bag.
Is that all right with you?
It's strictly routine.
We've got all your
paperwork, so...
everything's ready.
Um, sorry.
So, come on, Alice,
and we'll get you checked in.
Just Alice.
Give me a minute.
I'll call you tonight.
- I'm sorry. There's no phone calls.
- Excuse me, uh-
She's my wife. She can call me
whenever she needs to call me.
She'll be in detox
until Tuesday...
and she'll be busy getting well.
She'll call you as soon
as she can after that.
I love you.
I can hear her heart beat
From a thousand miles
Yeah, the heavens open
Every time she smiles
And when I come to her
That's where I belong
And I'm runnin' to her
Like a love song
She gimme love, love, love, love
Crazy love
Jess?
It's 6:00 in the morning.
Kids are unbelievable.
First she wants French toast,
then she wants tuna.
And then she wants
a cucumber sandwich.
Case!
Wanna know what
she finally eats?
- She ate fruit.
Right.
My hair hurts.
Casey, is that you?
- Oh! God.
- I did her hair.
Oh, I like it.
Let's see that hairdo.
Ooh, that's a little tight there.
Let me see that.
- Ow!
- Ooh, sorry!
- Mommy does it better.
- Oh, Mommy does everything better.
She cooks better, she looks better,
she kisses better.
Mommy's a better person.
You know, I bet you have
a lot of questions...
things you're feeling
about Mommy.
We could talk about that.
See, like if you're sad or
scared or angry or something...
- you could just-
- What's a alcoholic?
Someone with a bad habit, you know, like
if you drank stuff that made you sick.
But you really liked it, so you kept
drinking it and it kept making you sick.
Wouldn't you want
to learn how to stop?
- What's a alcoholic?
- It's why she does all that stuff.
When she does all that stuff,
like when she talks like she's sleepy...
forgets stuff,
and when she's sad.
When she cries?
She cries in the bathroom.
She, she did that a lot,
I bet, huh?
Your hair is so pretty.
You know, Mommy can't wait
to get back just to brush it?
I got it. Alice?
I'm Dr Mendez.
I'm a counsellor.
You know you're supposed
to be in community now?
Your nurse said you've
got a problem?
No problem.
I don't have any problems.
- You think I have a problem?
- Yeah, at least.
I just want to make a phone call. I just
want to make a phone call to my husband.
If you wanted to make a phone call to your
husband, would you call that a problem?
No, but I'm not in detox
dealing with an addiction.
- Look, we'll let you make a
phone call, as soon as- - Now!
- Now is when I want to call him!
Now! Can you understand that? - Alice-
- Alice, look-
- Can you understand fucking anything?
Yeah.
I can.
Two more days, hon.
You can do this.
Hang in.
Come on.
Hello.
- Michael.
- Alice?
- Yeah.
You can call.
Yeah. What do you know?
They let me use the phone.
How was detox?
It was nifty, you know.
- I threw up like a good girl.
- Great.
Hard part's over, baby.
Yeah, the hard part's over.
Party time.
Well, so, uh...
basically, I just, uh,
sit around and...
think of you naked because,
you know, you have this...
amazing body.
You still do, don't you?
State of the art.
So, you'd be, what,
65 pounds now?
Honey.
Alice.
Honey, you there?
Yeah.
Everyone here is
pulling for you.
Alice, they say they tear
you down the first two weeks...
so they can build you back up.
- Alice.
- God, I'm sorry, baby.
It's just so hard.
- Honey, are you there?
- Yeah.
I'm here, baby.
I love you.
I miss you.
Listen, I'll see you, um,
I'll see you on Sunday.
- Okay?
- The kids are so excited to see you.
I can't talk for too long
because there's, um...
one phone and a whole line
of people, so-
Can you bring
my grey sweatsuit?
Yes.
I'm just, uh, running down
my list...
of dumb things to say
right now.
Good for you.
You're supposed to wrap it.
- What?
- In a newspaper or a paper bag.
So nobody sees it or something.
Mommy tell you that?
Hey.
You wanna do one?
Come on. Take your pick.
Vodka, huh?
All right.
Let me see.
Now if Mommy cries
when she sees you...
it's because
you're beautiful.
Okay?
Piggyback?
Oh, the purse. Ready?
- Where is she?
- I don't know. We'll see.
She said she'd be out here.
There she is.
Do you see her in the hat?
Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy.
Hi, baby.
Hey.
Say hi to Mommy.
- Hi, beautiful girl. Hi.
- Hi.
You want to take 'em for a walk
and I'll catch up later?
- Hmm? Bye-bye.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Come on, you guys. Let's go.
Art Braun left alone.
- Nice shot.
- Excuse me. Can you get some coffee in here?
What do I look like,
a fuckin' waitress?
Try the striped in the side.
Hey! I saw you with Alice.
You're her significant other.
Good to meet you, man.
Your wife's amazing. Malcolm.
- Oh, uh, Michael.
- Yeah, Michael.
- Good to know- Come on in. - How
are ya? No, I got the kids outside.
- Uh-uh. That's okay. This is Earl.
- Hey, I'm Earl.
- Hi, Earl. Michael.
- Hiya. Watch the game.
- No, I-I got the kids outside. Okay.
- Have a seat, man.
- Myers shooting at 50% tonight.
- Well, there's that middleman.
- Blalock is still on him. - Hi.
How ya doin'? - Good. How are ya?
...moved up the lane,
opened up that soft spot.
It's clear
on the other side there-
- Come on, Malcolm.
- Been a while since you watched a game without a beer?
- Me?
- You.
Actually, uh, I don- I don-
I don't, uh, drink much.
Can you believe that, man?
I been there, man. Denial.
- Jesus.
- Ain't just a river in Egypt.
- Hey, shut up!
- Cork it, Danny.
Are you guys sayin' that
this dude don't drink?
- I'm sayin' shut the fuck up, man!
- Fellas. Fellas, my fault.
Hey. It's a cunning,
baffling disease, man.
The man doesn't have a problem,
pecker-face. You do!
Cunning and baffling disease.
- Save it for group, man. Save it for group.
- Yeah!
- Nah, not in group, Earl.
- Save it for group, all right? Yo, Earl, man.
- I like your new friends.
- Oh, d'you meet Malcolm?
- Big black guy.
- Cokehead.
- We hit it off.
- The girls are with him.
Right now?
Oh, come on, Michael.
He's not a child molester.
He's an armed robber.
What?
Well.
Whatever you think of these people,
Michael, think that of me, because it fits.
- I thought you'd quit.
- I did.
Malcolm and I, um...
really talk, you know?
Talk about everything.
Everything.
We have a lot in common, and the
truth is that right- right now...
I really need these people.
I'm glad you have 'em.
And when you come home,
you'll have me.
What's wrong, Alice?
Hmm? You were fine when the kids
were around. What's wrong?
Long day.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Gary, this is Michael.
Hi.
- Feel like I know you.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Your wife's
a very comforting person.
- Yes.
- Very.
Do you mind if I talk
to her for a second?
- No. - I just need-
Just for a second.
- I'll just be one second. What's the matter?
- Okay.
Uh-
I'm sorry.
Sheila... called me.