THE WOMAN (2011)
Bitch.
You're a lifesaver, you know Belle?
Thanks.
Dina wants to talk to you.
Why is that, Belle?
She told me.
If you want to talk, so to speak.
I want a burger now ready.
Are you ready, Belle?
I do not know.
I see.
Great.
Keep an eye on Darlin '. Is behind that
naughty again.
Dina.
Chris.
What are you thinking, dear?
I have said, no kisses.
Did you hear?
I heard, is screaming in my ear.
Can I eat a hamburger?
We shall see.
What are you doing, Jenny?
Hold it.
Stop it!
Will call mommy?
What is it, Jenny?
Need to change diapers?
Stop it. Let me tell you.
Will tell, right?
Need to change diapers, Jenny?
Ouch!
Shut up.
I can spend time with Ed
there at the shelter.
I wish I could stay longer.
I understand.
I will do the following ...
I sell everything ...
get an apartment
room and bedroom close to there,
so you can be near him in this
his last months.
I think it has much longer
of life.
If you really are willing to sell,
I am grateful that I have tried.
Step into the office ...
for dealing with the paperwork.
It should not cost much,
but finding a fair price.
I know you will, Chris.
Friend is for these things.
No need to worry about
review services.
As it was, man?
8 out of 10, Dad.
Regularly?
The last and the penultimate.
But I think I got the hang.
Have to train free throws
to win matches.
I know.
That guy is stoked on the peg.
It's an asshole.
Just went out together once.
Do not say ...
Be careful not to smudge.
Do not fall into the water?
Chlorine ruin my hair.
We do not want that, right?
Gave food pros dogs?
Brian will when you wake up.
They can wait.
Cool this silence, no?
It is.
What is the average?
70 to 10.
Regular.
Very well. Great.
She picked up something?
What do you think?
Should lower the hem.
Very well. Do it.
Then come with me.
I also?
Sure, honey, you too.
Follow us, son.
Watch your step.
Well, I want you to remove all this stuff ...
to the other side of the basement ...
and then give a swept the floor.
Before dinner?
Yes, Peg.
Why?
Because her father is sending.
A problem with that, Brian?
No. Wherever we take
all this?
For the storage trailer.
What is small and can be burned,
put in the incinerator.
We will need gloves.
There are some in the barn.
It gave food to the dogs?
It's not my time.
Peg?
Okay. I will feed them
and picked up the gloves.
Have rats here?
Maybe.
Want to grab cheese?
I do not think a good idea.
Belle, you are responsible.
With the three of you should not take long.
I have to deal with some things at home.
Chris.
Why are we doing this?
You will see.
Trust me.
What is he doing?
Peg, you scared me
Sorry.
I could not sleep.
Well try.
Have college tomorrow morning.
What is Dad doing?
Go to bed, Peggy.
It's late.
Good night, mother.
Good night, sweetheart.
I do not want to hurt her.
Very well. QEM can tell me what is
a scalene triangle?
Three sides unequal.
Right. But he forgot to raise
hand again, is not Jackie?
Sorry, Miss. Raton.
What other triangles are there?
C'mon, say.
Peggy!
Always taking notes, eh, Peg?
I'm taking notes ... yes.
What other triangles you know, Peg?
Scalene?
People!
Will you excuse me?
Yes, of course
Miss. Fanchon.
All right, dear?
Yes.
Just went back to get my stuff.
See you soon.
That's right, Brian.
You're too good.
What is it, Cindy?
There's something sticky
in my brush.
Let me see.
It's gum.
You can leave, Cindy, I'll help.
're Hurting.
Sorry.
You can leave. Thanks for trying.
Damn.
Damn!
It was very civilized of you.
Damn it.
Oh my gosh.
So, you like to bite ...
And does not understand what I'm saying.
That I understand.
But I know it makes sense to ...
I am very upset with you.
I understand that ...
who's boss.
I have kids to raise, girl
And disobedience ...
is not something we need to see.
They are really nice guys.
I would love to present them to you.
But
if they do not behave ...
if you're naughty ...
So I can not do it.
Is not it?
And I also have to overcome
the loss of my finger.
I'm going home.
I will bring my wife and children ...
You behave.
Behave yourself.
Already I'm feeling better
with respect to the finger.
One shot.
I've heard. What do you shoot?
You will see.
What song is this new?
Where is it?
Of Korea.
Korea?
I like it.
Me too.
You'll lose your appetite.
Than nothing.
Say that now.
Absolutely.
Well, folks ...
Who wants to go down to the basement with me?
What's inside?
A mountain lion?
Much better than that, son.
Father?
What is this?
Only God knows where she has lived, Peg.
In the forest.
In caves.
We'll help you.
She needs a huge band aid.
That's right.
It remains to be done first.
She's hurt.
Let's just deal with it.
We will have to rotate the responsibility
to care for it.
Basic rules.
Do not touch.
I learned that our friend likes to bite ...
She bit you?
He tore a piece of finger and swallowed.
Christ.
What we do with it?
We will train it, Brian.
Civilize it.
Free her from herself,
their basic instincts.
She thinks it's an animal.
Only God knows how he was so ...
But we can not let people
walking through the bush
like animals. It's not right.
It is not safe.
Belle?
Yes ..
Could prepare a plate of cereal or oatmeal?
Something simple.
She must be hungry.
Since the capture, she just ate ...
His finger.
Peg,
get a first aid kit.
I want to treat the wounds.
Right?
Let girls. To work.
Rather than a mountain lion, son?
Let's stick with it?
Sure.
Well,
pay close attention ...
to keep everyone away.
What is it, Belle?
Oats?
Yes.
Great.
Very nutritious.
Go, put in front of her.
Right?
Put it down ...
not too close ...
Very well.
Now, Brian ...
bring the rake ...
Right?
Pull up next to her.
Be careful not to spill.
Come on.
Pronto.
Great.
Teamwork.
Each did his part.
See why I said to stay away?
I think the next time
have to use the hose.
When you feel hungry even, she will eat.
Okay.
Come on.
Listen to this.
This is our project.
It is no secret.
Needless to say, must keep his mouth shut ...
but I need to remember that.
All we have to take turns
in the care of her,
the same way with dogs.
Someone will have to do the cleaning, etc ...
Your mother and I take care of everything ...
it is more complicated.
Understood?
Yes.
Okay, then.
Dinner time.
It may not be hungry,
but I am.
Discuss the details later.
Let's eat.
All in agreement?
Agree?
Yes? So let's go.
Pass the salt.
Is there?
At night I like to listen to my radio.
Will you listen?
How will the school girl?
All right, Dad.
You're a good girl, Peg.
I know sometimes it's hard ...
at your age.
But you must see the good side of things.
Will get your driver's license
soon, right?
His grades are good, no?
Yes.
Will go to college.
Think about it.
All right father.
I love you, girl.
I love you too, Dad.
Dear ...
This woman ...
think we should be doing this?
Come to bed, dear.
Toby, how are you?
Hello, Cleek.
Good morning, Mr. Cleek.
Hello, Dorothy.
As with Ms. Goldenberg?
Are you satisfied with the contracts?
He signed everything.
Very well. Great.
Have lunch with Dina at noon ...
court and the two meeting
with the staff of the three oil.
The form of Ludlow eata ready?
Just missing the final print.
When finished, bring them ...
along with other ...
coffee cup
and started working.
Thank you, Dorothy.
First we stretch and then
eight laps, girls.
Tracey, we do stretching.
Not feeling well again, Peg?
She has a problem.
She changed a lot.
It is normal at this age.
You know how they're wearing lately ...
justinhas short skirts and blouses.
I had not noticed.
It used to be so ...
It is very beautiful.
Should ...
Blonde again?
Yeah, man!
Flattening.
Do you really?
Making rip your zipper, Mr. Ohr.
Hi, doll.
How are you?
Well
And you?
Great.
Bonnie measure again ...
and it grew another inch.
Can you believe it?
Let's score another BBQ soon?
I have nothing against.
The weather is great for that, right?
Sure. How about in your home then?
The house is a zone.
There could be different with the kids, right?
I have to go.
See you soon, Vik.
I will hop over there to take a
a coffee, right? I will surprise.
When finished, send it to
Dina Bludjak, and send
the check of the initial payment.
Okay.
Mr. Cleek, I say something?
Sure.
It's none of my business, but ...
As it is the economic situation,
do not think you are risking too much?
Seen me lose control, Dorothy?
No.
What a wonderful perfume.
It's new, right?
Like it?
A lot.
I really enjoyed.
It's great.
Oh, no.
Look what was done.
I approached a girl smelling too ...
and it just me ...
Hey, give me a little.
Ask in modes.
Please, Mom. I love you.
In the table!
What kind of cookie you want?
I want a little man.
This?
No. ..
No.
Yes.
Do you think the woman animal
eat little men?
I do not know ...
Do not know if I ate a cookie in life.
Then why are you here?
Dad is helping her.
You heard him speak.
I can lick each other?
Brian!
What are you doing?
I just wanted to see if she's okay.
I wish I knew your father?
Want a little man?
Had to eat the head first.
Not me. I prefer to crush.
Thank you, sis.
Gee, Dina, I did miss that check
a good neighbor ...
But someone had to do it.
I thought I could help
Sure.
Than nothing.
Yes.
I'd love to have a drink
but today it does not.
Us ..
we have a commitment to family.
Another time.
Right?
Great. Said.
We'll talk later, Dina.
Okay, bye.
Father
You can not smoke?
Speaking ...
Do not forget the dogs.
It's time for Brian.
All right, Dad.
Enjoy and grab the hoe.
Quiet!
They want a hose?
Ready
Wretched.
Can I talk to you a moment, Peg?
I do not want to delay the next class.
Do not worry.
Sit down here.
Is everything okay?
Yes, why?
Nausea, loose clothing ...
Ms.. Hendl told me that for weeks
just sits in PE classes.
I'm not stupid, Peggy.
Why not take care of their own lives?
You are part of it.
Where were you?
Playing with the dogs.
You?
It is.
I think this is going.
Are you ready, Belle?
I'm ready.
Very well.
Bring the buckets.
How are we today?
I hate to do this.
But I'm not going to risk with you.
We bathe in it, father?
Never seen anything so smelly so in my life.
Your mother and I'll wash it,
but you will clean the swineherd
she did ..
I?
Take the shovel and a piece of cloth.
I think we'll have to do it ...
until she ...
to use the potty?
Exactly.
Anda.
Maybe it will help.
Close the door.
Come
Give me the bucket.
Thank you.
Maybe it's better to let it cool a bit ...
No.
We know very well that the best way to clean ...
is hot water.
Otherwise ...
would only spread germs ...
if it is cold ...
or even warm.
That's it.
See? Very well.
Belle,
I need another bucket.
Bring another bucket.
It will tell who is jealous.
This has to be done.
You can bring another bucket, please?
Chris?
Look.
I look, eh, Belle?
I think I have what I need to fix that ...
Cool ...
gives the first place.
Thank you.
Well ..
now I need to call Brian.
Send him to the shed ...
grab a piece of wood about 3 feet.
We can not clear it here.
We'll have to take it outside.
We will also need the peg.
Thank you, Belle.
Got it?
Perfect. That's good.
Go call your mother and Peg.
Can I help?
No, I did enough.
Dad is calling you.
Peg also.
So go call her.
Hey, Peg!
Dad is calling you!
Brian!
Climb to call it.
Do not yell at my house.
Sorry.
Go to your room and stay there while
are working. Got it?
Said.
Please.
Peg!
It is not clear.
Please.
Girls, grab the towels ...
and the first aid kit.
Legal? Anda.
He is learning.
Wipe it.
Is it safe?
No, do not worry.
Look who's talking
the guy with nine fingers.
You can go.
It's crisp.
I do not want it to cool.
Honey, give me a cotton ...
soaked in hydrogen peroxide.
This will hurt.
It has buttons here ... and here ...
so you can have ...
undress her.
Cool.
Why not put it?
Okay, she will not do anything.
For her everything is new,
that's it.
Is frightened.
It is covered in scars.
How could that be?
Maybe someday we can tell.
I do not think you like it.
Never wore a dress.
You also must not have liked
the first time she wore.
Pronto.
It's looking ...
a polygamous wives of those, right?
Slowly.
Thank you.
Obliga-cattle.
I am tired.
Your students gave you work?
No, they're right.
What role is this?
It's a phone number and address.
Peggy's parents Cleek.
I think she's pregnant.
Are you thinking about tell them?
Should not I?
It will only make things worse.
It'll be pretty obvious very soon.
You decide.
I need to lock the room.
Be right back.
Damn, always at dinner time.
Peg, see who is, please.
They have all day to call ...
Not so loud, daughter, do not want ...
Leave your message after you hear the beep.
Hi, this is Genevieve Raton ...
The message is for Mr. and Mrs. Cleek.
Her daughter, Peggy, my student is geometry ...
Message deleted.
No new posts.
Put it down, Darlin '.
Peggy, what are you doing?
Time to go to school.
Come on, I'll take today.
I'm not feeling well, mother.
Can I stay home today?
Peggy.
You have nothing.
Today we have half a day off, right?
It is.
What will you do with all this off?
Do not do anything I would not.
He spoke, father.
If I get sick to get up.
Okay.
I'll take Brian then.
Hi, Brian.
Okay?
Go to the movies.
Want to come with us?
I have to go home.
I have things to do.
Okay. It is next to.
He spoke the next.
Bye, Brian.
"Dentist's Darlin '. Sandwich in the fridge.
Food dog, Brian. Back at 3:00
Mummy. "
Who does not like cookies?
What are you doing, Brian?
You're screwed.
Get out of here.
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry, even ...
for everything that is happening.
Darlin ', go to your room.
Why?
I did nothing.
Honey, is not with you,
is with your brother.
Be good and go to your room.
Do you know what your son did?
You know what?
Of course I want.
He thought nobody was home ...
Then he got down there,
with it.
He took her dress ...
left her naked ...
was groping her ...
e. ..
is groping ...
If Peg had not arrived on time ...
who knows what would have happened.
Yes, son?
Peggy took it.
Did you hear me?
Why are you asking if it's true?
Calm down, Belle.
He had a hand in it ...
and the other tucked in his pants.
I am sending ...
take it easy.
Look at me when
talking to you.
Is it true?
Since no one got hurt ...
What?
No one was injured.
It's a boy.
A teenager.
Teens have impulses.
Kid thing.
Now that is spick and span
is not to throw away ...
You can no longer continue with this!
You can not do this to us, Chris.
You lost your mind?
Can not get there with this guy,
with his son finding normal
do ...
What?
You are a bailiff.
She is a human being.
You know what would happen to us all
if they catch you?
What do you do with those dogs ...
is enough to send you
to jail.
Anophthalmia, Belle, is your fault.
Anophthalmia, remember?
Huh?
I never agreed with what you did.
Never.
Can not wait to continue making their ...
and you think you could get away ...
forever
Chris ...
Comes to me.
Very well.
What would you do?
This is ...
What are your plans?
I do not understand ...
I wonder.
What do you think you can do, put?
I'm leaving ...
I'll let you, Chris.
I'll take the girls with me.
You can keep the baby rapist.
It is teaching you everything
you need to know.
Or not?
You two can more
is burning in hell.
But in my daughters
you will not play more.
Over!
Now!
You can not do this to us, Chris.
I can not!
She'll be fine.
She's fine.
Take a damp cloth
his mother, Peg.
Peg! Anda.
It will not open the door?
See who you are.
Miss. Raton!
Peggy.
Hi
It's not going to invite me in?
There is a good time.
Oh yeah, Peggy.
You do not come to any harm.
I just want to help.
Can not help.
How do you know?
I know.
I know all sorts of people,
doctors, counselors.
I said that is not the best time,
Miss. Raton.
Peg, what ways are these?
Hi, can enter.
Thank you.
Miss ...
Raton.
I remember.
Geometry.
Yes.
Geometry, that's right.
We met at the meeting of parents.
Yes.
Sit down.
Can I serve you something?
Are you thirsty?
Would you like a ...
No.
... Soda, coffee?
No, thank you.
Very well.
I can speak privately with you and
his wife, Mr. Cleek?
You can call me Chris, Miss. Raton.
Chris.
And you are ...
Geneviève.
Beautiful name.
Do not you feel any better.
Is napping to recover his strength.
You are here because of the peg,
I suppose.
Yes.
So I imagine that must be present.
My son also.
We have no secrets in this family,
Miss. Raton.
Brian.
Come here, son.
I have seen a ...
disturbing behavior lately,
Mr. Cleek.
Chris.
Peggy has not the good guy.
Often runs out of the classroom
to go to the bathroom.
Is falling behind in studies
and has used clothing sizes
much larger than hers.
She always enjoyed using my shirts.
Do you know if Peggy has a boyfriend,
Mr. Cleek?
No.
Had I know.
Why?
I think Peggy is ...
pregnant, Mr. Cleek.
Pregnant?
I'm not, no!
What makes you think you are pregnant,
Srta.Raton?
're Seeing, Mr.. Cleek.
Not so much anymore, but ...
will soon not to disguise.
His colleagues agree with his opinion,
Miss. Raton?
I did not talk with them ...
I thought it best to speak directly to you
and his wife.
And he did well.
I thought teachers knew hear,
but it seems that is not your case ...
because as you said, Miss. Raton,
Peggy has no boyfriend.
And if I had, I know.
It was not what I said?
Yes, but ...
He is accusing ... Brian?
It's just a boy.
Of course not!
So you're accusing me.
No. ..
No, I ...
Are you accusing me?
Father!
Come to my house ...
and accuses me of such a thing?
I did not do anything about that, Mr. Cleek.
I know I did not say so.
It's not what you said.
Think I'm stupid?
No.
Miss. Raton!
Yes?
Do you really think ...
who would commit such a sin?
Think?
Brian.
Take the rope.
Father!
Please for.
Father, please, she's my teacher.
Please, she's my friend.
Amiga?
He said he is your friend?
Your friend has just expose her as a bitch
you really are.
Father, can not do that!
You can not.
You can not? You can not?
I'm tired of you women
I can not say that.
His mother.
Her sisters idiots.
You-
I swear I did not tell anyone.
I know not.
You know what?
In fact all women.
All.
Are a leech.
All of you.
You suck everything in a man.
Every single day ...
suck you in!
Chris.
Stop it!
Shut up!
To know that you serve, Peg?
Do you know?
You and all the bitches like you.
They only serve for one thing.
Only one.
And most of the time ...
suck it up.
Think you do not know how you are?
Think you do not know?
It's just like that thing.
That thing down there.
That is where you all should be.
All of you.
Brian.
I lost control there.
Acted emotionally.
Never let emotions overcome you.
Right?
Right.
Great.
Open the door, son.
We'll fix this soon.
No!
No, please.
I swear I will not tell!
Hold it there.
Peggy.
Mommy, what's happening
with the dogs?
Come on, darlin '.
Go to your room and lock the door.
I do not think a good idea.
Bad idea.
Can you tell anophthalmia?
Legal, wanted to see her do it.
Anophthalmia!
Peggy.
What did you do?
Nor does it seem more real, right, Dad?
It seems to me, son.
Now I want to go home and wake his mother.
Take cleaning supplies and sacks.
Will not be able to eat it all.
Okay, Dad.
Enjoy and bring me a soda.
Darl.
Stay here, you know?
I want Mommy, I want Mommy.
Damn, where are the keys?
Hold this for me.
Not large.
Damn.
Peggy, his wife and sister.
Darlin '!