[peaceful sitar music]
♪ ♪
- And do, you know,
and wait it out
like the rest of the world?
You know what I mean?
I mean, the streets look like
any normal holiday.
People are pretty calm,
at least for now.
- Okay, so the green
is the voltage.
Do back-l liked it the way
it was a moment ago.
- Yeah, I hope I'm not boring
you, my dear friend.
Cisco?
- Why even bother?
- What?
- Cisco!
- No, I'm talking to Skye.
For you.
I do it for you.
I know you like it smooth.
- Son of a bitch.
Is that a meter maid
giving someone a ticket today?
Well, what do you expect?
It's Beverly Hills, right?
[water running]
All l can say is, you better
put that fine in an envelope
lickety-split before
the post office closes tonight.
You know what I'm saying?
- We're now 14 hours
and 44 minutes away
from the end of the Earth.
Our live coverage continues
with our crews in New York
and our colleagues
around the world.
As much as l would like
to give you the news otherwise,
there has been no information
to suggest any reprieve
in the rapid decline
of the Earth's ozone layer.
The top scientists still
predicting the lethal...
[siren wailing]
Will occur at 4:44 a.m.
eastern time.
When that moment comes
tomorrow morning,
the end Will be sudden
and global.
In Rome, the pope is
at the Vatican
preparing to deliver
a final blessing
to an estimated
3 million people
who have converged
on St. Peter's Square.
In the holy cities
of Mecca and Jerusalem
spontaneous pilgrimages
are under way.
Millions are on the move there,
hoping their religions...
[computer beeps]
[computerized phone ringing]
- Guess what, man.
I just caught the owner
as he was leaving.
Said he couldn't let down
his customers.
- Oh, shit.
- Wanted to say good-bye
to the regulars.
Anyway, he's leaving the door
open with a sign saying,
"Just take what you need.
Think of the others."
I love this guy.
He's a total mensch.
[indistinct voices from TV]
- But then the pilot came on.
"So there's
an emergency light on.
"We don't know
if the landing gear went down.
"Then we're gonna buzz
the control tower,
and they're gonna try to see
if our landing gear is down."
- You think they're right?
- Yes.
- [sighs]
- I know they're right.
[TV continues in background]
I know they're right.
- I know.
- "Take your shoes off,
because they might melt.
"All jewelry off,
because it Will burn
through your fingers."
And then someone
started to cry.
And then, uh, someone
got up from the other side
and came over and hugged them,
you know?
And then somebody else
started to cry,
and then somebody else got up
and went over and hugged them.
And then everybody, it was,
either you were breaking down
or you were hugging.
And, uh, everybody on the plane
was loving everybody else
on the plane,
unconditionally, you know?
"l could die in ten minutes
with you.
And let's spend the last
ten minutes, um, with a hug."
You know,
and it was just-
everybody just wanted
to hug everybody.
It was really beautiful.
- Oh, yes.
[breathes heavily]
[exhales loudly]
[sighs]
Oh.
- Mm.
[moaning]
- What do you got?
Oh, yes.
[breathing heavily]
[moaning]
- [moans]
[both moaning]
- Can you see the whole pen
without looking at the bottom?
- Well, this is
the continuation of a process
that actually began in '92
in Rio de Janeiro
at the so-called Earth Summit.
The Kyoto Protocol
was the first iteration
of how to get those commitments
into a binding form.
- No, you have to look
at the top.
And then you have look
at the bottom,
and then you say,
"There's a whole pen there,"
okay?
But by the time you get
to the bottom,
you don't know if
there's still a top there.
But in your mind,
you think there is.
You say,
"Geshla, it's a whole pen.
Geshla, it's a whole pen."
That's a proof.
That's a tiny little proof.
You ain't looking
at a pen.
You're looking at a tiny image
in your own mind, okay?
You are looking at a tiny image
in your own mind.
Now, immediately,
we have to call you back
from the precipice.
[sirens wail in distance]
- Hey.
- We have to pull you back
from the edge of this thing.
- You let me sleep.
Are you crazy?
- Don't think you're living
in your head.
- Well, what time is it?
- Okay, don't get confused.
- How long have I been sleeping?
- It hasn't been that long.
- We really don't have
too many years
to begin reducing
the global warming pollution
that is driving
the Earth's ecological system
towards catastrophe.
- Okay, stay with that.
They say ten years, don't you?
The window, they say,
is ten years, essentially?
- Yeah, and l actually said
that three years ago, yeah.
- And "catastrophe" means what?
- There are certain elements
in the Earth's
ecological system
that could be pushed beyond
a kind of tipping point.
The phrase is controversial.
But if the Greenland ice pack,
for example...
- Turn it off already, Cisco.
I'm tired of hearing
their bullshit.
And him, I'm sick of him.
How many times can you watch
the same shit over
and over again?
Just turn it off, please.
- Would produce
a six- to seven-meter increase.
The disappearance
of the North Polar ice cap
the size of the continental
United States:
it's been there
for 3 million years,
a key element in the Earth's
ability to cool itself.
[computerized phone ringing]
If it disappears, it would not
come back on a timescale
that would be comfortable...
- [laughs]
- Yes!
- How you doing, man?
I don't see you.
Hey, I don't see you.
What's on-
hey, there you go.
How you doing, man?
- Yeah, we're celebrating, man.
You know, party.
What can l say?
What else can we do?
- That's a strategy.
- Yeah, well, I don't know
about strategy.
I'm just letting
my feelings go; that's all.
What's Skye up to?
She working?
- She's working.
You know.
- Yeah.
Well, man, l Wish you were here
to party with us.
- I wish I was with you too,
but just keep doing
what you're doing.
[guitar music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Lola, girl.
Having a good day?
Getting your good-byes in?
♪ ♪
[sighs]
"At 4:44 a.m. EST
tomorrow morning,
"give or take a few seconds,
"the world
Will come to an end.
"It Will be the result
"of the ever--weakening
ozone layer
"that has now thinned
and dissipated
"far more rapidly
than even the worst doomsayer
"could have ever imagined.
"So the final explosion:
"meltdown Will come
with fair warning
"but no possible means
of escape.
There Will be no survivors."
"The world Will end."
- A little, tiny clock
is popping up
in the back of your head.
Why?
'Cause you have a seed
in your mind for that, right?
How did that seed get there?
Who put it there?
You did.
How?
That's karma.
Okay?
What does karma mean?
Karma means doing something,
saying something,
or thinking something
which puts an image
in your mind.
Something happens
under the influence
of kindness,
of your teacher's blessing.
Why are we talking about pot?
Why are we talking about clock?
Why are we talking about pen?
Because the world is not coming
from the outside.
The world is coming
from the images
you plant in your mind,
and you can plant whatever
world you want, you see?
You can plant whatever world
you want.
You don't need a body
to die in,
'cause it doesn't exist
down here.
It's an image in your mind.
Plant a different image
in your mind,
and you stop death.
You see?
'Cause this pot's not a pot,
and the pen's not a pen,
and the clock's not a clock,
and the arm is not an arm.
It's all the same, okay?
If it existed out there,
if there was pots,
and if there was clocks,
and if there was pens,
and if they were out there,
then,
then shoot yourself.
My brother killed himself.
He got it, and he shot himself,
you know.
He said, "What's the use?
Why should l waste my time?"
you know?
Kill yourself.
There's no point.
You can't change anything.
If a pot is a pot
and a pen is a pen, it-
you can't change.
Give it up.
What, you're just gonna
get older?
[bluesy guitar music]
♪ ♪
- [singing indistinctly]
- Whoo!
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- We were talking a lot
here in the newsroom
about how to deal
with these final minutes.
I've been in this chair
bringing you the news
literally thousands
of times.
Honestly, I don't want to spend
my final minute on Earth here.
We want the people
who work here
to be with their loved ones.
There was a spirit in New York
after the September 11th
terrorist attacks
that was about caring
and giving.
We have seen
that again today
under these unimaginably
tragic circumstances.
Al Gore was right.
By the time we realized
what we'd done,
we had already ruined
the planet.
And today it doesn't
matter where you live
or how much money you have.
We are all about
to face the same fate
at the same moment.
My family is waiting
for me now.
There's nothing more for us
to say here
but to repeat
what we have told you:
we don't have much time left.
You don't need me to sit here
and tell you how tragic
this is,
so this is the end
of our commentary.
We are going to fill the screen
with live camera views
from all over the city,
and we Will leave those
pictures up until the end.
[loud drumming]
♪ ♪
[haunting blues music]
[haunting drumming
and guitar music]
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
How can you not
think about the end?
How do you not plan
for the future?
How do these guys
not think about
what the hell is gonna
happen next?
You know, whether you're-
whether you're
cutting down a tree
or building the Trade Towers
or the atomic bomb-
fuck that.
I'm sick of it.
Where are the experts?
Where are the fucking experts?
These guys,
they're just talking, talking,
don't even have
the fucking slightest clue.
Never mind doubt.
I mean, we don't know
what the fuck is going on.
[muffled voice in the distance]
We're all gonna die, guys!
We're already dead!
[car horn honks]
Damn.
He looked right at me.
He was thinking straight.
Why let someone dictate
when you're gonna die?
Fucking motherfuckers.
Hey, don't put that coat on him!
Leave that man alone!
If you want to help him,
light a candle.
No!
Is that my fuckin' landlord?
Hey!
Hey, Wally!
How's that 2.5% a year
feel now, huh?
No, no, I'm not saying him.
Fuck you!
It's not his fault.
It's not anybody's fault.
We're all in the same boat.
We're all doomed.
I don't want to leave you.
These guys chopped down
every fucking tree
on the island
to make a statue.
Fuck.
And they don't have anything
to build a boat to get the fish.
At least they were doing-
worshipping God-
the fucking-
I shouldn't be saying that.
[sighs deeply]
[grunts]
Fuck that book!
What is wrong with you people?
Leave that man alone!
What is wrong with you?
- Baby.
- Come on.
Come on.
What are we waiting for?
- I'm waiting for you
to come down.
Come on.
- What are we waiting for?
A couple hours' difference?
- Get down, Cisco.
Come on.
Get down.
thump!
[both scream]
Stop it.
Stop!
[screams]
Hey.
- What?
- Come on.
It's gonna be okay.
- You're so sweet.
- It's gonna be okay.
- I don't know
what to do.
- Just be with me.
- I know.
I am.
You want to fly?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Yes?
You'd like that?
- Shoes off!
- Now, that I can do.
- Grab my wrists.
- Ah-ya!
Must have been the gaff tape.
- What happened to your legs?
- Okay.
- Spaghetti legs.
Okay.
Fly on home,
fly on home.
Where you goin', girl?
She be a pink butterfly.
Oh, yeah.
Where you goin', girl?
Where you goin'?
- We're going together up.
- Where are we going?
Ah-ya-ya!
[both laugh]
- Isn't it beautiful up here?
- Too beautiful.
I pissed my pants.
[both laugh]
- Your turn.
[buzzer]
- Who's that?
Yeah?
- Delivery.
- Yeah, come on up.
Yeah, I was wrong.
- You're kidding me.
- No.
Come on.
You hungry?
- Yeah.
Not again!
[bell dings]
- Hi.
Come on in.
Thank you very much.
What's your name?
You've been here, like,
a thousand times,
but I don't even know
your name.
- Chung.
- How are you doing?
You know what's going on,
or don't you give a shit?
Hey, kid.
Hey, you want some food?
Oh, I doubt it, huh?
You've probably had
plenty of this stuff.
Oh.
Keep the change.
Take it.
[chuckles]
Is there anything
I can do for you?
Can I get you anything?
- Skypey.
Skypey.
- Oh, yeah, Skype.
Yeah, I can do that for you.
I just got to get my computer.
Okay.
Okay, you just go ahead.
It's just...
You know how to do it, right?
Just-
yeah, there you go.
Skye.
Come and get it.
- Is it ready?
- Well, yeah.
[computer beeping]
[computerized phone dialing]
[both speaking
in foreign language]
- That's Vietnam.
That's Vietnam he's calling.
[baby crying on computer]
- [speaking in foreign language]
[computerized bubble pops]
- Chung?
Thank you.
I'm so glad I've known you.
Chung.
Thank you.
- We human beings are the-
almost like
a creator of the world
or the controller of the world.
Through technology,
through science,
we can do anything, everything.
We do not run nature.
I think we human beings
something above nature.
I think that's wrong.
After all, we are part
of the nature.
Uh, so through that way,
it become clear, you see,
we have the responsibility
to take care
of the environment,
of the nature,
because ultimately,
we are part of the nature.
So the nature balance
dramatically change,
we will suffer,
the entire humanity.
Then, this will,
what-what were instinct
will disappear.
So that's either one,
one force.
Then another, I think,
I think,
every human...requirement
or meaningful life,
we need to seek internal,
sort of inner
spiritual development.
Now, here, when l say
it's a spiritual-spirituality,
not necessarily
religious faith.
But even without
religious faith,
still there are such-
a sense of caring
one another,
sense of sharing one another.
There's a sense of community.
These are the basic
human good qualities.
These are
our fabled spirituality.
Without that,
you can't be happy person.
- One says that money
is the source of all evil.
Is that true?
- Yes.
- No
- Of course, if we, uh,
just become slave to money...
- Eh.
- Then all our energy
or mind, this is-
concentrate on money.
And then, uh, the greed,
that kind of thing,
extreme greed...
- [laughs]
- Then in order
to get more money,
then no hesitation to adopt
various different method.
Scandals or corruptions
or exploitation,
forcing these things.
Then, of course, money,
it then becomes evil.
But for sustain, for life,
without money, you can't.
[bluesy guitar music]
♪ ♪
- You're a medical man.
What do you think happens
after bodily death?
- After bodily death,
then they all get wings,
and they all start
flying up toward heaven.
[both laughing]
- Yeah?
And do you think
you'll be a good flyer?
- I think I'll fly up there
eventually.
- Yeah?
And then once you gets there,
what happens?
A big party?
- Big party up there.
Oh, yeah.
- And then you fly around
some more?
- Now that's the whole idea
behind it.
It's a big party.
[laughter]
And you're getting with
your old friends, and even,
even those that aren't
too friendly with you.
- The people
that are responsible
for the end of the world:
how do you feel about them?
- Well, the people
that are responsible...
[computerized phone ringing]
Hopefully it'll backtrack
on them,
and they'll get the same
treatment that they gave
to the ones that they
subjected to that fate.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Hang on.
I just got to open this up.
There we go.
Oh, baby.
I'm not very technological.
There we go.
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
How you doing?
- I'm all right.
- Yeah?
And your mother?
- You know her.
She's acting like nothing's
gonna happen tonight.
She's acting like
everybody's stupid.
What's with her?
She thinks I'm stupid.
She's-she's in denial.
- Well, listen.
She's your mother,
so that's just the way it is,
okay?
- Okay.
How's Skye?
- She's all right.
What are you gonna do tonight?
- Oh, um, Lena's
coming over to stay.
- And her mom?
- She can't stand her.
Besides, her boyfriend's over.
It'll be better for her
over here.
Um, I don't know.
We'll play some video games.
- You say hi to her for me,
okay?
I've always liked her.
She's doing all right?
- [scoffs]
She says she doesn't want
to die a virgin.
- [laughs]
- Guess it's too late for that.
- [crying]
- Dad, don't cry.
- I'm sorry.
- Because you're gonna
make me cry,
and l did my makeup
perfect.
- I'm sorry.
I miss you.
- I miss you too, Dad.
- J.J.
J.J., you have to let
your friend in downstairs.
- Here comes Morticia Addams.
- Yeah.
- Hurry up, J.J.
- Hi.
- She's locked out
downstairs, honey.
The doorman's not there.
You're gonna have to hurry up
before something happens
to her.
Go on.
She's downstairs.
- See ya, hon.
Hon.
- Hi.
- Look, you should not be
upsetting her like that.
How can you be so selfish?
Seriously.
- You gonna be angry still?
Now?
I didn't leave.
It was you that didn't stay.
- I-I didn't stay?
Who ran off with the teenager?
- I didn't run off.
It was you.
It was your pride.
If you would've just
hung in there,
everything would have
been different.
- Yeah, different.
I'll tell you different.
- Yeah, tell me.
- Your daughter would have had
a father instead of some guy
who didn't even really care
about her.
- I cared!
- Never.
- I-
- When?
- I cared.
I didn't want to leave.
I'm a guy that sticks.
It was you that didn't want me.
I--I was--
I was so, so confused.
And you just had to be
a little more patient with me,
but you were too scared.
You were-
you were too anxious.
- Anxious?
What-what-
you know what?
You need to just
to grow the fuck up.
Grow up!
- You think-
You think I love her more
than I love you?
You think I love my family...
- [screaming]
[overlapping screams and shouts]
- [laughing]
- Calm down!
Calm the fuck down!
- [screaming and sobbing]
- You don't understand.
You don't understand.
- Get away from me!
Get away from me!
- Stay, stay, stay, stay.
- No!
- Don't go.
- [breathing heavily]
[screaming]
How could you?
- Skye.
- I need to speak to my mother!
- Okay, but you
don't understand.
[computerized phone dialing]
[phone beeps]
- Hi.
- Hello, darling.
- Hi, Mom.
- What's the matter?
I'm so glad you called.
- He's such a jerk.
He was just telling her
that he loves her.
Doesn't he know
how much it hurts me?
And that bitch,
she was just looking at me.
She was just laughing at me.
- Well, was she at your house?
- No, it was on the phone.
It was on Skype.
She's so ugly.
How can he be with such a woman?
- It's all right.
He's with you now.
That's what matters.
- I can't take him
sometimes, Mom.
I can't help it.
[horns honking]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[rap music]
♪ ♪
- The whole system.
I don't believe in anything
that's going on.
And honestly,
I just can't stand all this,
and I don't want to
believe all what's going on.
I'm still gonna be hanging on,
you know, the fact that,
that, uh, you know, I mean-
I know that the world,
that the Chinese had an atomic
explosion 5,000 years ago.
I know that the world
will stay.
If we perish,
okay, we perish.
But then we live on as well,
so we live on.
But I'm just so angry
at all of this,
and l can just barely,
barely talk about it.
I want to scream
at those fuckers,
All those politicians and all
those rules and the PC world.
And, you know, I mean,
look at this smoking.
l can't even smoke anymore.
What's the matter with me?
You know, you can't smoke.
You can't smoke
in your own house.
You know, people denounce you.
If you throw a butt
on the ground,
you have to pay 50 quid.
It's outrageous.
I mean, what the fuck has
the world come to, you know?
I'm just, you know,
I'm just so upset.
- Don't get upset now, Mom.
Really, please.
- Deep down, you're at peace
in your heart.
- I know, it's...
- You've done the right things.
You've done your art.
You've done everything that you
can possibly do to have-
to have a faith in this world
that they've destroyed.
And I'm proud of you.
And I don't want
to see you sad.
I don't want to see you upset.
I don't want to see you-
you know,
I want to remember you happy.
I want to remember you
with a big smile on your face
and your little green eyes
and your little grin.
I love you.
I love you so much.
- I love you.
I love you so much, Mom.
- Yes, I love you.
- Good-bye.
- I love you.
- Thank you for being my mom.
- Just transcend that.
Just go to another sphere.
- Yeah.
- And we'll be all right.
- Yeah, a better sphere.
Thank you for being my mom.
I love you.
[knocking]
- Hey, Javi.
Javi.
- Yo, it's Cisco.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, right.
You scared me for a second.
- Cisco!
[laughs]
- What are you doing here?
- Hey.
- Hey, brother.
Good to see you.
- Yeah, good to see you.
- Come here.
Why didn't you use
the front door?
You're gonna get yourself killed
doing that.
Oh, shit.
- I don't believe it.
- No, I can't either, man.
I'm surprised to see you here.
- Yeah, man.
Get him a chair.
- Here.
Have a seat.
- Thanks.
- Tempting fate tonight.
- What a surprise.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you.
- You want something?
You want a-
we've got brandy.
- Some water.
- Yeah, please.
- Yeah?
Thanks.
Sticking with it, huh?
Guess we're all here.
Want to look death in the eyes.
- Looking good, buddy.
- Good, good.
- Salud.
- To end times.
- To old friends.
How much time you got?
- 2 years, 22 days.
Uh, 23 days.
- Awesome.
That's awesome.
- And you?
- Well, if things weren't
the way they are,
I'd have 20 years
end of next month.
[woman scoffs]
- 20 years.
- Yeah.
- If things weren't the way
they are.
- Yeah, well, you know,
if we ain't gonna get high now,
we're never getting high.
- Why not?
- Why?
Have you got a good enough
reason to get high?
Tell me.
I'll get high with you.
- [laughs]
How about-
how about, like,
the ending of the world?
- Eh, no.
Not good enough.
The world's been ending
ever since it started, man.
You know, we've been ending
ever since we were born.
Don't take that shit
too seriously.
- I don't.
- Good.
- I'm not sure I can take this
rap right now, man.
- What rap?
- I don't know.
I just feel you
winding up a little bit.
- Who, me?
I'm not winding up.
I'm sitting here
with a fucking choice, man.
You know,
the choice is for me,
I mean, I don't care.
You can
get high right there.
You know, I won't judge.
I don't give a shit, you know.
I would prefer you didn't,
but, for me, I feel like,
I just feel like
I got a choice, you know?
I could shoot some dope,
go out nodding,
or go out eyes wide open.
You know,
see the fucking light show.
I mean, what the fuck is that
gonna look like, you know?
The end of the world,
the end of the dream.
The end of-
I want to see it.
I want to fucking be wide awake.
So that's the choice.
- Yeah, I'm not sure I want to.
What's going on
changes everything.
- It does, and it doesn't.
- Tell me.
- For me, I just think
it changes a lot,
but I got to stay true to-
for me, I just feel like
I got to stay true
to who I've been.
The good stuff.
- Oh, shit, you guys
are getting heavy.
I just want to get laid,
you know?
- You just want to get laid?
- Yeah.
[chuckles]
- You just want to get laid?
- Uh-huh.
- Come here.
You're gonna get your wish.
- Mmm.
Get it while you can, right?
[laughter]
- Good to know what you want.
- Got to get off some way
tonight.
- And may I-
this is not a rap.
It's a suggestion.
- Okay.
- If I may humbly offer
this suggestion to you,
my junkie brother, right,
who I've been through
everything with?
- Yes.
I'm listening.
- Don't pick up a minute
before the end of the world.
- [chuckles]
Seems like as good time as any-
[laughter]
- That's the choice, though.
That's the-
you know?
- I know.
- That's the choice.
- Yeah, I know.
- Let's watch
the light show, man.
We were walking home
from this meeting,
and we walked by here,
and I see the light on, right?
And I'm like, "I wonder
if these guys are still here."
Haven't thought of them
in fucking years, man.
This used to be my family.
This was like, you know,
my brother,
my sisters,
like my family.
I saw the lights on.
So I ring the buzzer,
and Javi answers
the fucking door,
and they're right
in the chairs
where I fucking left them,
you know?
And so come to be
of service over there,
be of service here,
whatever.
I don't know.
If some idiot comes in
and needs another idiot,
I figured I'd be here.
And who walks in?
- You're that idiot.
- It's a miracle.
It's a fucking miracle.
- It's not a miracle.
- No, there's something
going on.
Why are you here?
Why did you come through
the fucking window?
- Just, you know...
- I haven't seen you
in how long?
- A long time.
- Long time.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know,
I just think, you know-
it's not-
I just been thinking about,
you know,
the past and friends,
and I just felt the need
to drop by, huh?
And so I'm not, you know-
I don't know.
I got to go, though.
- You got to?
- Yeah, no, I can't,
because Skye's-
no, Skye's at home.
You know, she's by herself.
- You gonna go right home,
though?
- Yeah, I got to go.
- I mean, go right home.
Just-
it's dangerous out there.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no, it feels-
I don't know.
It's weird out there.
But no.
I got to go, okay?
- I'll walk you out.
- Listen.
I love you, buddy.
- I love you too.
- Use the front door
like a normal person.
[laughter]
Glad we saw you.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
All right.
Thanks, man.
- Hey, Cisco.
- Yeah?
- What if they're wrong?
- [laughs]
- Huh?
Think about it.
- Okay, I'm thinking.
- All right, buddy.
Love you.
- Take care.
Thanks.
- Hey, uh, Javi?
- Yeah?
- He didn't...
- No, no, no.
He didn't get nothing.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- He better not.
He's better just the way he is.
- Right, right.
No, I'm sure.
I'm honest.
- You wouldn't lie, what-
being a drug dealer
and everything.
- I would not.
- All right.
- He didn't.
- What'd I say?
- Go easy.
- [chuckles]
- ♪ You made me cry
when you said good-bye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ You broke my heart
when you said we're apart ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ Oh, well, good-bye ♪
♪ Although I'll cry ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
[saxophone solo]
♪ ♪
♪ You made me cry
when you said good-bye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
- I don't want to die!
- ♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ Oh, well, good-bye ♪
♪ Although I'll cry ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame? ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ ♪
[buzzer]
- Cisco.
[elevator whirring]
[gasping]
[bell dings]
Where were you?
- I just went out on the streets
to see what was going on.
I forgot my keys.
I didn't mean what I said.
I was just trying to get her
to understand.
She's a hard case.
You're not like her.
That's one of the reasons
I love you.
Forgive me.
- Come inside me.
[both breathing deeply]
[ethereal music]
♪ ♪
[sizzling]
[door clicks]
- [shrieks]
How could you?
- Let me have it.
It's mine.
- No.
- Give it to me.
- No!
- I want it.
- How could you?
- Come on.
Give it to me.
All right.
Come on, we'll-
we'll throw it out together.
- [pained shout]
You're hurting me!
[shouting]
[cries]
[crying softly]
[wind howling]
- Ah, this is fantastic.
Also the serpent-
which represents
the dynamic of life-
the serpent can shed its skin
to be born again,
and so represents
the power of life
to throw off death
and represents the bondage
of life to time.
It's the dynamic of life
and consciousness
in the field of temporal
pairs of opposites-
birth, death and all that.
And life goes on through it.
It's been turned
into the negative principle
in our tradition,
as though our tradition
were against life.
And, uh, so, since-
since our tradition is
against life, well,
the deity himself
is against life.
And you have a deity
who's talking about
supernatural grace
and virtue and all,
but life is something
to be, as it were,
despised instead of celebrated
and a body as something awful
rather than awesome.
[wind howling]
[gunshot]
[static hissing]
[rumbling thud]
- [screams]
Cisco!
Cisco, come to me, please!
What's happening?
What's that?
- I'm here.
[rumbling thud]
[glass shatters]
- [screams]
- Hold on to me.
[rumbling thud]
[raucous music]
♪ ♪
[voices overlapping]
Stay with me.
Stay with me!
- I am.
[indistinct voices]
[bell clanging]
[people shouting]
[rumbling thud]
Don't be scared.
- I'm scared.
- Don't be scared.
[indistinct voices]
- Who makes this whole tub run?
Ain't it us, guys?
- Yeah!
- Well, then, we belong,
don't we?
We belong and they don't,
that's all.
As far as this being hell,
aw, nuts, you lost your nerve.
That's what.
This is a man's job, get me?
It belongs.
It runs this tub.
No stiffs need apply.
We aren't stiffs, see?
- What comes down
to a ultra feeling,
I mean, the ultra feeling
that love, family is important.
Hey, have you ever
heard of this?
What are we gonna do
when it's 4:44?
- But l can see that deep down
you're at peace in your heart.
You've done the right things.
You've done your art.
You've done everything
that you can possibly do
to have a faith in this world
that they've destroyed.
[faint rumbling]
- And this is very difficult
to explain, okay?
In those few minutes,
you see the face
of every living creature
in this world, okay?
In the minute.
At the same time,
you see the whole face
of billions of creatures.
And I'm not talking
just people:
animals, insects, birds,
worms, snails,
you know, all of them.
You can see.
- We're together.
I'm-I'm here.
I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
We're here together.
[intense drumming music]
♪ ♪
[driving rock guitars]
- I'm gonna smoke my cigarette,
and I'm gonna die.
- There's gonna be
a really big light, Cisco.
But don't be afraid of it.
- I'm not afraid.
- It's our love.
- It's our wisdom.
We're going together
towards this big light.
towards the big light, Cisco.
My heart against your heart,
and together, we're taking
all beings with us.
And we're protecting them,
and we're loving them,
and we're taking them with us.
And we have each other.
And we surrender completely
to God.
And you're protected.
And we're together,
and we're going together.
And all we have is right now.
All we have is each other.
All we have is
each other.
I love you.
And we're angels already.
[bluesy guitar music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Lit cigarette ♪
♪ Blindfold in place ♪
♪ Your time has come ♪
♪ 20 steps away ♪
♪ Throw it away ♪
♪ It's the last day ♪
♪ Your time has come ♪
♪ All hell to pay ♪
♪ From sweet Detroit ♪
♪ To the Great Plains ♪
♪ They bared his heart ♪
♪ He watches and waits ♪
♪ He knew it would come ♪
♪ Like the wind and the rain ♪
♪ Get on your knees
and pray ♪
♪ On your knees and pray
on the last day ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Silver and gold ♪
♪ Taken away ♪
♪ They lockin' it up ♪
♪ For the kings and the slaves ♪
♪ The Duke Ellington's hand ♪
♪ Touching your face ♪
♪ All is his ♪
♪ 'Cause he gave it away ♪
♪ His kingdom gone ♪
♪ Without a trace ♪
♪ I'm talking to you ♪
♪ Throw it away ♪
♪ Let's sit and wait ♪
♪ Get on your knees ♪
♪ On your knees and pray ♪
♪ It's the last day ♪
♪ The last day ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The way he was born ♪
♪ Seems insane ♪
♪ From their mother's arms ♪
♪ To their daddy's grave ♪
♪ It's the devil's work ♪
♪ So the devil pay ♪
♪ Watch what we got ♪
♪ And do it our way ♪
♪ That's what they say ♪
♪ That's what
they say ♪
♪ Throw it away ♪
♪ Well, that's it anyway ♪
♪ God is gone,
God is gone ♪
♪ Well, they say,
they say ♪
♪ That our last day ♪
♪ It's the last day ♪
♪ The last day on Earth ♪
♪ ♪