Class of 199-fucking-9!
Come on, we gotta
party like It's 1999!
I just don't
understand anything.
I don't wanna
face those people.
Only you know
what you want.
I'm stuck with this routine.
It's the last day
of school forever.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Come on, wake up, Julia.
Hm.
Today is the beginning of the
end and the end of the beginning.
And you don't
wanna be late for it.
You always say that.
Angie.
Angie. It's time
to wake up.
It's your last day
In middle school.
You know what
your counselor said.
You won't be able to
finish junior high school
If you miss
one more half day.
Little Angie
Get the fuck out of here!
Unbelievable.
Hm.
I wrote a new
song last night.
Sweet.
We can
practice it later.
H m.
You want
some of this? Huh?
Last day
of school! Oh, shit!
Oh, shit!
The car,
what the hell.
Fuck you both.
Oh, nice nighty.
I'll see you later.
Shit. Shit!
What's up, ass fuck?
Come on. Come on.
More. More. More!
Oh. God.
What's wrong
with you?
Wow!
I don't even remember when
I actually ever decided
Brown was where I
wanted to got to college.
God. Rhode Island. I'm not
gonna know a single soul.
Man, you know, even
if Brown does suck,
at least you're
experiencing some place new.
I mean, I was looking at
this brochure the other day,
for NYU and my mom
started flipping out
saying that New York
was all about sex and drugs
and I wanted to be,
like, you know what?
I'm not a virgin.
I already have a tattoo
and I do
a ton of drugs here.
Oh, God.
I'm gonna be real
famous some day.
Watch!
Stacy.
Stacey, you forgot
your lunch. Stacey.
Stacey. Stacey.
Mom. Stop saying
my name so much.
You forgot your lunch.
Stacey.
Hi, Mrs. Cherry.
Hello, Julia. Hi. Say hello, Sockets.
Yeah. Your
dog hates you.
So you guys are ready for summer?
Mom.
Has Stacey been smoking
any of the funny stuff, huh?
Mom. Go in the
house, now. Okay? Bye.
Bye. Say Bye-bye.
Bye. Mom.
Oh my God.
My mom is so insane.
I
wouldn't complain,
your boyfriend lives
in your basement
for a year now? And
she still has no clue.
What was I supposed to do?
His grandmother kicked him out.
I'm just saying I can't believe
she still hasn't figured it out.
Well my mom choses what she wants to
know and what she doesn't want to know.
Hm. Kinda like, you.
Hey, Dylan might
treat me like crap
but he's not cheating on me. And if he
cheated on me, then I would dump him.
Let's not talk about it.
Don't do it.
What?
Julia, don't.
Come on.
This isn't funny You're
gonna hurt our friend.
Ahhh!
There she goes.
Hey, ugly.
Ha, ha, ha.
You're such an ass.
Oh, I know. Come
on, shut up and get in.
I love you.
I hate you.
I know,
I know.
So you guys are coming to
my pep rally later, right?
Yeah. About that... Nah.
Stop it.
You are coming.
Class of '99.
The sons of bitches.
I can't believe that we
are officlally seniors.
Like, next year that's gonna be
out last year. How crazy is that?
Another whole year until we
actually get out of this place.
Exactly.
In the meantime we can still get
really, really, really wasted.
Oh my God. You're such a cheerleader.
Good morning to you.
I hope this very reliable
tardiness habit of yours
will not be continuing
into the next year.
High school is just one mind
In a whole lot of bodies.
And I know how
that mind thinks.
So keep that in mind.
What Is our
purpose? Our meaning?
Why are we all here and what
are we each supposed to do?
Is there some
predetermined plan
driving all the decisions that we make,
or are we ourselves
making our choices
based on our
own free wills?
These mental thoughts
are liminal phases.
Childhood Is about magic,
but teen Is about mystery.
It is the time when the
world suddenly gets closer
and the colors get brighter.
Rules seem
ready to be broken.
You all may have
different problems.
But It Is the same problem.
You got to figure
out what you want.
Sorry, so, Mod, are you listening
to anything I'm saying? Mod!
Mod I
You look like
a mangloid baby.
Here.
What's a mangled In baby?
Just... Just...
Weirdo.
Mom give you
lunch money?
Yeah Yeah.
I gotta, I gotta ask you for
a favor I need you to, uh...
I need you to... Uh...
I need you to
sell. All of this.
I need you to sell everything
in there. Yeah? Is that cool?
It's my last
day at school, man.
It's your last
day at school?
Yeah. Before summer.
You mean you're like leaving
for college or something...
No, man. I'm a Junior.
Oh, good. Uh...
There's a big
ass party tonight.
Really? Where?
I don't have a
fucking clue.
Here.
Peace out.
Smoke that weed, bitch.
What It Is the
never ending equation
otherwise known as chaos?
Chaos theory Is really about
finding the underlying order
apparently random things
Mod.
Speaking In...
You're in
the wrong class.
That the entire
human world might be...
What's up, Sylvia?
Which states
that we are all part
of some greater order.
Mod.
A w, come on.
You girls
want some weed?
You've all played
dominoes. When you topple one
the others fall In sult. This
would be an Isolated system
except for the fact that
something outside the system
Yeah, Mod.
He didn't take a hall pass.
Oh, he's got a permanent
note, Mr. Shapiro.
You know, for AD H D.
He'd better not miss
my frigging pep really.
Don't forget it.
It's during last period.
Okay.
I will be tumbling.
I just want to remind
everybody of the pep rally.
Oh, great.
The spirit
is important.
I don't want to
see one empty seat.
Pull your skirt up!
So, you
should all come.
Okay?
In the larger systems...
You'd better run, bitch.
I gotta shit.
Oh, yeah.
What's up, babe?
How are you doing?
How you doing
son? Hey, hey.
Why don't you come to
our show tonight? Huh?
Come on, we gotta go.
Gotta run. And just go.
Ah!
Jesus.
See you.
Hey.
What's up. Hey.
You suck.
Hey. Uh!
Dude, remember that
time that I got so wasted
that I pissed
on your sock drawer?
And I didn't tell you about it
for like three months or something.
Okay. You better just
come to my pep rally.
Hi, guys.
Guess what?
The Banks have shrooms.
Hey, I told
her that.
Oh my God, we should totally
trip our faces off later.
Yeah.
How much
do they have?
See what you've done to her? N ice work.
Hanky, have
you seen Pete?
Uh, okay, you're lame, he's
your boyfriend, after all.
No, you're lame.
Your name is Hanky.
Alright,
I'm leaving.
I'll see
you later.
Are you going
to get wasted?
No, I'm going to Pete's house
and drag his lazy ass out of bed.
Don't you dare
miss my pep rally!
Wake up.
Hm. Come here.
Get up. No!
I'm serious.
I'm serious. I'm serious,
dude. Just get up.
You act like there's a
reason for me to get up.
It's a nice
thing to say to me.
Do you not get it?
This is embarrassing.
Just because you're not graduating
today doesn't mean it's forever.
Stop it.
Stop it and get up. I'm begging you
for the millionth morning, please.
Come and help
me pick out a shirt.
Don't.
You know what?
I really can't go.
What? I just drove all the way down
here and waited while you got ready.
Whatever. The only reason you
come here is to get me out of bed.
You act like
that's a bad reason.
I just wish it
wasn't the only one.
Oh my God.
You're ridiculous.
Are you coming
with me or not?
Maybe I'll see
you later tonight.
Who-hoo. Stacey
Is the girl I
Shot gun!
Pick me up when you get pot, okay?
Brianne, I have pot.
I thought we were getting the mushrooms.
I'll see you later.
You did good out there.
Thanks, I wish more than
ten people came, but thanks.
Okay. Where do
we go from here?
Where did Brianne go?
Can you take me home?
What? Summer just started.
I can't believe this.
What? I just have to
change. I'll be right back.
You still have
boring old me, Dawn.
Hey, guys.
The Banks
have mushrooms.
Yeah, Brianne
already told me.
Of course she did.
That was the last
time I shared.
I was so proud of myself
I fucked my brother, man.
I'm serious, fuck him, dude, he's probably
got 20 left and he's the fucking sell.
Hey.
Huh? Hey.
Hey, Mod.
Ah!
What?
Help.
Sorry you had to wait.
Had to handle, uh,
some business. Fuck!
Take care of business. What business?
That business. You just witnessed
my fucking business. Okay?
For your fucking Information,
I sold all my weed.
Did you sell yours?
I don't fucking think so.
You're so
special to me.
Stop touching me and shit, man.
I'm jumpy right now. Just fuck out.
Yeah, I need to
smoke some weed.
So is Dylan downstairs?
Yes.
Yeah, tell that
asshole I said hi.
Bye, guys.
Hey.
Oh, watch this.
Look up.
It took me
all day to do that.
I can't wait to
get drunk tonight.
It's not fair, you know,
I have to go to school
and you get to sit in here
and do what you want all day.
Tell me again why suspension
Is such a bad thing.
Because I sit down here alone
all day waiting for your fine ass.
And I'm starving.
Why don't you just make
yourself a sandwich upstairs?
'Cause I'm lazy and I
knew you'd be home soon.
Dylan.
My mom might
be home any minute.
She ain't never
been a problem before.
You know what
this kid said?
I'm telling you, man, butts are
the new boobs Trust me. I know.
Now that I'm in high school I'm
gonna go get me a nice big Freshman...
Yeah. Freshman.
Hey, Riley,
what's popping?
You all know Riley?
Riley's a sophomore.
First of all, you sound
like a complete fucking tool.
And second, fuck a
freshman, you know?
Talking about the seniors. So get back
to me on how that butt stiffing goes.
'Cause I'm gonna be busy
punishing that prime ass.
18-year-olds
know what's up, son.
What's up?
Don't touch me.
Riley lost his virginity
when he was like 9 years old.
He's fucked like every girl
in the entire freshman class.
You're damn
right I have.
Hello, kiddies.
Wooo!
Woo-hoo.
Howdy howdy.
Let's get rowdy.
How're you doing?
Alright.
Son of a bitch.
Woo!
Do you wanna get
some beer or what, man?
Whatever. I don't care.
Dude, what is
wrong with you?
I don't know, I failed too many
classes to graduate on time.
And my girlfriend
doesn't like me anymore.
Whatever, man.
Screw it.
None of that shit matters.
I'll tell you what matters.
Beer. Beer matters.
Do me a favor. Stop
trying to cheer me up.
Aw, fuck Julia, dude.
High school girls suck.
College bitches are way
cooler. Trust me, I know this.
Oh, and, um, who here
is going to college?
No, I don't know if I want
to break up with Pete or not.
I mean, after all
is he gonna be around my whole senior
year as the guy that didn't graduate?
But what If I break up with
him and then I want him back?
What I need to do, I need
to hook up with someone else.
That way I can see.
I won't make the break up
decision without knowing for sure.
But I need to think about It
because Pete can't find out.
No. The last thing you wanna
do Is be caught up In a secret.
I'm stuck In
this routine.
I try to get my sister to be more
obedient and help out with my parents
I try to get Stacey out of
her abusive relationships
so that she can actually be
happy instead of faking it.
Do you think
Dylan hits Stacey?
I know he's not good.
I'm gonna fucking
kill that kid.
Stacey won't break up with
him unless he cheats on her.
I know exactly who
you should hook up with.
Dylan, I wasn't finished.
That's my
homies. Peace.
Come on, come on, come
on. Bring your yellow ass.
Move, man. I ain't got all day.
I like the back
seat anyway.
Yeah, that's
what I thought.
What's up, son?
There's crank
in this mother.
Hey, what the
hell is that smell?
You smell that?
It smells like what Stacey
wears, that Plumero shit...
No, this is Country Apple, man,
it's nice, I got two bottles.
But Plumero's cool too, I
got some of that at the house.
Eddie, you're
so gay.
Well, I mean, I think
it smells really good.
Just what
I thought.
You're gay. You've never fucked a bitch.
That's true.
No, man, that's
not true, I have so.
No. Bullshit. The simple fact
Is you want that shit so bad.
You end up driving the pussy
away, Now, you take a cat like me,
I did everything I want
'cause I don't want nothing.
Fuck bitches.
Hold on, man, I ain't saying all that.
Zack, don't even listen
to Biz, he's ugly.
Me and you are
on the same page.
We're on the same
side of the tracks.
You make your own fate.
Now matter how many dudes
shot you down, you'll get one.
You make your fate.
Yeah, man, my fate is
working in my dad's garage.
It's a
great thing.
Yo. Slow down.
What's up?
What's your name?
Holly. Oh my gosh, we just
finished middle school.
Right now.
So you guys are officially all
high school freshmen now, huh?
Hell, yeah.
About time.
Man, move it, dip shit.
So, you got a
license, young blood?
No. Why? Are you a cop?
Not yet.
So where
are you'all goin'?
Wherever you tell us.
What should we say?
And where are we going?
Man, fuck it.
Drive away.
Let's go to Bailey's. They're
practicing for tonight.
Meet us at
Bailey's House.
Alright.
You could even
just follow us there.
Man, what the fu... Bailey don't want
hoes over there when they're rehearsing.
I do. I love hoes.
Big Bailey.
How ya doin' man?
Hey, man.
What's up, man?
Good to see you.
What are you guys doing? Are
you sort of chilling out or...
Hey, hey.
What's up, man?
Hi.
Hey, uh, you guys came
here just to hang out...?
Yeah.
Cool. We're just practicing. You
can sit on the couch over here.
Alright.
Yeah. To the left.
Are you ready for
some monkey ass?
Yo. Gimme
that. Go.
You know who it is it's
that big boy Biz. Now.
Oh, yeah.
Have you ever looked
out to a blue ocean?
Oh, man.
What's happenin', baby?
So, hey, did you
all graduate today?
Fuck,
no. These two did.
I got one more year more
to go. I'm a young bitch.
Are you gonna keep playing
together when you go to college?
We're actually not going to
college. We're punk rockers
So we're just gonna continue playing.
Yeah. We're just
gonna do that.
Yeah.
That's cool. And your parents
just don't care? It's awesome!
No...
No, fuck, my parents are furious
at me for not applying to college.
This is your
family too, right?
You're choosing us, right,
not... not your parents.
I'm just saying. It's a pretty
risky decision these days
to not apply to
college. That's all.
Regardless, we're gonna, you know,
continue until we have success, right?
I mean, that's
the plan. Right?
Who cares if we're
successful, man?
As long as we're
having a good time.
These good times, right, how are they
gonna continue unless we make money?
Fucking idiot.
He does write all our songs and,
you know, he's a lyrical genius.
So I guess that's why he
doesn't live In reality.
God. Uh! Ah!
Uh...
I like this.
It likes you.
So what are
you doing later?
I don't
know. Actually...
Right. Right.
Okay, so.
Time to start.
I'm an idiot. We're
actually playing at a show
um, I'm in this
band, Over It.
Uh, you know... That's alright...
The band's called Over It.
And, see? You can see
it on that drum there.
You should come to the show. I mean,
do you wanna come? Do you wanna come?
Do you guys have plans or
what are you guys doing?
I don't really know.
My first time
babysitting.
Try to act like
a normal person.
Oh, that'll be hard.
Tori, hi, wow,
who's running late?
Please, hurry up and come in
because I need to leave like now.
Hi, mwah. Oh. Come in.
Come in. Come in. Come in.
I am so sorry, Mr. Turner
told me 4:45. Am I really late?
Oh, well, apparently not
In my dear husband's mind.
Hm. So, we should probably
just be a few hours.
Oh my God...
and you!
And your whole Valedictorian
thing and the making us proud.
Oh, God. Congratulatlons.
Yay! H m. Bye-bye.
What...?
Hey!
Hey.
Dude, how many of
these things are there?
There's three children.
This is Reagan,
and Jenna and Sam.
Hi, little girls,
my name's Sylvia.
God! What the fuck?!
Hey, do not say
those things...
Jesus! You
son of a bitch!
Hey.
Holy Mother of God!
Time for you
to leave, now!
I didn't do
anything. God!
You keep driving,
bitch. You don't know me!
What?
Hi, Mrs. Ford.
Is Angie here?
Yes.
Um. Do you think that maybe we could
come in and say hi to her real fast?
Is that alright?
Yeah, I was
totally...
You're coming
with us, right Angie?
I'm sorry. Are
you talking to me?
Yeah. You're
coming with us, right?
No fucking way.
- No, you have to come with us.
- I need you.
Okay? I'm gonna hook up with
someone. I'm gonna hook up.
You don't need us.
Just wear your underwear.
Bitch.
Rahhhrr.
So, are your
parents mad
'cause you missed
last day of school?
No, they're trying to get over
last 1000 days she's missed school.
I have A's on all my exams, they
know I'm gonna graduate anyways.
Well, it's called
attendance, smart ass.
Oh my God, please attendance should
be applied on a basis only situation.
I get good grades.
I get perfect grades.
Why does it even
matter if I'm in class?
Don't you wanna
see your friends?
You bitches
all come to me!
Okay, shit head, why don't you go to school
'cause that's the way real life works.
And you're a part of it.
I don't
like real life.
Mrs. Ford
Angie.
What do you want?
Don't come in.
Your father and I are not exactly
happy about you having friends over.
Oh, it's okay. We'll
be gone soon anyway.
Are you planning
on leaving, Angie?
Mom. Does it
really matter?
Of course it matters.
You know your father and I want
to have a serious discussion
about how things
are going to be...
I have friends over right
now. Can't we talk later?
Yes. Look, you were grounded
until we've worked things out.
If I feel like I wanna
go out with my friends
then I'm going to. And if you keep
bugging me about it then I definitely will.
You're only 14 and you
don't even go to school!
You're growing
up too fast.
Compared to the 1700's where children
were forced to work In factories?
Wait. No. You must be
comparing me to the 1970s
when you were a teenager, but weird
because last time that I checked
my generation is less likely to smoke, drink,
do drugs, commit a crime, get pregnant,
or drop out of high
school. God, that's weird
and I don't have time to explain the
gap in between, but peace and love.
- How can you...
- I am your mother!
Duh.
So...
Dad?
Is anything wrong?
No.
Dawn and I are picking
up Brianne and Stacey
and then we're probably
gonna go out for the night.
Okay. Love you.
I want you to sleep at
home. And I love you, too.
What?
Dad, no. I've already, like, decided that
I was gonna sleep at Stacey's or wherever.
It's the first
night of summer.
I don't want you guys to
force me to drink and drive.
Then just don't drink. There you go.
You're not In your bed In the
morning, we've got problems.
You just don't
understand anything.
Right. I'm just trying
to ruin your life.
And Julia, would you
please talk to your sister?
I really need you to stay
home tonight. It's important.
Please.
Love you.
I know...
Excuse me,
can you knock?
Excuse me, can
you suck my ass?
Julia! What are you even doing in
my room, you stupid bitch, get out!
So, what are
you doing later?
Holly and Lighty have Holly's
mom's car. I might go out with 'em.
Since when did
Holly get a license?
Julia. Shut up!
Do you have any weed?
No. Sorry.
Mom and dad look like they're about
to kill themselves. Stay home tonight.
Are you staying at Pete's?
Would you please
just stay home?
Give me some
weed and maybe I will.
Can we borrow
some weed? Please?
Get us some
later. Come on.
Fine.
You better make sure that we get it
from Mod, not his creepy older brother
or I'll shoot myself.
Why?
He's a pervert and
he's obsessed wlth me.
And he's really old.
Okay. Sweet.
Alright.
You're dismissed.
Love you.
Good bye.
Bitch.
Oh.
So, what have
you been doing?
Nothing.
Then why did you leave?
What's up?
You're headed
to my house?
I'm gonna pick
up your girl.
That's my house.
You ain't paying
no bills.
Ou!
What?
Alright. Well, um
so we gotta go.
Maybe we'll
see you later.
Yeah, maybe.
Wait a second, I'm gonna roll
with them. Gotta get my beak wet.
Alright. I'll off to
the races, son.
Hey, Zack.
Eat this.
What up, kids?
Hi, Eddie.
Julia. What the
hell was that?
What?
Don't give me that.
You and Dylan.
Hello, I have a
boyfriend, actually.
Okay, hello, and so does
your best friend Stacey.
Remember Dylan Is
Stacey's boyfriend?
Believe It or not some people
actually do flirt once and a while.
Well, what's that
supposed to mean?
When was the last time
you hooked up with anyone?
Just give me break, man.
Oh, Stacey, Stacey.
Mom, stay there.
Hi, girls! There's
a boy in the car.
Clark Gable,
I could say.
No, mom, you can't say anything
at all, you're an alien.
Oh my God,
how embarrassing.
I think I wanna
hook up with Mod.
Ha!
Are you bastards ready
to get wasted tonight?
Because I am.
My boyfriend just uses
me as a body to bang
and then he just ditches me
right afterwards
Isn't that so funny?
So, anyway, Mod said for us to meet
him at the park to pick up weed.
Hey, Eddie.
Hey.
What's it gonna take
for you to leave him?
What if he was
cheating on you?
Real subtie, Julia.
I'd leave him.
You should check his
pager when he's sleeping.
I haven't found a way or a reason
or an opportunity to leave him yet.
When I do that, I will.
I can think
of many reasons.
Okay. I don't
wanna talk about it.
You know it's a lot harder to leave
someone that it seems. Like you know that.
You know what, Brianne?
Stacey really needs to just
go fuck some really hot ass guy
so Dylan can realize what
he has and appreciate it.
You know what, Dawn?
Go find your hunk...
I'm right here.
Uh uh, what she should
do Is find another guy.
That way she
can make a choice.
You've been dating
Pete for three years
during which you claimed you
haven't even liked the guy.
So I wouldn't
talk if I were you.
Phew, I love girls.
Julia, look out.
I pissed myself.
God, Eddie,
It's disgusting.
Okay, no thanks.
Yeah, I think
I'll pass.
Oh, no.
Oh, my
goodness. Hi.
Hi.
Yoo- hoo!
She's completely
destroyed.
So what have you
guys been doing?
Ah!
Why don't we go
to the back yard?
Hey, can I um,
use your bathroom?
Yeah. Of course,
it's down the hall.
Come on.
What...
What is that whole Mod
thing about you, asshole?
People are starting
to get suspicious, man.
Did you hear what Julia
said earlier in the car?
I think she started
to suspect something.
You're so fucking paranoid. We've
kept it all a secret for this long.
I am so tired
of living in secret.
I can't even keep my
head on straight right now.
I'm the one who said we should
tell people if we wanted to.
Shh. Shut up.
Just shut up.
God, you know damn well why I don't
want anybody to know about this shit.
You just don't
fucking get it.
I can't actually remember when
spinning on a tire was so thrilling.
How old were we when
we first started drugs?
Can we not say the
D- R-U-G-S right now?
I really want
to get wasted.
Oh my God.
Where did you
get the shrooms?
What's going on?
Hey. We are babysitting young
children right now. Have you gone mad?
No, but I'm about to.
Hello? We were supposed to
do them together, remember?
You still have
yours. Eat 'em!
I'll eat 'em.
I think I might
want them.
You'd better
eat then now.
If you don't eat them,
you're gonna be tripping.
All night.
All by yourself.
All alone.
Well, If I take
them right now,
how long is it gonna
take for them to kick in?
Are you kidding?
You've never
done shrooms before?
No, I haven't I figured
I may as well try them
with my best friends.
It's my graduation.
I will take them if
you don't want them.
Come on, Tori. Just do it. For the
first time In your life be Irresponsible.
Do it.
Do it. Do it. Do it.
Hey, you all. I'm gonna get picked up to
go to this kid's house, It's a big party.
Okay-kay-kay.
Who did you talk to?
Dylan's there.
Dylan's there?
I'm gonna go.
Me too.
Me three.
I wanna get really drunk.
I'm happy with a beer.
Right. But I'm rolling with
Riley. I'll meet you kids there.
Why don't you roll with us?
Nosy. Riley and I gotta
take care of some things.
Yo. Let me drink
this for you, girl.
Ah! Shit! Phew!
Yeah.
Bye, Eddie.
Boy!
Give it to me.
Uh. Uh. Uh. Alright,
kid. Who you got for me?
Who you got for me, man?
What are you talking about?
Who you got for me?
I'm a get your
beek wet later, Dog.
Holly, Lighty, freshmen, fucking,
somebody's mom's car. I don't know.
Dude, thank you
for hooking us up.
Yo, don't even worry
about it. Let's do this.
Come on.
Wanna drive?
Drive this. Get out.
Anything for
you, baby.
Let's go!
Hey, yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Hold on
to your panties.
Shit.
Talk to me, wassup?
Why are you
rushing for it?
When I'm talking to one of these
older chicks, what do I say?
Oh, you don't
know what to say...
Uh, give us a second.
Senior girls are a little bit smarter so
if you wanna tap that older ass tonight
you gotta listen
to my rules, alright?
First, give
'em the look.
Yeah. Yeah.
Be smooth, alright?
Listen first.
Make moves later.
Let 'em know you're for real.
Take control of the situation.
And be a little arrogant.
Girls love that shit.
Use some smooth little
one-liners. Um, like, uh...
Hey, sweet milk,
Holla at your boy.
Something like that.
Okay. Holla at your
boy, sweet milk.
Ah! You got this
boy, let's do it.
I'm gonna get you some
senior ass tonight, boy.
Hi. Do I know you?
Hey, Holla at your boy, barbecue
sauce. That's how we do it.
Come on.
Brianne.
Surprise!
Shit.
You wanna dance?
Uh. No.
Oh. Do you believe
in love at first sight?
This whole thing. I know,
I'm sorry, you've heard it.
Damn it.
Bucket!
Aw, shit!
Yes, sir. You'd better
finish that drink, bitch.
There are children
sober in India.
M m. Ah!
That's a good boy! That
one was for the kids.
Beer and me,
friends for life. Ah!
Aw, shit. Pete's doing that
thing that makes him fart again.
Hey, Pete, hold
on one second.
Everybody in.
Come on, come on.
Alright. Ready?
Set? Go, bro.
That's my
friend, right there.
You didn't tell
me anything.
Why are you being so fucking annoying?
I need to
talk to you.
Hey, asshole!
You're the
shit, bro. Yeah!
We're out of toilet paper.
Can somebody help me?
I need toilet paper!
So what have
you been doing?
Don't worry
about it. Damn.
I don't think I should
be treated like this.
You'd better start acting
like I'm your girlfriend.
And not just some girl you come home to.
Who sent you this?
How the hell would I know, you got it.
Apparently someone wants
to know if you want to fuck.
Shut up, it don't
say that. Fu...
Brianne!
I hate you.
I love you.
Oh, Have you guys seen Brianne? I've
not seen her once since we came In.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna go find someone who's
mature and who likes me for me.
And not just for my house
and my turkey sandwiches.
And my flower.
I fucked that
chick like two weeks ago.
That's Dylan's girlfriend.
Must've been
somebody else then.
Class of 199-fucking-9.
Man this is
lame, '99, '93.
What's the shit,
I mean, it's crazy.
Spinning crazy. Crazy,
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy.
So what does that mean?
Graduation day, right? So after
we broke a few school windows
and tied up Professor
Fuck-My-Face's car
I was In my place
to smoke a jay, right?
Then Jamie comes over,
and she comes over,
but I'm trying to
bang her all year.
And she comes over
and she's balling.
And she even tells me couple of
days about this friend of hers
uh, uh, Allie,
who was a Russian spy
Okay, and like, you know,
ding-dong, a little bell running.
Next thing you know Allie
pulls out a Smith and Wesson
and starts waving
around speaking Russian.
I grab, uh, I got
my lucky knife.
I got my fucking knife
I'm gonna do something.
I was gonna do something
but I don't have to.
Get me what he's
smoking.
Smoke. Drink.
Don't think.
Hey, douchebag.
Eat me.
Uh. Yo smoking grass
Gives a little laugh, we want
your ass 'cause I'm about to blast.
And I'm about to have a good
time Grab some titties and ass.
It's all on the same run Everybody
knows what's coming outta my mind.
But I breathe so fast
I can't leave these words.
Trees, trees, I smoke trees I roll weed
Hey, sweet milk
What?
I'm Riley.
I'm sorry.
I'm such a mess.
Oh.
Beer.
That's all I wanted.
I just became a senior.
And I just can't keep on
living my life like this
and still have respect
for myself, you know?
I wake up
every single morning
and I tell myself that
today's gonna be different
I'm not gonna be
mistreated by, like,
anyone.
And then I go through
my day and I come home
and everything
starts right back
where it left off.
I think you should
come home with me.
Hey, guys. Hi.
Hey, thanks for inviting me to smoke
with you. It's great. It's nice.
Hi, Brianne.
Hi, Dawn.
I called your name.
'Cause I wasn't gonna smoke.
There's a lot of smoke and I've
always got it, so, stick with me.
Thanks, but I'd
rather kill myself.
Oh.
You're just... Do you know how I
feel about you? You're so feisty.
Hey, Brianne. Here's that
tampon that you really needed.
Remember? Can I talk to
you alone for one second?
Hey, Zack, I have
your tampon.
That's nasty.
I thought that whole you
and Mod was just bullshit.
Dawn, you've been my best friend
for like a gazillion years.
But this has got too
way out of control.
It drives me crazy
when you flirt with Mod right
in front of my face, you asshole.
I was just
smoking a blunt.
I saw what you
were doing.
Let's just all have
a good night, okay?
Come on.
Fuck it, the light.
Ah I Fuck.
Um, uh, What... What the
hell is the matter with you?
Put this on. What's wrong with you?
Is that the way you wanna flash those
perverts? You didn't even get to know 'em.
Young, how
old are you?
I'm old enough.
Old enough for what? What
are you trying to prove?
Don't get caught up being so hot
you forget to be a real person.
You think I'm hot?
Come on, you said you love young girls.
I care about younger girls but
don't believe what I say to the guys.
What?
Uh, hey, hey, I'm gonna be
famous some day, You know that?
Hey, some people are just born for
stardom and I'm just one of them.
What can I say?
My charm's a felony.
Alright.
Are we cool?
Yeah.
Is Bailey coming here?
Son of a shit.
Get your clothes on.
I forgot. Come on.
Come on, come on.
Make moves, make moves.
Hey, I'm gonna roll
with you guys, man.
I don't wanna even
be near Felix, man.
Now why don't you
like your brother?
Because his brother is
a pedophile, I'm convinced.
He'll bitch at me...
Alright. Roll
with us. Let's go.
Yo, guys, um
It's cool If you wanna be
smoking and drinking while I drive
it's totally illegal, but,
I mean, it's cool, right?
You're such a bitch.
He's afraid of a doey. Yo, Dylan,
bitches, it's cool, it's all good.
Yup. It is cool.
You know what? We need to
do some more illegal shit.
We need to hit the
trash cans right here.
Yeah.
Like with my car?
Like with your
car, man! Go, man.
Yeah, hit that one.
Just do it.
Come on I
You can do It I
Are you frigging serious?
My dick goes faster than your
car. Will you hit a trash can?
He's gonna do It I
Hey, go back, go back.
Let's go to
Stacey's mom's house.
Zack, you're
still a bitch.
Go bitches, yeah.
Come on I
Get the shit.
Let's do it, let's go.
Yo, move your fat ass.
Ah!
Move your ass!
Get back In now.
Roll the car!
Go! Go!
Go, go, go, man.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Holy shit
Yeah!
Come on, come on, come on.
Get out of here.
Yeah!
What in God's
name was that?
I'm sure it's just
good friends of ours.
Vandalizing, probably.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my Jesus, you just
gave me the best idea ever.
Oh, God.
Get ready,
for awesome.
Sylvia.
Do you think this music might
wake all the kids back up?
Wait. I have to know this.
Did the movie The Matrix
actually come out of reality
or did I just make that
whole thing up in my head?
Dude, I don't know, I just can't
stop thinking about pink lemonade.
Sylvia.
What?
Let's talk to each other.
Here I come.
Okay.
Here I am.
I'm scared to leave home.
There's no such thing as
home. It's all just an idea.
I promise.
You know
what I mean.
Like,
the comfort and familiarity of
what home is to me right now.
This home that
you think Is home
is really just
the first one.
It's like we
have this family
and we go off
and we do stuff
and eventually we start
ourselves a new family
and then our family wlll go
off and start more families.
And really it's just like
this whole chain reaction
of, like, creation
and we try to
classify It In stages
so that we can find
comfort in where we're at.
At that one particular moment in time.
And really,
there's no
such thing as time.
And we're all just
walking, talking patterns.
Shh!
I heard that, too.
This place is a wreck.
Should I go down there?
No.
It's all wet.
What should I do?
I'll soak it clean, so
you clean up real fast.
And, I will
distract them.
And then
Tom, when he...
Hello, hellooooooo.
Wooooooo.
Wow, it is all so wonderful
to finally meet you.
Oh.
Mwah, mwah.
Oh! Yeah.
Are the, uh,
children not sleeping?
Oh, they most
certainly are!
Yes, they are!
They love sleeping!
They told me so!
They said,
"I love sleeping. "
Sleep, sleep, sleep.
I want to sleep.
Wow.
You smell legendary,
by the way.
What's this
music I'm hearing?
So, anyways, um...!
That was actually my
first time babysitting.
You know kids.
And, um, I just wanna say that
I think It was like 9:00 o'clock
Yeah.
And I all of a sudden got this urge
to just go murder
the kiddies, right?
So believe It or not,
I actually had to grip
the sides of your sofa
to keep me from
running into the kitchen
and grabbing a butcher
knife and just stabbing them
Mr. And Mrs. Turner.
Mister and Mister.
She's my friend Sylvia and I'm so
sorry you had to meet her. But...
I'm Sylvia.
Everything's good and
wonderful. We gotta go. Good bye.
Oh, we're
leaving. Oh, yeah.
Oh.
What?
I don't know.
Maybe these are really strong
shrooms or something, but...
I think there's a
goose back there.
Oh.
You wanna go to
that punk show?
I want you
to understand.
Fucked. Fucked.
You left me.
Do you understand?
I'm not happy. I drove around 40 blocks.
Okay? 40 blocks.
Come on, man.
Hey.
Damn, we missed
the whole show?
I wish I had
your timing.
It sucked?
No.
It was
really good.
Everybody, that
was awesome.
Fucking great
that shit, man.
You rock, man.
Hey, uh, did you bring
your friend Lighty?
Hey, light this.
What's up, you sliding?
I'm sliding,
mother fucker.
Guys, guys.
There's a keg party.
Yes!
Thank God. I'm so out of my damn mind.
This place would need some, actually.
I got something for you.
Oh, can you drive me by my house later?
Sausage fest.
What's up, bitch?
Hoe.
Yo, bitch
what's up?
Hey, what do you want?
What, daddy? Staring
like there's a problem.
You're full of it.
You ain't rough, man.
What are they
fighting about?
So lame. What are they ever
fighting about? It's so stupid.
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Go fuck yourself.
Go fuck myself?
You know what?
I will do that. After I fuck
your sister and your momma.
At least we got mommas.
Hey, hey, wait.
Not here,
man. Chill out.
Bye, bitches.
We got spice.
We'll be there.
What the fuck?
Ain't got my back?
Wh... What, I was, I-
I- was right here. What?
We got these
mother fuckers.
Sa...
No, no, no. Hey.
Hey, hey, man,
Do me a favor, Thomas.
Can you please send
young girl to get Bailey?
What?
Shut up.
Be brave.
He's nice, okay?
You're in the gang.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Hi.
Um, you guys
were really good.
It was awesome.
Thanks for coming.
I was glad that you
came, I appreciate that.
We sounded like shit.
I couldn't hear myself,
it was fucked up.
Ridiculous.
We sounded like garbage.
Horrible.
Uh. Well, there's
this keg party tonight.
Yeah.
Um, you
should really come.
I don't know.
Like, big parties are
not really my scene.
You know, it's like...
And I gotta get up early and
take the van to the shop so
I probably shouldn't stay
up that late, you know?
Take the van to the shop? Oh, man.
Ready to smoke
some week kids?
Blah!
I've never used one
of those before.
Just take this
and pull through that.
Pull and suck, baby.
Shut up!
God.
Ready? Your's ready? We got
to all pull at the same time.
So why don't
you like big parties?
Why don't you?
I don't know.
Oh, I guess, um, I don't
really like drinking that much.
Fag.
It's always the same
thing, you go, drink,
you, you know, you stay
around with the same people
and then you do the same crap, you
know, and you go home to go to sleep.
Na-na.
All the
meaningless conversation
Yeah, man.
Meaningless conversations
may not be that bad.
I graduated today and I never
talked to anyone In four years.
And I'm a little sad.
That's so
depressing, dude.
Where does
he come from?
Jesus!
That was ridiculous.
A picture is worth
like a thousand words.
That means he's talked with
probably, like, a million people.
No! Barf on
your ass! No!
I liked that.
God damn
right you did.
Hey, I don't usually
say much either.
Everybody thinks,
I'm like, this airhead
but really, I just,
don't feel the need to talk unless
I have something meaningful to say.
Oh, gag me
with a dick!
I'm really sorry,
I can't stop him.
You know what?
Fuck off, we're here.
Leave my van now.
Get the fuck out.
It's your party. Go.
I gotta take care of some business.
He's going with you, right?
Hey, yeah.
You enjoy
your little party.
We're gonna get some
cigarettes for you, Nancy pants.
Get me cigarettes.
We'll be right back. Shit. Shit.
Ah I
Fuck, man I
Yo, slam that
door hard, alright?
Alright, ready?
That is a piece.
Dylan!
Dylan.
Hey.
Get off!
Want some?
I would love some.
Howdy, howdy.
Beer!
The best damn
drink in the world.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, man come on. You gotta get
over this not graduating thing
at least tonight, we've got kegs
here and they have your name on them.
Come on, we gotta party like
it's 1999 up in this bitch.
Yeah I
Thank you.
Want to get wasted?
By all means.
Oh, okay.
What have you got?
I got whatever
you need.
Hey.
Hey, how
are you?
Uh... Um... Yeah,
you know what?
I'm actually gonna get some cigarettes,
like lots and lots of cigarettes.
Baby, I have a
pack right here.
Uh, I don't like
that kind. Dawn I
H m.
I'll take it.
Man, if you just gotta shake
that one off, just go ahead, bro.
Do you wanna chill? Or do
you wanna chill with beer?
Alright. Who
should we prank call?
Let's get
Stacey's mom.
Oh, dude.
Alright.
Hold it, hold it.
Uh-uh, uh-uh.
Stacey, Stacey Is that you?
Yes, it's me, ma.
And I am smacked.
Stacey.
Maybe you can tell about
the sound of my voice
That I am definitely a man!
And not your female daughter.
I know who you are.
Oh, do you now?
Shut up.
You took my goosel Is
Stacey doing the funny stuff?
Is she? You put my Stacey on the phone
right now. Where Is my damn goose?
Ah! What?
What in the hell
was she talking about?
What... What
fucking goose, dude?
I don't know.
It could be
fucking that one.
Excuse me.
What the fuck?
Thank God they
didn't just stop.
Yeah. I don't really want to
go to a keg party right now.
Everybody's
reacting so weird.
Should we just go lay down In that
nice grassy green field over there?
Yes!
Wow.
Except I think there's like
some army soldiers out there too.
That's my boy. Now, come
on. Here comes round two.
Ah! Hi.
Hi. Hi. Hi. Hey.
Hey.
Come here.
Concentrate.
Quick question.
How bad
do you wanna fuck me?
Don't think.
Just answer.
Dawn!
Okay.
Yeah.
No?
No.
Oh, God.
What?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
So what? I ain't telling
you every God damned thing.
Just be cool with me.
Man, fuck this.
You're right. Someone
should come in between them.
You know, someone's gotta
play sacrificial asshole and...
Well, uh...
Rlley I
Oh! I can't
believe you're here.
And look, I'm
even dried out.
Oh, I liked
you all wet.
Holla.
I'm so happy
you came!
Man, fuck you!
Yeah, what
else is new?
Hey, so, uh...
It looks like little light
protectors and stars, you know,
they pierce
Straight through the sky.
And they spotlight
us, you know?
Yeah.
Oh! How mother
fucking sweet!
Oh, you kids
are so sweet.
See that?
You see that?
Okay. Alright.
Look at that.
Hey! Um,
can you not.
Alright.
See man, why you gotta be so punk?
Whoa!
I'm not.
What?
I'm actually normal.
Everything we do at all
Is God coming through us.
So how am I smoking weed? God
obviously put It here to grow
on the Earth for us.
Weed is proof
that God loves us and wants
us to be happy. Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Are you happy?
How many smoke weed?
No, how many?
Let me tell you.
A lot.
Pass me the butt.
You're messing up
the whole philosophy.
Some of the kids, uh, something's
not right, something's wrong, uh,
something is,
uh, backwards.
What do you mean?
Everything Is backwards.
Smoke. Just
smoke. Come on.
There's something
in that, man.
But you're the one
that gave it to us.
I know, I know, I know,
Something's wrong.
Don't touch It.!
gotta go to a hospital.
Call a hospital.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Just
call... Just, um...
Just Ignore him. He's...
Are you sure?
Yeah. He gets
anxiety attacks.
Yeah, last week he thought
he was possessed by the devil.
He hid In the attic
for like three hours.
Ain't that great?
AD H D to yourself, man!
Suck my
fucking AD H D dick.
Oh, God.
Hey, man, I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh.
When I'm riding in my car
Got my seat
on lean.
Hey, Felix. You alright
man, you need help up?
When I'm at the house
Oh. God!
Don't get all
emotional on us.
Pete, look at her, man. She's crying.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
Yes, you are.
Hey, guys, you know when you go to
the movies and you get to the sad part
and your eye
always starts to itch
but you can't scratch it because everybody
else is gonna think that you're crying.
Where do you
come from?
Man, everybody keeps
asking me that today.
Dude, remember that time when I was
wasted and we found that secret island?
That never happened.
Damn it.
Dude. Are you sure
that didn't happen?
It never happened.
Dude.
I feel so bad about being
so annoying. You know?
It's just so hard.
The more you pull away,
the more suffocating I get.
Shh.
I can't help it...
Please stop it, okay. We're gonna
try to have a normal night tonight.
Alright.
So I'm a cheerleader.
Oh, yeah?
That's hot.
Yeah, we, we practice more than
football and basketball players.
Combined.
You look like
you practice a lot.
This town sucks.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Damn, let's do this!
God damn.
Hang on. Wait, man.
Come on, come on.
I got 'em!
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
Yeah?
It's Charles!
Charlesl Charlesl
Charles!
Who the shit
is Charles?
Oh, it's Eddie's
piss-wasted alter ego.
Gimme that.
Charles.
Sometimes it
gets violent.
What are you doing, man?
Are you wearing some panties?
I think you are. Why'd you let him
do that to you. You're a pussy, yo.
Yo, get the fuck outta
here. Yo, do your thing, man!
Do your mother
fucking thing, Charles!
What is he doing?
Ah!
Who's that?
Oh, hell, no!
Somebody's
called the boys.
Come on, let's go.
Let's fight these guys.
Let's go and kick their
mother fucking asses.
Fight I Fight I
Come on, come on.
Don't leave me.
What do you want? Huh?
I got a whole life right here.
Come on, baby. Kick his
ass for me. Take him down!
Bitch!
Want some more?
What the fuck...?
Did you just see
Zack attack Biz?
That was awesome.
It's Tupac!
My man, Ponte!
Who's Ponte?
That guy's In a gang.
Come on. Come on.
Fuck West Po Homie.
What's going on?
Come on, let's go.
We gotta get outta here.
Is that my boy, Charles?
I am. I am.
Go have sex with
your mother, bitch.
Take that.
It's like
you're supposed to be
starting the next big something
this upcoming millennium but I have
no clue what I should do with myself.
Make a difference.
Maybe the Y2K will
blow up the world.
Go, come on. This way.
I'm, I'm proud of you.
My fucking jaw.
My knees. I didn't get punched.
Because I used my knees. Yeah.
Fuck.
Man, I wanna know who in
the hell bitch-slapped me.
Man, I swear it
looked like Zack.
No, man. Zack can't
even hold his own dick.
Hey, you
know what?
We should go to that
bitch Holly's house.
It's a ha-ha.
I'm just
gonna take off.
What?
How are we
gonna find a ride?
I don't know, but
I'm gonna go home.
What the...
You're crazy.
You see, the whole fight,
it was like nothing to me
I've been working
out a lot, wanna see?
You wanna feel them?
Yeah. Yeah.
Enough.
Are you gay?
Nah. Nah.
I just don't care.
You know?
About what?
Being like everybody
else, you know?
I love life
and I'm living it!
But Eddie
Style, though.
Eddie Style.
It's a good style.
You have to go after
what you want and get It I
Am I right?
Dad says it's not
getting what you want
but wanting
what you've got.
Yeah? Well, your
dad didn't know shit.
Only you know
what you want.
Eddie. Where's Dylan?
Man, I don't know. Go
call the cops or something.
You're the one who called him out
of the woods and he never came back.
So where is he?
What were you guys
doing in the woods?
What? Why are you always taking
so many stupid ass pictures?
I mean, why? Why did you
just take a picture of me?
What is so great about this? What is
so fucking great about all this? Huh?
You're still here.
Yes.
Life sucks.
Yeah.
It's my
Mom's goose.
Let's break
into a boat.
Whatever's clever.
It's all you.
Let's do it.
You know we can't do
this forever, right?
I know.
Okay.
It's just that I never actually thought
about the reality
of that, you know?
Because I've
been so happy.
We have not
Look,
the longer
that we do this
the harder it's gonna be when the
inevitable eventually does come.
Which It will.
There's really just like no reason
for this shit to go any longer.
So being in love
isn't a reason?
We would always have to hide
and that doesn't make any sense.
We do not always
have to hide it.
Who gives a shit?
What are you so scared of?
Why won't you give us a try?
Because I can't handle what
that might end up meaning.
H m. I hate
you already.
Hi, Angie, It's Stacey.
I'm in your neighborhood...
and I was just wondering,
Is your sister In?
Did you drive
by my house?
Yeah, I did.
Was her car
parked outside?
No.
So, what? Are
you retarded?
Do you think maybe I
can just sleep over there?
Yes, fine. You know
where the key is.
Can I please go
back to sleep?
Oh, wait, Angie.
Uh. Do you have any pot?
Wait. Um. Tell me if this sounds
like a phone hanging up on you?
Yes.