This has been America News
Radio from Washington.
Now back to your local
ANR station for news on the hour.
Good evening. You're listening
to 108.9 FM, KMZR, Portland. This...
Evening, ma'am.
You, too.
- Good evening.
- Careful. Careful, it's hot.
- Thank you.
- Busy night for the bad guys?
- Even busier night for us.
Okay.
Let's see what you got for me.
Oh, hey,
because you're dying to know...
...l'm almost positive my first date last
night is eligible for the hall of fame.
She was amazing.
She looked exactly like her photo.
You'll never see her again.
- How do you know?
- Because you look nothing like yours.
Nice one.
- Here's that guy I was telling you about.
- Oh, yeah?
He changes his name every day.
It's taken me a week to isolate him.
Listen to this.
- Tunethief. Com.
- Oh, how original.
Yeah, he offers free downloads
of pirated music.
I'm running this
in a fake virtual machine.
Watch what happens
when I accept his offer.
Now, he's stealing my financial data...
...and all my passwords.
Which I happened to have gathered
in a file called "passwords."
Nice touch.
I threw in a backdoor Trojan so
we can see what he's doing with it.
He's run up a quarter-million dollars
in fraud the past three weeks.
- Well, what's he into?
- High-end tech and low-end porn.
God. You sure it's a guy? If it's
a woman, she could be my soul mate.
Send it over to me.
There you go.
My dummy Capital One card.
Hope he goes for it.
Okay, I see it.
I'm surprised he has
the patience for auctions.
- Oh, you've got him now.
- Okay, there's his IP address.
Let's get his physical one.
Portland Police sent this over.
They weren't sure what to do with it.
Thank you.
- It is a woman.
- ER nurse, lives alone.
No priors,
no history of online purchases.
It's not her. Gotta be a neighbor...
...somebody close by, someone
who could access her wireless router.
Sharon Dobbs lives here.
All right. Here we go,
here's somebody.
Sam Barrows. He's a computer
programmer for the school district.
He's lived there six weeks.
He's a renter.
He's registered for three handguns
and two assault rifles.
That's your guy.
Jennifer Marsh, FBI Cyber Crimes
up in Portland.
We need you to knock down
a door for us.
Oh, I gotta get reassigned.
What's the matter?
It's just a sickness. It's just too much.
I got this
retired high school principal...
...offering to come over
to where I'm babysitting.
He's got so many chats,
he can't keep his names straight.
He keeps calling me Jill
instead of Molly.
I'm only interested in what his
cellmates are gonna call him.
I'm taking a break. Do you want...?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right.
I see feet! Get your hands up!
Get your hands up!
On your stomach! On your stomach!
- On flawless, cut Natalie K diamonds.
Huge savings on one-karat diamonds.
Presented by the LaRog Brothers.
- What the hell is this?
- I don't know. I'm running it down now.
It is streaming live.
Just when you thought
you've seen it all.
Oh, look, a message from our sponsor.
"Ha-ha. Only serious."
Jennifer Marsh, Cyber Crimes.
Carter Thompson here.
I'm at the Barrow residence.
The suspect's in custody.
Hard drive's intact.
- Plenty of contraband.
- Good work. Hey, let me guess.
It's not just Barrow. His son's
involved. He's got a son?
What makes you say that?
Well, high-tech toys and porn...
...and then out of the blue,
he buys a gold wristwatch.
How come? And then it hit me.
01-10-57.
Sunday's his father's birthday.
Sweet dreams, Marsh.
Good morning.
We'll return to America News Radio
after the local news and weather.
It's the 7:00 hour.
This is KMZR, 108.9 FM, Portland.
And on the Web at mzrnews. Org.
First, the weather.
The hurricane system that has poured
3 inches of rain on western Portland...
... in the past 24 hours
has finally let up.
Though there is no sign of an easing
of the near-freezing temperatures...
OnStar operator Tina. Good morning,
Ms. Marsh. How can I assist you?
Yes, Tina.
I'd like to get home
sometime before Easter.
I'm in a traffic jam here.
Okay, let's see.
You're in the middle
of a gaper's block.
You should be past the accident
in about 100 yards.
- Okay, I see it now. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Come on, keep it moving.
- Shit, you scared me.
- Watch your mouth, young lady.
Hey, that's what I said to you
when you were a kid.
I know, Mom. That's what
makes it so darn funny.
Oh, somebody's crabby.
Sorry. Long night.
Mom!
- Look at the outfit I'm making.
- I can see that.
- You're stealing my job.
- You were late.
I know. I'm sorry about that, sweetie.
Catch any bad guys?
One. Just one.
Okay, I'm coming.
Slowpoke. The slowest poke
I've ever seen, ever.
I'm coming.
- How are things with you and Maddy?
- Better.
Mrs. Tischler's gonna
give us a second chance.
- A second chance at what?
- Being friends.
Oh, of course. I think that's great.
She can come to my party now.
Make sure to send her mom an Evite.
- You got it.
- Maybe Grandma should do it.
- I'll do it.
- Are you sure?
When I say I'll do it, I'll do it,
okay? I promise.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, babe.
I bet you'd like me
to do this some other time!
Hey, friendly.
All right, Jennifer. Let's see
this tortured kitty of yours.
Torture's over, sir.
- Yeah, I should say so.
- Poor Lulu.
That was the cat's name.
The owner, Scotty Hillman,
26, from West Linn...
...says she was snatched a few days
ago from his lawn during a yard sale.
He recognized her fancy collar.
West Linn. So this site...
...which could have originated
anywhere from Oslo to Istanbul...
Is local. Yes, sir.
The odds of that are pretty steep.
About a million to one, if it were
a coincidence, which it's not.
The only way we found out about this
is because it was tipped...
...to the county sheriff's office and the
police within minutes of it going up.
Both tips came from a pay phone
in the central city...
...so whoever is behind the site
is local and wants attention.
- Shut him down.
- I just did.
- There you go.
- I'll type the address in again.
It's been doing that all night.
The site's IP changes constantly. Each
new address is an exploited server...
...that's running a mirror of the site.
The site's Russian name server
uses a low TTL...
...so your computer constantly queries
the name server's record.
That's how it gives
you a new address consistently.
There are thousands of exploited
servers on the Internet...
...so he won't run out of victims soon.
He's accessing these machines
so quickly...
...he's got to be
running his own botnet.
We are blackholing these IPs...
...but every time we shut one down,
a new mirror pops up.
I don't understand a single word
you just said.
What does Russia
have to do with this?
The domain registrar
and name servers are all in Russia.
We have no jurisdiction there.
Jennifer...
...it's a cat.
- Yeah.
Considering the state of the world,
aren't there more important things...
...to be concerned about, like
something under our jurisdiction?
Back to work, gentlemen.
Things are about to get warmer when
one of the hottest hockey rivalries...
Are you the guy? You got the
extra ticket for the hockey game?
Grandma! Grandma! Grandma!
- Did you get it?
- Yes, I did!
Oh, my God, I'm so proud of you!
And the boy I fought was so tall too.
- Careful, I'm all wet.
- So am I.
We celebrated. We had an ice cream.
Hello.
Mom?
- Honey... Mom, please!
- Okay, okay.
Come on, baby.
Let's get you out of these clothes.
I've been monitoring the site all week.
Nothing but a still of the dead kitten.
Last night around 11, the site
went down, I'd hoped forever.
Anyway, a few minutes ago, this.
It's the same basement
still streaming live.
The top is the number of active viewers
and some chemical-dosage flow.
He's carved the name of the website
into the guy's chest.
He's threatening to drain him.
Threatening to drain what, his blood?
How's he gonna do that?
Those letters aren't any deeper
than paper cuts.
Not the cuts, it's the bleeding.
We think that box regulates
the fluid going into the victim.
Those cables are probably
connected to our guy's computer.
Look, his nose is starting
to bleed and he's bruising.
We think those bags have
some anticoagulant in them.
I've got a list of them right here.
The most common is heparin.
If you get the dose right, you save a
life. Wrong, you've got a hemophiliac.
So the more people who visit the site,
the more the drug is released...
...and the faster he bleeds.
- That's what we believe.
- Well, isn't that wonderful?
Well, if that counter is accurate,
the public would seem to agree.
They're tuning in at an alarming rate.
The victim's name
is Herbert Miller, 54.
Lives in Sellwood, works
for Burnside Executive Charter.
Friday night, got back from a shuttle
to Mount Hood, called his wife...
...says that he gets an e-mail
from a friend of a friend...
...offering center-ice seats
to the Winter Hawks game.
He promises
he'll be home afterwards.
- He wasn't.
- Any priors?
- Who, Miller?
- Why is that relevant?
Remember that snuff film
sent to the L.A. Office last year?
Teenage geisha cut in two.
Looked as real as anything you saw.
Six weeks later, they found her alive
and well, waiting tables in Little Tokyo.
Maybe Miller's involved somehow.
Maybe there's a connection.
What are you doing to me?
Mrs. Miller!
Just go away. Just leave.
- Okay, folks, one side, please.
- I don't know.
Come on. Police.
Coming through. Mrs. Miller.
Back off. Back off. Mrs. Miller.
- Portland Police. May we come in?
- Thank God you're here.
I need you to back off right now.
My name is Detective Box.
This is my partner, Detective Moy.
Listen, is there someplace
else we can talk?
Yeah, let's go outside.
Oh, shit. Fuck!
So, Mrs. Miller, when was the
last time you saw your husband?
Yesterday morning.
He called, and he said he'd got tickets
to the Winter Hawks game last night.
He likes hockey, and I just wanted
him to come straight home.
Okay. Listen...
...I understand what you're going
through is very difficult. All right?
But you're making it worse by talking
to the press. Don't talk to the press.
Do you understand? Listen.
Don't talk to the press
and stay off the computer. Okay?
Listen to this. I'm running the logs
from that mirror we took down.
He's blocking all the foreign IPs. Only
Americans can gain access to the site.
How patriotic.
We've scanned every newsgroup,
chat room, blog, website and forum...
...referencing "Kill With Me,"
and I think we found our first post.
It appeared just before the site went
up, then it was spammed Web-wide.
"A cat caught in a rattrap.
How's that for irony?
It's streaming live on killwithme. Com.
It's awesome. Check it out."
It was posted by a sophomore
named Andrew Kilburn.
It came from his account, but it didn't
actually originate from his computer.
So our guy hacked his account
and used it to start the thread.
- Yeah.
- Let's go after the originating IP.
Oh, God.
It's too bad this guy wasn't
a Boy Scout.
He could just blink Morse code
and tell us where he is.
Okay, I've got the "who is."
It comes back Blue Sky ISP.
- Username and password, please.
- Coming to you now.
- "Chang's Restaurant"?
- He hacked into their site?
No. No. Half the office eats there.
He's messing with us.
He wanted us to find this.
Who the hell is this guy?
Jennifer Marsh, Detective Eric Box.
Portland Police has him
on the Miller abduction.
- Jennifer's our case agent on this.
- Case agent, sir?
- You caught it, you got it.
- Please.
Sir, anyone else. You know I'm
on nights because of my daughter.
I understand that, but you're it.
- We forming a task force?
- Not yet.
Not yet?
How much more do you need?
So far we have one dead cat and a man
who may or may not be in danger...
That's today. You think this is it?
It's just the beginning.
Marsh, hold it.
You share what you've got,
and then you take it from there.
Appreciate your coming in, detective.
All right. You first.
Well, we found Miller's car
in the Rose Garden parking lot.
No prints but his own.
We passed out photos of the
basement to some local contractors.
They say, judging from the timbers,
the house was built in the '20s or '30s.
Which narrows it down to,
you know, half the city.
Yeah, what else?
Miller appears to be a decent guy.
He's a Vietnam vet...
...coaches his daughter's soccer,
they go to church every Sunday.
So why'd the subject pick him?
"Subject"?
Are we in science class?
- What would you prefer?
- How about "piece of shit"?
Why Miller?
I don't know. Maybe it was random.
What about the kitten?
Talk to that guy?
Scotty Hillman, yeah.
He's a fucking jackass.
All he cares about is getting
the kitten's collar...
...because he paid 12 bucks
for it on bidityours. Com
Which I suppose is a lot of money
if you're flipping burgers.
What I would like to know is,
why him? Why his kitten?
Why take the risk of stealing when
you can get one free at any shelter?
- What do you guys got?
- It's a website.
It's like nothing we've ever seen.
It's extremely sophisticated.
As long as its source-streaming site
is a ghost, it's untraceable.
This guy can invite the world to help
him kill Miller or anybody...
...and there's not a goddamn thing
we can do about it.
Excuse me.
- It's over.
- Yeah.
The numbers, they just... exploded.
"Rolling on the floor laughing.
Thank you for..."
"For all your support.
More to come."
Well, we'll see about that.
It's a jungle in there.
Hey, I just went to the site
after the guy was dead...
I got a list of assholes my girlfriends
and me think he ought to kill next.
Last seen five days ago, FBI agents
have been working around the clock...
There's a pickup truck.
What's that on the back, a gun rack?
Yeah, well, there's no way that freak is
stepping foot in my dad's country club.
So call Tucker.
- At 7: 15 a.m., a vehicle at the home...
... of Oregon congressman
Joseph A. Restom.
Herbert Miller had been the focus
of an intense local...
... and statewide police
and FBI search...
... since midday Saturday
when he showed up...
...on an Internet website
being tortured and murdered live.
Now, because of the uniqueness
of the crime, and because the FBI...
...is able to provide resources
critical to this investigation...
...they will be leading the interagency
task force assigned to the case.
He flew helicopters for a living. What's
his connection to a U.S. Congressman?
Our guy had to dump the body.
Why not on a national stage?
You think he did it to get a press
conference? Build up his fan base?
Don't call them fans.
They're accomplices.
All right, whatever.
Why'd he choose Restom?
He's owned by Silicon Valley.
He sits on the House Judiciary
Committee on Net neutrality.
No restriction on content,
all traffic treated equally.
- Wouldn't our guy be for that?
- You'd think so.
Miller's clients
were corporate executives.
Maybe some were from high-tech.
I'll track down a customer list.
- What about the neighbors?
- One saw a van drive by at 4 a.m.
Another heard a car door slam
a minute later.
Figured it was the paper
being delivered.
Excuse me a second.
Might have something here.
- What is it?
- Tip just came in through a hot line.
Guy named Arthur James Elmer, an
engineer at Chadwick Technologies.
He was fired six months ago...
...for installing a wireless Webcam
in the men's room.
Nice. Anyway, he's been talking
about killwithme.com nonstop...
...ever since the kitty died.
Wanna ride with us?
Let me check this guy out
on my end.
- We'll catch up later.
- Yeah.
- So, what's going on?
- He won't let us in. Kind of shy.
Elmer.
Look, if you didn't do anything,
you got nothing to lose letting us in.
And if you did, we can always
come back with a warrant.
So how do you wanna play it?
Hi.
I'm Detective Box.
Unusual name.
Well, it wasn't up to me.
So you really think I killed that guy?
I don't know. Did you?
Well, I'm flattered.
I found it highly entertaining,
especially at the end.
The way viewership
increased exponentially...
...like some sort of epidemic.
Can I see the basement?
You like movies, huh?
Yeah, who doesn't?
Me.
Burn your own copies?
You know that's illegal, right?
Can't say they didn't warn you.
Got our proof it wasn't Elmer.
Starting Friday at 1 p. M...
...Elmer was logged into a chat
room for 12 consecutive hours.
At the time Miller disappeared,
Elmer was in a steamy private chat...
...with the first tenor of the
Men's Chorus of Greater Tacoma.
It still felt good arresting him.
- Hello?
- I caught you.
- Barely. I've got a big date tonight.
- Big, special or big, large?
I don't know. I haven't met Peggy
the secretary yet. What's up?
I had a thought. Remember that
Andrew Kilburn guy and his review?
Yeah, sure. What about it?
Well, why use his account?
I mean, maybe it wasn't random.
Maybe they know each other.
- Yeah, it's possible.
- Yeah.
- All right. I'll see you Sunday.
- Wait, Sunday?
Annie's birthday.
Oh, shit, I forgot.
- Okay, can I bring a date?
- Are you kidding?
You don't even know
if you like this girl.
No, not Peggy. Melanie.
She's a social worker.
She likes sushi and rock-climbing
and Dickens.
- I can't believe you.
- It's a numbers game.
Fine, fine. I gotta go.
Okay. Hey, you got a date?
- Good night.
- Okay. Bye. Good night, Sam.
Molly gave me
a birthday present already.
It's a computer game
that I downloaded.
- It's about horses.
- How sweet of her. That looks like fun.
Not really. It's kind of silly.
- I'll show it to you later.
- Okay, honey. I love you. Gotta run.
Come on, Annie. Let me get one first.
Somebody order a bunch of pizzas?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Hey, Griffin.
- For the birthday girl. Hello.
- How are you? Over here?
- Over here.
Listen, I only made it through
a few months of Kilburn's posts.
- We'll need more bodies on this.
- Okay.
He blogged, he uploaded vids, he
built sites. He practically lived online.
- What, not anymore?
- Not since he died...
...of something called
diabetic ketoacidosis.
Which is what happens when you
don't take your insulin for a few days.
Anyway, an hour after his body
was found...
...Kill With Me went up.
And an hour after that, Kilburn's
review was spammed Web-wide.
- And you think our guy killed him?
- The ME called it a suicide.
Hi.
You're right on time.
Yeah, well, it's a curse.
I spend half my life waiting for people.
So... Dave Williams.
That's a great address, by the way.
Eights bring prosperity.
- I didn't know that.
- Yeah.
- Come in.
- Thanks.
Here you go, honey.
- You're welcome.
Detective.
- Hi.
Griffin invited me
to his birthday party.
Yeah. Kind of a young crowd.
Kind of a young crowd, Griffin.
- Well, do you skate?
- No.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, go ahead.
Look, I'm gonna get out of here.
I'm sorry.
You just got here. Don't go.
Have some pizza.
Come on. It's not that bad.
Wow, you must really like Asia, huh?
Just Korea.
Korea.
Well, it's fabulous.
Thank you.
So you gonna let me see them?
Of course.
Through the kitchen.
I gotta tell you, a 710 Pullman
and a 712 Observation Car?
My heart skipped a beat
when I got your e-mail.
- Lf they're really in mint condition...
- My dad and I hardly ever used them.
We mostly played foosball
and we built things.
Toys, contraptions.
We had a workshop.
He died last year.
Well, I'm sorry.
Annie, would you come over here
for a second? Bring your skates.
- Okay.
- I want you to meet someone.
This is Annie, the birthday girl.
This is my friend, Eric.
- Hello, Annie.
- Hi.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
You must be, what, 8?
How did you know?
Everyone else thinks I'm older.
Well, I'm a detective.
- Are you ready to go skating finally?
- I think.
I sure hope you like it.
It's a punching bag.
Okay, so you blow it up...
...and whenever you
get in a really bad mood...
...you sock it in the head.
Can I do karate on it?
Of course you can. You can do karate,
kung fu, tae kwon do.
- Thank you, Griffin.
- You're welcome, sweetie.
That might be my date.
Mom.
Oh, come on.
Happy birthday, sweetie.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
Sweetheart...
...I gotta go.
It's a real emergency, or I
would never leave you like this.
- I'll make it up to you, I promise. Okay?
- Okay.
I'm looking for Griffin Dowd. He's...
- Yeah. Hi.
- Hi.
- I'm Melanie.
- Oh, yes. Hi, Melanie.
Wow, you are gorgeous.
I'm sorry. I've gotta run.
Todd!
Isn't that your dad?
- Same build, same coloring.
- The counter's faster than last time.
Yeah.
I swear I've seen this guy
somewhere before.
- Yeah.
- We all have. He's David Williams.
He used to be
a reporter for Channel 12.
He now hosts a TV show
on public access.
Call Bagley.
Set up a press conference.
Sir, wait just a minute, please.
This is what he wants. Anything
you say will promote the site.
That's a possibility,
but what would you prefer?
Talk to National Security Agency.
Their computer capability's
beyond ours. We need their help.
That's fine, but I've got
a man being publicly tortured.
How will it look if he dies and the
Bureau never tried to help the guy?
Not as bad as if we reach out
and it kills him faster.
You honestly believe
that could happen?
Yes, sir, I do.
I'm sorry, Marsh.
I got no choice.
We're gathered here
to share some information...
... in regards to criminal conduct...
... that originated in the
Portland metropolitan area...
... but that has
far-reaching implications.
Let me introduce
Special Agent-in-Charge...
... of the FBI's Portland field office...
...Richard Brooks.
Thank you, chief.
A week ago, a man was killed
in this city.
This barbaric, cowardly murder
was streamed live on the Internet.
As part of the killer's design, the more
people who logged on to the site...
... to witness the victim's suffering,
the sooner the victim died.
Millions of Americans
chose to visit the site...
... believing that they were witnessing
a mere hoax, a stunt or a prank.
Well, unfortunately, it wasn't.
Today a second individual...
... has appeared on the site
and his life, too, is in jeopardy.
The victim is the doting father
of two boys...
... a loving husband of 22 years...
... and a devoted son. In other words,
he's a good American, one of us.
The torture that he is experiencing
now is unimaginable in its cruelty.
We're doing what we can...
... to shut down the site
and bring the killer to justice.
In the meantime, we ask that
everyone stay away from the site.
Any visit to this site,
no matter how brief...
...will only hasten the victim's death.
Any American who visits the site
is an accomplice to murder.
We are the murder weapon.
- We ask that you spread the word...
- Let's main-screen the website.
Hey, Tim, I think
he's trying to say something.
Eight... Eight...
Eight, eight, eight.
Oh, I get it. It's an address, I think.
Eight... Eight-oh-eight...
...Newberry.
- Newberry?
There's a Newberry Road
in Laurelhurst.
Police! Open the door!
Basement's here!
It's the wrong house.
- Any American who visits the site...
- He was here, though.
... is an accomplice to murder.
We are the murder weapon.
Any American who visits the site
is an accomplice to murder.
We are the murder weapon.
Any American...
All right. We should send
Forensics in here.
Any American who visits the site
is an accomplice to murder.
We are the murder weapon.
Yeah, I understand that. Just
have her check it again, okay?
- Six hours. So fast.
- Twice as fast as Miller.
Nobody thinks
they did anything wrong.
Why should they?
They're curious about a website.
You check the headlines,
check the stock market...
...watch some strangers have sex.
See a journalist get his head cut off.
When did the world
go so fucking insane?
You've been working
the streets too long.
He was definitely here.
He just got moved and didn't know it.
So Mrs. Williams is checking her
husband's e-mail for us.
She says he was contacted about the
trains through the public TV website.
I guess in his bio, he mentions he's
a collector. That was about a week ago.
Who owns the house?
Tom Park, 60s, widower. He's out
of town visiting family in South Korea.
He runs a local market here.
He makes the trip every year.
So our guy's a customer.
We're trying to get ahold of Mr. Park,
see if he knows anything.
We'll do a canvass. Seems like
a pretty tight-knit community.
Maybe somebody saw something.