Good evening, Sander Vanocur
with the GNT world news.
The civil war in Shadaloo may
have reached a turning point.
The capital has just fallen.
Chun-Li Zang, GNT News.
AN forces are consolidating
their hold on Shadloo City, -
- after skirmishes to secure
this key Southeast Asian port.
But they're not celebrating yet.
Defeating a rag-tag
militia is one thing, -
- defeating the forces of
Gen. M. Bison is quite another.
The Allied Nation forces know
Bison is a power-mad dictator, -
- whose drug money has bought
him hi-tech weaponry -
- that some experts fear
may equal anything in the West.
It's been only 24 hours since this
dangerous, unpredictable warlord -
- seized 63 AN relief workers
from a village north of here.
This self-styled general's ransom
demand... 20 billion dollars.
Meanwhile, the location of
the 63 hostages remains unknown.
Of the 15 AN troops assigned
to guard the relief workers, -
- 12 are confirmed dead, the rest
missing, their location unknown.
You came from across the world
to fight me.
Now is your chance.
Pathetic.
I can see the AN commander.
I'll try to talk with him.
Yes, your turn now.
Colonel Guile...
GNT news.
May we speak to you, please?
Don't you want to speak
to the world audience?
I do want to talk to someone...
That bastard Bison.
I know you like to see yourself
on television, so look at this!
What are you doing?
Dee Jay, break in.
Now!
You want me on TV,
I'm on TV now!
What the hell?
- Balrog, do you believe this?
- Believe it? I'm shooting it!
- Colonel Guile, greetings!
- He took it. Trace that signal.
- Show respect for a fellow warrior.
- Warrior! You?
How many doctors and nurses
have you killed?
How many children
have you orphaned?
- You will choke on that.
- Any time! We'll go worldwide.
- They're tracing this.
- You think you're so clever.
Think about this.
You have three days.
If my 20 billion dollars are not
delivered by then, -
- the hostages will die,
and you will be held responsible.
Victory!
You hostages! If you can hear me,
we're coming.
Charlie! Hang on, buddy.
Hang on.
Carlos Blanka.
Charlie...
So you are Guile's friend?
Take him to the laboratory.
Attention! All personnel must be
in full gear with sidearms.
- We couldn't trace it.
- You were almost useful.
- He doesn't like women, does he?
- No, he doesn't like journalists.
I assure you,
it's an equal oppurtunity dislike.
We're off the street.
You feel safe yet?
- Yeah. Real safe.
- This way.
In here.
- Good evening, gentlemen.
- Good evening, Sagat.
- No one told you there's a curfew?
- Here, no one tells me anything.
There is a 7 p. m. Curfew.
Violators will be shot on sight.
May I offer you a drink?
Or anything else?
Let's just get down to business.
Do you have the $100,000?
- Do you have the weapons?
- They're hidden.
When we get outside, with our money,
we'll call you and tell you where.
Do we have a deal or not?
- You'll need this, Sagat.
- Oh, no.
I already know the weapons are on
the pier by the Mt. Brazer brewery.
In fact, my men have unloaded the
truck and brought the weapons here.
What's the matter? Surely you're
not afraid of your own weapons?
Toys. I like my games live.
And in living colour!
Interesting.
You werert all talk, after all.
Doctor Dhalsim!
How is your research today?
The same.
Warped. Corrupted.
My science twisted
to serve perversion, not peace.
After I crush my enemies,
we'll get you published.
That should cheer you up.
Now,
let's have a look at the patient.
Excellent. He'll do very nicely.
A perfect soldier.
- You mean a perfect killer.
- Don't quibble over definitions.
A reaction to the programming?
What's he receiving?
See for yourself.
Merely educational software.
Why does it disturb him?
Because unlike you,
he's not psychotic.
You take risks, Doctor.
Do not presume so much
on my good nature.
When his brain has become
a killing machine -
- my loyal scientists
will start on his body.
DNA-MUTAGENS
ANABOLIC PLASMA
The next fight!
The challenger... Ryu!
The defender, my champion, Vega!
All bets start at $100, American.
- Sorry I talked you into all this.
- Sorry I listened.
- Popular guy.
- Greatest fighter since Iron Fist.
- What happened to him?
- He retired... and became me.
No weapons!
- Why must I watch this?
- Research. You fight next.
You are all under arrest.
Good morning, Shadaloo!
- Meeting in session. New business?
- Colonel, my commandos are ready.
But will the assault
be by land, sea or air?
I knew that was coming.
Cammy?
We got Bison to break radio silence,
but not long enough to trace him.
All we say for certain is that his
base is hidden somewhere here...
Any other new business?
Sir!
Look... Shadaloo Tong.
Attention! Mandatory inoculations
for all prisoners at 1400 hours.
Delousing will follow immediately.
- They're afraid of us?
- Not us.
This could be our break.
If Sagat runs guns to Bison, -
- then he must know
where Bison is hiding.
All we have to do
is infiltrate his gang.
Sagat didn't get to the top of
the underworld by taking risks.
He doesn't make new friends.
Who are those two men?
Ken Masters and Ryu Hoshi.
We picked them up last night.
Get them patched up
and bring them to me.
If Sagat won't trust new friends,
maybe he'll trust new enemies.
Subject's muscle mass
increased by 49 percent.
increased by 50 percent.
Attention all medical personnel.
Refugees incoming on dock three.
Doctor Howard,
report to refugee infirmary at once.
Come on.
These people here have a chance.
The hostages have less than that.
- What is this? A guilt trip?
- Call it a wake-up call, gentlemen.
Manila, Hong Kong, Shadaloo...
You justify your con games by saying
you've been stealing from criminals.
Are you the same as
Sagat and Bison?
Or am I right,
and you're different?
We're different.
Can we please leave?
The only way you two are leaving,
is over my dead body.
What do you do if a Bison trooper
throws a hand grenade?
Pick it up, pull,
and throw it right back!
All right! Load 'em up!
I'm tired of being a warden.
Take them to the harbour.
There's a brig waiting.
Bon voyage, Sagat.
Enjoy the sea air.
This isn't over, Guile.
I own this city!
Well, I'm the repo man.
And you're out of business.
You just had to come
to this country, huh?
- You can't think, you can't fight!
- I'm sick of your crap.
Break it up!
Get in the truck.
- Ryu! Ken! Throw us the keys.
- Go to hell.
Forget our past.
I can help you escape the city.
Don't!
You'll hit the colonel.
Medics! Medics!
The temple above us
was the wonder of the ancient world.
Bisonopolis
shall be the wonder of my world.
But I think the food court
should be larger.
All the big franchises will want in.
Dateline: Shadaloo City,
Shadaloo, Southeast Asia.
The world is in shock. Col. William
S. Guile has been killed.
It happened during
a jailbreak by Victor Sagat, -
- the gunrunner who was principal
arms supplier to General M. Bison.
It was hoped that Allied Nation
forces would restore order.
But after today's tragedy
nothing is certain, -
- except Bisors mad threats, -
- and that the new AN commander's
first duty is to bury Colonel Guile.
For GNT, this is Chung-Li Zang.
- Great news, congratulations!
- On the contrary, I mourn.
I was hoping to face Guile
personally on the battlefield.
One gentleman warrior to another,
in respectful combat.
Then I would snap his spine.
The road not taken!
But why, -
- why do they still
call me a warlord?
And mad?
All I want to do is to create
the perfect genetic soldier.
Not for power, not for evil, -
- but for good.
Carlos Blanka will be the first
of many. They shall march out -
- and sweep away every adversary,
every creed, every nation -
- until the very planet is in the
loving grip of the Pax Bisonica.
And then peace
will reign in the world.
And all humanity shall bow to me -
- in humble gratitude.
That was beautiful.
Curfew violators will be arrested.
Anyone resisting will be shot.
A wireless mike. On
the coastal highway, heading north.
- Damn! We've got interference.
- It's too steady for interference.
There's another homing device
in that truck.
Let's analyse this other signal.
Looks like it's aimed right here.
AN headquarters.
Here?
That doesn't make any sense.
- Your five minutes are up!
- Honda! We've got to go, bro.
Follow our signal. I'll catch up
at the Thieves' Market.
I'll find out who's playing games.
You're worried?
No. But only you can
sign our expense accounts.
It's clear. Go!
- Their pass is good for a week.
- They can go.
MORGUE
Another homing device.
If I didn't give you an interview
alive, I won't when I'm dead.
Of course! The two who led
the prison break and "killed" you.
They're working for you,
aren't they?
Are you asking as a reporter,
or as something else?
- Sergeant, take her into custody.
- No, wait, please!
You're right. It's not for the news.
I don't want a story about Bison.
I want his head!
It's taken me 20 years
to get this far.
You can't lock me up
when I'm this close.
Take her away.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
I do understand. But this war is
not about your personal vendetta.
It's about mine.
Darling,
basic black's not really you.
Come back here!
Stop!
You don't have a chance.
What a screw-up!
What a woman.
Cruise missile!
Add your own warhead!
Armoured Personnel Carrier,
Iraqi Army. Five speeds.
Turbo chopper. Only used once, to
evacuate American embassy in Saigon.
Welcome, warlords of Shadaloo.
General Bison offers
food, drink and entertainment.
No, no...
She likes me.
- And the explosive finale?
- Not yet. We've a problem.
Now...
...to business.
This makes Detroit
look like Disneyland.
I wonder whose lowlifes will
kill us first, Sagat's or Bisors.
Guile was right. We've forgotten
what our sensi taught us.
Trust, honour...
But we're in this until we get that
homing device into Bisors fortress.
Ken?
You got another mask for me,
darling?
I am pleased with your goods, Sagat.
As for payment...
why settle for mere money?
After I defeat the AN, what if I
were to share the country with you?
When the war is over, we'll see
how much of the country is left.
Meanwhile...
let's see the colour of your money.
Enough!
Is this a joke?
- This "money" is won'thless!
- On the contrary.
Every Bison dollar
will be won'th five British pounds.
That will be the exchange rate
once I've kidnapped their queen.
We know you're working for Guile.
Believe me, we're your friends.
I was insane to think I could
do business with you, Bison!
You raving lunatic!
I know you. You're Edmund Honda,
the sumo from Hawaii.
- You almost made Yokozuna.
- The Tong destroyed my reputation.
They did the same
with my boxing career.
Don't tell me...
figure skating!
All you need to know is that the
weapons Bison and Sagat deal in -
- will blow them to hell.
This conclave is over!
You will die for this insult.
- You've got ten minutes.
- Well, that was special.
It's showtime.
She said this place will blow in
ten minutes. Things can't get worse.
- I was wrong.
- Back me up.
Loosen up, it's a party.
- Are you with me or not?
- Is that multiple choice?
- You dare to interfere?
- Yeah. Because...
- There are enemy spies among us.
- Show me these spies.
This is Chun-Li Zang.
This may be my final broadcast.
But if it is, I and my comrades
did not die in vain, -
- for we have killed the warlords
that brought death and destruction.
Bison, Sagat! All your weapons
of death will be blown sky high!
Happy landings!
Quick, change the channel!
Evacuate at once!
Search the camp.
Find Chun-Li!
AN SURVEILLANCE SATELLITE 5
EXPLOSION DETECTED
SHADALOO MOUNTAINS
ZANG, HONDA, BALROG
CAPTURED BY BISON FORCES
TRACKING HOMING DEVICE
The technology of East and West...
Their governments scorned me,
their corporations adored me.
Zangief, see that Ken and Ryu
are given clean clothing.
They warned us of Chun-Li's
treachery. They are honoured guests.
Sagat, Vega,
you are welcome to stay here.
I think you will find the coming
events most... educational.
General... what about them?
Take them
to the interrogation room.
They will talk...
or they will die.
Preferably both.
Take the "journalist"
to my chambers.
We've decided to grant her
a private interview.
Ken, Ryu, come with me.
We'll take care of you.
This way.
You'll dehydrate yourself.
- This sucks. They're good guys.
- Lately I don't feel very good.
An attack from the air
is impossible.
The only chance is an assault
with a small amphibious force.
We attack from the north -
- while a single vessel equipped
with stealth technology -
- comes up this channel
and distract his defences.
Colonel?
A single boat against them all?
The pilot would have to be crazy.
Luckily, Bison has driven me crazy.
So I'm going to do it.
Synchronise your watches.
0500. Cast off at 0600.
This is it.
Let me show you
how we treat foreigners.
- You are next, yankee!
- Maybe you ought to lie down first.
And take a bath.
Oh, man...
How do you keep from crying out?
I am sumo. My body can be
one place, my mind another.
Next time your mind leaves,
have it bring back a pizza.
- Give me a hand.
- Maybe next month.
Give me your hand!
Ready? Go!
Now you look like Bison troopers!
This is where we train, in our
struggle against AN tyranny.
- How're you doing?
- Looking great!
- Nice gun.
- Great uniform.
- Long live Bison!
- Yep, Bison.
I'll see you later,
in the commissary.
- See the video map?
- The left half.
Good, I saw the right.
I'll handle this.
- As you were, Colonel.
- Welcome to the Shadaloo front.
- Just in time for the kickoff.
- The Security Council has voted.
They want to negotiate.
We can deal with Bison.
Call off the assault. Request
an extension of his deadline.
- We are prepared to pay the ransom.
- 20 billion dollars?
What if he takes more hostages and
asks for 50 billion? 100 billion?
- Colonel, have you lost your mind?
- No. You've lost your balls.
Deliver these instructions
to your troops, -
- and then consider yourself
relieved of your command.
Troopers!
I've just received new orders.
Our superiors say the war is
cancelled. We can all go home.
Bison is getting paid off, and
our friends have died for nothing.
But we can all go home.
Meanwhile, ideals like peace,
freedom and justice are packed up, -
- but we can all go home.
Well, I'm not going home.
I'm going to get on my boat,
go upriver, -
- and kick that son of a bitch
Bisors ass so hard -
- that the next Bison wannabe
is going to feel it.
Now, who wants to go home,
and who wants to go with me?
- Come on!
- Let's go, Colonel.
Colonel Guile...!
Colonel Guile!
These instructions...
Stop them, please.
I would love to,
but some moron just canned me.
It was twenty years ago.
You hadrt made yourself a general.
You were just a petty drug lord.
You and your gang of murderers
gathered your ounce of courage -
- to raid across the border
for food, weapons, slave labour.
My father
was the village magistrate.
A simple man with a simple code.
Justice.
He gathered the few people
he could, to stand against you.
You and your bullies were driven
back by farmers with pitchforks.
My father saved his village
at the cost of his own life.
You had him shot,
as you ran away.
A hero at a thousand paces.
I'm sorry...
I don't remember any of it.
You don't remember?
For you,
the day Bison graced your village -
- was the most important day
of your life.
But for me...
it was Tuesday.
Attention all troopers! Weapons
inspections will continue at random.
If your weapons are not at full
readiness, penalties will be severe.
Those guys will be happy to see us.
Well, if it isn't our little buddies
who double-crossed us!
- What did he say?
- "Hail Bison!" They're fanatics.
I think he said
he could meet us outside.
What I said was,
'We're on the same side. "
I spent the past ten years
working in the media world.
Using it
to gather intelligence on you.
I found partners who hated you
and your friends as much as I did.
But most importantly, I studied the
martial arts of three continents.
So that one day I could meet you, -
- avenge my father, -
- and end
your reign of terror myself.
I don't think so.
You see...
no one has ever seen you in combat.
You always hid
behind your sumo and your boxer.
Since you entered this country,
you never even threw a single punch.
No, my dear.
I know women...
...and you are harmless.
That's exactly
what I wanted you to think.
- Li!
- We're coming, Li!
No!
Li, let me at him!
Son of a...
It's gas!
Attention!
Stand by at attack vector Alpha.
I'll take out the enemy radar.
Captain Sawada, I'm counting on you.
We'll be there, Colonel.
Just save some for us.
Formation attack!
Subject's muscle mass increased
by 71 percent.
by 72 percent.
Subject's muscle mass increased
by 73...
CEREBRAL DOWNLOAD HALTED
49 PERCENT COMPLETE
ALTERNATE CEREBRAL
DOWNLOAD ACTIVE
Attention! Sidearms will be issued
to the Shadaloo Tong by 1800 hours.
- Move it, fat boy! Come on!
- Move it, cutie!
I told you
we couldn't trust them.
Vega, be civil.
They worked so hard to get here.
Let them enjoy their ringside seats.
You know, it's interesting...
Had you worked together,
you might have been successful.
- Approaching radar perimeter.
- Prepare for stealth mode.
- On-line.
- Systems ready.
Armed.
Three, two, one... now!
- Enemy radar position ahead.
- It's going down.
General! Something
very strange on the river.
- Two radar stations are down.
- Go to visual.
System alert Radar stations
two and three are off-line.
- Radar stations are off-line.
- Activate sonar detectors.
Colonel, someone's picked us up.
They're jamming us!
Stealth mode compromised, sir.
We're busted.
Alert alert!
Intruder craft detected
at radar station seven.
Prepare for attack mode.
Yellow alert All off-duty personnel
report at once to shift commanders.
Perimeter guns...
Fire!
This is General Bison.
Our defences are locked onto you.
- Identify yourself!
- It's the collection agency.
Your ass is six months overdue,
and it's mine!
- Guile? Alive?
- Of course!
His death was designed
to ingratiate his spies with you.
I guess you didn't see that,
did you?
This time, Colonel,
you die for real.
Attention, attention.
Stand clear.
And now, Miss Zang...
You will witness first hand
the power you spurned.
- Minefield ahead.
- Oh, great!
They have a radar lock.
In 30 seconds, we're swimming.
In that case...
Let's get an early start.
- Game over!
- Intruder destroyed.
Stand down from yellow alert
Repair crews
to radar stations one through six.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Nothing, hey?
Security, this is...
So you think you're smart, eh?
Let's see how smart you are
when you're not breathing!
Come on!
Yes, I gave him the orders.
The mars impossible.
No, I stopped him taking all the
soldiers. The rest are at the base.
- What's with the headband?
- I wear it for good luck in battle.
You should have brought three.
Colonel, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- Is the rope secure?
- Almost.
Four years of ROTC
for this shit!
It is now only moments
from the deadline -
- for delivery of the ransom
for the hostages.
Reports are unclear.
GNTcorrespondent Chun-Li Zang
is missing with her news crew.
We hope for a peaceful solution
to this crisis, -
- and we appeal to General Bison
in the name of humanity.
Has the AN deposited
the 20 billion in my Swiss bank?
Hell no, General.
We've set
electronic and visual markers.
- ETA landing zone: 12 minutes.
- Roger, Lieutenant. I'll be ready.
If I'm alive...
Open the hostage chamber.
Hostage pit open.
Stand clear.
Charlie, it's me!
I'm your friend William.
Friend...?
What have they done to you?
Charlie?
What have they done to me?
Help me.
I'll help you.
And then I'll make them pay.
No.
You have no right.
The world thought
very little of you, my dear guests.
Too little to pay
the pittance I asked for.
Too little to even mount
a decent rescue attempt.
Move out!
Your masters at the AN
call me a wild beast. So be it.
You do not deserve the
martial dignity of a firing squad.
You shall be killed
by a wild beast!
A beast born of my own genius!
Raise the incubation chamber!
Bisors scientists warped his body.
I did what I could to preserve
his mind. To keep him human.
- You call this human?
- He retains the capacity for good.
Yes, and for evil as well.
Will you kill him because
he can't understand the difference?
Stand clear. Incubation chamber
rising to command room level.
The signal! The real monster's
upstairs. He wants to see him.
Incubation chamber rising...
Behold the face of your destruction,
and of my victory.
Shoot the hostages!
Go!
Red alert! All personnel,
report to battle stations.
- You don't have our passports?
- Free them, and I'll get you home.
Go!
Go, cowards!
All that's left is revenge.
Find Ken and Ryu
and get the hostages out.
Goodbye!
- We'll do what we can.
- Go!
Attention! Remember, health benefits
are your responsibility.
- Where is Blanka?
- I don't know. It's all crashing!
He's fighting my men!
The cerebral programming.
Patch it in!
No!
Then defeat is a possibility?
Very well.
We shall face it together, Dee Jay.
With the stoicism
of the true warrior.
Battle systems compromised.
Repair time: 18 months.
Sayonara, buddy!
Ryu, Guile put a gun to our head.
We did our part.
- The real soldiers are here now.
- They're fighting and dying!
They get paid for it, we don't!
Are you coming?
- We can find something won'thwhile.
- I already found something.
- I don't understand.
- I know you don't.
Stop! Stop!
We're winning, but there's
skirmishes on every level.
No sign of Bison.
He's probably hiding.
Hiding? What do I have
to fear from you? Worker ants -
- scurrying about
with their pitiful weapons.
Afraid of the purity
of unarmed combat.
Come out from behind the curtain,
Wizard. Let's see how pure it is.
Come on.
- No, that's what he wants!
- No, that's what we both want.
Right, Bison?
Are you man enough to fight me?
Anyone opposing me dies.
- Colonel, you can't!
- Yes I can. Take the hostages out.
If I'm not topside in 15 minutes,
evacuate without me.
Both of you.
That's an order.
Troopers, out! Throw the enemy
into the sea. Leave us!
- You have made me a happy man.
- Next, a dead one.
Captain Sawada, we have tapped into
the enemy's security system.
Excellent.
Show it to me at once.
This could be
strategically important.
You'll have to do better than that!
Okay! That's for Charlie.
That's for the soldiers.
The hostages!
Where are they?
Now then,
where are those hostages?
- This is Guile.
- Cammy. Are you all right?
- I'm okay. I'm just half dead.
- And Bison?
- All dead. What's the situation?
- Fighting everywhere.
- Have the reserves arrived?
- Sawada's men are at the beachhead.
They have their hands full
with the enemy outside.
- It could go either way.
- It'll go our way.
Have our troops on the upper level
fall back and attack.
We'll trap them outside
between both columns.
Okay, but we haven't found
the hostages yet.
I've got some volunteers on it.
And maybe they'll be able...
to help.
Colonel, I didn't read that.
Ah, yes.
My mama didn't raise no fool.
I should have stayed at Microsoft.
All personnel,
report to battle stations.
There's got to be something.
Okay...
Where's the old front door?
Ryu, where are you going?
Ryu, U-turn, amigo!
You're walking into a trap!
Ryu, get out of there!
- Vega...
- Where were we?
You were losing.
Bison... What happened to
the purity of unarmed combat?
This is merely
superconductor electromagnetism.
You've heard of it. It levitates
bullet trains from Tokyo to Osaka.
It levitates my desk, where
I ride the saddle of the world.
And it levitates... me.
Something wrong, Colonel?
Did you come to fight a madman,
and instead you found a god?
Ken!
You die.
Here you go, Sagat.
I owe you.
If I hadrt met you,
I might have become you.
You still refuse
to accept my godhood?
Keep your own God. In fact, this
might be a good time to pray to him.
"For I beheld Satan
as he fell from heaven...
...like lightning. "
Bison, you're off the air.
Warning! Warning!
Energy field unstable.
- This will take one minute.
- Excuse me.
Maybe less.
A rescue team will
take you to safety. Up the stairs!
- Get going!
- This way, hurry!
Sorry, man.
I can't play no more.
Coward!
Come back!
Superconductor field meltdown.
Evacuate!
All personnel,
go to main entrance level.
Dee Jay!
Why are you out of uniform?
The enemies of freedom
are inside our walls.
Are you demented?
Our boss is the enemy of freedom.
These people have come to stop him.
If you're smart, save your ass!
General Bison is a bad guy?
Then why do you serve him?
Because he paid me a fortune,
you moron!
You got paid?
Backup superconductor compressors
have failed.
Meltdown will occur in 60 seconds.
Evacuate at once.
Keep moving up towards daylight!
Don't panic.
- Pigtails?
- Look who's talking.
- This way!
- Sealing blast doors... now.
This way!
50 seconds until superconductor
meltdown. Evacuate at once.
- Jamaica, here I come!
- Here we come.
40 seconds to total meltdown.
Charlie, we have to go.
The whole place is going up.
I can't go back, my friend.
Not like this.
- Charlie...
- Don't worry. He won't be alone.
I must atone
for my part in this evil.
- You did nothing.
- That is evil enough.
Ten seconds to meltdown.
Where's Guile?
Guile didn't make it.
- Easy! That's my severance pay.
- Severance pay?
He was a brave man.
A true warrior.
He told us to leave.
We did the right thing.
Well it still feels
pretty wrong to me.
Guile!
Lieutenant, make a note.
I need a vacation.
Tear gas, sir.
On the way out.
- You've earned your passports back.
- Who'll put all this back together?
Maybe a couple of hustlers
can help.
- Ever think of enlisting?
- No, no!
Colonel Guile...
How about that interview
for my network?
Sure.
But only if you wear that dress.
Solar batteries recharging...
One solar battery on-line...
Attempting to activate system...
System activated.
Good morning, General!
What is your menu choice today?
WORLD DOMINATION
REPLAY